<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 05:38:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Japan Eyes Crypto Push With Loser Margin Trading Rules</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/japan-eyes-crypto-push-with-loser-margin-trading-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 04:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Agency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FSA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While the West has initiated a heavy crackdown on cryptocurrencies, regulators in Asia have been trying to bring crypto-friendly rules to accommodate more firms in the market. Japanese regulators are now planning for a relaxation of curbs on margin trading. As per the Japan Virtual &#38; Crypto Assets Exchange Association, industry players want to permit <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/japan-eyes-crypto-push-with-loser-margin-trading-rules/" title="Japan Eyes Crypto Push With Loser Margin Trading Rules"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/japan-eyes-crypto-push-with-loser-margin-trading-rules/">Japan Eyes Crypto Push With Loser Margin Trading Rules</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="680" height="356" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/19165212/japan-fsa.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="japan fsa" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/19165212/japan-fsa.jpg 680w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/19165212/japan-fsa-300x157.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/19165212/japan-fsa-678x356.jpg 678w" sizes="(max-width: 680px) 100vw, 680px" /><p>While the West has initiated a heavy crackdown on cryptocurrencies, regulators in Asia have been trying to bring crypto-friendly rules to accommodate more firms in the market. Japanese regulators are now planning for a relaxation of curbs on margin trading.</p>
<p>As per the Japan Virtual &amp; Crypto Assets Exchange Association, industry players want to permit leverage for retail players of four to ten times. However, at present, customers can only double their exposure via borrowing.</p>
<p>The association’s Vice Chairman Genki Oda said in an interview: “Reforming the leverage rule could make Japan more attractive for crypto and blockchain companies&#8221;. He also said that such a step would encourage more trading in the market.</p>
<h3>Japan&#8217;s FSA In Discussion With Local Exchanges</h3>
<p>The local crypto exchanges of Japan are already in talks to reach a consensus on the recommended leverage limit. They are likely to take their proposal further to the top financial regulator &#8211; Financial Services Agency (FSA).</p>
<p>According to an official from the Financial Services Agency (FSA), cryptocurrency companies are required to provide strong justifications for relaxing margin trading limits, which align with the government&#8217;s objective of expanding blockchain-related sectors. The FSA is willing to engage in discussions with digital asset businesses regarding this matter.</p>
<p>This development comes just at a time when Hong Kong is making a greater push towards establishing itself as the crypto hub of Asia. Thus, Japan is also mulling to ease some of its crypto rules on token listing and taxation.</p>
<p>In Japan, cryptocurrency platforms used to allow trading with leverage up to 25 times, which led to high volumes of margin trading reaching around $500 billion in 2020 and 2021. However, the volumes significantly decreased by 75% in 2022 after the Financial Services Agency (FSA) implemented a limit of two times leverage. This measure aimed to reduce excessive speculation and protect investors from substantial losses.</p>
<p>In other parts of the world, the availability of spot margin trading on digital asset exchanges varies based on local regulations. Typically, these platforms offer leverage between five and ten times the initial deposit. Some platforms even provide more aggressive lending, which reflects the risky speculation that can create waves of greed and fear within the crypto market.</p>
<p>Oda said that crypto volatility has called down over the last three years and Japan&#8217;s local crypto exchanges are well-equipped to help investors manage risks with margin trading.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/japan-eyes-crypto-push-with-loser-margin-trading-rules/">Japan Eyes Crypto Push With Loser Margin Trading Rules</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/19165212/japan-fsa.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did You Know: IMF Silently Recognized XRP In 2018</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/did-you-know-imf-silently-recognized-xrp-in-2018/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152242</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: While the International Monetary Fund (IMF) now began helping governments across the world develop Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs), XRP token had long been in the eyes of the international financial institution. The International Monetary Fund had on Monday revealed it was developing a global platform to facilitate CBDC interoperability. On the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/did-you-know-imf-silently-recognized-xrp-in-2018/" title="Did You Know: IMF Silently Recognized XRP In 2018"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/did-you-know-imf-silently-recognized-xrp-in-2018/">Did You Know: IMF Silently Recognized XRP In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/14001631/XRP-token-price.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP news price ripple IMF crypto" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: While the International Monetary Fund (IMF) now began <a href="https://coingape.com/imf-developing-a-global-cbdc-platform-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">helping</a> governments across the world develop <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs)</a>, XRP token had long been in the eyes of the international financial institution. The International Monetary Fund had on Monday revealed it was developing a global platform to facilitate CBDC interoperability. On the other side, Ripple Labs had already been helping many companies and central banks explore the CBDC use case. This comes despite the setback to XRP token holders, even as the wait for the Summary Judgement drags on.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-announces-bitcoin-wallet-migration-triggers-on-chain-transfers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance Announces Bitcoin Wallet Migration, Triggers On-Chain Transfers</strong></a></p>
<p>Earlier, CoinGape <a href="https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that Ripple Labs Inc stitched a <a href="https://coingape.com/ripple-to-help-colombia-central-bank-explore-cbdc-use-cases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partnership</a> with Colombia’s central bank Banco de la República to explore blockchain technology use cases. However, it is the United States market that is strategically important for Ripple, to be able to expand to full scale. Yet, it is unclear as to whether the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripple-lawsuit-summary-judgement-fednow-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FedNow service</a> would in future integrate crypto payments and thus XRP.</p>
<h2>When IMF Recognized XRP As Virtual Currency</h2>
<p>In a 2018 presentation on &#8216;The Regulation of Virtual Currencies,&#8217; the IMF recognized XRP in the virtual currencies category, describing it as &#8220;a coin issued by Ripple as the digital asset for payments.&#8221; Interestingly, the IMF also <a rel='nofollow'  href="/Users/DELL/Downloads/rebecca-simons-the-regulation-virtual-currencies%20(2).pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mentioned</a> the virtual currency&#8217;s capabilities in the cross-currency border payments space, which is exactly what the IMF is trying to solve for the central banks. XRP was described in the presentation as:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;(XRP) is the token used to carry out cross-border, cross-currency payments through the Ripple network.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The IMF also categorized virtual currencies as assets &#8220;not issued by a government,&#8221; while CBDCs are central bank issued. Ripple&#8217;s strength in cross border payments could be put to use in the IMF project, irrespective of the XRP token.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-xrp-can-grow-even-if-ripple-loses-sec-lawsuit" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Expert: How XRP Can Grow Even If Ripple Loses SEC Lawsuit</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/did-you-know-imf-silently-recognized-xrp-in-2018/">Did You Know: IMF Silently Recognized XRP In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/14001631/XRP-token-price.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC has no Proof that &#8220;Secondary XRP Sales are Securities&#8221; &#8211; John Deaton</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/sec-has-no-proof-that-secondary-xrp-sales-are-securities-john-deaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 20:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[John Deaton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152245</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pro-XRP lawyer and the CryptoLaw founder John Deaton has made a bold statement implying that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) cannot justify that secondary XRP sales are securities. In response to a Twitter post made by Marc Fagel, a former partner with the law firm of Gibson, Deaton painted a hypothetical picture <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/sec-has-no-proof-that-secondary-xrp-sales-are-securities-john-deaton/" title="SEC has no Proof that &#8220;Secondary XRP Sales are Securities&#8221; &#8211; John Deaton"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sec-has-no-proof-that-secondary-xrp-sales-are-securities-john-deaton/">SEC has no Proof that &#8220;Secondary XRP Sales are Securities&#8221; &#8211; John Deaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/29002255/33796.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">Pro-XRP lawyer and the CryptoLaw founder John Deaton has made a bold statement implying that the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) cannot justify that secondary XRP sales are securities. In response to a Twitter </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1670861813901033474?s=20"><span style="font-weight: 400">post</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> made by Marc Fagel, a former partner with the law firm of Gibson, Deaton painted a hypothetical picture of a progressive movement of XRP as a form of payment from Ripple down to four other entities.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I understand Marc’s comment that secondary sales are an open legal question and whether a Howey analysis must be applied to secondary market transactions. But when you look at the existing case law in totality it strongly favors that you must apply Howey at each subsequent sale. <a href="https://t.co/bc2WaeGTjM">https://t.co/bc2WaeGTjM</a></p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1670861813901033474?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&#8220;If you don’t apply Howey at the time of each transaction and XRP is a security per se b/c Ripple sold to a guy named Johnny Crypto then, in effect, Johnny Crypto, his employee, the employee’s friend, Jeremy Hogan, Uphold, and TapJets are all in a common enterprise w/Ripple,&#8221; Deaton </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1670861872549986315?s=20"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> referring to all the entities involved in the progression.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">To this end, he noted that secondary XRP sales do not qualify as securities. Furthermore, the Crypto Law founder referenced the 2nd Circuit which states that when a purchaser is motivated by a desire to use or consume the item purchased, the securities law does not apply. </span></p>
<h2><b>SEC Chair Gets Bashed Over Howey Test</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Deaton had previously </span><a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-can-us-sec-win-against-ripple-with-howey-test/"><span style="font-weight: 400">questioned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> SEC chair Gary Gensler over his approach towards crypto with the Howey Test. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to him, Gensler has another thought about how cryptocurrencies should be classified and regulated and that has derailed him from the court&#8217;s definition of securities from way back in 1946 in connection to the Howey Test. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As detailed in the Howey Test, &#8220;a transaction is a security if it is an investment of money, in a common enterprise, with a reasonable expectation of profit derived from the efforts of others.&#8221; Per Deaton’s argument, the 4 other entities who received the XRP tokens cannot logically be in a common enterprise with Ripple Labs.</span></p>
<h2><b>SEC vs Ripple &#8211; XRP -Lawsuit Verdict Expected Soon</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Markedly, the Ripple vs SEC case over the sales of </span><a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp-lawsuit/"><span style="font-weight: 400">XRP</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> as unregistered securities has lingered for far too long and is hopefully coming to an end in the next few months. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ripple is hopeful that by the end of this year, the case would have come to a positive </span><a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripples-new-prediction-on-end-date-of-sec-lawsuit/"><span style="font-weight: 400">close</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. Brad Garlinghouse, Ripple&#8217;s Chief Executive Officer (CEO) is more optimistic that a verdict will be given by the first half of the year. The release of the Hinman speech after so much </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-ripple-call-secs-motion-to-shield-hinman-speech-premature/"><span style="font-weight: 400">resistance</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from the regulator has proven to be a game-changer in the lingering case.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sec-has-no-proof-that-secondary-xrp-sales-are-securities-john-deaton/">SEC has no Proof that &#8220;Secondary XRP Sales are Securities&#8221; &#8211; John Deaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/29002255/33796.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Countries Co-Investigating Binance Alongside US SEC &#8211; Report</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/european-countries-co-investigating-binance-alongside-us-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The recent indictment of Binance by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), has set off a chain of reactions among European authorities. Cross Atlantic Investigation Recent reports from Protos have revealed that the SEC has been actively soliciting information from various European authorities regarding Binance&#8217;s activities for some time now. While some countries <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/european-countries-co-investigating-binance-alongside-us-sec/" title="European Countries Co-Investigating Binance Alongside US SEC &#8211; Report"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/european-countries-co-investigating-binance-alongside-us-sec/">European Countries Co-Investigating Binance Alongside US SEC &#8211; Report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19225248/BIN2.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">The recent indictment of Binance by the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/binance-vs-sec-on-chain-data-shows-withdrawals-worth-623-million-from-binance/"><span style="font-weight: 400">United States Securities and Exchange Commission</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> (SEC), has set off a chain of reactions among European authorities.</span></p>
<h2><b>Cross Atlantic Investigation</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Recent </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://protos.com/scoop-european-states-working-with-sec-on-binance-investigation/"><span style="font-weight: 400">reports</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from Protos have revealed that the SEC has been actively soliciting information from various European authorities regarding Binance&#8217;s activities for some time now. While some countries have already taken steps in response to the SEC&#8217;s indictment, others are still assessing the intricacies of the case and have yet to comply with the SEC&#8217;s information requests.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, the news comes shortly after the company announced that it has withdrawn its Virtual Asset Service Providers (VASP) </span><a href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-cryprus-crypto-sec/"><span style="font-weight: 400">registration</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in Cyprus and ceased offering </span><a href="https://coingape.com/binance-dutch-netherland-us-sec-crypto-news/"><span style="font-weight: 400">services in the Netherlands</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> due to a lack of required licensing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">These decisions come as Binance prepares for the forthcoming Market in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulations, which will impose stricter rules on crypto exchanges and service providers in the European Union (EU).</span></p>
<h2><b>Unraveling Binance&#8217;s Blurred European Network</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The extensive layering and dissipation of information through multiple countries, as observed in Binance&#8217;s operations, has reportedly affected its European network.</span> <span style="font-weight: 400">Similar to FTX, Binance, the world&#8217;s biggest crypto exchange has numerous firms in various European countries. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Remarkably, Binance has obtained licenses to operate as a crypto exchange in some European countries. For example, it has acquired licenses in countries like France and Cyprus, allowing it to offer its services to customers in those jurisdictions.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Additionally, Binance&#8217;s subsidiary, MoonPay, operates in Spain and provides payment services related to cryptocurrencies. Furthermore, Binance has reportedly registered or had entities registered in other European countries, including the UK, Ireland, and Malta.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In terms of revenue, some companies affiliated with Binance have declared relatively small tranches while others have reported significantly higher revenue figures, reaching hundreds of millions in Euros per year.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The presence of loans given to Binance&#8217;s affiliated companies by Guangying Chen, an individual associated with the company, has also contributed to the complexity and opaqueness of Binance&#8217;s operations. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Such lending arrangements between a company and its shareholder are not uncommon, but they can make it more challenging to trace the flow of funds and understand the overall financial structure of the organization, a situation that has largely made regulators skeptical of the firm’s standing.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/european-countries-co-investigating-binance-alongside-us-sec/">European Countries Co-Investigating Binance Alongside US SEC &#8211; Report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19225248/BIN2.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Price Analysis: Can $ADA Buyers Hold $0.24 Support As Market FUD Rises?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/cardano-price-analysis-can-ada-buyers-hold-0-24-support-as-market-fud-rises/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EMAs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=152243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano Price Analysis: The aggressive downfall in ADA price initiated during early June has started losing momentum. Over a week, the coin price showed no clear follow-up for a downside move and several short-bodied candles indicating weakness in selling pressure. Can the Cardano price approach to $0.24 support recuperate the bullish momentum or there&#8217;s more <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/cardano-price-analysis-can-ada-buyers-hold-0-24-support-as-market-fud-rises/" title="Cardano Price Analysis: Can $ADA Buyers Hold $0.24 Support As Market FUD Rises?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/cardano-price-analysis-can-ada-buyers-hold-0-24-support-as-market-fud-rises/">Cardano Price Analysis: Can $ADA Buyers Hold $0.24 Support As Market FUD Rises?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/20000105/EYMEMh53-e1687199489984.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Cardano Price Analysis" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/20000105/EYMEMh53-e1687199489984.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/20000105/EYMEMh53-e1687199489984-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/20000105/EYMEMh53-e1687199489984-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/20000105/EYMEMh53-e1687199489984-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cardano Price Analysis: The aggressive downfall in <a href="https://coingape.com/price/cardano/">ADA price</a> initiated during early June has started losing momentum. Over a week, the coin price showed no clear follow-up for a downside move and several short-bodied candles indicating weakness in selling pressure. Can the Cardano price approach to $0.24 support recuperate the bullish momentum or there&#8217;s more to price correction?</span></p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-cardano-founder-charles-hoskinson/">Cardano Founder Finds Fault With Blackrock Bitcoin ETF</a></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cardano Price Daily Chart: </span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the overall market trend still bearish, the Cardano price is likely to plunge lower and retest the high accumulation zone of $0.24</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ADA price may face heavy supply pressure at a downsloping trendline</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the ADA coin is $140.3 Million, indicating a 28.9% gain</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/e/EYMEMh53.png" alt="Cardano Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1105" />Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On June 10th, the Cardano coin showed a long-tail rejection candle at $0.24 support indicating the active accumulation from buyers. After a minor pullback, the prices are reapproaching the aforementioned support to recuperate the bullish pressure.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By the press time, the ADA price trades at $0.258 with an intraday loss of 0.92%. The falling prices associated with decreasing volume indicate less conviction in sellers and a higher possibility for a bullish reversal.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, the altcoin price could tumble 6.5% and retest the monthly support of $0.24. The Cardano price has a high possibility of giving a bullish reversal from support, which may offer a dip opportunity to interested traders.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Will Cardano Price Recover to $0.35?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A downsloping resistance trendline gives particular direction to the ongoing downtrend in ADA price. For the Cardano buyers to reclaim lost ground it needs to breach the overhead trendline to gain strong footing for further rally. A bullish breakout above the trendline will bolster a recovery rally above $0.35 </span></p>
<ul>
<li><b>Average Directional Index: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The high value of the ADX slope reflects the instability of the current downturn and therefore a possible consolidation or recovery is possible.</span></li>
<li><b>Exponential Moving Average: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 20-day <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMA</a> wavering near the $0.3 level increases the resistance strength of this barrier.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/cardano-price-analysis-can-ada-buyers-hold-0-24-support-as-market-fud-rises/">Cardano Price Analysis: Can $ADA Buyers Hold $0.24 Support As Market FUD Rises?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/20000105/EYMEMh53-e1687199489984.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Likely To Get A Boost With New Developer Proposal</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-likely-to-get-a-boost-with-new-developer-proposal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: A group of Ethereum developers have proposed key changes to validator requirements keeping in mind future consensus layer upgrades. Effectively, this proposal may have some real time impact on investor decisions, considering that the proposal deals with Ethereum (ETH) tokenomics, which would ultimately have an impact on the pricing. This could also <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-likely-to-get-a-boost-with-new-developer-proposal/" title="Ethereum Price Likely To Get A Boost With New Developer Proposal"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-likely-to-get-a-boost-with-new-developer-proposal/">Ethereum Price Likely To Get A Boost With New Developer Proposal</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13214025/Ethereum-IMAGE.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Ethereum price developer proposal" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: A group of Ethereum developers have proposed key changes to validator requirements keeping in mind future consensus layer upgrades. Effectively, this proposal may have some real time impact on investor decisions, considering that the proposal deals with Ethereum (ETH) tokenomics, which would ultimately have an impact on the pricing. This could also lead to operational changes to small and large validators. In the current set up, having a large validator set size is forcing staking operators to have thousands of validators.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-announces-bitcoin-wallet-migration-triggers-on-chain-transfers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance Announces Bitcoin Wallet Migration, Triggers On-Chain Transfers</strong></a></p>
<p>The new Ethereum proposal deals with assessing the need to increase the max effective balance of Ethereum validators from 32 ETH. The developers argue that this move could potentially have multiple operational benefits as the blockchain goes through future updates.</p>
<h2>What is Max Effective Balance</h2>
<p>The Max Effective Balance is a parameter that sets a hard cap on the effective balance of any individual validator. One of the many advantages resulting from having this parameter being low is that the need for having a huge number of validators shows the infrastructure is decentralized. The developers <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://ethresear.ch/t/increase-the-max-effective-balance-a-modest-proposal/15801" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>“As of June 6, 2023, there are over 600,000 active validators 1 with an additional 90,000 in the activation queue. While having many validators signals decentralization, the Max Effective Balance artificially inflates the validator set size by forcing large staking operations to run thousands of validators.”</p></blockquote>
<p>By increasing the balance, the developers believe that two upgrades: single-slot finality and ePBS (Enshrined Proposer-Builder Separation) can be unblocked. Hence, if the proposal is passed, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum price</a> could likely have a significant positive impact.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-xrp-can-grow-even-if-ripple-loses-sec-lawsuit" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Expert: How XRP Can Grow Even If Ripple Loses SEC Lawsuit</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-price-likely-to-get-a-boost-with-new-developer-proposal/">Ethereum Price Likely To Get A Boost With New Developer Proposal</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13214025/Ethereum-IMAGE.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Analysis Hints High Volatility Before an Explosive Move</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/dogecoin-price-analysis-hints-high-volatility-before-an-explosive-move/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EMAs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=152232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin Price Analysis: For over a week, the Dogecoin price has remained flattish trading below a local resistance of $0.063. The daily chart showed several short-bodied candles, indicating a lack of initiation from buyers or sellers to retake trend control. Despite this uncertainty, the DOGE price has not violated the levels of the falling channel <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/dogecoin-price-analysis-hints-high-volatility-before-an-explosive-move/" title="Dogecoin Price Analysis Hints High Volatility Before an Explosive Move"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/dogecoin-price-analysis-hints-high-volatility-before-an-explosive-move/">Dogecoin Price Analysis Hints High Volatility Before an Explosive Move</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19211549/xjd76z5k-e1687189562994.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Dogecoin Price Analysis" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19211549/xjd76z5k-e1687189562994.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19211549/xjd76z5k-e1687189562994-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19211549/xjd76z5k-e1687189562994-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19211549/xjd76z5k-e1687189562994-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dogecoin Price Analysis: For over a week, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/dogecoin/">Dogecoin price</a> has remained flattish trading below a local resistance of $0.063. The daily chart showed several short-bodied candles, indicating a lack of initiation from buyers or sellers to retake trend control. Despite this uncertainty, the DOGE price has not violated the levels of the falling channel pattern, validating it as a crucial setup to predict future prices.</span></p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-elon-musk-refutes-owning-dogecoin-wallets/">Elon Musk Refutes Owning Pump-Dump “Dogecoin Wallets” </a></p>
<h2><strong>Dogecoin Price Daily Chart</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The support trendline of the channel pattern may prevent the DOGE price from excessive downfall.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A breakout above the $0.063 resistance would signal an upcoming relief rally</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 24-hour trading volume in the Dogecoin coin is $182.5 Million, indicating a 0.74% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/x/xjd76z5k.png" alt="Dogecoin Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1104" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dogecoin traders are still trying to stabilize the price action after the massive on June 10th. Though the coin price found suitable support at the lower trendline of the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/parallel-channel-pattern/">channel pattern</a>, the buyers are struggling to regain higher grounds</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By the press time, the Dogecoin price traded at $0.0618 with an intraday loss of 0.43%. The daily chart shows higher price rejection at the immediate resistance of $0.063, suggesting the sellers continue to pressurize the coin price.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Therefore, it is likely the Dogecoin price prolongs the current consolidation until the buyers recuperate the bullish momentum. Under the pessimistic scenario, the price could retest the $0.056 support to attract more buyers at discounted value.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Will Dogecoin Price Reach $0.07?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A retest to the channel pattern’s support trendline usually triggers a significant upswing back to the upper trendline. However, a bullish breakout from $0.063 overhead resistance with daily candle closing will be the first signal for Doge traders for potential recovery. This breakout will provide buyers with a stepping stone to climb higher and a lead price of 12% higher to reach the $0.07 psychological barrier.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Exponential Moving Average: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The dynamic resistance of 20-day <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMA</a> could increase the resistance power of $0.063 resistance.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Directional Movement Index: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The DI+ and DI- slopes gradually nearing a bullish crossover indicating the losing bearish momentum.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/dogecoin-price-analysis-hints-high-volatility-before-an-explosive-move/">Dogecoin Price Analysis Hints High Volatility Before an Explosive Move</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19211549/xjd76z5k-e1687189562994.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMF Developing a Global CBDC Platform &#8211; Report</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/imf-developing-a-global-cbdc-platform-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IMF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152228</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) is doubling down on its effort to help governments around the world actively developing Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs).  The Global CBDC Platform As reported by Reuters, the International Monetary Fund is developing a global platform that will enhance CBDC interoperability. IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva revealed on Monday that <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/imf-developing-a-global-cbdc-platform-report/" title="IMF Developing a Global CBDC Platform &#8211; Report"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/imf-developing-a-global-cbdc-platform-report/">IMF Developing a Global CBDC Platform &#8211; Report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="815" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19210800/IMF.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">The International Monetary Fund (IMF) is doubling down on its effort to help governments around the world actively developing Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs). </span></p>
<h2><b>The Global CBDC Platform</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/imf-working-global-central-bank-digital-currency-platform-2023-06-19/"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Reuters, the International Monetary Fund is developing a global platform that will enhance CBDC interoperability. IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva revealed on Monday that when finally launched, the platform will foster transactions between two countries.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">&#8220;CBDCs should not be fragmented national propositions&#8230; To have more efficient and fairer transactions we need systems that connect countries: we need interoperability,&#8221; Georgieva told a conference attended by African central banks in Rabat, Morocco.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">It is a known fact that the global financial ecosystem is unified through payment systems like SWIFT. CBDC innovation is a new territory for most countries and while many are still conducting research on the suitability of these new national currencies, the IMF is working proactively for a future where more than 50% of all nations will have their own CBDC in circulation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When these new digital fiat are now ubiquitous, the IMF global CBDC platform will come in handy. According to Georgieva, the IMF is working hard to convince countries to agree on a unifying regulation that will permit global interoperability of CBDCs. She reiterated that the full potentials of the technology underpinning CBDCs will not be harnessed if they are designed just for domestic purposes only.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At the moment, about 114 countries are actively involved in researching and developing a CBDC and according to Georgieva, about 10% are crossing the finish line.</span></p>
<h2><b>CBDCs in Operation</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Central Bank of the Bahamas was the first to launch a CBDC dubbed the Sand Dollar back in October 2020. The Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) has also </span><a href="https://coingape.com/nigerian-central-bank-insists-cbdc-use-amid-bitcoin-bull/"><span style="font-weight: 400">launched</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the e-Naira, coming off as the second country with a functional CBDC in circulation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While it has not launched its CBDC for mass usage, the People’s Bank of China (PBoC) is the most biggest nation that is at an advanced stage of its CBDC testing. The Digital Yuan has been </span><a href="https://coingape.com/china-digital-currency-winter-olympics/"><span style="font-weight: 400">tested</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> at the Beijing Olympics and is being drafted as a payment method by some of the largest retail companies in the country.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/imf-developing-a-global-cbdc-platform-report/">IMF Developing a Global CBDC Platform &#8211; Report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19210800/IMF.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Expert: How XRP Can Grow Even If Ripple Loses SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/heres-how-xrp-can-grow-even-if-ripple-loses-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp Lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152230</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) lawsuit against Ripple may be one of earliest major legal battles in crypto market, but the recent lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance showed the regulatory agency is in for a long drawn fight with many companies. It is generally perceived that the Ripple XRP lawsuit <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-xrp-can-grow-even-if-ripple-loses-sec-lawsuit/" title="Expert: How XRP Can Grow Even If Ripple Loses SEC Lawsuit"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-xrp-can-grow-even-if-ripple-loses-sec-lawsuit/">Expert: How XRP Can Grow Even If Ripple Loses SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/12215210/Ripple-LABS.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ripple XRP lawsuit crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) lawsuit against Ripple may be one of earliest major legal battles in <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>, but the recent lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance showed the regulatory agency is in for a long drawn fight with many companies. It is generally perceived that the Ripple XRP lawsuit gains all the more significance as the judgement could act as a precedence for the ongoing crypto cases. Yet, experts warn that the SEC could argue saying the Ripple lawsuit was a one-off situation and that it has nothing to do with the wider crypto market.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a rel='nofollow'  href="http://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-can-btc-bulls-anticipate-30000-breakout-in-current-recovery/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>Bitcoin Price Analysis: Can $BTC Bulls Anticipate $30000 Breakout in Current Recovery?</strong></a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the XRP holders await the Summary Judgement from Judge Analisa Torres, more than 100 days after she delivered the Daubert motion ruling. Yet, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP price</a> is not swayed a lot by the long wait for the final judgement, as the token still holds the sixth position among top cryptocurrencies with a market cap of $25 billion.</p>
<h2>How Ripple Can Ensure XRP Growth If Lawsuit Goes In SEC Favor</h2>
<p>While the industry expects that the SEC lawsuit judgement goes in Ripple&#8217;s favor, the company is well placed to handle defeat just in case. Ripple&#8217;s market engagement in the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC)</a> and payments space could make it a potentially strong market participant to compete for dominance in the altcoin space. The company&#8217;s strategic alignment could also pay dividends in terms of regional presence as well. According to Twitter account DS, the company&#8217;s <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/xspectds/status/1670778544069263361" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">presence</a> in Europe and Latin America could mean a big deal even if it loses the lawsuit.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Ripple is already hedging against a potential no-win in SEC vs Ripple by setting a strong foot fold in both Europe and Latin America.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Ripple management expects that the lawsuit judgement could be delivered by the last quarter of 2023.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-former-cto-founded-guilty-by-montenegro-court" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Terra’s Do Kwon, Former CFO Found Guilty By Montenegro Court</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/heres-how-xrp-can-grow-even-if-ripple-loses-sec-lawsuit/">Expert: How XRP Can Grow Even If Ripple Loses SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/12215210/Ripple-LABS.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Analysis: Key Resistance Breakout Sets XRP Price for 12% Upswing; Buy Now?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/xrp-price-analysis-resistance-breakout-sets-xrp-price-12-upswing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=152226</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP Price Analysis: Last week’s correction phase in XRP price found immediate support at an ascending support trendline. This dynamic support has been assisting buyers over the past three months to maintain a sustained bullish trend. Moreover, the long lower price rejection candle on June 16th reflects the buyers actively accumulating this coin at dips, <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/xrp-price-analysis-resistance-breakout-sets-xrp-price-12-upswing/" title="XRP Price Analysis: Key Resistance Breakout Sets XRP Price for 12% Upswing; Buy Now?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/xrp-price-analysis-resistance-breakout-sets-xrp-price-12-upswing/">XRP Price Analysis: Key Resistance Breakout Sets XRP Price for 12% Upswing; Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19193800/DEonePrP-e1687183705603.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP Price Analysis" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19193800/DEonePrP-e1687183705603.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19193800/DEonePrP-e1687183705603-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19193800/DEonePrP-e1687183705603-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19193800/DEonePrP-e1687183705603-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">XRP Price Analysis: Last week’s correction phase in <a href="https://coingape.com/price/xrp/#:~:text=About%20XRP%20(XRP),trading%20volume%20of%20%242%2C154%2C768%2C042%20USD.">XRP price</a> found immediate support at an ascending support trendline. This dynamic support has been assisting buyers over the past three months to maintain a sustained bullish trend. Moreover, the long lower price rejection candle on June 16th reflects the buyers actively accumulating this coin at dips, indicating a higher possibility for a bullish reversal.</span></p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-soars-200-against-bitcoin-defies-lawsuit-odds-august-price-targets/">XRP Soars 200% Against Bitcoin, Defies Lawsuit Odds: August Price Targets</a></p>
<h2><b>XRP Price Daily Chart:</b></h2>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The recent downfall in XRP price rebounded from the 50% Fibonacci retracement level indicating the correction phase was healthy to promote an overall uptrend.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The XRP buyers can hold their bullish outlook until the support trendline is intact.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the XRP is $860.5 Billion, indicating a 53% gain.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/d/DEonePrP.png" alt="XRP Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1104" /></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bullish reversal from the rising support trendline recuperated the buying pressure in the XRP price. The resulting recovery surged the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoin</a> price by 7.5% in the last four days to reach the current trading price of $0.49.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the recent upswing, the buyers pierced the immediate resistance of $0.487 and obtained additional footing to rise higher. If the daily candle closes above the aforementioned resistance the bullish momentum will surge and may extend the recovery rally 12% higher to hit the $0.55 resistance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On June 13th, the XRP price showed another failed attempt from the $0.55 resistance indicating the supply pressure is still active, and therefore, the buyers would need strong momentum to surpass this barrier.</span></p>
<h2><b>Will XRP Price Rise Back to $0.55?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A retest to the long-coming support trendline replenishes the buying pressure on the XRP price. A potential recovery from this trendline may surge the prices by 12% and hit the next significant resistance of $0.55. Though the above-mentioned level stands as a formidable barrier, the rising could gradually assist buyers to break this ceiling.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Vortex Indicator: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The VI and VI- slope edging close to a bullish crossover could offer additional confirmation for buyers.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Super Indicator: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The trend-defining indicator projects a green film indicating the market sentiment sustains a bullish outlook.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/xrp-price-analysis-resistance-breakout-sets-xrp-price-12-upswing/">XRP Price Analysis: Key Resistance Breakout Sets XRP Price for 12% Upswing; Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19193800/DEonePrP-e1687183705603.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon, Former CFO Found Guilty By Montenegro Court</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-former-cto-founded-guilty-by-montenegro-court/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152222</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Montenegro Basic Court on Monday ruled that Terra co-founder Do Kwon and former chief financial officer Han Chang-joon are found guilty in the passport forgery case and sentenced to four months in jail. Montenegro’s authorities expedite their investigations and legal procedure before Terra co-founder Do Kwon is extradited to South Korea within the next <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-former-cto-founded-guilty-by-montenegro-court/" title="Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon, Former CFO Found Guilty By Montenegro Court"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-former-cto-founded-guilty-by-montenegro-court/">Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon, Former CFO Found Guilty By Montenegro Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="750" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/17182524/1686912054-don-knon-u-osnovnom-sudu-1606-2023-dragan-mijatovic-6-i_960x600-e1687006541127.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: Terra&#039;s Do Kwon, Former CFO Founded Guilty By Montenegro Court" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/17182524/1686912054-don-knon-u-osnovnom-sudu-1606-2023-dragan-mijatovic-6-i_960x600-e1687006541127.jpg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/17182524/1686912054-don-knon-u-osnovnom-sudu-1606-2023-dragan-mijatovic-6-i_960x600-e1687006541127-300x188.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/17182524/1686912054-don-knon-u-osnovnom-sudu-1606-2023-dragan-mijatovic-6-i_960x600-e1687006541127-768x480.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/17182524/1686912054-don-knon-u-osnovnom-sudu-1606-2023-dragan-mijatovic-6-i_960x600-e1687006541127-150x94.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p>The Montenegro Basic Court on Monday ruled that Terra co-founder <strong>Do Kwon</strong> and former chief financial officer <strong>Han Chang-joon </strong>are found guilty in the passport forgery case and sentenced to four months in jail.</p>
<p>Montenegro’s authorities expedite their investigations and legal procedure before Terra co-founder Do Kwon is extradited to South Korea within the next six months.</p>
<h2>Do Kwon Found Guilty By Montenegro Court</h2>
<p>During a hearing at the Basic Court on June 19, Montenegro Court Judge <strong>Ivana Becic </strong><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://sudovi.me/ospg/sadrzaj/D264" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ruled</a> that defendants <strong>Do Kwon</strong> and <strong>Han Chang-joon </strong>used fake Costa Rican passports in an attempt to board a flight to Dubai in March. Both are sentenced to four months in jail, which will include the time spent in custody from March 23 to June 15.</p>
<p>Judge briefly explained her decision why the sentence is lower. She also said the dissatisfied party can appeal within eight days of the receipt of the written verdict.</p>
<p>On June 15, <a href="https://coingape.com/do-kwon-bail-approved-by-montenegro-high-court-extradition-to-south-korea/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Montenegro High Court also approved</a> Do Kwon and Han Chang-joon’s bail request. However, at the request of South Korea, the Montenegro High Court ordered extradition custody for up to six months. Thus, both will remain in custody.</p>
<p>On June 16, <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-on-fake-docs-south-korea-extradition-political-ties-in-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Do Kwon and Han Chang-joon said</a> they didn’t know the passports under the economic citizenship program were fake as they traveled around the world with these Costa Rican and Belgian passports. Terra founder Do Kwon also revealed how he gained passports in Singapore.</p>
<p>Moreover, Do Kwon testified before the Special State Prosecutor’s Office (SDT) and the defense attorneys that he doesn’t have any financial transactions or meetings with former finance minister Milojko Spajic.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale" href="https://coingape.com/fidelity-investments-reportedly-filing-blackrock-type-spot-bitcoin-etf-acquire-grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale</a></strong></p>
<h2>Extradition to South Korea</h2>
<p>Goran Rodić, the lawyer representing Do Kwon and Han Chang-joon, said &#8220;It is still too early to talk about whether the two will be extradited.&#8221; They plan to file a complaint against the detention after receiving written verdict within 30 days.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, a Montenegro High Court looking to extradite both South Korean citizens to their country as the court looks to expedite the extradition proceedings.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="Breaking: Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus" href="https://coingape.com/binance-officially-exits-uk-after-the-netherlands-and-cyprus/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-former-cto-founded-guilty-by-montenegro-court/">Breaking: Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon, Former CFO Found Guilty By Montenegro Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/17182524/1686912054-don-knon-u-osnovnom-sudu-1606-2023-dragan-mijatovic-6-i_960x600-e1687006541127.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MEMEVENGERS Takes Giant Step Towards Web3 Community Development; NFT Membership, Listing Update And Much More</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/memevengers-takes-giant-step-towards-web3-community-development/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Stan Peterson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While the meme coin frenzy that heated up the cryptocurrency market has temporarily subsided, the never-ending wave of Pepe imitations continues unabated. Some argue that the ongoing wave of Pepe imitations resembles a gambling-like, speculative cryptocurrency frenzy, raising concerns that another wave of virtual asset speculation has begun. Nevertheless, various meme coins continue to emerge <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/memevengers-takes-giant-step-towards-web3-community-development/" title="MEMEVENGERS Takes Giant Step Towards Web3 Community Development; NFT Membership, Listing Update And Much More"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/memevengers-takes-giant-step-towards-web3-community-development/">MEMEVENGERS Takes Giant Step Towards Web3 Community Development; NFT Membership, Listing Update And Much More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19190212/mrvel.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Memevengers" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the meme coin frenzy that heated up the cryptocurrency market has temporarily subsided, the never-ending wave of Pepe imitations continues unabated.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some argue that the ongoing wave of Pepe imitations resembles a gambling-like, speculative cryptocurrency frenzy, raising concerns that another wave of virtual asset speculation has begun. Nevertheless, various meme coins continue to emerge incessantly.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Should meme coins be seen only from the perspective of gambling and speculation? No, that&#8217;s not the case. Among numerous meme coins, there are visible attempts to gradually incorporate the core purposes and functionalities of blockchain technology.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the popular meme coins, &#8216;MEMEVENGERS,&#8217; is a prime example.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8216;MEMEVENGERS ($MMVG)&#8217; is the first group-style meme universe coin that brings together popular meme coins. Similar to the movie &#8216;Avengers,&#8217; it gained attention for its storytelling approach of creating a universe by assembling a heroic legion of seven popular meme coins that make their mark in the meme coin market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After its appearance on the 26th of last month, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.memevengers.top/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MEMEVENGERS</a> quickly gained popularity as a meme coin, showing a surge of over 28,000%</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, it is at the center of attention with the upcoming announcement of listings on five centralized exchanges in July, along with the news of being the first meme coin to offer an NFT membership service.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">MEMEVENGERS shared two pieces of news through their official website and Twitter posts. Regarding the exchange listings, only the listing dates were disclosed, and the specific exchanges remain undisclosed, creating even more curiosity. The revealed exchange listing schedule spans from July 18th with a gap of three days, and a total of five listings will take place.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Among them, MEMEVENGERS&#8217; unique NFT membership service, which was previously unseen in the meme coin ecosystem, encompasses the current market trends of Web3, metaverse, and play-to-earn (P2E). The NFTs that grant access to this membership will be distributed in three phases. The first phase involves obtaining whitelist eligibility through completing missions and receiving them via airdrop. The second phase will be conducted through a presale, and the third phase will be carried out through a public sale.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NFT membership grants a total of five benefits, including access to exclusive Discord channels for members, participation rights in governance, participation in Sandbox land purchase and operation, distribution of land operation profits. Particularly, through off-chain governance, NFT members are granted decision-making authority over key ecosystem operations, and the operating profits are distributed to the members. This indicates a goal of achieving a true realization of the Web3 ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As attention is drawn to the future endeavors of <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.memevengers.top/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MEMEVENGERS</a>, which presents another potential and future for meme coins, detailed information about listings and NFT membership will be announced through the official Twitter channel.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/memevengers-takes-giant-step-towards-web3-community-development/">MEMEVENGERS Takes Giant Step Towards Web3 Community Development; NFT Membership, Listing Update And Much More</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19190212/mrvel.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Backs Hinman Speech On Ethereum; Expert Says This Is Not The Case</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/jpmorgan-hinman-speech-ethereum-xrp-lawsuit-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP Lawsuit News: The crypto community finally got access to the infamous Hinman’s Ethereum Speech linked documents and emails in US SEC Vs Ripple Lawsuit last week. The release of crucial memos is expected to boost Ripple’s native crypto, XRP in the market, however, JPMorgan (JPM) doesn’t think so. Also Read: Ripple Seek To File <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/jpmorgan-hinman-speech-ethereum-xrp-lawsuit-news/" title="JPMorgan Backs Hinman Speech On Ethereum; Expert Says This Is Not The Case"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/jpmorgan-hinman-speech-ethereum-xrp-lawsuit-news/">JPMorgan Backs Hinman Speech On Ethereum; Expert Says This Is Not The Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13003409/ripple1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ripple xrp news lawsuit price hinman speech SEC JPMorgan" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>XRP Lawsuit News:</strong> The crypto community finally got access to the infamous Hinman’s Ethereum Speech linked documents and emails in US SEC Vs Ripple Lawsuit last week. The release of crucial memos is expected to boost Ripple’s native crypto, XRP in the market, however, JPMorgan (JPM) doesn’t think so.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-misconduct-hinman-docs-release-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Seek To File For Misconduct Post Hinman Docs Release?</a></strong></p>
<h2>JPMorgan To Bet On Ethereum?</h2>
<p>According to reports, JPMorgan in a research report suggested that the US SEC executives admitted the fact that tokens on a sufficiently decentralized network cannot be landed under the “Security” category originates a regulatory gap.</p>
<p>It added that the speech delivered by then SEC Director Hinman noted that there is an other category. However, the official stated that Ethereum is not a security there is no controlling group but still, there may be a call for regulation to shield purchasers.</p>
<p>Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou, a JPMorgan analyst stated that these revelations could suggest that why the authority has not taken action against Ethereum while going after other crypto assets. The report added that the released documents could influence the direction of the current US congressional efforts in order to regulate the crypto industry. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More XRP Lawsuit News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<p>Crypto expert, Mr. Huber <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/Leerzeit/status/1670736632490672131" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">mentioned</a> that the JPMorgan report didn’t address the context given in the drafts and he is just repeating the speech itself. Meanwhile, the thing which is needed to be noted from the drafts is that the executive had no legal authority to make new rules. However, the analyst is noting how Hinman describes the switch from ETH to a commodity in the speech.</p>
<p>He added that ETH supporting people see that several people worked on Hinman’s speech and believe that this can prove the legitimacy of the speech.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/rug-pull-alert-list-of-altcoins-celsius-network-will-sell-on-july-1st/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Rug Pull Alert: List Of Altcoins Celsius Network Will Sell On July 1st</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/jpmorgan-hinman-speech-ethereum-xrp-lawsuit-news/">JPMorgan Backs Hinman Speech On Ethereum; Expert Says This Is Not The Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13003409/ripple1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Announces Bitcoin Wallet Migration, Triggers On-Chain Transfers</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-announces-bitcoin-wallet-migration-triggers-on-chain-transfers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC Whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152220</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent announcement, Binance, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, revealed its plans to migrate funds from its previous Bitcoin (BTC) cold wallet to a new address. Shortly after the announcement, on-chain data confirmed significant movements of BTC from Binance wallets, catching the attention of market participants. Binance Wallet Migration Binance stated that <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-announces-bitcoin-wallet-migration-triggers-on-chain-transfers/" title="Binance Announces Bitcoin Wallet Migration, Triggers On-Chain Transfers"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-announces-bitcoin-wallet-migration-triggers-on-chain-transfers/">Binance Announces Bitcoin Wallet Migration, Triggers On-Chain Transfers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24200934/5184.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Binance Bitcoin Wallet Migration" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>In a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1670723088802283520?s=20">recent announcement</a>, <a href="https://coingape.com/companies/binance/">Binance</a>, one of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, revealed its plans to migrate funds from its previous Bitcoin (BTC) cold wallet to a new address. Shortly after the announcement, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/ScopeProtocol/status/1670747954880348160?s=20">on-chain data confirmed</a> significant movements of BTC from Binance wallets, catching the attention of market participants.</p>
<h2>Binance Wallet Migration</h2>
<p>Binance stated that it would be moving funds from its previous BTC cold wallet to a new address, identified as 1Pzaqw98PeRfyHypfqyEgg5yycJRsENrE7. The migration process aimed to enhance the security and infrastructure of Binance&#8217;s BTC holdings.</p>
<p>This wallet transfer involved a substantial amount of BTC, totaling 130,177 BTC or approximately $3.45 billion at the time of the announcement.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-ceo-launches-spot-dca-amidst-market-volatility/">Binance CEO Launches Spot DCA..</a></strong></p>
<p>Following Binance&#8217;s announcement, on-chain data revealed the specific BTC movements associated with the wallet migration. The migration involved two main addresses:</p>
<ol>
<li>1Pzaqw98PeRfyHypfqyEgg5yycJRsENrE7: This address received 1,500 BTC as part of the wallet migration process. It serves as the new destination for a portion of exchange&#8217;s BTC holdings, aligning with their commitment to bolster security measures.</li>
<li>39884E3j6KZj82FK4vcCrkUvWYL5MQaS3v: Another address received a significant portion of the transferred funds, totaling 115,177 BTC.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Bitcoin Whale Movements</h3>
<p>An on-chain data analysis platform LookOnChain reported significant whale movement in this course of time. A <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/btc-whales/">BTC whale</a> withdrew 15,000 BTC (equivalent to approximately $396 million) from Binance.</p>
<p>Interestingly, this transaction was preceded by a test transfer of 1 BTC, highlighting the meticulous approach taken by the whale before executing the substantial withdrawal.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fy-jMrAaAAEdhOE?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096" alt="Image" /></p>
<p>The exchange also reassured the users about their safety of bitcoin holdings by adding this to tweet:</p>
<blockquote><p><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">If you see any significant movements of </span><span class="r-18u37iz">#BTC</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> from our wallets today, that&#8217;s why. Funds are SAFU.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-officially-exits-uk-after-the-netherlands-and-cyprus/">Binance Exits UK Aftr Netherlands and Cyprus..</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-announces-bitcoin-wallet-migration-triggers-on-chain-transfers/">Binance Announces Bitcoin Wallet Migration, Triggers On-Chain Transfers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/24200934/5184.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-officially-exits-uk-after-the-netherlands-and-cyprus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Conduct Authority]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange Binance&#8217;s request to deregister Binance Markets Limited (BML) is approved by the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). Binance Markets Limited didn&#8217;t start offering services and had no users due to heightened scrutiny from regulators. Troubles for crypto exchange Binance continue to mount as it exits from the Netherlands and Cyprus <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-officially-exits-uk-after-the-netherlands-and-cyprus/" title="Breaking: Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-officially-exits-uk-after-the-netherlands-and-cyprus/">Breaking: Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/05221954/1200x-1-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>The world&#8217;s largest <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/binance-exchange-review/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange Binance&#8217;s</a> request to deregister Binance Markets Limited (BML) is <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://register.fca.org.uk/s/firm?id=001b000000nojfNAAQ" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">approved</a> by the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). Binance Markets Limited didn&#8217;t start offering services and had no users due to heightened scrutiny from regulators.</p>
<p>Troubles for crypto exchange Binance continue to mount as it exits from the Netherlands and Cyprus markets amid regulatory challenges and uncertainty.</p>
<h2>Binance Withdraws UK Registration With the FCA</h2>
<p>According to the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), Binance&#8217;s request to deregister Binance Markets Limited was completed on May 30. Now, no other Binance entity holds any authorization from the FCA to provide regulated services in the country.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Following the completion of the cancellation of permissions, the firm is no longer authorized by the FCA. No other entity in the Binance Group holds any form of UK authorization or registration to conduct regulated business in the UK.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Ilir Laro, Binance’s sub-regional manager for growth in the UK and Europe, said the deregistration of Binance Markets Limited doesn&#8217;t impact Binance operations as it never offered any services and has no users.</p>
<p>&#8220;BML was successfully acquired back in 2020 by Binance Group, intended to launch a regulated business in the UK. This attempt was not successful, however, and has since then remained dormant since its acquisition,&#8221; he added.</p>
<p>The firm was previously authorized by the FCA or PRA, thus, issued a warning against Binance Markets Limited, stating that the firm provided regulated services without prior written consent from the FCA.</p>
<p>Binance has been in a battle with the regulators in the UK ever since it launched its crypto service in 2020.</p>
<p class="n0jPhd ynAwRc MBeuO nDgy9d" role="heading" aria-level="3">In March, Binance also ceased Sterling withdrawals and deposits for UK clients after its local partner Paysafe terminated operating agreements.</p>
<p role="heading" aria-level="3">According to Kaiko <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1670767740951445507" target="_blank" rel="noopener">data</a>, the exchange previously accounted for most Sterling-denominated crypto volume until it lost its banking partner.</p>
<p role="heading" aria-level="3"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fy_B6GEWYAIU8bf?format=jpg&amp;name=large" width="738" height="400" /></p>
<p role="heading" aria-level="3"><strong>Also Read: <a title="Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale" href="https://coingape.com/fidelity-investments-reportedly-filing-blackrock-type-spot-bitcoin-etf-acquire-grayscale/" rel="bookmark">Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale</a></strong></p>
<h2 role="heading" aria-level="3">Troubles Faced By the Crypto Exchange</h2>
<p>Binance is facing two lawsuits in the US, <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-vs-sec" target="_blank" rel="noopener">one by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> and another by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The experts point that the Dept of Justice may soon follow a lawsuit against the crypto exchange.</p>
<p>Binance recently withdrew its <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-news-cryprus-crypto-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cyprus virtual asset service providers</a> (VASP) registration as it prepares for MiCA. The crypto exchange also stopped offering <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-dutch-netherland-us-sec-crypto-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">services in the Netherlands</a> due to not obtaining a license.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-key-events-to-impact-bitcoin-ethereum-price-this-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Key Events To Impact Bitcoin, Ethereum Price This Week</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-officially-exits-uk-after-the-netherlands-and-cyprus/">Breaking: Binance Officially Exits UK After The Netherlands And Cyprus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/05221954/1200x-1-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: Can $BTC Bulls Anticipate $30000 Breakout in Current Recovery?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-can-btc-bulls-anticipate-30000-breakout-in-current-recovery/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=152210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Price Analysis: The Bitcoin price initiated a minor recovery rally in mid-June offering relief to the coin holders from the recent sell-off in the crypto market. From the local support of $25200, the prices surged 5% to reach the current price of $26473. However, the daily candles started to project higher price rejection suggesting <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-can-btc-bulls-anticipate-30000-breakout-in-current-recovery/" title="Bitcoin Price Analysis: Can $BTC Bulls Anticipate $30000 Breakout in Current Recovery?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-can-btc-bulls-anticipate-30000-breakout-in-current-recovery/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: Can $BTC Bulls Anticipate $30000 Breakout in Current Recovery?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19172846/4O4mlBUi-e1687175942284.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Analysis" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19172846/4O4mlBUi-e1687175942284.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19172846/4O4mlBUi-e1687175942284-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19172846/4O4mlBUi-e1687175942284-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19172846/4O4mlBUi-e1687175942284-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Analysis: The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> initiated a minor recovery rally in mid-June offering relief to the coin holders from the recent sell-off in the crypto market. From the local support of $25200, the prices surged 5% to reach the current price of $26473. However, the daily candles started to project higher price rejection suggesting the broader market sentiment is still bearish. Can buyers turn the tables with the current recovery or will the seller continue to have the upper hand?</span></p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-bulls-take-charge-is-a-42000-breakout-imminent/">Bitcoin Price Bulls Take Charge: Is a $42,000 Breakout Imminent?</a></p>
<h2><b>Bitcoin Price Daily Chart:</b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The narrow area between the wedge pattern can be considered a no-trading zone</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Bitcoin fear and greed index at 48% reflects neutral market sentiment.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Bitcoin is $9.12 billion, indicating a 38% loss. </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/4/4O4mlBUi.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1104" />(Source: </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">)</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under the influence of a <a href="https://coingape.com/education/falling-wedge-pattern-what-to-do-if-it-appears-on-a-crypto-chart/">falling wedge pattern</a> that governs the current retracement phase in Bitcoin price, the recent relief rally is likely a temporary growth. A bullish reversal from the pattern’s lower trendline triggers a new bull cycle which may push the prices back to the upper trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of now, the BTC price trades quite close to the overhead trendline, and there, the supply pressure is visible with the long-wick rejection candles. If the selling pressure persists for a few more trading traders, the coin price could trigger a bearish reversal.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This potential reversal will signal the continuation of the downward trend and lead the price back $25000.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, the completion of this chart pattern is needed to free the Bitcoin price from the correction phase.</span></p>
<h2><b>Will Bitcoin Price Rise to $27,000?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the recent price surge, the BTC price is likely to hit the resistance trendline of the wedge pattern, trying to validate the overhead supply. The potential traders must remain still and watch the price behavior at this trendline to determine future prospects. A potential reversal from this barrier will prolong the current downfall, while an upside could pave the way for sustained recovery.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative Strength Index</strong>: Contrary to the new lower low in price action, the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> forming the same lows indicate the underlying bullish momentum in growing.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Exponential Moving Average</strong>: The 50-and-200-day <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMA</a> creates a narrow range that may carry the possible consolidation phase in Bitcoin price.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-can-btc-bulls-anticipate-30000-breakout-in-current-recovery/">Bitcoin Price Analysis: Can $BTC Bulls Anticipate $30000 Breakout in Current Recovery?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19172846/4O4mlBUi-e1687175942284.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Burn Rate Soars Over 1000%, Will SHIB Price Explode?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-soars-over-1000-will-shib-price-explode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib burn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152198</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu burn rate has spiked over 1000% in the past 24 hours, burning a total of 15,487,160 $SHIB tokens. The trading volume has seen an upsurge of around 80% in the same time period. After weeks, SHIB&#8217;s price surge yesterday has propelled a substantial number of tokens to reach their break-even point. Shiba Inu <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-soars-over-1000-will-shib-price-explode/" title="Shiba Inu Burn Rate Soars Over 1000%, Will SHIB Price Explode?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-soars-over-1000-will-shib-price-explode/">Shiba Inu Burn Rate Soars Over 1000%, Will SHIB Price Explode?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06181825/Highs-and-Lows-Is-Shiba-Inu-a-Good-Investment.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="shib portfolio" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Shiba Inu burn rate has spiked over 1000% in the past 24 hours, burning a total of 15,487,160 $SHIB tokens. The trading volume has seen an upsurge of around 80% in the same time period. After weeks, <a href="https://coingape.com/price/shiba-inu/">SHIB&#8217;s price</a> surge yesterday has propelled a substantial number of tokens to reach their break-even point.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Burn Rate Soars</h2>
<p>According to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.shibburn.com/">Shibburn</a>, the website tracking token burns, the burn rate of SHIB tokens has skyrocketed by an impressive 1027.94% in just 24 hours. This surge in burn rate highlights the growing interest and demand for SHIB within the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the trading volume for SHIB has surged by around 80% demonstrating a substantial increase in investor activity and trading interest.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has achieved a market capitalization of $4.2 billion with a 0.70% increase, while the trading volume of $202,163,917 indicates robust activity in the market.</p>
<h3>SHIB Price Action</h3>
<p>The price of SHIB currently stands at $0.000007207, experiencing a minor decrease of 0.51% within the hour but an overall increase of 0.82% over the past 24 hours. Moreover, over the course of the last week, SHIB has risen by an impressive 8.80%, further contributing to its recent bullish momentum.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-152200" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19161910/shub-.png" alt="" width="1303" height="775" /></p>
<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s BONE has also shown bullish trend over the past week, with a gain of 5.70% in 07 days. Its trading volume stands at $4,690,825, up around 20%.</p>
<p>SHIB broke through a crucial resistance level at $0.000007 yesterday, resulting in a remarkable 4.6% gain within a mere 30 minutes. Recent market data analyzed by IntoTheBlock highlights a remarkable development: over a trillion SHIB tokens have regained their initial value as a direct result of the latest price action.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://u.today/sites/default/files/inline-images/shibitb.png" /></p>
<p>On October 28, 2021, SHIB reached its all-time high price of $0.00008616. However, since then, the price has experienced a sharp decline, dropping by 91.64%.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-soars-over-1000-will-shib-price-explode/">Shiba Inu Burn Rate Soars Over 1000%, Will SHIB Price Explode?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06181825/Highs-and-Lows-Is-Shiba-Inu-a-Good-Investment.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO CZ Calls “No Beef” With Dutch Central Bank Amid Exit</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-cz-dutch-central-bank-crypto-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CZ Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance News: The world’s largest crypto exchange, Binance recently announced its exit from the Dutch market due to its inability to register as a VASP with the regulatory authorities. Reports suggest that the crypto exchange might have been forced to move out. However, Binance CEO issued a statement addressing the concern. Also Read: Ripple Seek <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-cz-dutch-central-bank-crypto-news/" title="Binance CEO CZ Calls “No Beef” With Dutch Central Bank Amid Exit"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-cz-dutch-central-bank-crypto-news/">Binance CEO CZ Calls “No Beef” With Dutch Central Bank Amid Exit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/08160005/Top-Altcoins-Crash-by-Over-20-As-US-Court-Summons-Binance-CEO.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Binance" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Binance News:</strong> The world’s largest <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange</a>, Binance recently announced its <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-dutch-netherland-us-sec-crypto-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">exit from the Dutch market</a> due to its inability to register as a VASP with the regulatory authorities. Reports suggest that the crypto exchange might have been forced to move out. However, Binance CEO issued a statement addressing the concern.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-misconduct-hinman-docs-release-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Seek To File For Misconduct Post Hinman Docs Release?</a></strong></p>
<h2>Binance Threatened To Face Hefty Fines?</h2>
<p>As per reports, De Nederlandsche Bank (DNB), the central bank of the Netherlands fined Binance $3.3 million for operating without registration. The authority now decided not to grant the biggest crypto exchange with a VASP license to operate.</p>
<p>It is important to note that there are several exchanges that continue to operate in the Netherlands without registration. As of now, US’s biggest exchange, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://companies.coingape.com/coinbase" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coinbase Global Inc (NASDAQ: COIN)</a> managed to gain a VASP license in the country. Meanwhile, Binance decides to withdraw from the market. It is being speculated that the Dutch Central Bank might have threatened the exchange to face a heftier fine than before.</p>
<p>Responding to speculations, Binance CEO, Changpeng Zhao (CZ) <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1670709239835242498" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> “No Beed” but that their crypto exchange is large and complex. He mentioned that there are around 50 simple local VASP license holders which should provide decent access to crypto. He added that the Netherlands is still much more progressive for digital assets than others. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/Binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More Binance News Here&#8230;<br />
</strong></a></p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/rug-pull-alert-list-of-altcoins-celsius-network-will-sell-on-july-1st/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Rug Pull Alert: List Of Altcoins Celsius Network Will Sell On July 1st</strong></a></p>
<h2>Biggest Crypto Exchange Lossing Ground In EU?</h2>
<p>Amid facing regulatory complications from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Binance was focusing on gaining clarity in European nations. However, the biggest crypto exchange&#8217;s latest move left the users thinking of the uncertain future of the digital assets market.</p>
<p>According to reports, Binance has been able to gain just approval to operate in an EU country under the current regulatory regime. The exchange received such approvals in France, Italy, Poland, Lithuania, Spain, and Sweden.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-cz-dutch-central-bank-crypto-news/">Binance CEO CZ Calls “No Beef” With Dutch Central Bank Amid Exit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/08160005/Top-Altcoins-Crash-by-Over-20-As-US-Court-Summons-Binance-CEO.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/fidelity-investments-reportedly-filing-blackrock-type-spot-bitcoin-etf-acquire-grayscale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152191</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity Investments, the world&#8217;s third-largest asset management firm with $4.2 trillion in assets under management (AUM), preparing to file a spot Bitcoin ETF similar to BlackRock iShares spot Bitcoin ETF. The financial giant is also planning to submit an offer to acquire the largest digital asset management firm Grayscale Investments. Fidelity Investments Filing a Spot <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/fidelity-investments-reportedly-filing-blackrock-type-spot-bitcoin-etf-acquire-grayscale/" title="Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/fidelity-investments-reportedly-filing-blackrock-type-spot-bitcoin-etf-acquire-grayscale/">Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1201" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/03012103/Fidelity_Canada.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Fidelity Investments</strong>, the world&#8217;s third-largest asset management firm with $4.2 trillion in assets under management (AUM), preparing to file a spot Bitcoin ETF similar to <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/blackrock" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> <strong>iShares spot Bitcoin ETF</strong>. The financial giant is also planning to submit an offer to acquire the largest digital asset management firm <strong>Grayscale Investments</strong>.</p>
<h2>Fidelity Investments Filing a Spot Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>After BlackRock iShares spot Bitcoin ETF filing, Fidelity Investments also preparing a similar spot Bitcoin ETF application with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Fidelity Investments operates its digital asset operations under <strong>Fidelity Digital Assets</strong>.</p>
<p>Moreover, Fidelity Investments is also looking to submit a bid to acquire Grayscale Investments. Barry Silbert&#8217;s Digital Currency Group-owned Grayscale sued the US SEC for rejecting its application to convert Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) to spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">UPDATE: <a href="https://twitter.com/DigitalAssets?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@DigitalAssets</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/Fidelity?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Fidelity</a> is about to make a seismic move in crypto via both <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>. </p>
<p>Sources expect Fidelity to either make a bid for <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Grayscale</a> or quickly launch their own spot <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bitcoin</a> ETF. One or both are coming, soon. </p>
<p>**Blackrock and Fidelity will own…</p>
<p>&mdash; Andrew (@AP_Abacus) <a href="https://twitter.com/AP_Abacus/status/1670455968608538624?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/best-telegram-crypto-channels-list" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto Telegram Channels List 2023; Updated List</a></strong></p>
<p>Crypto influencer <strong>Andrew Parish</strong> also <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/AP_Abacus/status/1670455968608538624" target="_blank" rel="noopener">believes</a> that as traditional financial firms enter the crypto industry, he wouldn’t be surprised to see Fidelity offer staking services soon. Fidelity Digital Asset already offers Ethereum ETF in the US and Bitcoin ETFs on international exchanges. Moreover, it is mining Bitcoin since 2014 and accumulating BTC, as well as offering crypto custody services.</p>
<p>Fidelity Investments and Grayscale have yet to confirm the buzz surrounding filing a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund and bid to acquire GBTC issuer Grayscale.</p>
<p>The news was shared by notable crypto influencers including Scott Melker or The Wolf Of All Streets, Michael van de Poppe, and Ash Crypto.</p>
<p>The crypto community reacted positively to the news and anticipates Fidelity can file for spot Bitcoin ETF as it continues to deepen its crypto presence.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="Crypto News: Key Events To Impact Bitcoin, Ethereum Price This Week" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-key-events-to-impact-bitcoin-ethereum-price-this-week/" rel="bookmark">Key Crypto Events To Impact Bitcoin, Ethereum Price This Week</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/fidelity-investments-reportedly-filing-blackrock-type-spot-bitcoin-etf-acquire-grayscale/">Fidelity Investments Reportedly Filing BlackRock-Type Spot Bitcoin ETF, Acquire Grayscale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/03012103/Fidelity_Canada.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit: Ripple Seek To File For Misconduct Post Hinman Docs Release?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-misconduct-hinman-docs-release-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 08:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=152172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP Lawsuit News: The release of crucial Hinman speech linked documents in the XRP lawsuit led to several speculations in the crypto industry. The memos revealed that the Ethereum (ETH) founder, Vitalik Buterin was involved in the process of the infamous speech. However, this event has also raised questions about the involvement of judges in <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-misconduct-hinman-docs-release-news/" title="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple Seek To File For Misconduct Post Hinman Docs Release?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-misconduct-hinman-docs-release-news/">XRP Lawsuit: Ripple Seek To File For Misconduct Post Hinman Docs Release?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19132439/xrp_sec_lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP Lawsuit Ripple Misconduct Hinman Docs Release News" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>XRP Lawsuit News:</strong> The release of crucial <a href="https://coingape.com/hinman-ignored-all-warnings-split-up-howey-test-ripple-legal-chief/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hinman speech linked documents</a> in the XRP lawsuit led to several speculations in the crypto industry. The memos revealed that the Ethereum (ETH) founder, <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-eth-vitalik-hinman-speech-docs-lawsuit-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vitalik Buterin was involved</a> in the process of the infamous speech. However, this event has also raised questions about the involvement of judges in the case.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ripple-ceo-alleges-sec-chair-incorrectly-labels-tokens-as-securities-in-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple CEO Alleges SEC Chair Incorrectly Labels Tokens As Securities</a></strong></p>
<h2>Judge Torres To address Overreach In XRP Lawsuit?</h2>
<p>Attorney John Deaton, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/amicus-curiae/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amicus curiae</a> in the US SEC vs Ripple lawsuit mentioned that there are several instances of corrupt judges and political affiliations in history. However, this might not be the situation in the XRP lawsuit as he knows how District Judge Analisa Torres got selected. He added that she was less political than most of the federal judge.</p>
<p>XRP holders’ lawyer hinted that government overreach and the commission’s conduct might offend the judge to a certain point that she decides to comment on it. Despite the motives involved by former SEC director Hinmans and the US SEC, Judge Torres is expected to apply the law the way she sees it.</p>
<h2>Misconduct In Ripple Case?</h2>
<p>It is important to note that there is no such motion presented to throw out the XRP lawsuit due to misconduct. There are many voices in the industry that consider this as an option but Ripple hasn’t filed anything like that.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/rug-pull-alert-list-of-altcoins-celsius-network-will-sell-on-july-1st/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Rug Pull Alert: List Of Altcoins Bankrupt Celsius Network Will Sell On July 1st</strong></a></p>
<p>The attorney <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1670474870692405249" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stated</a> that he is not surprised that Ripple didn’t move forward to file a motion around bad motives or misconduct. However, it is a bit of a shocker that the defendants didn’t intertwine the narrative of the pleadings. He suggested that selective enforcement happens all the time but this doesn’t mean that Ripple would take that route.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-misconduct-hinman-docs-release-news/">XRP Lawsuit: Ripple Seek To File For Misconduct Post Hinman Docs Release?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/19132439/xrp_sec_lawsuit.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
