<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:08:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>ApeCoin (APE) Price Prediction: Here&#8217;s How Metacade (MCADE) Will Outpace Apecoin in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-ape-price-prediction-heres-how-metacade-mcade-will-outpace-apecoin-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-ape-price-prediction-heres-how-metacade-mcade-will-outpace-apecoin-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-ape-price-prediction-heres-how-metacade-mcade-will-outpace-apecoin-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investors all across the crypto scene are reflecting deeply on a tough year, while actively seeking out opportunities for life-changing gains. It&#8217;s no surprise that some more established projects like ApeCoin are being carefully looked at, but it&#8217;s a newcomer, Metacade, that&#8217;s really starting to shake things up. Keep reading to learn more and see [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-ape-price-prediction-heres-how-metacade-mcade-will-outpace-apecoin-in-2023/">ApeCoin (APE) Price Prediction: Here&#8217;s How Metacade (MCADE) Will Outpace Apecoin in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Investors all across the crypto scene are reflecting deeply on a tough year, while actively seeking out opportunities for life-changing gains. It&rsquo;s no surprise that some more established projects like ApeCoin are being carefully looked at, but it&rsquo;s a newcomer, Metacade, that&rsquo;s really starting to shake things up.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Keep reading to learn more and see if the Metacade and ApeCoin price predictions below can help shed some light on the best investment for your hard-earned cash.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> has taken on the world of gaming, looking to establish a new community that fuses together the best of both gaming and crypto into an immersive experience &ndash; allowing gamers and crypto lovers to connect with one another while playing their favorite games.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has <a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>set out</u></a> to provide gamers with a one-stop shop for all their gaming needs. Most importantly, Metacade features a play-to-earn arcade with aspirations for a huge number of titles, allowing users to earn rewards in the process &mdash; including through competitive play in tournaments and other ways of engaging with the community. The project also supports staking for token holders, allowing MCADE holders to earn a passive income while contributing to the ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Metacade work?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade uses the MCADE token throughout its platform. It is required to enable much of the functionality; for access to games, as well as for entry into competitive gaming tournaments and prize draws.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Easily the most novel element is Metagrants, where funding for metaverse game development will be up for grabs to talented game designers. Token holders within Metacade&rsquo;s community can vote for which projects are funded and later could even earn rewards for testing the very games they supported. All of this is to take place thanks to one of the platform&rsquo;s core philosophies of Work2Earn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team behind Metacade is working towards achieving full DAO governance by Q4 2024. This will involve handing over key roles and responsibilities to the Metacade community so that it becomes a fully community-staffed business, and to ensure the project measures up to the high standards required in Web3, Metacade has submitted its specification, smart contract, and team for a <a href="https://metacade.co/certik-audit" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Certik audit</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade looks set to be an incredible investment opportunity, with all signs pointing towards a bright future ahead and with huge potential for both developers and gamers alike looking for new opportunities on Web3 platforms.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MCADE Price Prediction General</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE is the powerful utility token used throughout the Metacade platform. Aside from the staking transactions, it also provides two wide-ranging use cases: as a medium of exchange and within the Metacade rewards system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The value element of MCADE means that as adoption increases, the need for more MCADE to be held by the user base increases &ndash; as more users look to play games, developers seek funding, as well as the host of other gaming activities facilitated by the Metacade ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The retention of users is aided through the rewards offered on the platform, further strengthened by the security and transaction fee benefits that come with being on the Ethereum network. All of it means the project is likely to continue to build momentum, putting sustained buying pressure on the MCADE token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In light of these factors, it seems clear that the price of MCADE is likely to increase significantly. This is likely to occur as soon as 2023 due to the exciting roadmap deliverables, of both the classic arcade launch and the awarding of the first Metagrant. As more users begin to see the exciting reality of the platform and FOMO kicks in, a price prediction of 30x from the presale is not out of the question.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for a price prediction further into the future, it&rsquo;s useful to look at the market cap for projects like The Sandbox, which comfortably achieved a $6 billion market cap in 2021 despite a small user base. As such, a $20 billion market cap for Metacade is achievable if their vision continues to stay on course over the next few years, meaning the price could increase 1,000x to $10.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">ApeCoin Price Prediction General</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://apecoin.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ApeCoin</u></a> is relatively new itself, having launched in March 2022, and has been adopted by popular NFT releases Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) and Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC). The Bored Ape ecosystem focuses on NFTs and especially collectables and art.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ambition of ApeCoin, run by the community through a DAO, is to try to allow community governance to provide an art-first ecosystem that can provide value to creative industries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ApeCoin price prediction is difficult, but with so many unknowns and <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2022/12/06/30m-pours-into-apecoin-staking-in-first-day/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>regulatory concerns in the US</u></a>, it&rsquo;s hard to see a dramatic price rise. Indeed, if ApeCoin can rise by 20% in 2023 to $4.60, that would be deemed a big success for the project &mdash; hence why many believe Metacade will likely surpass the well-known project sooner rather than later.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade &ndash; Set to see dramatic price rises</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The challenges facing APE make the ApeCoin price&nbsp;prediction&nbsp;sobering, but there&rsquo;s still a chance of a reasonable amount of upside. In contrast, it&rsquo;s hard to ignore the potential that Metacade offers. Reviewing the Metacade and ApeCoin price&nbsp;predictions&nbsp;leaves all rational investors with only one real choice for life-changing gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s no wonder that Metacade, even in its early stages, is attracting so much attention from crypto communities. With stage 1 of the presale underway, the MCADE tokens available are likely to have been secured by savvy investors very soon.</p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the Metacade pre-sale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-ape-price-prediction-heres-how-metacade-mcade-will-outpace-apecoin-in-2023/">ApeCoin (APE) Price Prediction: Here&#8217;s How Metacade (MCADE) Will Outpace Apecoin in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/apecoin-ape-price-prediction-heres-how-metacade-mcade-will-outpace-apecoin-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CNBC: SBF to plead not guilty to buy time for his legal team</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cnbc-sbf-to-plead-not-guilty-to-buy-time-for-his-legal-team/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 14:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cnbc-sbf-to-plead-not-guilty-to-buy-time-for-his-legal-team/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gary Wang, former CTO of FTX and Caroline Ellison, former chief executive of Alameda, are cooperating with investigators Bankman-Fried is charged with illegally using FTX customer funds to buy real estate properties and supporting Alameda Research He was released on a $250 million bond after being extradited to the US from the Bahamas Sam Bankman-Fried [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cnbc-sbf-to-plead-not-guilty-to-buy-time-for-his-legal-team/">CNBC: SBF to plead not guilty to buy time for his legal team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Gary Wang, former CTO of FTX and Caroline Ellison, former chief executive of Alameda, are cooperating with investigators</li>
<li>Bankman-Fried is charged with illegally using FTX customer funds to buy real estate properties and supporting Alameda Research</li>
<li>He was released on a $250 million bond after being extradited to the US from the Bahamas</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried is expected to enter a plea of not guilty today. He has been charged with cheating investors and stealing billions from the collapsed FTX cryptocurrency exchange, CNBC&rsquo;s Squawk Box <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/01/03/sam-bankman-fried-to-plead-not-guilty-to-federal-charges-reports-say.html">reported</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to insiders, the reasons for the plea are to buy time for his legal team to explore legal defenses and to enable the start of a discovery process, i.e. what prosecutors will have against him.</p>
<h2>A heavy blow &nbsp;</h2>
<p>Gary Wang, former CTO of FTX and Caroline Ellison, former chief executive of Alameda, are cooperating with investigators. They pleaded guilty to four and seven criminal charges, respectively.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is a huge blow because they were his closest allies. They were privy to the inside workings of FTX and if there was any evidence of the charges alleged. On one hand, it seems there has been an absence of records, but insiders expect there must be some &ldquo;semblance of bookkeeping.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried is charged with illegally using FTX customer funds to buy real estate properties, support his <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alameda-liquidates-millions-worth-of-tokens-for-bitcoin/">Alameda Research</a> hedge fund, and donate millions to various political causes. He will appear at 14:00 ET in Manhattan before US District Judge Lewis Kaplan.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Plea might change&nbsp;</h2>
<p>It is common for criminal defendants to start with a not guilty plea. They can change their plea at a later date.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried was released on a $250 million bond after being<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/">&nbsp;extradited to the US</a> from the Bahamas, where FTX was based and which he had made his home. Since his release a month ago, he has been required to live with his parents and been subject to electronic monitoring.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>He faces up to 115 years in prison</h2>
<p>The MIT graduate has been charged with six counts of conspiracy and two counts of wire fraud, including money laundering and campaign finance violations. If he is found guilty, he faces up to 115 years in prison.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The new CEO of FTX, John Ray, commented that the exchange had been run by &ldquo;grossly inexperienced&rdquo; people. Ray has worked on the insolvency of energy company Enron Corp.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cnbc-sbf-to-plead-not-guilty-to-buy-time-for-his-legal-team/">CNBC: SBF to plead not guilty to buy time for his legal team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockdaemon CEO: Success of crypto is predicated on systemic failure; we’ll see more of that</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockdaemon-ceo-success-of-crypto-is-predicated-on-systemic-failure-well-see-more-of-that/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockdaemon-ceo-success-of-crypto-is-predicated-on-systemic-failure-well-see-more-of-that/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/blockdaemon-ceo-success-of-crypto-is-predicated-on-systemic-failure-well-see-more-of-that/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>All major players should work with multiple infrastructure providers &#160; Companies like Nasdaq will continue to work on Bitcoin, permissioned networks, and stablecoins Talia Caplan of CNBC Crypto World talked to Konstantin Richter, the founder and CEO of Blockdaemon, about blockchain adoption following the fall of FTX and what 2023 holds for crypto. Richter also [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockdaemon-ceo-success-of-crypto-is-predicated-on-systemic-failure-well-see-more-of-that/">Blockdaemon CEO: Success of crypto is predicated on systemic failure; we’ll see more of that</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>All major players should work with multiple infrastructure providers &nbsp;</li>
<li>Companies like Nasdaq will continue to work on Bitcoin, permissioned networks, and stablecoins</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Talia Caplan of <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/01/02/blockdaemon-ceo-discusses-blockchain-adoption-following-the-fall-of-ftx-and-what-2023-holds-for-crypto.html">CNBC Crypto World</a> talked to Konstantin Richter, the founder and CEO of Blockdaemon, about blockchain adoption following the fall of FTX and what 2023 holds for crypto. Richter also broke down whether crypto&rsquo;s adoption rate would slow down after FTX&rsquo;s failure.</p>
<h2>Institutionalizing the chaos&nbsp;</h2>
<p><strong>Talia Caplan: How do you serve your customers?</strong></p>
<p>Konstantin Richter: We are a middleware platform. We make the process of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/">buying crypto</a> seamless. These networks are all open source, thousand of users control them.&nbsp;We institutionalize the chaos.</p>
<p><strong>TC: You wanted to work with FTX but they insisted on running their blockchain infrastructure in-house&hellip;</strong>&nbsp;</p>
<p>KR: When it comes to transparency and reliability, it&rsquo;s important for all major players to work with multiple infrastructure providers and not only rely on their in-house infrastructure because it breeds the potential for abuse.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Will crypto adoption increase?&nbsp;</h2>
<p><strong>TC: This year we saw increased institutional adoption. Wall Street firms like Nasdaq are moving into crypto. Do you see more of this happening in 2023?</strong>&nbsp;</p>
<p>KR: I don&rsquo;t necessarily see a slowdown in institutional adoption. Companies like Nasdaq will continue to work on Bitcoin, permissioned networks, and stablecoins. We will see continued growth this year. There is more focus on quality, on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/three-large-cap-cryptocurrencies-that-brave-the-crypto-bear-wave-this-week/">large cap tokens</a> like Bitcoin and Ethereum. I think volume will be a little lower; slower consumer adoption in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>TC: What will it take to turn that around?</strong></p>
<p>KR: Regulation is part of the answer. I can&rsquo;t speak for the industry as a whole. Regulators have the responsibility to do a lot more, to protect consumers by providing a clear framework that companies can adhere to. Otherwise you have companies like FTX who claim to be regulated, but really aren&rsquo;t. The other factor is general macroeconomics, rising interest rates&hellip;general equities will be more impacted than crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>TC: What advice do you have for centralized entities and DeFi after the collapse?</strong></p>
<p>KR: These entities should be public and open about the board of directors, who the people involved are, who the main investors in the entity are. It&rsquo;s important to understand what motivates stakeholders. That would have been hugely beneficial in the case of FTX. I can&rsquo;t say enough good things about Coinbase. You have ultimate transparency, they&rsquo;re a public company.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He added that DeFi was the solution to lack of transparency because it offered software that was externally verifiable. The problem for him is that DeFi is complicated. He said it was community-driven and there was no clear regulation at this point.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Still bullish on crypto</h2>
<p>When asked if he still felt bullish on crypto, he said he felt more bullish than ever, adding:</p>
<p><em>I was talking to investors earlier and the general consensus is that what happened to crypto is really bad. We all thought FTX was a lot better. It&rsquo;s a great reminder not to trust individuals, but to verify. FTX was a one-man fraud that was using components of crypto to solicit funding. The promise of crypto in taking out middlemen&hellip;is truer than ever. The success of crypto is predicated on systemic failure and we&rsquo;re going to see more of that. The use case of crypto is more relevant than ever. &nbsp;&nbsp;</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockdaemon-ceo-success-of-crypto-is-predicated-on-systemic-failure-well-see-more-of-that/">Blockdaemon CEO: Success of crypto is predicated on systemic failure; we’ll see more of that</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockdaemon-ceo-success-of-crypto-is-predicated-on-systemic-failure-well-see-more-of-that/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FLOW leads the charge as broader crypto market experiences mixed performances</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/flow-leads-the-charge-as-broader-crypto-market-experiences-mixed-performances/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/flow-leads-the-charge-as-broader-crypto-market-experiences-mixed-performances/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/flow-leads-the-charge-as-broader-crypto-market-experiences-mixed-performances/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FLOW is up by more than 8% today, outperforming the other coins and tokens in the top 100 list. The broader crypto market has recovered from its poor performance this week. Bitcoin and Ether are trading in the red zone. FLOW outperforms the other major cryptocurrencies FLOW, the native coin of the Flow blockchain, emerged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/flow-leads-the-charge-as-broader-crypto-market-experiences-mixed-performances/">FLOW leads the charge as broader crypto market experiences mixed performances</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">FLOW is up by more than 8% today, outperforming the other coins and tokens in the top 100 list.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The broader crypto market has recovered from its poor performance this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ether are trading in the red zone.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>FLOW outperforms the other major cryptocurrencies</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">FLOW, the native coin of the Flow blockchain, emerged as the best performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap on Tuesday. The coin has added more than 8% to its value today and could rally higher soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/flow/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of FLOW</u></a> stands at $0.7193. There is no catalyst behind FLOW&rsquo;s ongoing positive performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The surge comes as the broader crypto market recovers from its earlier slump. The total cryptocurrency market cap stands above $805 billion, up by less than 1% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While FLOW is rallying, some of the major cryptocurrencies are outperforming. Bitcoin is down by less than 1% today and could record further losses in the coming hours. The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> currently stands at $16.735. Meanwhile, ETH has also lost less than 1% of its value and is now trading at $1,215 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The FLOW/USD 4-hour chart has just turned bullish, as FLOW has been performing well in the last 24 hours. The technical indicators show that FLOW could rally higher soon.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/03/1672751316873-f16af2c6-e199-4d62-91f0-38cfa89c1d53.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="261"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/FLOWUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>FLOW/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The 14-day relative strength index of 75 shows that FLOW could be heading toward the overbought region if the rally continues.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line crossed into the positive zone a few hours ago, indicating that the bulls are now in charge. With a more bullish move, FLOW could surge past the first major resistance level at $0.874 before the end of the day.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the support of the broader cryptocurrency market, FLOW could cross the $1 psychological level for the first time since December 11.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy FLOW now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkwMzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FLOW with Binance today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Uphold</h3>

    <p>Uphold is a platform which has over 50 cryptocurrencies to choose from.

It's users can make crypto trades with a bank account, credit card or crypto debit card. It has variable fees and allows users to automate trades.

Users who are on Brave's internet browser can also earn BAT tokens based on their browsing habits.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/uphold-crypto?guid=OTkwMzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FLOW with Uphold today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/flow-leads-the-charge-as-broader-crypto-market-experiences-mixed-performances/">FLOW leads the charge as broader crypto market experiences mixed performances</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/flow-leads-the-charge-as-broader-crypto-market-experiences-mixed-performances/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana jumps by 7% to surpass the $11 resistance mark: Should you buy?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-reclaims-jumps-by-7-to-surpass-the-11-resistance-mark-should-you-buy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-reclaims-jumps-by-7-to-surpass-the-11-resistance-mark-should-you-buy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana is the best performer amongst the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. SOL is trading above $10 again after rallying more than 7% in the last 24 hours. The total cryptocurrency market cap remains above $800 billion. SOL soars past the $10 resistance level SOL, the native token of the Solana ecosystem, is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-reclaims-jumps-by-7-to-surpass-the-11-resistance-mark-should-you-buy/">Solana jumps by 7% to surpass the $11 resistance mark: Should you buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Solana is the best performer amongst the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">SOL is trading above $10 again after rallying more than 7% in the last 24 hours.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap remains above $800 billion.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>SOL soars past the $10 resistance level</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">SOL, the native token of the Solana ecosystem, is the best performer amongst the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. The coin has added more than 7% to its value, allowing it to surpass a crucial resistance level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Solana</u></a> stands at $11.89, up by more than 7% in the last 24 hours. There is no catalyst behind SOL&rsquo;s ongoing positive performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The broader crypto market is trading in the green zone, but several of the leading coins and tokens are recording losses. The total crypto market cap stands at $808 billion, up by less than 1% today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, is trading in the red zone. It has lost less than 1% today, and the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> currently stands at $16.735.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key levels to watch</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The SOL/USD 4-hour chart has turned bullish, as Solana has been performing well over the last few days. The technical indicators show that Solana has been outperforming the broader market since the start of the week.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable fr-fil" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/03/1672751316660-abf133d1-39b1-4ff0-b4f0-81fd567dbc0f.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="261"><span class="fr-inner"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/?exchange=COINBASE"><u>SOL/USD Chart By TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The MACD line crossed into the positive zone earlier this week, indicating that the bulls are now in control of the Solana market. With the support of the broader market, the line could enter deeper into the positive region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The 14-day RSI of 76 shows that SOL could be heading into the overbought region if the rally continues.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the bulls remain in charge, SOL could surge past the first major resistance level at $13.09 before the end of the day. However, unless SOL gains support from the broader crypto market, it would find it hard to move past the second major resistance level at $14.90 in the near term.</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Where to buy Solana now</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTkwMjk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=OTkwMjk&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-reclaims-jumps-by-7-to-surpass-the-11-resistance-mark-should-you-buy/">Solana jumps by 7% to surpass the $11 resistance mark: Should you buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kava price has staged a comeback but risks remain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-has-staged-a-comeback-but-risks-remain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-has-staged-a-comeback-but-risks-remain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-has-staged-a-comeback-but-risks-remain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kava price has crashed by more than 94% from its all-time high. The total value locked (TVL) in its DeFi ecosystem has crashed to $197M. KAVA price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few months as demand for the token eased. The token crashed to a low of $0.5165 on Tuesday, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-has-staged-a-comeback-but-risks-remain/">Kava price has staged a comeback but risks remain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Kava price has crashed by more than 94% from its all-time high.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The total value locked (TVL) in its DeFi ecosystem has crashed to $197M.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">KAVA price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few months as demand for the token eased. The token crashed to a low of $0.5165 on Tuesday, which was about 94% from its highest level in September 2021. Its market cap has crashed to about $224 million, which was lower than its all-time high of more than $1 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Kava total value locked has crashed</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Kava is a blockchain project that is relatively unique from other popular platforms like Cardano and Aptos. It is a dual platform that combines features found in&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum"><u>Ethereum</u></a> and&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cosmos/"><u>Cosmos</u></a>. Ethereum, the biggest smart contract project in the world, is known for its stability and power. Cosmos, on the other hand, is significantly faster and has additional features than other blockchains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kava has seen remarkable developer interest in the past few months. This interest is partly because of its $750 million developer incentive fund. People who deploy on Kava receive developer incentives worth millions of dollars.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kava has over 100 projects, mostly in the DeFi industry. Recently, however, activity in the network has been in a downward trend. The&nbsp;<a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Kava" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>total value locked</u></a> (TVL) in its ecosystem has plunged to about $197 million from its all-time high of almost $700 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most applications in its ecosystem have lost money in the past few months. Some of the most dominant players in its ecosystem are Kava Mint, Kava Lend, Kava Earn, Kava Liquid, Kava Swap, and Kava Boost have struggled to attract inflows. Kava Mint, which has a TVL of over $84 million and a market dominance of 43%. The most recent high-profile platform in its ecosystem was Curve.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is unclear why KAVA price has risen by more than 12% on Tuesday. A possible reason is that the developers are about to make a major announcement on the ecosystem.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Kava price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/03/1672748436480-47c5075c-dcd3-4652-879a-a1ca8359d21e.png" style="width: 697px;height: 346.177px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="697" height="346.177"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/KAVAUSD/?exchange=BINANCE">KAVA chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that Kava price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few months. As it crashed, the coin managed to move below the important support level at $0.80, which was the lowest level on November 9. It has also moved below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the MACD remains below the neutral point.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the downward trend will likely continue falling as sellers target the next key support level at $0.500. A move above the resistance point at $0.70 will invalidate the bearish view.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Kava</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTkwMjU&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy KAVA with Binance today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Wazirx</h3>

    <p>WazirX is India's largest crypto exchange. Started in 2018, WazirX has grown to be the most trusted exchange in the Indian crypto market. It is a part of the binance group, serving users in 180 countries.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/wazirx-crypto?guid=OTkwMjU&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy KAVA with Wazirx today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-has-staged-a-comeback-but-risks-remain/">Kava price has staged a comeback but risks remain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-has-staged-a-comeback-but-risks-remain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bahamas denies allegations it told Bankman-Fried to mint new coins</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-denies-allegations-it-told-bankman-fried-to-mint-new-coins/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-denies-allegations-it-told-bankman-fried-to-mint-new-coins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-denies-allegations-it-told-bankman-fried-to-mint-new-coins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Court filings accused Bahamas officials of asking Bankman-Fired to mint new tokens and transfer them to officials The Securities Commission of the Bahamas (SCB) has also fired back against claims tokens under its control were stolen Hard to know what allegations are true, but anybody remotely connected to FTX is coming out badly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-denies-allegations-it-told-bankman-fried-to-mint-new-coins/">Bahamas denies allegations it told Bankman-Fried to mint new coins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li>Court filings accused Bahamas officials of asking Bankman-Fired to mint new tokens and transfer them to officials</li>
<li>The Securities Commission of the Bahamas (SCB) has also fired back against claims tokens under its control were stolen</li>
<li>Hard to know what allegations are true, but anybody remotely connected to FTX is coming out badly amid the whole debacle &ndash; and that includes the Bahamas regulator</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>There were a lot of startling revelations to emerge over the last month or two following FTX&rsquo;s <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">spectacular collapse</a>. But one of the most insidious, for me at least, was that the Bahamas government worked with Bankman-Fried to mint a new token in the wake of the exchange&rsquo;s collapse.</p>
<h2><strong>Lawyers accuse Bahamas officials of attempting to mint new tokens</strong></h2>
<p>Lawyers for FTX said in a court filing in December that Bahamas government officials asked Bankman-Fried to mint new digital assets worth &ldquo;hundreds of millions of dollars&rdquo;, while requesting that the disgraced CEO transfer the new tokens over to the control of government officials.</p>
<p>The report, published by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-12/ftx-says-bahamas-trying-to-help-bankman-fried-access-key-systems">Bloomberg</a> also outlines that Bahamas officials worked to try to help Bankman-Fried regain access to essential computer systems on the FTX platform. The officials were &ldquo;responsible for directing unauthorised access&rdquo; to the systems in order to take control of some of the digital assets that were on the FTX platform.</p>
<p>This was all particularly concerning as money was evidently moving on the blockchain after FTX&rsquo;s collapse. A reported &ldquo;hack&rdquo; led to $477 million of crypto moving in the days after the bankruptcy filing, with the hacker then looking to bridge the funds into various entities and currencies.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">(1/2)&nbsp; Exchanges should be aware that certain funds transferred from FTX Global and related debtors without authorization on 11/11/22 are being transferred to them through intermediate wallets.</p>
<p>&mdash; FTX (@FTX_Official) <a href="https://twitter.com/FTX_Official/status/1594354846370758657?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 20, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Whether this has any connection to the story regarding the Bahamas&rsquo; pressure on Bankman-Fried is pure speculation, and to be clear, no evidence at all suggests that authorities have anything to do with it.</p>
<p>The Bahaman regulator today released a statement fighting back against the aforementioned comments by John Ray III, the representative of US-based FTX debtors. The statement read that it &ldquo;must once again correct material misstatements made by Mr. John J. Ray III&hellip;in both the press and court filings&rdquo;.</p>
<p>The statement outlined that Ray&rsquo;s court filings, which were &ldquo;under oath&rdquo;, were &ldquo;without evidence&rdquo;, staunchly firing back against the claim that officials had ordered Bankman-Fried to mint new tokens, as well as instructing &ldquo;employees (of FTX) to mint $300 million in new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ftx-token/">FTT</a> tokens&rdquo;. It went on to dispute the claim that digital assets under the control of the Securities Commission of the Bahamas (SCB) were &ldquo;stolen&rdquo;. &nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>What actually happened?</strong></h2>
<p>In truth, it is impossible to know the ins and outs of the debacle here. But what is obvious is that this entire saga continues to get more sordid and embarrassing for cryptocurrency as a whole each day, and anybody remotely connected to FTX is looking worse and worse as time goes on. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The was obviously a massive failure with regard to regulation in the Bahamas, and the SCB is getting rightfully hammered as a result. Whether any of the other allegations hold water, we do not have evidence to opine on, but I&rsquo;m sure time will tell.</p>
<p>With over one million creditors, $8 billion in missing client assets, and many lives ruined, the sadness and gravity of the FTX situation is tough to overstate. Now, it&rsquo;s time to sort through the mess and try to find out who exactly was at fault beyond Bankman-Fried, because there is more than enough blame to go around. &nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-denies-allegations-it-told-bankman-fried-to-mint-new-coins/">Bahamas denies allegations it told Bankman-Fried to mint new coins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bahamas-denies-allegations-it-told-bankman-fried-to-mint-new-coins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jasmy price prediction as Japan’s Bitcoin surges</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/jasmy-price-prediction-as-japans-bitcoin-surges/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/jasmy-price-prediction-as-japans-bitcoin-surges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/jasmy-price-prediction-as-japans-bitcoin-surges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jasmy price has jumped in the past four days. It has jumped by more than 40% from the lowest point in 2022. Jasmy price has had one of the best performances in 2022 as investors bought the dip in Japan&#8217;s&#160;Bitcoin. It has risen in the past five straight days and moved to the highest level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jasmy-price-prediction-as-japans-bitcoin-surges/">Jasmy price prediction as Japan’s Bitcoin surges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Jasmy price has jumped in the past four days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It has jumped by more than 40% from the lowest point in 2022.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Jasmy price has had one of the best performances in 2022 as investors bought the dip in Japan&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a>. It has risen in the past five straight days and moved to the highest level since December 11. These gains represent about a 40% increase from the lowest level in 2022, giving it a market cap of over $100 million.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is Jasmy soaring?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Jasmy is a relatively small blockchain project that has become popular in Japan. The platform was started by a team of former executives at Sony, one of the leading entertainment companies in the world. The platform was created to provide decentralized data storage solutions to companies and individuals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The creators recognized the importance that data plays in the world today. Indeed, we have seen multi-billion dollar companies like Google and Meta Platforms that make money from selling data to advertisers. Data privacy has also become an important part of the word debate today.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Jasmy plays an important part in the democratization of data by combining blockchain and Internet of Things to provide an infrastructure that allows anyone to use data safely and securely. Users can store and control their data, manage and control devices, and provide a safe place to use data in a secure manner.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Jasmy&rsquo;s platform is made possible by a number of popular technologies. Some of the top components of its technology are the Personal Data Locker, which enables data storage within a peer-to-peer network. It also has a secure knowledge communicator which allows data democratization and smart guardian that allows the registration of devices.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is unclear why Jasmy coin price has done well in the past few days. A likely reason is that the developers are about to make a major announcement such as a partnership with a major company. There is speculation that the network will soon partner with Sony.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Jasmy price prediction&nbsp;</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/03/1672746534253-902d5abd-40e4-47f8-bcdc-9a6c0cab5520.png" style="width: 697px;height: 346.701px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="697" height="346.701"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/JASMYUSD/?exchange=COINBASE">JASMY chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that Jasmy price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. It has risen in the past fou straight days and managed to move above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved slightly below the overbought level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, as I&nbsp;<a href="https://www.investingcube.com/jasmy-price-short-squeeze-gets-underway-heres-why-cryptocurrencies/"><u>wrote elsewhere</u></a>, I suspect that Jasmy will retreat in the coming days as the short squeeze fades. Also, it will decline as some of the current buyers move into a distribution phase. If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $0.0032.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Jasmy</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    KuCoin</h3>

    <p>Kucoin is a cryptocurrency exchange which offers over 200 cryptocurrencies.

Kucoin has a wide range of services, such as; a built-in peer-to-peer exchange, spot and margin trading, bank level security and a wide range of accepted payment methods.

Users can benefit from a beginner-friendly interface and relatively low fees.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/kucoin-crypto?guid=OTkwMjE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy JASMY with KuCoin today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=OTkwMjE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy JASMY with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jasmy-price-prediction-as-japans-bitcoin-surges/">Jasmy price prediction as Japan’s Bitcoin surges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/jasmy-price-prediction-as-japans-bitcoin-surges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Solana dead? Top projects flee the blockchain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Solana has shed 95% of its value, falling from $54.5 billion to $4.4 billion Its association with Sam Bankman-Fried has caused further bearish price action Top projects have fled the blockchain this year, with concern over long-term future of Solana &#160; For cryptocurrency investors, the year 2022 was one to forget.&#160; But even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/">Is Solana dead? Top projects flee the blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li>Solana has shed 95% of its value, falling from $54.5 billion to $4.4 billion</li>
<li>Its association with Sam Bankman-Fried has caused further bearish price action</li>
<li>Top projects have fled the blockchain this year, with concern over long-term future of Solana</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For cryptocurrency investors, the year 2022 was one to forget.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But even amongst all the pain, fans of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/buy/">Solana</a> have been hurt more than most. At the start of 2022, Solana was the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/2022-looking-back-at-the-top-10-coins-one-year-ago-today/">fifth biggest crypto</a> in the world with a market cap of $54.5 billion. Today, it is sixteenth in the ranks, having shed over 95% from its peak, now worth $4.4 billion.&nbsp;</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12332747">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>What has happened Solana?</strong></h2>
<p>Firstly, the obvious. The macro climate has flipped immeasurably over the last year. After a decade of basement-level interest rates and a free-flowing money printer, the Federal Reserve pulled the plug.&nbsp;</p>
<p>And just like that, for the first time in cryptocurrency&rsquo;s short history, it is facing a bear market in the wider economy. During the explosive bull run of the prior decade, everything with a pulse enjoyed dizzying returns. But now, the party is over.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Having said this, plotting Solana against Bitcoin shows quite how stark the underperformance has been.&nbsp;</p>
        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12332827">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2><strong>Solana&rsquo;s outages are a massive problem</strong></h2>
<p>The first problem is the incessant outages. I wrote in June about how Solana reminds me of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-reminds-me-of-my-broken-earphones/">my broken earphones</a>. You know, great when they work, but given I need to keep twisting the earphone, disconnecting and reconnecting, in order to listen to music, they&rsquo;re not much good to me.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Solana is like those earphones. It has flexed its market-leading TPS and cheap gas fees for a while, positioning itself as an &ldquo;ETH killer&rdquo;, and enjoyed a flood of interest and lofty gains during the pandemic as a result of this.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Of course, as I said above, this was during a period of expansion of all risk assets, and due diligence in the cryptocurrency altcoin space was not exactly as granular as it should have been. There were &ndash; and are &ndash; serious problems under the hood of Solana, as the outages have continued at a relentless pace.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Riddle me this &ndash; how useful is a blockchain if it frequently switches off?</p>
<p>Back in that article from June, I wrote that &ldquo;I&rsquo;m getting a little tired of using the words &lsquo;potential&rsquo;, &lsquo;could&rsquo; and &lsquo;perhaps&rsquo; when it comes to discussing Solana&rdquo;. Since then, it has cratered another 70% in price, with the market seeming to all but give up on Solana&rsquo;s hope of achieving relevance.</p>
<p>The rise of Layer 2s also threatens the core premise of Solana, attacking its core use case. Layer 2s work, which is a simple statement that Solana simply cannot argue for itself right now.</p>
<h2><strong>Sam Bankman-Fried</strong></h2>
<p>Sigh. It has been tough over the last month to talk about anything crypto-related and not mention the golden-knight-turned-arch-villain that is Sam Bankman-Fried. But unfortunately, his demise has had dire consequences for Solana.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The disgraced founder of FTX was a staunch early backer of Solana, with the token even showing up on the much-publicised balance sheet of FTX as it desperately sought investors at the last minute. In fact, Bankman-Fried was Solana&rsquo;s biggest champion.&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I'll buy as much SOL has you have, right now, at $3.</p>
<p>Sell me all you want.</p>
<p>Then go fuck off.</p>
<p>&mdash; SBF (@SBF_FTX) <a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX/status/1347964322459262977?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 9, 2021</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Critics now argue that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/">SOL&rsquo;s</a> vertical rise during the pandemic was partially caused by Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s interventions. The distribution of SOL tokens was also notorious for being VC-heavy, meaning whale wallets were likely to have been able to influence its price significantly more than other cryptos.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the near two months since <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/">FTX&rsquo;s implosion</a>, Solana has struggled significantly more than other cryptos.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors are fearful that some of Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s support of SOL came via fraudulent activity, given the revelations around what happened behind closed doors at FTX. Caroline Ellison, Alameda CEO and close confidant of Bankman-Fried, has stated to the SEC that Bankman-Fired deliberately manipulated the FTT token. In this context, what is to say that he did not do the same for SOL?</p>
<p>Regardless, the mere association with the fraudster has been enough to dent Solana&rsquo;s prospects.&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Projects and capital are leaving Solana</strong></h2>
<p>Looking at DeFi, the total value locked (TVL) on the Solana blockchain is now $217 million, compared to over $10 billion in late 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Perhaps even more concerning is the migration of projects from Solana to rival blockchains. Prominent NFT collections DeGods and y00ts announced last week that they are migrating to Ethereum and Polygon respectively, a hammer blow to the Solana faithful.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;There&rsquo;s an argument to be made that (DeGods) has capped out on Solana,&rdquo; DeGods project leader and y00ts creator, Rohun Vora, said&nbsp;in a Twitter Spaces. &ldquo;It&rsquo;s hard to accept, but it&rsquo;s been tough to grow at the rate we want to grow. If Ethereum is where we have to go to keep growing, it&rsquo;s what we have to do.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The slide of Solana has been so stark that even its supposed biggest rival, Ethereum creator Vitalik Buterin, waded in to say some kind words. It speaks volumes about SOL&rsquo;s fall, as it is hard to even call it a rival of Ethereum any longer, given it is now not even in the top 10 of blockchains in terms of TVL.&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Some smart people tell me there is an earnest smart developer community in Solana, and now that the awful opportunistic money people have been washed out, the chain has a bright future.</p>
<p>Hard for me to tell from outside, but I hope the community gets its fair chance to thrive&#129470;&#129470;</p>
<p>&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1608591727316684804?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 29, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2><strong>Can it recover?</strong></h2>
<p>The question now is whether all these problems are terminal. Can SOL bounce back? Well, the issue here is two-fold. As Vitalik states, &ldquo;the awful opportunistic money people have been washed out&rdquo;. This, while damaging SOL significantly as previously discussed, does point towards a short-term problem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, there are myriad issues which predate the Bankman-Fried saga and still remain problems. Solana&rsquo;s market-leading TPS and cheap fees are great, but they come with a trade-off against security and stability, something users have felt keenly over the last year with the much-publicised issues.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Personally, I think Solana has a very difficult road ahead. For the entire altcoin space, the tide has gone out and it is now evident how much these projects were valued based on zero interest rates and the FOMO frenzy of the pandemic. With inflation still high, a tenuous geopolitical climate and many more bearish variables and uncertainty, the macro climate won&rsquo;t change anytime soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This makes any altcoin a risky bet. But for Solana in particular, which is fighting an additional battle of some of its biggest projects abandoning it, its most famous backer being a fraud and possibly manipulating its price, and a wave of negative sentiment, things are particularly murky.&nbsp;</p>
<p>I hope the developers keep at it and the underlying potential does eventually get delivered upon. But in this climate, the catalysts for a price rise back to where it was simply are simply not present right now.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/">Is Solana dead? Top projects flee the blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-solana-dead-top-projects-flee-the-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
