<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 09:13:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Starknet 0.12.0 Upgrade For Ethereum Scaling: Better UX And Lower Transaction Costs</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199386-starknet-0-12-0-upgrade-better-ux-lower-costs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Thana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 09:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Starknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Starknet 0.12.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[StarkNet&#039;s developer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Starknet announces significant upgrades prioritizing performance and UX, including faster transactions and lower costs, attracting more developers to Ethereum.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Starknet has recently announced significant upgrades to its network prioritizing performance and user experience based on ecosystem feedback.</em></li>



<li><em>These upgrades include significant throughput and latency enhancements, failed transaction inclusion in blocks, data cost reductions, and a fee market to address potential congestion issues.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Starknet announces significant upgrades prioritizing performance and UX, including faster transactions and lower costs, attracting more developers to Ethereum.</strong></h5>



<p>Starknet, a Layer 2 scaling solution for Ethereum, has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/Starknet/status/1675052386862399489" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://twitter.com/Starknet/status/1675052386862399489" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced </a>several significant upgrades to its network, as shown in the picture below. The roadmap now prioritizes performance and user experience (UX), in response to feedback from the ecosystem, with a primary goal of improving network performance to support anticipated growth in users and developers.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-1024x576.png" alt="Starknet 0.12.0 Upgrade For Ethereum Scaling: Better UX And Lower Transaction Costs" class="wp-image-199390" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-19.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Starknet 0.12.0 Upgrade For Ethereum Scaling: Better UX And Lower Transaction Costs 1"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Starknet v0.12.0, which has been in the integration phase for some time, will move to the public testnet next week. This version will offer significant throughput and latency enhancements, thanks to six months of work on Rust-ifying the Starknet stack, which has dramatically reduced block execution time and increased throughput.</p>



<p>Version 0.12.1 will include a crucial update that failed transactions will be included in the block, fixing UX issues and protecting the sequencer from spam, ultimately providing a more seamless user interaction.</p>



<p>As for v0.13.0, it will drastically cut transaction costs by targeting L1 (Ethereum) data cost, which represents 95% of current transaction costs. Ethereum&#8217;s EIP-4844 and its Volition (off-chain data availability) will significantly reduce data costs.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="1024" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18.png" alt="Starknet 0.12.0 Upgrade For Ethereum Scaling: Better UX And Lower Transaction Costs" class="wp-image-199387" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18-300x300.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18-150x150.png 150w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18-768x768.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18-75x75.png 75w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18-350x350.png 350w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-18-750x750.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Starknet 0.12.0 Upgrade For Ethereum Scaling: Better UX And Lower Transaction Costs 2"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Starknet v0.14.0 will introduce a fee market to address potential congestion issues, allowing efficient allocation of the network&#8217;s limited resources.</p>



<p>In v0.15.0, the platform will transition to constant, shorter block intervals by decoupling the 1:1 relationship between a Starknet block and its proof, attesting to the integrity of one or more blocks, fixing block intervals, and enhancing UX.</p>



<p>The combination of future-proof functionality and best-in-class performance and UX improvements are expected to continue attracting developers and dApps to Starknet. With these new upgrades, users can expect faster and more efficient transactions and a better user experience. Starknet is undoubtedly one of the most promising Layer 2 scaling solutions for Ethereum, and these upgrades only add to its appeal.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Thana</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ban-sao-cua-Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-84-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking?</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199377-asymetrix-protocol-refreshing-eth-liquid-staking/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto 101]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asymetrix Protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Asymetrix protocol allows holders of a small amount of ETH to participate in the exciting world of LSDfi with high margins]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Asymetrix Protocol is focused on Ethereum as the underlying asset because it is a top asset that natively generates yield. Asymetrix offers them the opportunity to centrally distribute the income of all bettors to a few lucky ones through a fair and transparent mechanism so that they can reap outstanding profits. In contrast, those who bet Other bettors keep their capital and don&#8217;t get any money.</strong></h5>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Asymetrix Protocol?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="577" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-1024x577.png" alt="How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking?" class="wp-image-199380" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-1024x577.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-768x433.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-1536x866.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-2048x1155.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-750x423.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-16-1140x643.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking? 3"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Asymetrix is a decentralized, non-custodial protocol for the asymmetric distribution of profits generated from staking.</p>



<p>Asymetrix focuses on Ethereum as the underlying asset, as it is the leading asset that generates profits from staking. In creating the Asymetrix protocol, different <a href="https://coincu.com/191618-lsdfi-top-6-potential-projects/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">liquidity staking derivatives (LSDs)</a> offered by different liquidity staking providers were evaluated.</p>



<p>Currently, liquidity staking providers offer two types of LSD: c-Token (rewards are reflected in token prices, such as rETH, cbETH, and others) and a-Token (rebase, more generated rewards for more tokens, balance updates every 24 hours such as stETH).</p>



<p>stETH was chosen as the main asset because of its transparency and product-market fit. The stETH token is currently the most dominant token in liquidity staking protocols, with a market capitalization of over $5 billion.</p>



<p>With a unique staking mode, the platform allows its users to earn up to 999% APR in stETH. While some users may get a 0% staking bonus, the winners will receive an impressive 500% return on their investment.</p>



<p>The goal is to create an analog of Premium Bonds in crypto with a large number of winners. Asymetrix is going to distribute staking rewards in a way that the basic average profitability for all users does not decrease significantly (e.g., 3% APR instead of 5% for ETH staking) while still offering the chance for super-large rewards (up to) 1 million USD equivalent).</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How does the Asymetrix Protocol work?</h2>



<p>The first step involves users depositing their stETH tokens into the Asymetrix protocol. On deposit, the protocol generates 1:1 Pool Sharing Tokens (PSTs) for the sent stETH and sends them to the user&#8217;s wallet. These PST tokens reflect the user&#8217;s share in the protocol and are required for withdrawals. Please note that the current version of the Asymetrix protocol has a minimum deposit of 0.1 stETH.</p>



<p>In the second step, ETH staking rewards are accumulated within the protocol, with the balance of stETH growing at the current Lido Annual Percentage (APR) rate and updating every 24 hours.</p>



<p>The third step involves distributing profits to users, with a random draw taking place every 604800 seconds (approximately once a week, with parameters adjusted at the discretion of the DAO). Winners are randomly selected with the help of Chainlink VFR and their exact win rate dynamically changes in real time. The user&#8217;s initial deposit remains in the protocol for the next withdrawal by default, so there is no need to re-enter it for each withdrawal manually.</p>



<p>In the fourth step, winners will automatically receive their reward in the form of PST, which is equivalent to the amount of stETH won. The user&#8217;s balance is increased, automatically increasing the chances of winning in future draws. Therefore, it is unnecessary to claim the reward every time as it is done automatically.</p>



<p>Finally, in the fifth step, the user can withdraw his initial deposit at any time. The Asymetrix protocol will burn their existing PST tokens for stETH tokens at a 1:1 ratio. Asymetrix is a non-custodial protocol, which means users have full control over their funds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Why the Asymetrix Protocol adds excitement to ETH staking</h2>



<p>ETH staking may be exciting for large stakers, but it may not be the same for smaller ones. For individual investors with limited funds, the annual rate of return brought by the ETH commitment is usually only around 5%, which makes it difficult to stimulate their investment interest. They often dive into the cryptocurrency market in search of higher profit margins. Besides, the betting process is also considered by users to be complicated but tedious. Therefore, the Asymetrix Protocol sought to overcome these shortcomings.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-1024x576.png" alt="How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking?" class="wp-image-199379" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-2048x1152.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-15-1140x641.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking? 4"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<ul>
<li>Users deposit staking ETH (stETH) into a common pool powered by the smart contract;</li>



<li>The general team makes a profit every 24 hours;</li>



<li>The profits generated from this pool are distributed periodically (currently once a week) according to the protocol among the participants of the pool in a random and asymmetric manner;</li>



<li>In any event, users keep their initial deposit and are exposed to an increased ETH price, fostering saving behaviour;</li>



<li>All users receive rewards in ASX tokens as an initial distribution according to their stake in the protocol&#8217;s emissions schedule and TVL. See more details in ASX token distribution;</li>



<li>Users always have access to their deposits and can withdraw them at any time.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Governance model</h2>



<p>Asymetrix Protocol was a DAO with the ultimate goal of creating a fully decentralized protocol owned, controlled, and designed by the community.</p>



<p>A user&#8217;s value in the DAO, represented by an ASX token, gives them weight in the governance vote. These tokens will be distributed among users and protocol participants.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Tokenomics</h2>



<p>The protocol uses the AXS token as the governance token. By holding AXS tokens, users can participate in the governance process, where they can recommend and vote on various parameters and strategies affecting the operation and performance of the protocol.</p>



<p>Asymetrix has developed a unique tokenomics model around cultivating thrifty behavior and providing equal earning opportunities for all users. The $ASX governance token, based on the ERC-20 standard, has a total supply of 100 million.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="436" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17-1024x436.png" alt="How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking?" class="wp-image-199381" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17-1024x436.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17-300x128.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17-768x327.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17-750x319.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17-1140x485.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-17.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="How Is Asymetrix Protocol Refreshing The World Of ETH Liquid Staking? 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Token Allocation:</p>



<ul>
<li>50% of the tokens are allocated to the Community, with 40 million having a 12-month cliff followed by linear vesting over 48 months, and 10 million tokens available initially;</li>



<li>25% of the tokens are allocated to the Team and Founders with a 12-month cliff and 48-month vesting period;</li>



<li>25% are allocated to investors with a 12-month cliff and 48-month vesting period.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>The Asymetrix protocol allows holders of a small amount of ETH to participate in the exciting world of LSDfi, where they can enjoy high returns and randomness through asymmetric reward distribution. The protocol is also easy to use, as users simply deposit stETH into the smart contract and wait for weekly withdrawals.</p>



<p>The Asymetrix protocol does exactly what its name suggests. It distributes bet profits asymmetrically. In other words, it randomly allocates additional bonuses as you bet. The protocol tries to attract as many people staking ETH. In return, you can get a great reward. In return, you can get a great reward. That&#8217;s why, now add Asymetrix to the mix. You can earn interest on your stETH and can withdraw at any time.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of&nbsp;<a href="https://coincu.com/">news</a>&nbsp;:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-38-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199362-token-unlocks-event-in-july/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 06:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AXS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dYdX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IMX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[July]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token Unlocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Some upcoming unlocking of some tokens could cause price fluctuations. Let's find out with Coincu about the major token unlocks that will take place in July.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The past June has been quite a smooth journey for the crypto market as Bitcoin has regained its important $30,000 mark. However, altcoins do not seem to show signs of a strong recovery like in April. Besides, some upcoming unlocking of some tokens could cause price fluctuations. Let&#8217;s find out with Coincu about the major token unlocks that will take place in July.</strong></h5>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">DYDX</h2>



<p>DYDX is still hanging onto its gains from the June lows. This suggests that you are likely to see more gains, particularly if you can increase investor confidence. 6,520,128 tokens will be unlocked in July corresponding to $13,170,659 and 0.652% of total supply.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-1024x419.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="419" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-1024x419.png" alt="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July" class="wp-image-199365" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-1024x419.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-300x123.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-768x314.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-1536x629.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-750x307.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30-1140x467.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.35.30.png 1842w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July 6"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">APT</h2>



<p>APT&#8217;s risk gauge rank indicates that it is now a low-risk investment. Risk-averse traders will find the indicator most helpful for avoiding dangerous trades. 4,543,478.03 tokens will be unlocked in July corresponding to $32,576,737 and 0.454% of total supply.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="416" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-1024x416.png" alt="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July" class="wp-image-199366" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-1024x416.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-300x122.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-768x312.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-1536x623.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-750x304.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10-1140x463.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.37.10.png 1838w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July 7"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">IMX</h2>



<p>18,075,990.61 tokens will be unlocked in July corresponding to $13,337,767 and 0.904% of total supply.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="413" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-1024x413.png" alt="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July" class="wp-image-199367" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-1024x413.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-300x121.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-768x310.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-1536x619.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-750x302.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26-1140x460.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.40.26.png 1830w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July 8"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">APE</h2>



<p>Notwithstanding the uncertainty that APE investors are experiencing, there is newfound optimism for them as a new hybrid token offers incredible potential for big returns. This has piqued the interest of APE investors, who are now reducing their losses and shifting their focus to the hybrid meme currency, which is expected to provide a 20,000% Return for investors by the end of 2023. This large outflow of APE whales is a big contributor to the APE coin&#8217;s continuous price decline. 15,601,326 tokens will be unlocked in July corresponding to $34,322,917 and 1.56% of total supply.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="435" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-1024x435.png" alt="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July" class="wp-image-199368" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-1024x435.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-300x127.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-768x326.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-1536x652.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-750x318.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30-1140x484.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.42.30.png 1828w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July 9"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">AXS</h2>



<p>Axie Infinity (AXS) has benefited from the revived metaverse interest generated by Apple&#8217;s Vision Pro Augmented Reality (AR) headset introduction in recent weeks. Nonetheless, the positive impetus seems to be fading. 3,425,625 tokens will be unlocked in July corresponding to $20,793,544 and 1,269% of total supply.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-1024x421.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="421" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-1024x421.png" alt="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July" class="wp-image-199369" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-1024x421.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-300x123.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-768x316.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-1536x631.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-750x308.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15-1140x468.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.46.15.png 1840w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July 10"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">OP</h2>



<p>Optimism (OP) price is recovering faster than other cryptocurrencies and may outperform the rest of the group. This month could be a busy one for this token. 24,159,191.04 tokens will be unlocked in July for $31,890,132 and 0.562% of total supply respectively.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-1024x416.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="416" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-1024x416.png" alt="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July" class="wp-image-199370" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-1024x416.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-300x122.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-768x312.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-1536x624.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-750x305.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06-1140x463.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-01-at-13.49.06.png 1842w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Token Unlocks Event Worth Noting In July 11"></a></figure></div>


<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to<a href="https://coincu.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> keep track of news</a>:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Final-Thumb-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Exchange Had Leaked OTC Transaction Info, User Data From 2017 To 2021: Report</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199356-huobi-exchange-had-leaked-otc-transaction-info/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Thana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 05:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Huobi Tech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi Global]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199356</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Huobi exchange suffers massive data leak, including OTC transactions, user/VIP info, and tech data. Huobi responded, but the incident raises data security concerns.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Huobi exchange experienced a large data leak, including OTC transaction info, user and VIP data, and technical infrastructure data.</em></li>



<li><em>The leak was caused by the irregular operation of personnel in the S3 barrel of the Japanese station&#8217;s test environment, and relevant user info was isolated in Oct 2022.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Huobi exchange suffers massive data leak, including OTC transactions, user/VIP info, and tech data. Huobi responded, but the incident raises data security concerns.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-14.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="701" height="835" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-14.png" alt="Huobi Exchange Had Leaked OTC Transaction Info, User Data From 2017 To 2021: Report" class="wp-image-199359" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-14.png 701w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-14-252x300.png 252w" sizes="(max-width: 701px) 100vw, 701px" title="Huobi Exchange Had Leaked OTC Transaction Info, User Data From 2017 To 2021: Report 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Wu reported that Huobi exchange has suffered a massive data leak, according to <a href="https://phillips.technology/blog/huobi-crypto-aws/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://phillips.technology/blog/huobi-crypto-aws/" rel="noreferrer noopener">Aaron Phillips</a>, a white hat security researcher. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Breaking: White hat Aaron Phillips disclosed that the Huobi exchange had leaked nearly all OTC transaction information from 2017 to 2021 on a large scale in 2021; some user information, VIP user information and its own technical infrastructure. Read more: <a href="https://t.co/QJx45LHLhg" target="_blank">https://t.co/QJx45LHLhg</a> <a href="https://t.co/ln6pzpbjin" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/ln6pzpbjin</a></p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1675005132180955136?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">July 1, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The leaked data includes OTC transaction information, user information, VIP user information, and technical infrastructure data. The leaked data is said to have occurred between 2017 and 2021.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-13.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="990" height="310" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-13.png" alt="Huobi Exchange Had Leaked OTC Transaction Info, User Data From 2017 To 2021: Report" class="wp-image-199358" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-13.png 990w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-13-300x94.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-13-768x240.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-13-750x235.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 990px) 100vw, 990px" title="Huobi Exchange Had Leaked OTC Transaction Info, User Data From 2017 To 2021: Report 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Huobi Leaks ‘Whale Reports’ on Wealthy Users, Source: <a href="https://phillips.technology/blog/huobi-crypto-aws/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://phillips.technology/blog/huobi-crypto-aws/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Aaron</a></figcaption></figure></div>


<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">An attacker exploiting Huobi’s mistakes would have had the opportunity to carry out the largest crypto theft in history. The company has previously reported handling over a billion dollars a day in trading volume. If Huobi hadn’t taken action, this breach could have been leveraged to steal user accounts and assets. The company deleted the compromised account and their users are no longer at risk.</p>
<cite>Aaron Phillips wrote in a blog <a href="https://phillips.technology/blog/huobi-crypto-aws/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://phillips.technology/blog/huobi-crypto-aws/" rel="noreferrer noopener">post</a></cite></blockquote>



<p>Huobi has confirmed the incident and stated that it was caused by the irregular operation of relevant personnel in the S3 barrel of the test environment of the Japanese station. The relevant user information was completely isolated on October 8, 2022.</p>



<p>After the incident was discovered by the white hat team, Huobi&#8217;s security team took action on June 21, 2023, and immediately closed the relevant file access permissions. The vulnerability has been fixed, and all relevant user information has been deleted. Huobi has thanked the White Hat team for their contributions to its security.</p>



<p>Huobi’s updated response stated that the OTC data mentioned in the article is not real transaction data, but test data. The user information leak only involves 4,000 users. The log shows that only the white hat team has downloaded the data, and the team has also stated that they have deleted it. Therefore, no actual leakage has occurred.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Thana</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ban-sao-cua-Ban-sao-cua-Noi-dung-doan-van-ban-cua-ban-83-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199344-coinbase-support-valkyrie-bitwise-btc-spot-etfs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitwise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Galaxy Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Valkyrie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VanEck Bitcoin Trust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199344</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Coinbase will also supply services for Valkyrie and Bitwise's bitcoin spot ETF, according to individuals familiar with the situation.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Coinbase partners with Valkyrie, Bitwise, and others for Bitcoin ETF services, potentially boosting revenue amid low crypto-exchange volumes.</em></li>



<li><em>The exchange&#8217;s role as custody and market monitoring provider addresses fraud concerns, crucial for SEC approval of Bitcoin ETFs.</em></li>



<li><em>Fidelity and other firms include Coinbase in revised filings, highlighting the significance of monitoring mechanisms for SEC approval and increasing token values.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-30/fidelity-leads-flurry-of-bitcoin-btc-etf-refilings-to-answer-sec" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bloomberg</a></em>, Coinbase will also supply services for Valkyrie and Bitwise&#8217;s bitcoin spot ETF, according to individuals familiar with the situation.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="682" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg-1024x682.jpeg" alt="Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report" class="wp-image-199351" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg-1024x682.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg-750x500.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg-1140x760.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1_cCe3FwIHV9YzyALH0znmKg.jpeg 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report 14"></a></figure></div>


<p>Coinbase&#8217;s partnership with the planned ETFs might result in an increase in income at a time when the crypto-exchange sector is experiencing low volumes. Coinbase&#8217;s revenue last year was less than half of what it was in 2021, when the sector was booming. The announcement also comes amid Coinbase&#8217;s legal fight with the SEC, which accused the company of operating an unlawful exchange.</p>



<p>Coinbase will become the custody-sharing agreement partner of Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF, VanEck Bitcoin Trust, WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust, Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust, and ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF, according to <a href="https://coincu.com/199318-cboe-updates-bitcoin-etf-spot-profile-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recent reporting</a>.</p>



<p>Fidelity Investments led a flurry of corporations that submitted a second batch of applications for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund on Friday afternoon to add additional information after the US Securities and Exchange Commission suggested that the earlier files were inadequate.</p>



<p>The companies are among eight that are attempting to establish the first generation of US spot Bitcoin ETFs. In mid-June, BlackRock Inc. surprised the market by registering for such a fund.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="682" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12-1024x682.png" alt="Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report" class="wp-image-199353" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12-1024x682.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12-300x200.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12-768x511.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12-750x499.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12-1140x759.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-12.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report 15"></a></figure></div>


<p>All five that refiled on Friday said that Coinbase Global Inc. would offer market monitoring in support of their funds, which was not included in prior revisions.</p>



<p>Crypto market monitoring might be crucial in obtaining SEC clearance for a spot Bitcoin ETF. The monitoring may significantly minimize fraud and market manipulation, which have been the primary reasons the SEC has rejected about 30 spot Bitcoin ETF applications so far.</p>



<p>According to a source familiar with the subject who was not allowed to talk publicly about the arrangements, Coinbase is also in line to supply different services for the other planned fund issuers. These firms, in addition to BlackRock, include Valkyrie and Bitwise. In a recent filing, 21Shares said that Coinbase would also offer custody services.</p>



<p>The crypto community is ecstatic at the possibility of cryptocurrency possibly becoming more accessible to average investors, and the surge of filings has boosted token values.</p>



<p>Bitcoin reclaimed the $30,000 mark in June and is trading at nearly its highest levels in almost a year. The coin is now worth roughly $30,400.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-1024x623.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="623" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-1024x623.png" alt="Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report" class="wp-image-199350" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-1024x623.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-300x183.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-768x467.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-1536x935.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-2048x1246.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-750x456.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-11-1140x694.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Coinbase To Support Valkyrie And Bitwise Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Report 16"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">BTC price chart. <em>Source: TradingView</em></figcaption></figure></div>


<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to<a href="https://coincu.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> keep track of news</a>:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Final-Thumb-5-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Logan Paul Hasn&#8217;t Refunded $1.8M To CryptoZoo Scam NFT Buyers After 6 Months</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199341-logan-paul-hasnt-refunded-cryptozoo-buyers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 03:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CryptoZoo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logan paul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199341</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The publisher of the CryptoZoo NFT scam project, Logan Paul, has yet to fulfill his promise to return $1.8 million to investors over the past six months.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Logan Paul still hasn&#8217;t refunded the buyer of his scam NFT project after six months of promises.</em></li>



<li><em>In January, Logan Paul pledged to burn ZOO tokens and refund $1.8 million to CryptoZoo NFT buyers.</em></li>



<li><em>In 2021, CryptoZoo NFT was released with ZOO token, but this game has yet to come to fruition.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The publisher of the CryptoZoo NFT scam project, <a href="https://coincu.com/158092-logan-paul-sue-coffeezilla-cryptozoo-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Logan Paul</a>, has yet to fulfill his promise to return $1.8 million to investors over the past six months.</strong></h5>



<p>YouTuber Logan Paul faced intense backlash six months ago for allegedly scamming his audience with an NFT gaming project called CryptoZoo, which was proposed in 2021. Paul and his crew were given ZOO tokens and sold NFT, but the game was never completed.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10-1024x576.png" alt="Logan Paul Hasn&#039;t Refunded $1.8M To CryptoZoo Scam NFT Buyers After 6 Months" class="wp-image-199347" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-10.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Logan Paul Hasn&#039;t Refunded $1.8M To CryptoZoo Scam NFT Buyers After 6 Months 17"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Paul posted a video on 13 outlining his &#8220;three-step plan&#8221; right after receiving criticism to set things from YouTube investigators in January like Stephen &#8220;Coffeezilla&#8221; Findeisen became true. A month later, a class-action complaint was filed against the influencer, alleging that Paul and his crew had duped and taken advantage of CryptoZoo purchasers.</p>



<p>In Coffeezilla&#8217;s latest video, he shared a screenshot of an email communication with Paul&#8217;s attorney, Jeffrey Neiman of the law firm MNR, which seems to suggest that a specific plan has yet to be established. No refunds have yet been made to the affected investors.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<div class="jeg_video_container jeg_video_content"><iframe loading="lazy" title="Logan Paul&#039;s Scam Isn&#039;t Over" width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uYYiypp6WaY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
</div></figure>



<p>&#8220;According to the victims, there [have] been zero payments. There&#8217;s no excuse for this. Logan made a public statement about this, took credit for it, and has ghosted the victims,&#8221; Coffeezilla said.</p>



<p>As alleged by Coffeezilla, Paul once promised to deposit all of their ZOO tokens into a burning wallet so that the tokens would be effectively destroyed. After that, they can only profit from their ZOO tokens. However, upon examining the official ZOO contract detailed in the token&#8217;s white paper, there is no clear evidence that Paul or Levin burned any of their ZOOs. According to BSC Scan data, no significant ZOO token burns from one or two wallet addresses have occurred since January 2023.</p>



<p>At the time of writing, Paul has yet to post a response on YouTube or Twitter.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of&nbsp;<a href="https://coincu.com/">news</a>&nbsp;:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-37-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Largest Crypto ATM Provider Bitcoin Depot Lists On Nasdaq On July 3</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199331-bitcoin-depot-lists-on-nasdaq-on-july-3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lists]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199331</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot, the largest crypto ATM companies in the US, announced the completion of a merger agreement and allowed listing on NASDAQ on July 3.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Bitcoin Depot, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency ATM operator and distribution company, announced its listing on NASDAQ on July 3.</em></li>



<li><em>On June 30, fintech company GSR II Meteora Acquisition Corporation successfully merged into Bitcoin Depot.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="https://coincu.com/148382-bitcoin-depot-spac-agreement/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin Depot</a>, one of the largest crypto ATM companies in the United States, <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/30/2698079/0/en/Bitcoin-Depot-and-GSR-II-Meteora-Acquisition-Corp-Announce-Closing-of-Business-Combination.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced </a>the completion of a merger agreement and allowed public listing on NASDAQ on July 3.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-1024x512.png" alt="Largest Crypto ATM Provider Bitcoin Depot Lists On Nasdaq On July 3" class="wp-image-199337" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-8.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Largest Crypto ATM Provider Bitcoin Depot Lists On Nasdaq On July 3 18"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>In a June 30 announcement, fintech firm GSR II Meteora Acquisition Corporation said its shareholders approved the merger so that the company would act as a special-purpose acquisition company for Bitcoin Depot. The deal, first reported in August 2022, is worth $885 million.</p>



<p>The combined company will be renamed Bitcoin Depot Inc. and will be led by the current management team. Bitcoin Depot common stock and public warrants are scheduled to begin trading on July 3, 2023 on Nasdaq under the tickers &#8220;BTM&#8221; and &#8220;BTMWW,&#8221; respectively.</p>



<p>Bitcoin Depot was founded in 2016 with a mission to connect those who prefer to use cash with the broader digital financial system. The company provides users with simple, efficient, and intuitive means to convert some money into Bitcoin, which users can deploy in the payments, spending, and investing space. The company has the largest market share in North America, with approximately 6,440 kiosks as of March 31, 2023.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-7.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="567" height="425" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-7.png" alt="Largest Crypto ATM Provider Bitcoin Depot Lists On Nasdaq On July 3" class="wp-image-199336" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-7.png 567w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-7-300x225.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 567px) 100vw, 567px" title="Largest Crypto ATM Provider Bitcoin Depot Lists On Nasdaq On July 3 19"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Bitcoin Depot will install thousands of crypto ATMs at Circle K-branded convenience stores in the US and Canada amid the cryptocurrency market boom.</p>



<p>But this year, the number of users of these machines has decreased significantly as the virtual currency market enters a &#8220;hibernation&#8221; period, with the average transaction value at each ATM globally reducing by about 75% compared to the previous year, early 2021.</p>



<p>In May, the American provider of Bitcoin ATMs announced that it would cease operations in Connecticut after the state&#8217;s Department of Banking said the company did not have the appropriate license.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of&nbsp;<a href="https://coincu.com/">news</a>&nbsp;:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-36-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Franklin Templeton As Co-Chair Of CFTC&#8217;s New Digital Asset Subcommittee</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199325-franklin-templeton-co-chair-cftc-digital-asset/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Asset Subcommittee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199325</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Caroline Butler, global head of digital assets at BNY Mellon, will co-chair the digital asset markets subcommittee alongside Franklin Templeton's Sandy Kaul.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>The CFTC has appointed new positions in the subcommittee focusing on digital assets.</em></li>



<li><em>Caroline Butler, global head of digital assets at BNY Mellon, will co-chair the digital asset markets subcommittee alongside Franklin Templeton&#8217;s Sandy Kaul.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to The Block Caroline Butler, global head of digital assets at BNY Mellon, and President Sandy Kaul of<a href="https://coincu.com/186746-franklin-templeton-takes-step-crypto-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> Franklin Templeton</a> are co-chairs of the CFTC Subcommittee on Digital Assets.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-4.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="315" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-4.png" alt="Franklin Templeton As Co-Chair Of CFTC&#039;s New Digital Asset Subcommittee" class="wp-image-199327" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-4.png 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-4-300x158.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="Franklin Templeton As Co-Chair Of CFTC&#039;s New Digital Asset Subcommittee 20"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The U.S. Commodity and Derivatives Regulatory Authority has added new crypto industry market participants to a committee focused on digital assets, according to an agency<a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8740-23" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> announcement </a>Friday.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;Franklin Templeton has been a passionate proponent of exploring and delivering opportunities in the digital asset markets, and we so appreciate the CFTC&#8217;s leadership in this arena and are excited to take on a leadership role and work with other industry participants towards the goal of shaping a 21st century financial ecosystem,&#8221;</p>
<cite>Sandy Kaul said in the statement.</cite></blockquote>



<p>Franklin Templeton is one of the most essential wealth managers in the world, with over $1.3 trillion under management. Franklin Templeton Senior Vice President Sandy Kaul emphasized that most regulators worldwide, including the CFTC, view cryptocurrencies differently than the SEC. However, she expects the SEC to develop laws and regulations that support cryptocurrencies soon.</p>



<p>Franklin Templeton views the crypto ecosystem as a collection of digital nations. Each of these blockchain ecosystems is its own country.</p>



<p>Other members include executives from crypto companies like Coinfund, Crypto.com, and Uniswap and representatives from traditional Wall Street financial institutions like BlackRock, DRW, and Goldman Sachs.</p>



<p>GMAC was established to help the regulator analyze issues related to the US capital markets, and make policy recommendations associated with financial instruments such as derivatives and companies that support their trading support such as exchanges and brokers.</p>



<p>New members have been added to the CFTC&#8217;s Global Market Structure group&#8217;s subcommittee on digital assets, according to Commissioner Caroline Pham. There are now 128 people involved in its GMAC group and relevant subcommittees.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of&nbsp;<a href="https://coincu.com/">news</a>&nbsp;:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-35-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cboe Immediately Updates Bitcoin ETF Spot Profile After SEC Complaint</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199318-cboe-updates-bitcoin-etf-spot-profile-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF spot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cboe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cboe Global Markets Inc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199318</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cboe updated the filings for the spot bitcoin ETF on its website shortly after the SEC said that the spot bitcoin ETF filings were not clear and comprehensive.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Cboe re-filtered five spot bitcoin ETF proposals on Friday following reports that the SEC had requested more information.</em></li>



<li><em>Cboe said it expected to sign a custody-sharing agreement with Coinbase.</em></li>



<li><em>Previously, the Exchange Operator, on behalf of five issuers of a spot bitcoin ETF filed it back with the SEC on Friday.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Exchange operator Cboe Global Markets Inc. <a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-028-Amendment-No-2.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">updated</a> the filings for the spot bitcoin ETF on its website shortly after the SEC said that the spot bitcoin ETF filings were not clear and comprehensive.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="660" height="440" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2.png" alt="Cboe Immediately Updates Bitcoin ETF Spot Profile After SEC Complaint" class="wp-image-199320" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2.png 660w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-2-300x200.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 660px) 100vw, 660px" title="Cboe Immediately Updates Bitcoin ETF Spot Profile After SEC Complaint 21"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Cboe, on behalf of five issuers of a spot bitcoin ETF filed with the SEC on Friday. Updated filings have been submitted to the Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF, VanEck Bitcoin Trust, WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust, and Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust.</p>



<p>The refreshed filing is intended to address concerns raised by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). According to these people, the agency <a href="https://coincu.com/199277-sec-says-bitcoin-etf-inadequate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">notified </a>exchanges Nasdaq and Cboe Global Markets, which had submitted applications for asset managers such as BlackRock and Fidelity Investments, that the files needed to be more precise and thorough.</p>



<p>One key issue is that the exchanges did not name the cryptocurrency trading platforms they plan to enter into custody-sharing arrangements to help detect fraud in the underlying Bitcoin market.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-3.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="750" height="375" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-3.png" alt="Cboe Immediately Updates Bitcoin ETF Spot Profile After SEC Complaint" class="wp-image-199321" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-3.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-3-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-3-360x180.png 360w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" title="Cboe Immediately Updates Bitcoin ETF Spot Profile After SEC Complaint 22"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The filings, in the second iteration, named Coinbase as part of a custody-sharing agreement for ETF applications by Wise Origin, WisdomTree, VanEck, and Invesco Galaxy.</p>



<p>The updated document states that the product, The Spot BTC SSA, will show signs of a custody-sharing agreement split between the two. The filing says that setup will allow additional access to data related to spot Bitcoin transactions on Coinbase if the exchange determines it is necessary as part of a monitoring program.</p>



<p>Following the wave of BlackRock is a wide range of traditional and crypto asset managers. In recent days, Fidelity Investments, Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Management, Invesco, WisdomTree, Bitwise Asset Management, and Valkyrie have all revived or revised their applications for spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of&nbsp;<a href="https://coincu.com/">news</a>&nbsp;:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-34-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Is Requested By The IRS For Customer Information From $20,000</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/199312-kraken-requested-irs-for-customer-information/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 01:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Information]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IRS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=199312</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kraken was ordered by a judge on Friday to provide certain user information to the Internal Revenue Service (IRS).]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Kraken has been ordered to provide certain user information to the US Internal Revenue Service (IRS).</em></li>



<li><em>The IRS wants to identify accounts with more than $20,000 in crypto transactions annually between 2016 and 2020.</em></li>



<li><em>The judge said the government had a legitimate purpose to search the documents.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to The Block,<a href="https://coincu.com/195499-20-liquidity-drop-kraken-emerges-as-winner/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> Kraken</a> was ordered by a judge on Friday to provide certain user information to the Internal Revenue Service (IRS).</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="674" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1024x674.png" alt="Kraken Is Requested By The IRS For Customer Information From $20,000" class="wp-image-199314" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1024x674.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-300x197.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-768x505.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-750x493.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Kraken Is Requested By The IRS For Customer Information From $20,000 23"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The IRS wants the exchange to identify accounts with more than $20,000 in crypto transactions annually between 2016 and 2020. Kraken has previously objected to the IRS subpoena partly because its concerns will create a great burden. The exchange called the agency&#8217;s summons an &#8220;irrational treasure hunt,&#8221; arguing that it crossed the line.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;The Government has a legitimate purpose for seeking the materials described in the summon. As discussed above, the summons was issued in connection with an investigation by the IRS to determine the identity and correct federal income tax liability of US persons who conduct transactions in cryptocurrency during the period 2016-2020,&#8221;</p>
<cite>Judge Joseph C. Spero said in the court document.</cite></blockquote>



<p>Kraken will have to disclose information such as name, date of birth, physical address, phone number, and tax identification number.</p>



<p>Friday&#8217;s ruling in favor of the government comes amid a deepening US crackdown on cryptocurrencies. The Securities and Exchange Commission this month filed a lawsuit accusing Coinbase of operating an illegal exchange and alleging that Binance.US mishandled customer funds, misled investors and agencies&#8217; regulatory authorities as well as violations of securities rules.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-1024x576.png" alt="Kraken Is Requested By The IRS For Customer Information From $20,000" class="wp-image-199315" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Kraken Is Requested By The IRS For Customer Information From $20,000 24"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Kraken is a leading cryptocurrency exchange with a daily trading volume of around $650 million globally, according to CoinMarketCap. The company did not immediately respond to an email request for comment on the ruling.</p>



<p>Kraken currently only offers US Forms 1099-MISC, 1099-INT, and 1099-NEC, which are filed with the US Internal Revenue Service (IRS), and a copy will be provided to you (if you qualify). This could change in the coming years as tax reporting laws constantly change.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of&nbsp;<a href="https://coincu.com/">news</a>&nbsp;:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Thumb-2023-Foxy-33-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
