<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 21:41:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>NFT trading volume rose 230% in Q1, Nansen finds</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-trading-volume-rose-230-in-q1-nansen-finds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-trading-volume-rose-230-in-q1-nansen-finds/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NFT trading volume rose 230% in Q1, 2023 with over $4.54B in sales compared to $1.97 billion in Q4, 2022. According to Nansen Data Journalist Martin Lee, the NFT marketplace Blur accounted for most of the volume in the quarter. The number of NFT users also grew significantly during the quarter, although the past few [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-trading-volume-rose-230-in-q1-nansen-finds/">NFT trading volume rose 230% in Q1, Nansen finds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">NFT trading volume rose 230% in Q1, 2023 with over $4.54B in sales compared to $1.97 billion in Q4, 2022.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to Nansen Data Journalist Martin Lee, the NFT marketplace Blur accounted for most of the volume in the quarter.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The number of NFT users also grew significantly during the quarter, although the past few weeks are seeing a decline in volume and user numbers.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">An analysis of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-are-nfts-and-how-do-they-work/">NFT market</a> by Nansen, a leading blockchain analytics firm, has hinted at a resurgence in the sector in the first three months of the year. Data comparing market performance in terms of trading volumes shows sales surged over 230% in Q1, 2023 vs. Q4 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Martin Lee, a Data Journalist at <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Nansen</a>, the significant increase is observable in both <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/eth/">ETH</a> and USD metrics. A new player in the NFT marketplace ecosystem accounted for a large share of the trading volume, the analysis reveals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>T</em><em>he increase has largely been driven by the rise of Blur</em>,&rdquo; Lee noted in an analysis shared with CoinJournal.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">NFT trading volume rose 230% to over $4.54 billion in Q1</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In Q4, 2022, over 1.5 million ETH, or more than $1.97 billion worth of NFTs was transacted. This amounted to NFT sales volume of 9,036,778 during the period. In comparison, the NFT market recorded a significant increase in transacted volume in Q1, 2023 with market volume hitting over 2.83 million ETH, or $4.54 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total transacted in the quarter was 11,498,022 NFTs, with the volume increasing 230% in Q1, 2023 compared to Q4, 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although Q1, 2023 showed significant increase in sales volume compared to Q4, 2022, Nansen data shows there was a lull in April. While $1.7 billion was transacted in March, the next 30 days saw a dip in volume with approximately $1.2 billion generated. The trend is also being observed in May as shown below.</p>
<p><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"></span></span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/09/1683667013793-b525c188-e62f-4ca4-acf7-955b5aa20c93.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="215"><span class="fr-inner">Data shows a decline in NFT volumes in April and May. Source:Nansen</span></p>
<p>There&rsquo;s also a slight decline in the number of users, with data for the past few weeks lower than what was recorded in the past year. Notably though, Q1 saw 13,999,528 in users, compared to 11,233,872 in Q4, 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/09/1683667148972-3aff75c2-526d-4d29-9cc5-d584a21b7c30.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="222"><span class="fr-inner">A visualization of NFT sales and wallets between January,2022 and April, 2023. Source: Nansen</span></span></span>The decline comes amid a surge in interest in meme coins, with the likes of Pepe (PEPE) and Floki Inu (FLOKI) top performers in the last month.</div>
<h2 dir="ltr">OpenSea saw $200 million worth of NFT sales volume in Q4, 2022</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In the last quarter of 2022, the NFT market observed noteworthy sales figures, particularly for OpenSea. The platform accounted for 219,992.50 ETH in volume, equivalent to $272,415,866.4. The total NFT sales across the platform during the quarter was 1,413,780 NFTs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">During this period, other platforms that recorded significant volumes were LooksRare, Mint, CryptoPunks, and X2Y2.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Blur emerges as key NFT marketplace, Q1 volume surpassed OpenSea&rsquo;s</h2>
<p dir="ltr">During the first quarter of 2023, Blur emerged as a prominent player in the NFT market. While OpenSea sales volume was 661,547.79 ETH, or approximately $1.02 billion from 3,727,299 NFTs sold, Blur&rsquo;s volume was nearly three times higher.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Nansen analysis, Blur saw its remarkable growth translate to over 1.8 million ETH, or $2.93 billion worth of NFT sales. The platform accounted for 1,999,688 of the quarterly NFT sales.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blur, launched in October 2022, is now one of the leading NFT marketplaces. The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>-based platform looks to offer traders and collectors a top marketplace that highlights a community-driven ecosystem. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blur&rsquo;s growth in terms of sales volume demonstrates the continued expansion of the NFT market, with traders and collectors keen to explore the best of both established and emerging platforms.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-trading-volume-rose-230-in-q1-nansen-finds/">NFT trading volume rose 230% in Q1, Nansen finds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft joins BNP Paribas, Goldman Sachs and others on new blockchain network</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/microsoft-joins-bnp-paribas-goldman-sachs-and-others-on-new-blockchain-network/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/microsoft-joins-bnp-paribas-goldman-sachs-and-others-on-new-blockchain-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/microsoft-joins-bnp-paribas-goldman-sachs-and-others-on-new-blockchain-network/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The new platform is a privacy-enabled blockchain dubbed the Canton Network. Canton Network allows for interoperable and synchronised transactions in finance, unlocking efficiency and innovation. Microsoft is a supporting partner and joins companies such as BNP Paribas, Deutsche B&#246;rse Group, and Goldman Sachs. Microsoft is among several global tech and finance companies looking to advance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microsoft-joins-bnp-paribas-goldman-sachs-and-others-on-new-blockchain-network/">Microsoft joins BNP Paribas, Goldman Sachs and others on new blockchain network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The new platform is a privacy-enabled blockchain dubbed the Canton Network.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Canton Network allows for interoperable and synchronised transactions in finance, unlocking efficiency and innovation.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Microsoft is a supporting partner and joins companies such as BNP Paribas, Deutsche B&ouml;rse Group, and Goldman Sachs.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/microsoft/">Microsoft</a> is among several global tech and finance companies looking to advance interoperabiloty in the financial markets via a new privacy-enabled <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The institutional-focused blockchain is dubbed the Canton Network and will offer access to a decentralised infrastructure targeted at unlocking the potential of synchronised financial markets, according to details shared in a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230509005497/en/New-Global-Blockchain-Network-of-Networks-for-Financial-Market-Participants-and-Institutional-Assets" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> on Tuesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Canton Network consortium includes crypto platform Digital Asset, investment banking providers BNP Paribas and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/goldman-sachs/">Goldman Sachs</a> and auditing giant Deloitte. Other partners are Cboe Global Markets, Cumberland, Deutsche B&ouml;rse Group, EquiLend, Moody&rsquo;s, and Paxos among others.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Harnessing the power of blockchain technology</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Created as a &lsquo;network of networks&rsquo;, Canton will see previously siloed systems within the financial markets ecosystem interoperate &ndash; with industry players benefiting from aspects such as proper governance, privacy, and permissioning applicable to the highly regulated sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apart from harnessing the power of blockchain, the project will also look to advance integration of Web3 and AI in the financial industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Rashmi Misra, the General Manager AI &amp; Emerging Technologies, Business Development at Microsoft, said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are excited to be a supporting partner of the Canton Network. We look forward to helping the financial community build and scale cloud enabled Web3 applications on Azure while harnessing the power of AI to improve the user experience and drive developer adoption</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Canton Network participants are set to test the interoperability capabilities of the platform starting in July. Users will be able to execute atomic transactions across multiple smart contracts, with rapid cross-chain settlement, privacy and security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Adoption of blockchain technology and digital assets among financial institutions and payments providers has picked up again after a lull that came with the turmoil of the crypto winter and regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recent moves in this direction have been made by companies like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/visa/">Visa</a> and Mastercard.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microsoft-joins-bnp-paribas-goldman-sachs-and-others-on-new-blockchain-network/">Microsoft joins BNP Paribas, Goldman Sachs and others on new blockchain network</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/microsoft-joins-bnp-paribas-goldman-sachs-and-others-on-new-blockchain-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the year of the meme coins will DOGEs growth be eclipsed by TOADS?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiToads (TOADS) is a play to earn full utility meme coin. DigiToads (TOADS) is currently ongoing. 2023 has seen new meme coins like PEPE overtake former meme coin stars like DOGE. Dogecoin (DOGE) became arguably the most famous meme coin buoyed by social media hype over the past few years. Millionaires were created out of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/">In the year of the meme coins will DOGEs growth be eclipsed by TOADS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>DigiToads (TOADS) is a play to earn full utility meme coin.</li>
<li>DigiToads (TOADS) is currently ongoing.</li>
<li>2023 has seen new meme coins like PEPE overtake former meme coin stars like DOGE.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> became arguably the most famous meme coin buoyed by social media hype over the past few years. Millionaires were created out of nowhere, and thousands of other meme coins sprung up to try and capitalize on increased demand for the &ldquo;next big thing&rdquo; in the crypto world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, only some of these meme coins have succeeded. This, combined with wider economic pressures and a general slowdown in the entire crypto market, has led some investors to look elsewhere.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But the meme coin boom isn&rsquo;t over. It&rsquo;s just getting started following the launch of new trending meme crypto projects like&nbsp;<a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl">DigiToads (TOADS)</a>.</p>
<h2>What is DigiToads (TOADS)?</h2>
<p>Savvy investors think that DigiToads (TOADS) is a win-win proposition. Unlike many other meme coin success stories, it&rsquo;s actually got a ton of solid fundamentals built-in to an incredibly innovative ecosystem that&rsquo;s rewarding, fun, and primed for growth. Memecoin hype can only get you so far, but TOADs has both the fun marketing appeal and the long-term profit potential investors have been crying out for.</p>
<p>DigiToads leads the charge as one of the hottest P2E cryptos in the crypto space, thanks to its extremely enjoyable swamp battle arena that lets users train and battle with a range of TOAD companions. The best-placed competitors will receive regular rewards in the form of TOADS tokens, which can then be used to buy food, train, and customize your companions to take them to the next level.</p>
<p>The TOADS ecosystem has been built from the ground up with a community-focused ethos at the core of everything it does. &nbsp;It is currently conducting its presale which provides early investors with long-term gains thanks to heavily discounted prices and sustainable passive income potential thanks to top NFT staking capabilities. You can participate in the <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl">DigiToads presale here</a>.</p>
<p>With prices already soaring during TOADS&rsquo; presale phase, the token price is locked in to go even higher before its official launch thanks to staggered increases. With the increased popularity and number of investors flocking to purchase the new TOADS token, DigiToads could surpass well-known meme coins like Dogecoin (DOGE) and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a>.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin (DOGE) market performance</h2>
<p>Dogecoin hype and price performance over the years have certainly shown what sort of gains are possible in the meme coin world. It also showed other crypto projects how much marketing power a few tweets from famous followers can get you.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However,&nbsp;<u><a href="https://dogecoin.com/">DOGE</a></u> could not solidify those huge gains, and its long-term journey has been slightly less appealing to investors. Analysts have suggested that this comes down to fundamentals: social media hype can only get you so far, and credible investors need credible crypto options.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>While DOGE remains a viable option for your crypto portfolio since it could still surge back to its former highs, experts think that TOADS also has everything needed to become the next meme coin.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/">In the year of the meme coins will DOGEs growth be eclipsed by TOADS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DigiToads (TOADS) stands out as the next big Meme Coin. Could it outperform Pepe (PEPE)?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-stands-out-as-the-next-big-meme-coin-could-it-outperform-pepe-pepe/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-stands-out-as-the-next-big-meme-coin-could-it-outperform-pepe-pepe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-stands-out-as-the-next-big-meme-coin-could-it-outperform-pepe-pepe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiToads (TOADS) is an exciting meme coin project that continues to see huge interest in its presale.&#160; Some of the factors setting it apart from peers include a unique branding and concept, strong community, innovative use cases, and limited supply.&#160; As the meme coin season gathers pace, DigiToads could establish itself as an ecosystem player [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-stands-out-as-the-next-big-meme-coin-could-it-outperform-pepe-pepe/">DigiToads (TOADS) stands out as the next big Meme Coin. Could it outperform Pepe (PEPE)?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">DigiToads (TOADS) is an exciting meme coin project that continues to see huge interest in its presale.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Some of the factors setting it apart from peers include a unique branding and concept, strong community, innovative use cases, and limited supply.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">As the meme coin season gathers pace, DigiToads could establish itself as an ecosystem player and potential outperform Pepe (PEPE) over the long term.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">As the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency market</a> continues to grow and evolve, meme coins have emerged as a new trend effective for engaging with investors and traders alike.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the many meme coins currently trending in the market is <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DigiToads (TOADS)</u></a>, which is emerging as potential standout project that could outperform its peers, including Pepe (PEPE). Here are some of the reasons why:</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Unique branding and concept</h2>
<p dir="ltr">What makes DigiToads stand out from other meme coins is its unique branding and concept. Unlike other meme coins based on popular internet memes or jokes, DigiToads has created original characters and storylines.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The DigiToads is a group of 10,000 unique and colorful toads that inhabit a virtual world called The Swamp. Each toad has its personality and backstory, and users can interact with them in various ways, including through games and other activities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Strong community and support</h2>
<p dir="ltr">What&rsquo;s likely to also set DigiToads apart from competing projects is its strong community and support system. The project has already attracted a large following on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/social-media/">social media</a> platforms, with thousands of users actively engaging with the team and each other.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This level of community support can be a significant advantage for DigiToads. It can help drive adoption and awareness of the project, ultimately leading to higher demand for the token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Innovative use cases and applications</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Beyond its branding and community support, DigiToads has several innovative use cases and applications that could help drive its value higher over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, the project plans to release several games and activities allowing users to interact with their DigiToads in new and exciting ways. Additionally, the team has hinted at potential collaborations with other <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> projects, which could further expand the reach and utility of the DigiToads token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Limited supply and deflationary mechanisms</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Another advantage that DigiToads has over other meme coins is its limited supply and deflationary mechanisms. There are only 10,000 DigiToads in existence, which means that the token has a fixed supply that cannot be increased.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the project has implemented several deflationary mechanisms, including a burn rate on transactions and a buyback program, which can help reduce the supply of TOADS over time. The token&rsquo;s limited supply and deflationary nature could increase its value as demand increases over time.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Potential to outperform Pepe (PEPE)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Pepe (PEPE) is another popular meme coin that has gained a significant following, DigiToads could outperform it over the long term. As noted, a key difference and which is an advantage that DigiToads has over PEPE is its unique branding and concept.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike PEPE, which is based on a popular internet meme, DigiToads has created its original characters and storylines, which could help it stand out in a crowded market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">DigiToads has several innovative use cases and applications in the works, including games and activities that allow users to interact with their toads in new and exciting ways. This could drive adoption and demand for the token over time, ultimately leading to a higher value.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, DigiToads has a strong community and support system that could help drive awareness and adoption of the project. This level of community support can be a significant advantage for any cryptocurrency project, and DigiToads is no exception.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">DigiToads (TOADS) is an exciting and innovative project that has the potential to make a mark in the highly competitive world of meme coins. With its unique branding, strong community support and innovative use cases, it could outperform other meme coins, including Pepe (PEPE), over the long term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, investors should proceed cautiously and do their due diligence before investing in cryptocurrency. It should also be noted that investing in any cryptocurrency, including meme coins, carries a high level of risk. The volatility of the crypto market is well-known in the industry, and prices fluctuate rapidly and unpredictably.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, conducting thorough research and due diligence is essential before making investment decisions. Investors should carefully consider the fundamentals of the project, such as its team, technology, roadmap, and overall market conditions and trends.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, investors should only invest what they can afford to lose and continuously diversify their portfolios to manage risk. This means investing in various assets, including stocks, bonds, and cryptocurrencies, to reduce exposure to any asset class.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For more information on DigiToads, visit the <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>, join the presale or join the&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/digitoadsworld" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>community</u></a> for regular updates.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-stands-out-as-the-next-big-meme-coin-could-it-outperform-pepe-pepe/">DigiToads (TOADS) stands out as the next big Meme Coin. Could it outperform Pepe (PEPE)?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/digitoads-toads-stands-out-as-the-next-big-meme-coin-could-it-outperform-pepe-pepe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum ecosystem predictions: The Shanghai upgrade, scaling and a potential peak</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-ecosystem-predictions-the-shanghai-upgrade-scaling-and-a-potential-peak/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-ecosystem-predictions-the-shanghai-upgrade-scaling-and-a-potential-peak/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-ecosystem-predictions-the-shanghai-upgrade-scaling-and-a-potential-peak/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its launch,&#160;Ethereum has become the second cryptocurrency in the world in terms of market capitalization and the most popular altcoin globally. Its good reputation is also because the blockchain is well-recognized for its innovative qualities, being a pioneer in the fields of decentralized applications and finance. Over the last year, its native currency, Ether, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-ecosystem-predictions-the-shanghai-upgrade-scaling-and-a-potential-peak/">Ethereum ecosystem predictions: The Shanghai upgrade, scaling and a potential peak</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Since its launch,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/price/ethereum" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum</u></a> has become the second cryptocurrency in the world in terms of market capitalization and the most popular altcoin globally. Its good reputation is also because the blockchain is well-recognized for its innovative qualities, being a pioneer in the fields of decentralized applications and finance. Over the last year, its native currency, Ether, was badly hit by the crypto winter and bear markets that affected the digital finance ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, in 2023, the market is on the mend, and investors are beginning to remake their portfolios. Considering that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrencies</a> are still recovering from the difficulties of 2022, it&rsquo;s time to examine some ways the digital asset environment could change over the following months.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Shanghai Upgrade&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Over the years, Ethereum has been at the forefront of innovation and technological development within the cryptocurrency backdrop. Recently, on April 12th, it finally launched its much-awaited Shanghai upgrade. As a result, the price has <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ether-price-closes-in-on-2k-following-the-shanghai-upgrade/">climbed over $2,000</a>, the highest level in nearly a year, since May 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the days since the upgrade has gone live, exchanges have recorded an approximate inflow of nearly 180,000 ETH, the rough equivalent of $375 million. Between the 13th and the 19th of April, traders deposited over one million coins, compared to the 921,579 tokens that were removed. This has been the most significant net inflow in a month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for the effects this might have on the price point, analysts have pointed out that investors transferring coins to exchanges is a clear indicator they are preparing to sell, which can contribute to a price decline. The latest update has also enabled the withdrawal of staked contracts. Shortly before Shanghai was implemented, many investors were worried that this would cause the market to become flooded with millions of coins, leading to an inevitable crash.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While those grim predictions have thankfully not become a reality, it is still too early to determine the long-term implications of this latest upgrade and how it will impact both the Ethereum blockchain and the larger crypto environment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Network congestion&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain is an outstandingly large collection of immutable data that is stored in individual blocks. And while there are many advantages that come with its system, including transparency and the fact that nobody holds complete access to the body of information, one of the problems is the network&rsquo;s scaling. The recent crypto rallies have proved yet again that this problem needs to be solved.</p>
<p dir="ltr">When the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> climbed back up, an unprecedented number of new users rushed to the blockchain. As a result, the network slowed down, which is bad news for the traffic-based fees that power transactions on the Ethereum blockchain. The congestion caused these figures to reach exceedingly high levels, and the high prices, unfortunately, make cryptocurrencies, something that should be readily available for everyone, inaccessible to most. These factors could also cause Ethereum to lose its spot as a hub of decentralized finance to other networks that operate better in this regard.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum developers have been looking into methods to boost the blockchain&rsquo;s core to increase speed and decrease fees. However, the impact has been modest so far, and gradual changes are expected to intervene over the following years. After they are completed, investors will be able to say that the blockchain has achieved its full potential.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hacker attack&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Unfortunately, the cryptocurrency world is no stranger to hackers. Cybercriminals are drawn in by the chiefly digital aspect of the assets, and cryptocurrency wallets are some of the most coveted prizes by hackers. Generally, investors can protect their assets by taking the necessary security measures, such as ensuring they don&rsquo;t share their private passwords with anyone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, since December, many Ethereum users have been targeted by hacker attacks that drain their wallets. So far, an estimated $10 million, or 5,000 ETH, has been extracted from traders, many of whom are either whales or early investors. What&rsquo;s even more baffling is that the attacks are focused on hardware wallets, traditionally believed to be much more secure than the software-based alternatives.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the cause and reason for these attacks are currently not well understood, researchers have claimed that the person behind the attacks may have accessed a considerable data cache dating back a few years ago and proceeded to use it as a means to drain the cryptocurrency wallets of investors with substantial crypto holdings. While this educated guess can offer an educated guess as to what is going on, nobody can be sure of the hacker&rsquo;s identity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For those concerned about the safety of their assets, the best advice is to avoid keeping everything under a single key over several years. Moreover, ensure you don&rsquo;t store your secret passcodes anywhere online or on any device directly connected to the internet. Hackers can get access to your funds via this channel. If you&rsquo;ve been an investor for quite some time and you&rsquo;re not 100% confident that you&rsquo;ve been very careful about security measures in the past, consider creating a new wallet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Sandwich bots&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The concept of sandwich trading refers to a process during which a bot is programmed to spot when an investor is attempting to make a purchase on the blockchain. The bot then proceeds to place an order on the same token. Recently, one sandwich bot connected to a wallet named &ldquo;jaredfromsubway.eth&rdquo; has been using this tactic on investors betting on tokens, particularly chad and pepe. The meme coins don&rsquo;t have intrinsic value but became popular due to the intervention of social media.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While sandwich attackers aren&rsquo;t exploitative per se, many within the crypto environment view them as predatory. That&rsquo;s because the bots skim value from the investors, meaning they can make millions of dollars from an attack. Simultaneously, they drive gas fees up, which doesn&rsquo;t benefit either the blockchain or its users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Ethereum blockchain continues to change and develop. If you&rsquo;re an investor looking to increase your revenue, it&rsquo;s essential to be mindful of all these changes and prepare for them. Don&rsquo;t rush into anything, and don&rsquo;t make impulsive decisions even if they might seem correct at the moment. You&rsquo;ll have a lot to be thankful for later on.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-ecosystem-predictions-the-shanghai-upgrade-scaling-and-a-potential-peak/">Ethereum ecosystem predictions: The Shanghai upgrade, scaling and a potential peak</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-ecosystem-predictions-the-shanghai-upgrade-scaling-and-a-potential-peak/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals presale accelerates even as Bitcoin cools down and meme interest grows</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-accelerates-even-as-bitcoin-cools-down-and-meme-interest-grows/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-accelerates-even-as-bitcoin-cools-down-and-meme-interest-grows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-accelerates-even-as-bitcoin-cools-down-and-meme-interest-grows/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals token presale is now 66.84% complete The presale happens amid a tepid crypto market and growing interest in memes $ASI could be attractively priced ahead of the token listings Bitcoin has cooled down after a tepid run to the $30,000 mark. The cryptocurrency trades slightly below $28,000 at a time investors are still showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-accelerates-even-as-bitcoin-cools-down-and-meme-interest-grows/">AltSignals presale accelerates even as Bitcoin cools down and meme interest grows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals token presale is now 66.84% complete</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The presale happens amid a tepid crypto market and growing interest in memes</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI could be attractively priced ahead of the token listings</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has cooled down after a tepid run to the $30,000 mark. The cryptocurrency trades slightly below $28,000 at a time investors are still showing much interest in other little-known or new tokens like PEPE. This also happens when new tokens on presale, like AltSignals, attract interest, with 66.84% of the tokens sold out. Investors have been looking at AltSignals as a quality project backed by an existing community of traders. You can&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>join</u></a> the presale and become part of the AI transformation happening in the crypto industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin slows, but meme interest grows</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">One of the most watched paradoxes in crypto is the trading behaviour of Bitcoin versus meme cryptocurrencies. Historically, increased interest in meme cryptocurrencies like Dogecoin has caused a slowdown in Bitcoin. This time around, interest is on another little-known coin, PEPE. The frog-themed meme coin debuted in mid-April but has grown exponentially. The market cap rose to $1.82 billion barely a week ago, but it has retraced.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The interest in PEPE has also seen other little-known tokens, such as 4TOKEN, DINO, and CHAD, increase in value. It shows investors&rsquo; interest in crypto remains strong despite a prolonged bear market. That&rsquo;s because meme cryptocurrencies are driven by speculations, meaning investors still hold ground.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The intense interest in new cryptos favours newcomers like AltSignals ($ASI). Beyond the speculative reasons that could spur its uptake, AltSignals token powers a service that is in high demand &ndash; AI trading. That makes it a more sound investment compared to the meme predecessors and one that could deliver long-term success.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>AltSignals &ndash; Leveraging the power of AI to power trading</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.altsignals.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a UK-based trading service. Since its inception in 2017, the platform has built a successful business that has attracted thousands of followers on Telegram. AltSignals has been using AltAlgo&trade;, an advanced technical analysis tool, to generate quality signals for its community. The signals cut across forex markets and digital assets. The company has produced over 3,700 signals, with an average accuracy rate of over 64%. The signals have directly benefited over 52,000 traders who use the service.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To capitalise on the early success, AltSignals is launching an artificial intelligence-led trading platform for its community. The platform will be dubbed ActualizeAI and will be powered by AltSignals token $ASI. With AI, AltSignals expects to improve the quality of signals it produces and benefit its community further. There are other utilities the community will enjoy, potentially explaining why the $ASI presale has attracted a lot of interest so far.</p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is ActualizeAI and $ASI really a good opportunity?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The world is shifting towards AI, and it&rsquo;s no coincidence that software like ChatGPT is growing popular. Trading is one of those areas that is projected to benefit immensely from AI. AI trading systems can quickly and more accurately process data, allowing traders to make the right decisions. The systems can filter human emotions, pull data from various sources, and integrate a range of parameters in advanced technical analysis. Thus, a platform like ActaulizeAI could be exciting, especially since it is built from an already existing system by AltSignals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Similarly, owning $ASI guarantees access to AltSignals AI platform ActualizeAI. Investors benefit from quality trading signals which they can use to grow their bottom lines. AltSignals also envisions a situation where the trader is in control. They can use $ASI to vote on decisions and be part of beneficial ownership in the AI Members Club. In other words, apart from speculating on $ASI, investors have other range of benefits for investing in ActualizeAI.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy $ASI this week?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">With less than 35% of $ASI remaining before the presale completes, it could be the right time to invest. After that, the price may rise exponentially as $ASI is expected to list on Uniswap in the second quarter of 2023. It means investing early offers a chance to buy the token at a low price before more investors have access to it.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-accelerates-even-as-bitcoin-cools-down-and-meme-interest-grows/">AltSignals presale accelerates even as Bitcoin cools down and meme interest grows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-presale-accelerates-even-as-bitcoin-cools-down-and-meme-interest-grows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wakweli partners with Blockchain Lawyers Group to promote Web3 certification</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-to-promote-web3-certification/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-to-promote-web3-certification/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-to-promote-web3-certification/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Wakweli has partnered with BLG to promote web3 legal expertise. Wakweli seeks to become the benchmark of trust for the decentralised ecosystem. The web3 protocol partnered with Polygon earlier this year and also raised $1.1 million in its seed funding round.&#160; Wakweli enters a crucial partnership with BLG Web3 protocol Wakweli announced on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-to-promote-web3-certification/">Wakweli partners with Blockchain Lawyers Group to promote Web3 certification</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Wakweli has partnered with BLG to promote web3 legal expertise.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Wakweli seeks to become the benchmark of trust for the decentralised ecosystem.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The web3 protocol partnered with Polygon earlier this year and also raised $1.1 million in its seed funding round.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Wakweli enters a crucial partnership with BLG</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Web3 protocol Wakweli announced on Tuesday, May 9th, that it has partnered with the Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG)</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, Wakweli said the partnership would enhance the solid Web3 legal expertise and enable deeper protocol refinements for the Proof of Democracy consensus algorithm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Blockchain Lawyers Group is a global network of legal professionals with a focus on blockchain and other cryptocurrency matters. The group seeks to make it easier for entities in the crypto space to gain access to competent and qualified legal advice.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of the partnership, group members will participate in the validation of the first certificates and assist in strengthening the whole process. The goal is to make Wakweli the benchmark of trust for the decentralised ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Blockchain Lawyers Group Founder and Member Miguel Dinis Lucas said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We are excited to partner with such an innovative company as Wakweli, which is trying to solve a preeminent issue in the NFT space. We are confident that our collaboration will bring new levels of innovation and user-friendliness to the market.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The partnership will boost legal services in the blockchain ecosystem</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Wakweli team, their partnership with BLG is a significant step towards providing competent and qualified legal advice in blockchain and crypto-related matters.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership will lay the foundation for deeper protocol refinements, enhance solid Web3 legal expertise, and ensure easy access to legal advice for businesses operating in the Web3 industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership with BLG is the latest one for Wakweli. In March, Wakweli&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-certification-protocol-wakweli-partners-with-polygon/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>partnered with Polygon Labs</u></a> to enable all digital assets on Polygon to become compatible with the certification system that has been developed by its team.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In February, Wakweli also&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-certification-protocol-wakweli-raises-1-1m-in-its-first-funding-round/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>raised $1.1 million</u></a> in its seed funding round and is using the funds to facilitate the rolling out of the company&rsquo;s product offerings&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Wakweli is an NFT certification protocol based on a decentralised consensus algorithm called Proof of Democracy (PoD).&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-to-promote-web3-certification/">Wakweli partners with Blockchain Lawyers Group to promote Web3 certification</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-to-promote-web3-certification/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s why the Bitcoin SV (BSV) price just went vertical</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-sv-bsv-price-just-went-vertical/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-sv-bsv-price-just-went-vertical/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 12:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SV News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-sv-bsv-price-just-went-vertical/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin SV price surged to the highest level since March 1 as investors moved to the coin, which is an alternative to&#160;BTC. BSV jumped to a high of $42.10, which was about 48% above the lowest level this year. The coin&#8217;s market cap has jumped to more than $748 million. Is this a pump-and-dump scheme? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-sv-bsv-price-just-went-vertical/">Here’s why the Bitcoin SV (BSV) price just went vertical</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin SV price surged to the highest level since March 1 as investors moved to the coin, which is an alternative to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>BTC</u></a>. BSV jumped to a high of $42.10, which was about 48% above the lowest level this year. The coin&rsquo;s market cap has jumped to more than $748 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is this a pump-and-dump scheme?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There was no news that pushed Bitcoin SV higher on Tuesday. A likely reason why the BSV is rising is because some investors believe that it is a better alternative to Bitcoin. As we wrote in this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today/"><u>article</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>on Monday, Bitcoin&rsquo;s fees jumped on Monday because of elevated congestion in the network.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/"><u>Binance</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the biggest&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/"><u>crypto exchange</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>in the world, suspended Bitcoin withdrawals several times on Monday. Bitcoin SV, which has less volume than the main Bitcoin, is therefore seen as a better alternative. For one, its transactions take less than 2 seconds to complete while the average transaction fee is about $0.0001. Also, the network can handle over 50,000 transactions per second (tps).</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BTC is unusable, why not just use something else like BSV?</p>
<p>&mdash; whalechart (@WhaleChart) <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleChart/status/1655314443524272128?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">However, it is worth noting that the BSV price rally could be a pump-and-dump scheme. This is a situation where insiders or large holders buys an asset, promote it, and then exits at a profit, leaving buyers holding the bag. This situation is common among low-volume coins like Bitcoin SV.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin SV price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/09/1683636775738-9f59b13c-dd45-44be-a2c7-49108ea1fce6.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the BSV price has been in a strong bearish trend. It has crashed by over 90% from the highest point on record. The coin has also moved below all moving averages. It moved slightly above the crucial resistance point at $34, the lowest point on November 22 last year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I believe that this Bitcoin SV rally does not have legs. As such, there is a likelihood that it will resume the downward trend to where it was before it jumped. This could see it retreat to the next key support at $30.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-sv-bsv-price-just-went-vertical/">Here’s why the Bitcoin SV (BSV) price just went vertical</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-sv-bsv-price-just-went-vertical/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paxful P2P exchange reopens after closure</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-p2p-exchange-reopens-after-closure/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-p2p-exchange-reopens-after-closure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[P2P]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-p2p-exchange-reopens-after-closure/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Paxful remained closed for the last month. A legal dispute between Paxful&#8217;s co-founders had disrupted the exchange&#8217;s operations. The Paxful wallet however remained open throughout the shutdown. Paxful on May 8, announced that it will be reopening its services after a month-long shutdown. The P2P crypto exchange, however, said that it will gradually restore its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-p2p-exchange-reopens-after-closure/">Paxful P2P exchange reopens after closure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Paxful remained closed for the last month.</li>
<li>A legal dispute between Paxful&rsquo;s co-founders had disrupted the exchange&rsquo;s operations.</li>
<li>The Paxful wallet however remained open throughout the shutdown.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/an-objective-review-of-paxful-com/">Paxful </a>on May 8, announced that it will be reopening its services after a month-long shutdown. The P2P crypto exchange, however, said that it will gradually restore its services in the coming days.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#119809;&#119825;&#119812;&#119808;&#119818;&#119816;&#119821;&#119814; &#119821;&#119812;&#119830;&#119826;: Paxful is back online.</p>
<p>Over the next couple of days, we'll be gradually restoring functionality to the marketplace.</p>
<p>Thank you to everyone for your support!</p>
<p>&#129505; <a href="https://t.co/UApEgHxLg5">https://t.co/UApEgHxLg5</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Paxful (@paxful) <a href="https://twitter.com/paxful/status/1655558177554055168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>When <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/peer-to-peer-crypto-exchange-paxful-to-suspend-operations/">Paxful announced its shutdown on April 4, 2023</a>, it gave users alternatives to where they could transfer their assets although the Paxful wallet remained open throughout. The P2P exchange closure sent shockwaves across the crypto market seeing that it followed the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-exchnage-localbitcoins-is-shutting-down/">closure of LocalBitcoins</a>.</p>
<h2>Paxful is currently owned by a custodian</h2>
<p>Paxful closure was a result of tensions between Paxful co-founders Ray Youssef and Artur Schaback. While Schaback hoped for the P2P exchange to resume operations, Youssef apparently recommended new providers to Paxful users.</p>
<p>According to sources, Paxful is currently under the management of a custodian who acts as a company director and &ldquo;tie-breaker&rdquo; alongside the two cofounders Ray Youssef and Artur Schabeck.</p>
<p>Ray Youssef resigned from his position in Paxful and contributed his personal company shares to a fund intended to compensate Paxful shares. However, by April 17, Paxful had restored access to 88% of funds although $4.4 million remained frozen due to the legal conflict between the co-founders.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-p2p-exchange-reopens-after-closure/">Paxful P2P exchange reopens after closure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-p2p-exchange-reopens-after-closure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
