<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:56:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208199-perpetual-futures-contracts-benefits-and-risks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[leverage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[long]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Margin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perpetual Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perpetual Futures Contracts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[short]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Perpetual futures contracts offer continuous and leveraged trading in the cryptocurrency market, eliminating the need for time-bound settlements.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208199-perpetual-futures-contracts-benefits-and-risks/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Perpetual futures contracts offer continuous and leveraged trading in the cryptocurrency market, eliminating the need for time-bound settlements.</em></li>



<li><em>The appeal of perpetual futures lies in higher leverage potential, flexible payment mechanisms, and the ability to profit from both upward and downward price movements.</em></li>



<li><em>Despite the benefits, traders must exercise caution due to the inherent risks, including counterparty risk and potential losses.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Perpetual futures contracts are one of the most used derivative products in crypto. In <a href="https://twitter.com/Coincuofficial" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coincu</a> today&#8217;s article, we&#8217;ll explore the perpetual <strong>futures</strong></strong> <strong>contract and its strengths and limitations.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-1024x576.png" alt="Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks" class="wp-image-208205" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-224.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks 1"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What are perpetual futures contracts?</h2>



<p>A futures contract, by definition, is an agreement between two parties to buy or sell a particular asset at a predetermined price on a specified future date. However, perpetual futures contracts operate on a different principle. They eliminate the element of time-bound settlement, allowing traders to maintain their positions for as long as they desire.</p>



<p>When engaging in futures trading, including perpetual futures, traders focus solely on the price movement of the underlying asset. The calculation of profit and loss (P/L) is based on the specified underlying asset&#8217;s value at the time of contract signing.</p>



<p>The appeal of perpetual futures contracts lies in their simplicity and ease of use. Cryptocurrency traders, in particular, have embraced these contracts for their convenience and versatility in the volatile crypto markets. By removing the pressure of expiration dates, traders can concentrate solely on market analysis and decision-making, enhancing their trading strategies.</p>



<p>Moreover, perpetual contracts offer a distinct advantage over traditional futures contracts &#8211; higher leverage. This increased leverage potential allows traders to amplify their positions and potentially magnify their gains (or losses) as they ride the market&#8217;s movements.</p>



<p><a href="https://coincu.com/207375-perpetual-contracts-work-makes-attractive/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Perpetual futures contracts</a> have quickly become one of the most traded derivatives in the cryptocurrency market, capturing the interest of a vast majority of users. The ability to engage in continuous trading without worrying about contract expirations has proven to be a game-changer for many traders.</p>



<p>However, it&#8217;s important to note that while perpetual contracts offer attractive benefits, they also come with increased risks due to their leveraged nature. Traders should exercise caution and employ risk management strategies to safeguard their capital.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="577" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-1024x577.png" alt="Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks" class="wp-image-208206" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-1024x577.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-1536x865.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225-1140x642.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-225.png 1776w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks 2"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Strengths and limitations</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Strengths</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Leveraging Potential</strong></p>



<p>One of the key benefits of perpetual futures contracts is the ability to trade positions that exceed the trader&#8217;s account balance. This feature allows investors to magnify their exposure to the market and potentially make significant profits if they correctly predict the price trend direction. In the realm of cryptocurrencies, perpetual futures contracts typically support leverage ranging from x20 to x100, enabling traders to amplify their gains while also acknowledging the associated risks.</p>



<p>The primary purpose of using financial leverage in Perpetual Futures trading is to magnify potential profits. By borrowing funds from the exchange or <a href="https://coincu.com/205329-perpetual-platforms-on-optimism/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">platform</a>, traders can access larger trading positions than their actual account balance would allow. For instance, with <a href="https://coincu.com/198533-binance-mav-perpetual-contract-20x-leverage/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">leverage ratios</a> reaching as high as x100 in the cryptocurrency market, a trader with $1000 could theoretically control a trading volume equivalent to $100,000.</p>



<p>To illustrate this, let&#8217;s consider an example. A trader starts with $1000 and decides to enter a Perpetual Futures trade with a Buy (Long) x100 leverage position. In this scenario, the total trading volume for this order would be $1000 x 100, which amounts to $100,000. Now, any profit or loss will be based on this amplified $100,000 trading volume, potentially leading to substantial gains if the market moves in its favor.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="577" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-1024x577.png" alt="Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks" class="wp-image-208207" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-1024x577.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-1536x865.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226-1140x642.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-226.png 1776w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Perpetual Futures Contracts: Benefits And Risks 3"></a></figure></div>


<p><strong>Risk Management</strong></p>



<p>Traditional spot trading in the cryptocurrency market often relies on the simple &#8220;buy low, sell high&#8221; approach to profit. However, perpetual futures contracts present a more flexible alternative, enabling traders to capitalize on both upward (long) and downward (short) price movements. By being able to profit from both market directions, traders have enhanced risk management capabilities, allowing them to adapt to various market conditions.</p>



<p>Moreover, perpetual futures contracts can serve as an effective hedging tool. For instance, a trader participating in a Binance Launchpad event by acquiring a BNB spot might use a BNB/USDT perpetual futures contract to hedge against the risk of a sudden and significant decline in BNB&#8217;s price. This hedging strategy can help mitigate potential losses during volatile market phases.</p>



<p><strong>Flexible Payment Mechanism</strong></p>



<p>Perpetual futures contracts on certain professional crypto exchanges provide traders with the convenience of choosing their preferred payment currency for profit and loss calculations. Traders can opt to have their gains and losses denominated in cash, like USDC or USDT, or in corresponding cryptocurrency assets. This flexibility empowers traders to align their trading strategies with their specific financial goals and preferences.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Limitations</strong></h3>



<p>The allure of perpetual futures contracts comes with inherent risks, as they remain unregulated and present challenges for both experienced and inexperienced traders alike.</p>



<p>Despite the benefits, perpetual futures contracts carry substantial counterparty risk due to their perpetual nature. The lack of a predefined maturity date exposes traders to the possibility of defaults and misconduct by counterparties, leaving victims unprotected. The absence of regulatory oversight, such as authorization by the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission, adds another layer of uncertainty, leaving traders without compensation in the event of default.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s essential to recognize that financial leverage is a double-edged sword. While it can amplify profits, it equally magnifies losses if the market moves against the trader&#8217;s position. The higher the leverage ratio, the greater the potential risk. Hence, traders must exercise caution and implement robust risk management strategies to protect their capital.</p>



<p>Another key aspect that makes perpetual futures complex is their convergence with the underlying asset&#8217;s value as the expiration date approaches, a unique characteristic not present in traditional futures contracts. This requirement ties the contract perpetually to the current market value of the assets they represent, making them challenging to navigate for traders.</p>



<p>It is crucial to acknowledge that perpetual futures are not for the faint-hearted or inexperienced. Given the inherent risks and complexities, novices to cryptocurrency trading are strongly discouraged from entering this high-stakes market. Successful participation demands a solid understanding of financial principles and significant experience in crypto trading.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Leveraging in perpetual futures contracts trading can provide traders with exciting opportunities to boost their potential profits significantly. By accessing larger trading positions, they can take advantage of market trends and capitalize on arbitrage opportunities. However, traders must approach leverage with caution, as it comes with increased risk exposure. A well-informed and disciplined approach to leveraging is vital for success in this dynamic and fast-paced trading landscape.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208199-perpetual-futures-contracts-benefits-and-risks/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-227-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Now Continues Strong Regulatory Plan For Stablecoins</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209083-uk-now-continues-regulatory-stablecoins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BoE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FCA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TerraUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Bank of England (BoE) of the UK is poised to forge ahead with its strategy for a systemic stablecoin framework, according to a recent consultation response.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209083-uk-now-continues-regulatory-stablecoins/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>UK&#8217;s Bank of England (BoE) and FCA collaborate on regulating systemic stablecoins, gaining support.</em></li>



<li><em>The government responds to consultation, focusing on payment reforms and stablecoin concerns.</em></li>



<li><em>The UK balances consumer protection and crypto industry support through evolving legislation.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Bank of England (BoE) of the UK</strong> <strong>is <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/consultations/payments-regulation-and-the-systemic-perimeter-consultation-and-call-for-evidence" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">poised</a> to forge ahead with its strategy for a systemic stablecoin framework, according to a recent consultation response, <em>CoinDesk</em> <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/08/uks-central-bank-forges-ahead-with-plans-for-a-systemic-stablecoin-regime/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a>.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-1024x614.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="614" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-1024x614.png" alt="UK Now Continues Strong Regulatory Plan For Stablecoins" class="wp-image-209091" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-1024x614.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-300x180.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-768x461.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-750x450.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452-1140x684.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-452.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="UK Now Continues Strong Regulatory Plan For Stablecoins 4"></a></figure></div>


<p>The response highlights the collaboration between the <a href="https://coincu.com/182480-bank-of-england-successfully-tests-dlt/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BoE</a> and the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) in supervising these stablecoins, a move that garnered positive feedback from stakeholders.</p>



<p>Additionally, support was expressed for extending the accountability framework to encompass systemic stablecoins, ensuring future adaptability.</p>



<p>The document also outlines updates on rulemaking and direction-making powers for the Financial Conduct Authority and Payment Systems Regulator.</p>



<p>It addresses retained EU payments law and signals the Senior Managers &amp; Certification Regime&#8217;s remit expansion in relation to payments, coinciding with the broader review of the regime.</p>



<p>In parallel, the <a href="https://coincu.com/208750-nca-expands-elite-team-to-combat-crypto-crime/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">UK</a> introduced consultations in the prior year detailing the integration of systemic stablecoins within existing regulations aimed at safeguarding customer funds and sustaining operations.</p>



<p>Some respondents expressed concern over potential conflicts between returning customer funds and ensuring service continuity. The government acknowledges these concerns and pledges continued collaboration with regulators to fine-tune its approach.</p>



<p>Recently, the UK enacted the Financial Services and Markets Act 2023, conferring the BoE with the authority to establish a systemic stablecoin framework.</p>



<p>These stablecoins, designed to emulate the value of conventional assets like fiat currencies, have raised regulatory alarms due to the underlying asset risks and potential financial system implications.</p>



<p>Notably, the volatility in crypto markets has spotlighted stability concerns, with instances like TerraUSD&#8217;s sharp value decline shaking investor confidence.</p>



<p>The stablecoin market has also recently welcomed a new entry as payment giant <a href="https://coincu.com/208927-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-may-freeze-by-paxos/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">PayPal</a> has launched its stablecoin, <a href="https://coincu.com/209065-huobi-to-listing-paypal-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">PYUSD</a>.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209083-uk-now-continues-regulatory-stablecoins/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/On-White-8_11zon-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance&#8217;s Latest Reserve Proof Report Reveals Shift From USDC To BTC And ETH</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209079-binances-peserve-proof-reveals-usdc-btc-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209079</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In its recent Proof of Reserve (PoR) disclosure on August 8th, Binance unveiled a significant reduction in its USDC balance from $3.4 billion on March 1 to $23.9 million on May 1. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209079-binances-peserve-proof-reveals-usdc-btc-eth/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Binance&#8217;s recent Proof of Reserve report reveals a significant shift from USDC to BTC and ETH.</em></li>



<li><em>The move aligns with the platform strategy to diversify holdings, totaling about $3.5 billion, amid evolving market dynamics.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In its recent Proof of Reserve (PoR) disclosure on August 8th, Binance unveiled a significant reduction in its USDC balance from $3.4 billion on March 1 to $23.9 million on May 1.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="569" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U-1024x569.jpeg" alt="Binance&#039;s Latest Reserve Proof Report Reveals Shift From USDC To BTC And ETH" class="wp-image-209086" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U-1024x569.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U-300x167.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U-768x426.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U-750x417.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U-1140x633.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/UJZCDJLDGJD6HOXHUMLQJMPH2U.jpeg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Binance&#039;s Latest Reserve Proof Report Reveals Shift From USDC To BTC And ETH 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> Binance-Reserve-Proof-Report:-Binance-sold-a-large-amount-of-USDC-in-exchange-for-BTC-and-ETH</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>According to analyst Aleksandar Djakovic, the decline in USDC holdings coincided with Binance&#8217;s strategic move to purchase approximately 100,000 BTC and 550,000 ETH, amounting to about $3.5 billion, between March 12 and May 1.</p>



<p>This reserve shift aligns with the platform&#8217;s move to diversify its holdings and adapt to market dynamics. Following the collapse of banks like Silvergate and Signature, the exchange aimed to bolster its crypto assets, reinforcing its resilience against potential market fluctuations.</p>



<p>The revelation of <a href="https://coincu.com/209068-dwf-labs-1-million-dodo-tokens-binance/">Binance&#8217;</a>s USDC reserves and subsequent asset reallocation has generated significant attention within the crypto community. Notably, the topic gained prominence after Brian Armstrong, CEO of Coinbase, mentioned during the company&#8217;s Q2 earnings call that Binance had converted USDC to another stablecoin.</p>



<p>As the cryptocurrency landscape evolves, major exchanges are continuously reassessing their asset management strategies. The shift from a substantial USDC balance to acquiring significant amounts of BTC and ETH illustrates Binance&#8217;s proactive approach to aligning its reserves with the evolving market trends. </p>



<p>This strategic move not only diversifies the firm&#8217;s holdings but also positions the exchange to leverage the potential benefits of BTC and ETH, two of the most prominent cryptocurrencies in the market.</p>



<p>The dynamic shifts in the firm&#8217;s reserve management underscore the constant adaptation and strategic decision-making required in the cryptocurrency industry, where market volatility and innovation necessitate continuous adjustments to optimize asset portfolios.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209079-binances-peserve-proof-reveals-usdc-btc-eth/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/coincu_Show_a_Binance_scale_tipping_over_as_USDC_coins_roll_awa_072c0bbb-3e29-4a6d-bc2c-960a5a44cbc4.png" width="1012" height="716" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Is The First Exchange Responds To The Crazy Of PayPal Stablecoin</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209065-huobi-to-listing-paypal-stablecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paxos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PYUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Huobi is the first exchange to back PayPal's PYUSD stablecoin, emphasizing innovation.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209065-huobi-to-listing-paypal-stablecoin/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Huobi is the first exchange to back PayPal&#8217;s PYUSD stablecoin, emphasizing innovation.</em></li>



<li><em>Zero fees for PYUSD/USDT trading on Huobi set a new industry standard for cost-effective trading.</em></li>



<li><em>PYUSD boasts strong security via Paxos yet faces challenges from counterfeit token circulation.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Huobi, a prominent player in the cryptocurrency exchange space, has <a href="https://www.huobi.com/support/en-us/detail/44945804382445" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">unveiled</a> plans to pioneer the listing of PayPal&#8217;s new stablecoin, PYUSD.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-1024x533.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="533" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-1024x533.png" alt="Huobi Is The First Exchange To Announce The Listing Of Paypal Stablecoin" class="wp-image-209074" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-1024x533.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-300x156.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-768x400.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-1536x799.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-750x390.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450-1140x593.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-450.png 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Huobi Is The First Exchange Responds To The Crazy Of PayPal Stablecoin 6"></a></figure></div>


<p>This strategic move marks a significant milestone as Huobi becomes the first exchange to embrace the PYUSD stablecoin. The exchange giant has also declared a groundbreaking policy of zero handling fees for the PYUSD/USDT trading pair, promising to uphold this fee structure indefinitely.</p>



<p>PYUSD, the brainchild of PayPal, serves as a secure and practical stablecoin for seamless transfers and payments denominated in US dollars. </p>



<p>Issued by the reputable Paxos Trust Company, the stablecoin boasts a robust backing of 100% US dollar deposits, short-term US Treasury bonds, and cash equivalents. Currently, there are 26.9 million PYUSD tokens in circulation.</p>



<p>Huobi&#8217;s commitment to fostering collaborative growth within the blockchain industry has driven this groundbreaking partnership. The exchange is primed to launch the PYUSD/USDT trading pair once optimal market circulation and liquidity conditions are achieved, a move keenly anticipated by industry observers.</p>



<p>In a parallel development, security has taken center stage. GitHub reveals that PYUSD has implemented stringent security protocols through its underlying technology provider, <a href="https://coincu.com/208927-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd-may-freeze-by-paxos/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Paxos</a>. </p>



<p>This means that, in the face of significant security threats, both the authorization and transfer functions of PYUSD can be swiftly suspended, ensuring the safety of user holdings.</p>



<p>However, the launch of PYUSD has not been without challenges. Reports indicate that opportunistic actors are attempting to exploit the situation by circulating counterfeit tokens under the &#8220;PYUSD&#8221; label across various decentralized networks. </p>



<p>The vigilant DEX Screener has <a href="https://coincu.com/208963-over-60-fake-paypal-stablecoins/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">identified</a> over 60 recently spawned token pairs masquerading as PYUSD since the initial announcement.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209065-huobi-to-listing-paypal-stablecoin/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Huobi-Is-The-First-Exchange-Responds-To-The-Crazy-Of-PayPal-Stablecoin-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/208696-origin-defi-prominent-lsdfi-trends-high-profits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LSDfi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Origin Defi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=208696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Origin Defi emerged in the LSDFi segment as a protocol that uses a combination of different strategies to increase revenue and thereby bring high profits to users. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208696-origin-defi-prominent-lsdfi-trends-high-profits/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="https://t.co/cRZ0jm0OsN" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Origin Defi</a> emerged in the LSDFi segment as a protocol that uses a combination of different strategies to increase revenue and thereby bring high profits to users. Origin DeFi&#8217;s OTokens use the same codebase but accept different collateral and utilize various strategies depending on the market&#8217;s opportunities. OUSD is designed to help you accumulate more dollars, whereas OETH enables you to earn more ETH. So what is Origin Defi? How does it work?</strong></h5>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is Origin Defi?</h2>



<p>As a new member of the LSDFi racetrack, Origin Protocol uses various income strategies to enhance earnings. The Native Protocol is a platform powered by Ethereum that aims to bring Non-fungible Tokens (NFT) and Decentralized Finance (DeFi) to the masses.</p>



<p>In 2020, Origin sought to make everyone profitable by launching its first profitable stablecoin, OUSD. We are now taking the next step forward, delivering continuous, accessible, and advanced returns on Ether. Origin recently launched Origin Ether (OETH), an innovative yield token that uses top-tier LSD as collateral.</p>



<p>Origin&#8217;s NFT and DeFi ecosystems are managed by the OGN token, allowing holders to ensure transparent monitoring and development of the Origin platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Origin Defi products</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Origin Dollar (OUSD)</strong></h3>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="475" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-1024x475.png" alt="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits" class="wp-image-208773" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-1024x475.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-300x139.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-768x356.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-1536x713.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-2048x950.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-750x348.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-371-1140x529.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits 7"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Origin Dollar (OUSD) marks the entry of the Origin team into the DeFi ecosystem. OUSD is an Ethereum-based stablecoin whose value is pegged to the US Dollar. OUSD was initially launched in September 2020 and has been battle-tested over time with hundreds of millions of dollars in circulating supply. The smart contracts have also been thoroughly audited by some of the top firms in the space, including Trail of Bits and OpenZeppelin.</p>



<p>OUSD is different from other stablecoins in that holders can earn a return on their assets directly from their wallets without the need to constantly stake and cancel or lock their funds in liquidity pools. Origin claims that OUSD is always accessible to make trades while holders earn this passive income from their wallets.</p>



<p>OUSD smart contracts automatically rebalance funds in a set of lending protocols such as Aave, Compound, and Curve in a method commonly known as yield farming.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Origin Ether (OETH)</strong></h3>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="500" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-1024x500.png" alt="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits" class="wp-image-208772" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-1024x500.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-300x146.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-768x375.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-1536x750.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-750x366.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370-1140x556.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-370.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits 8"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>OETH launched in May 2023 using the same core contracts as OUSD. The main difference is that OETH uses ETH and liquid staking tokens (LSTs) as the backing collateral instead of dollar-backed stablecoins. OETH also normalizes the accounting across the various supported LSTs, so you don&#8217;t need to do any math to figure out the amount of underlying ETH. 1 OETH is always worth 1 ETH.</p>



<p>Origin Ether shares much of its codebase with Origin Dollar, with the key distinction being that OETH is an ether-denominated token, whereas OUSD is denominated in USD. OETH takes advantage of liquid staking yield, boosting APYs through DeFi strategies and rewards tokens.</p>



<p>Ethereum staking participation currently pales in comparison to Solana (68% staked), Cardano (72% staked), Polkadot (46% staked), and Avalanche (62% staked). This is significantly due to stakers being unable to withdraw staked ETH until the recent Shanghai upgrade. Of the 15% of Ether staked, around 40% is provided through LST providers like Lido, Coinbase, Frax, and others.</p>



<p>Origin Ether earns yield from liquid staking tokens stETH, rETH, and sfrxETH. Holders earn superior yield with Origin Ether, as APYs are optimized between LSTs and liquidity provision strategies within DeFi. At launch, OETH utilizes an AMO strategy on Curve and Convex through the OETH-ETH pool. In doing so, Origin Ether accumulates increased trading fees and rewards tokens on top of validator rewards from the aforementioned LSTs.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Staking</strong></h3>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="726" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-1024x726.png" alt="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits" class="wp-image-208800" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-1024x726.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-300x213.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-768x544.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-1536x1088.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-120x86.png 120w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-750x531.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379-1140x808.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-379.png 1729w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits 9"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Staking OGV </strong></h4>



<p>Staking OGV for a period of time in exchange for economic and voting power in the form of Vote-Escrowed Origin DeFi Governance tokens (veOGV). The longer users choose to stake, the more power they receive. This ensures that power is held by those who are most committed to the long-term success of the protocol. In return for staking OGV, users not only earn the ability to create proposals and vote on the future of the protocol. They are also rewarded with additional OGV that can be collected at any time.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Staking other tokens</strong></h4>



<p>In addition to supporting ETH as collateral, Origin Ether supports liquid staking tokens stETH, frxETH, and rETH. The vault holds exposure to Frax Staked Ether (sfrxETH), but the vault does not support sfrxETH as a collateral type.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Mechanism of action</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Buying Tokens</strong></h3>



<p>Users can upgrade their existing stablecoins to OUSD using app.ousd.com or convert their ETH or supported LSTs to OETH using app.oeth.com. Once upgraded, your OUSD or OETH will immediately begin accruing yield that compounds automatically.</p>



<p>The Origin Defi dapps will intelligently route consumers&#8217; transactions while considering slippage and gas prices into account to provide them with the cheapest pricing. This implies that occasionally the dapps will advise users to purchase OUSD or OETH that is currently in use rather than creating fresh currencies from the vault. The dapps will select from various liquidity providers and recommend the one that offers the customer the best rate.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Selling Tokens</strong></h3>



<p>Users can redeem their OUSD or OETH for the underlying collateral. Just as with buying, the Origin dapp will intelligently route users&#8217; transactions to give them the best available price while considering slippage, gas costs, and the vault&#8217;s exit fee. This means that the dapps will often help users sell their OUSD or OETH on AMMs instead of redeeming with the vault and incurring the protocol&#8217;s exit fee.</p>



<p>On redemption of OUSD (0.25%) or OETH (0.5%) through the vault, a minor departure fee is assessed. The remaining vault participants (i.e., other OUSD or OETH holders) get this charge as an extra yield. In the event of mispriced underlying assets, the charge acts as a security measure to make it impossible for attackers to exploit lagging oracles. It prevents them from stealing stablecoins from the vault. The charge was put in place to reward long-term investors over short-term speculators.</p>



<p>The vault will choose which coins to provide the user after redemption. Coins will be returned from the vault in proportion to the present stock. In the case that any of the supported stablecoins loses its peg, the vault is safeguarded by the lack of user optionality.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Automated Yield Farming</strong></h3>



<p>The smart contracts generate yield by deploying the collateral into trusted DeFi protocols as Compound, Aave, Curve, Convex, and Morpho. There may be new diversified strategies added to the vault in the future as approved by governance. Earned interest, trading fees, and rewards tokens are swapped and reinvested to produce yield on OTokens.</p>



<p>Over time, the protocol will rebalance assets between different earning strategies in order to maximize yields. Users are able to benefit from faster compounding and rebalancing of assets as the farming costs are shared across the entire pool.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Elastic Supply</strong></h3>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-1024x576.png" alt="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits" class="wp-image-208774" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-372.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits 10"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Through ongoing (up only) rebasing of the money supply, the created returns are distributed to holders of OToken. In response to the protocol&#8217;s yield, both currencies steadily raise the amount of money in circulation. As a result, the price of OUSD and OETH may remain fixed at $1 USD and $1 ETH, respectively, while the balances in token holders&#8217; wallets can be updated in real-time to reflect yields the protocol has received.</p>



<p>The result is tokens that are easy to spend, earn outsized risk-adjusted yields automatically, and are more desirable to hold than Ether, stablecoins, or liquid staking tokens.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Tokenomics</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367-1024x640.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="640" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367-1024x640.png" alt="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits" class="wp-image-208765" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367-1024x640.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367-300x188.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367-768x480.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367-750x469.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-367.png 1100w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Origin Defi Review: A Prominent Protocol In LSDFi Trends With High Profits 11"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Native DeFi Governance (OGV) serves as the token that accumulates value and governance at the heart of Origin DeFi. Formerly a Native Dollar Governance, OGV has been used as a governance token for the Native Dollar protocol. With Origin DeFi, the utility of OGV is expanding to cover both OUSD and OETH.</p>



<p>OGV further innovates the voting margin token model pioneered by Curve Finance. Holders can stake their OGV for up to four years in exchange for veOGV, which carries voting and economic rights. veOGV holders also enjoy a generous passive profit from their staked OGV.</p>



<p>As part of our commitment to user autonomy, all OUSD and OETH strategic allocations are decided on a weekly basis through governance votes. This model has been carefully honed since its initial launch with impressive results.</p>



<p>1 billion OGV will be distributed to OGN holders along with rewards for liquidity mining campaign participants before launch on July 12. The total supply of OGV on July 12 will be 4 billion, with the majority locked for 1 to 4 years.</p>



<p>The only other exception is 125 million OGV which will be immediately available to the DAO to support the launch with initial liquidity provision and market-making efforts on centralized exchanges and DEXs. The remaining 2.825 billion OGV will be locked to vote for up to 4 years.</p>



<p>Having a gradual release schedule helps ensure a smooth release process and protects OGV&#8217;s performance. Pool tokens will be locked at launch and unlocked every year for 4 years as a retroactive bonus for OUSD holders.</p>



<p>Similarly, the rest of the DAO holdings will unlock gradually over a 4-year period to fund liquidity mining campaigns, liquidity provisioning, and partnerships with exchanges and exchanges. DeFi knowledge, future contributors and open source developers, new projects built on top of OUSD, long-term incentive programs, and other community-voted initiatives. We predict that the circulating supply at launch will be 1 billion OGV or less.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Team</h2>



<p>Origin Ether is created by Origin Protocol Labs and is managed by the existing OGV staking community. Origin was founded by Josh Fraser and Matthew Liu, who later joined PayPal co-founders, executives from Coinbase, Lyft, Dropbox, and Google, as well as many top engineers from the companies. web2 startup to build Native Protocol.</p>



<p>Origin Defi&#8217;s main investor is Pantera Capital, the world&#8217;s oldest crypto fund. Other notable investors include Foundation Capital, Blockchaintower, Blockchain.com, KBW Ventures, Spartan Capital, PreAngel Fund, Hashed, Kenetic Capital, FBG, QCP Capital, and Smart Contract Japan. Notable angel investors include YouTube founder Steve Chen, Reddit founder Alexis Ohanian, Y Combinator partner Garry Tan, and Akamai founder Randall Kaplan.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>As a new member of the LSDFi racetrack, Origin Defi is using a variety of income strategies to help users on the platform have attractive income and improve competitiveness with other competitors.</p>



<p>Underpinned by OGV&#8217;s unparalleled governance, Origin Dollar and Origin Ether provide powerful platforms for users to enjoy the full benefits of DeFi – from new adopters to veterans across the globe chain, DAO, protocol, and organization.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/208696-origin-defi-prominent-lsdfi-trends-high-profits/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Origin-Defi-Review-A-Prominent-Protocol-In-LSDFi-Trends-With-High-Profits-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DWF Labs Transfers 1 Million DODO Tokens To Binance Amid Soaring Prices</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209068-dwf-labs-1-million-dodo-tokens-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DODO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DODO & YGG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209068</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On August 8th, DWF Labs made a significant move in the cryptocurrency space by transferring 1 million DODO tokens, equivalent to approximately $172,000 USD, to Binance. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209068-dwf-labs-1-million-dodo-tokens-binance/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>DWF Labs transfers 1 million DODO tokens worth $172,000 to Binance amid surging prices.</em></li>



<li><em>The move comes as this token experiences a 30% price increase and Binance introduces a new perpetual contract, driving positive investor sentiment.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>On August 8th, DWF Labs made a significant move in the cryptocurrency space by transferring 1 million DODO tokens, equivalent to approximately $172,000 USD, to Binance.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-1024x576.png" alt="DWF Labs Transfers 1 Million DODO Tokens To Binance Amid Soaring Prices" class="wp-image-209070" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/532cbd65-5896-4ef3-8b19-1aa5c3a9fd47.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="DWF Labs Transfers 1 Million DODO Tokens To Binance Amid Soaring Prices 12"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> DWF-Labs-Transfers-1-Million-DODO-Tokens-To-Binance-Amid-Soaring-Prices</figcaption></figure></div>


<p>This transaction occurred as the price of this tokens experienced a notable surge just an hour prior. However, DWF Labs retains a substantial stake of 5 million DODO tokens, valued at around $810,000 USD.</p>



<p>The transfer follows DWF Labs&#8217; receipt of 6 million unlocked DODO tokens earlier that morning, as reported by The Data Nerd monitoring. The market witnessed a remarkable 30% increase in this token prices, accompanied by similar surges in other tokens like YGG.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The announcement of Binance&#8217;s introduction of the <a href="https://coincu.com/208809-dodo-ygg-skyrocket-after-binances-1-20x-futures/">USD₮-mDODO</a> perpetual contract, offering leverage of up to 20x, reverberated across the crypto community, sparking heightened investor enthusiasm.</p>



<p>With DWF Labs&#8217; strategic token transfer to Binance and their retained holding of 5 million of the token, valued over $800,000 USD, the crypto landscape is experiencing dynamic shifts. The recent surge in this token prices and the buzz surrounding Binance&#8217;s new perpetual contract offering demonstrate the ongoing evolution and vibrancy of the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>



<p>As investor sentiment remains positively impacted by these developments, the broader implications for the crypto sector are eagerly anticipated.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209068-dwf-labs-1-million-dodo-tokens-binance/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/DWF-Labs-Transfers-1-Million-DODO-Tokens-To-Binance-Amid-Soaring-Prices-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whales Make Significant $APE Deposits, Sparking Exchange Activity</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209045-whales-make-significant-ape-deposits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sparking Exchange Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209045</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a flurry of activity that has caught the attention of the crypto community, three prominent whales have collectively deposited a staggering sum of 1.85 million $APE (equivalent to $3.4 million) into various exchanges over the course of the past 12 hours.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209045-whales-make-significant-ape-deposits/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Three whales deposit 1.85M $APE ($3.4M) in exchanges within 12 hours. </em></li>



<li><em>Wallets 0xa3fb and 0x0A77 shift staked $APE to Binance. </em></li>



<li><em>0xbDEA receives 5M $APE, deposits 560K $APE ($1.02M) to OKX.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a flurry of activity that has caught the attention of the crypto community, three prominent whales have collectively deposited a staggering sum of 1.85 million $APE (equivalent to $3.4 million) into various exchanges over the course of the past 12 hours.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="490" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-1024x490.png" alt="Whales Make Significant $APE Deposits, Sparking Exchange Activity" class="wp-image-209048" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-1024x490.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-300x144.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-768x368.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-1536x735.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-2048x981.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-750x359.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-446-1140x546.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Whales Make Significant $APE Deposits, Sparking Exchange Activity 13"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Among these transactions, the wallet addresses 0xa3fb and 0x0A77 notably executed withdrawals of their staked $APE holdings before proceeding to deposit them onto the renowned exchange platform, <a href="https://accounts.binance.com/en/register?ref=753739699&amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwz8emBhDrARIsANNJjS4w2gxwuBtMHcyaLYxBMxAuLXDOpff0sUS0NRCPoNlMlpvytS2nkDgaAkIBEALw_wcB" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://accounts.binance.com/en/register?ref=753739699&amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwz8emBhDrARIsANNJjS4w2gxwuBtMHcyaLYxBMxAuLXDOpff0sUS0NRCPoNlMlpvytS2nkDgaAkIBEALw_wcB" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a>. This movement of funds from staked to exchange wallets has generated curiosity within the crypto space, leaving enthusiasts and investors speculating on the motivations behind these actions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">3 whales have deposited a total of 1.85M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24APE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$APE</a> ($3.4M) to exchanges in the past 12 hours.<br><br>0xa3fb and 0x0A77 withdrew all the staked <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24APE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$APE</a> and deposited to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#Binance</a>.<br><br>0xbDEA received 5M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24APE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$APE</a> from Apecoin Token Distributor and deposited 560K <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24APE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$APE</a> ($1.02M) into <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/OKX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#OKX</a> 3 hrs ago. <a href="https://t.co/vnY6qrMQGr" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/vnY6qrMQGr</a></p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1688804730305454083?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">August 8, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>In another intriguing development, wallet address 0xbDEA saw a substantial influx of 5 million $APE tokens from the Apecoin Token Distributor. Subsequently, a portion of these tokens, totaling 560,000 $APE (equivalent to $1.02 million), was promptly deposited onto the exchange platform OKX a mere three hours after the transfer was received.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="475" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-1024x475.png" alt="Whales Make Significant $APE Deposits, Sparking Exchange Activity" class="wp-image-209049" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-1024x475.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-300x139.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-768x356.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-1536x713.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-2048x950.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-750x348.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-447-1140x529.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Whales Make Significant $APE Deposits, Sparking Exchange Activity 14"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>These moves have triggered a surge of interest within the cryptocurrency community, prompting discussions about the potential implications for both the $APE token and the broader market. Analysts are scrutinizing the whales&#8217; actions to decipher potential trends or strategies, as such sizeable transactions can often serve as indicators of market sentiment.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209045-whales-make-significant-ape-deposits/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Whales-Make-Significant-APE-Deposits-Sparking-Exchange-Activity-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209037-chainlink-shows-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chainlink's price rises 2.75% to $7.36, outpacing Bitcoin's consolidation, with a 22% monthly gain.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209037-chainlink-shows-growth/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Chainlink&#8217;s price rises 2.75% to $7.36, outpacing Bitcoin&#8217;s consolidation, with a 22% monthly gain.</em></li>



<li><em>Whales collect $192.2 million in LINK, while Chainlink ranks among top 5 most active GitHub assets, hinting at further growth.</em></li>



<li><em>LINK eyes a rebound to retest $8.47 highs, with $9.46 presenting a formidable challenge, as technicals and accumulation bolster its potential.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Amidst the ongoing struggle of the bulls to reignite a bullish trend in the markets, Bitcoin (BTC) remains ensnared within a stagnant range. However, an intriguing twist unfolds as altcoins take center stage, with Chainlink leading the charge in a surging bullish momentum.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-1024x576.png" alt="Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales" class="wp-image-209053" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-448.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales 15"></a></figure></div>


<p>LINK&#8217;s price currently demonstrates a 7% surge in two days, reaching $7.34 while boasting a market capitalization of $3.95 billion. Impressively, despite the broader crypto market&#8217;s consolidation, <a href="https://coincu.com/204614-chainlink-surge-in-price-over-22/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">LINK</a> has soared over 22% in the past month, drawing attention from major market players.</p>



<p>Of particular interest is the consistent accumulation of LINK by both shark and whale addresses amidst the coin&#8217;s persistent fluctuations. The LINK price has repeatedly encountered resistance, just shy of the $10 mark, since the rally setback in May 2022. While various altcoins have made strides in recovering their positions, Chainlink steadfastly trades within the $6 to $8 range. Notably, heightened trading volume indicates an impending surge on the horizon.</p>



<p>Noteworthy developments on the technical front include <a href="https://coincu.com/203471-chainlink-new-protocol-is-now-live/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Chainlink</a>&#8216;s robust activity on GitHub this summer, elevating it to the top 5 most actively developed assets. Meanwhile, significant holders, colloquially known as whales and sharks, wielding 100K-10M LINK have amassed their largest reserves since December 2022. Their acquisition surpasses $192.2 million worth of LINK in under a month, according to <a href="https://app.santiment.net/charts?settings=%7B%22slug%22%3A%22chainlink%22%2C%22ticker%22%3A%22LINK%22%2C%22from%22%3A%222022-08-06T07%3A00%3A01.436Z%22%2C%22to%22%3A%222023-08-07T06%3A59%3A59.436Z%22%7D&amp;widgets=%5B%7B%22widget%22%3A%22HolderDistributionCombinedBalanceWidget%22%2C%22wm%22%3A%5B%22%5B3%3Bpercent_of_holders_distribution_combined_balance%3B100k_to_1M%3B1M_to_10M%5D%22%2C%22dev_activity%22%2C%22price_usd%22%5D%2C%22whm%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wax%22%3A%5B0%2C1%2C2%5D%2C%22wpax%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wc%22%3A%5B%22%23FFCB47%22%2C%22%238358FF%22%2C%22%230d461e%22%5D%2C%22ws%22%3A%7B%221%22%3A%7B%22transform%22%3A%7B%22type%22%3A%22moving_average%22%2C%22movingAverageBase%22%3A14%7D%2C%22interval%22%3A%227d%22%2C%22node%22%3A%22area%22%7D%2C%222%22%3A%7B%22node%22%3A%22bar%22%2C%22interval%22%3A%221h%22%7D%7D%7D%5D" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Santiment</a>.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-scaled.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="664" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-1024x664.jpeg" alt="Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales" class="wp-image-209044" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-1024x664.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-300x194.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-768x498.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-1536x996.jpeg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-2048x1327.jpeg 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-750x486.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/F25GprebsAAkKVu-1140x739.jpeg 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales 16"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Source: Santiment</em></figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Projections suggest that the LINK price, previously rejected near interim highs of approximately $8.47, is poised for a rebound and a retest of these levels in the coming days, underpinned by bullish indicators. Beyond this lies a substantial hurdle at $9.46, an obstacle unbroken for over a year. With Chainlink&#8217;s ascending development trajectory and heightened accumulation, the altcoin&#8217;s journey toward renewed highs seems promising.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-1024x620.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="620" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-1024x620.png" alt="Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales" class="wp-image-209047" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-1024x620.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-300x182.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-768x465.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-1536x931.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-2048x1241.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-750x454.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-445-1140x691.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Chainlink Shows Growth With 7% Gain Thanks To Big Whales 17"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">LINK price chart. <em>Source: TradingView</em></figcaption></figure></div>


<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209037-chainlink-shows-growth/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-449-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Banks Navigate &#8216;Challenges&#8217; as CBDC Dreams Encounter Public Skepticism</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209030-russian-banks-navigate-challenges-as-cbdc-dreams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Association of Russian Banks (ARB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russian banks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Key Points: Russia&#8217;s largest banking association, the Association of Russian Banks (ARB), has voiced concerns and sought clarification from the Central Bank regarding Moscow&#8217;s plans for a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC). The ARB&#8217;s stance reflects public skepticism and uncertainty surrounding the digital ruble&#8217;s introduction. In response to the Central Bank&#8217;s ongoing collaboration with multiple [&#8230;]<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209030-russian-banks-navigate-challenges-as-cbdc-dreams/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Russia&#8217;s largest banking association, ARB, seeks clarity on Moscow&#8217;s CBDC plans. </em></li>



<li><em>Public skepticism arises as citizens express wariness towards the digital ruble. </em></li>



<li><em>ARB urges Central Bank to address key questions, emphasizing transparency and impact.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Russia&#8217;s largest banking association, the<a href="https://arb.ru/en/" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://arb.ru/en/" rel="noreferrer noopener"> Association of Russian Banks (ARB)</a>, has voiced concerns and sought clarification from the Central Bank regarding Moscow&#8217;s plans for a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC). </strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442-1024x538.png" alt="russian-banks-navigate-challenges-as-cbdc-dreams" class="wp-image-209035" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-442.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Russian Banks Navigate &#039;Challenges&#039; as CBDC Dreams Encounter Public Skepticism 18"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The ARB&#8217;s stance reflects public skepticism and uncertainty surrounding the digital ruble&#8217;s introduction.</p>



<p>In response to the Central Bank&#8217;s ongoing collaboration with multiple commercial banks for a real-world pilot of the digital ruble, the ARB has issued a letter with a request for clarification on key aspects related to the CBDC.</p>



<p>The ARB highlighted that Russian citizens are &#8220;wary&#8221; of the digital ruble&#8217;s implementation, echoing sentiments shared by consumers of financial services. The association&#8217;s letter also emphasized the need to prevent the imposition of a mandatory digital ruble wallet for citizens, while urging the Central Bank to limit potential tariff increases by digital ruble operators.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-style-default"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="427" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-1024x427.png" alt="russian-banks-navigate-challenges-as-cbdc-dreams" class="wp-image-209038" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-1024x427.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-300x125.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-768x320.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-1536x641.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-2048x854.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-750x313.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-444-1140x476.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Russian Banks Navigate &#039;Challenges&#039; as CBDC Dreams Encounter Public Skepticism 19"><figcaption>Russian Banks Navigate 'Challenges' as CBDC Dreams Encounter Public Skepticism 20</figcaption></figure>



<p>The ARB&#8217;s communication further outlines a series of fundamental questions that the Central Bank is called upon to address. These questions include the nature of the digital ruble (whether it is a &#8220;third form of money&#8221; or a &#8220;non-cash currency&#8221;), the compensation to banks for providing CBDC access, the obligations of banks to participate in the project, and the required infrastructure-related changes.</p>



<p>Oleg Sysuev, the CEO of Alfa Bank, expressed that the legal nature of the digital ruble remains unclear. As Central Bank Digital Currencies are a relatively recent development on a global scale, he highlighted the unique position of the Russian banking system as it navigates the uncharted territory of CBDCs. Sysuev emphasized the need for comprehensive answers to the many questions arising from the digital ruble&#8217;s introduction.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209030-russian-banks-navigate-challenges-as-cbdc-dreams/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/On-White-6-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Preparing To Support BEP20 Network Upgrade &#038; Hard Fork</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/209011-binance-preparing-to-support-network-upgrade/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BEP20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB smart chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum virtual machine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EVM]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=209011</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Binance supports the BNB Smart Chain upgrade on August 10 with a temporary token suspension.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209011-binance-preparing-to-support-network-upgrade/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Binance supports the BNB Smart Chain upgrade on August 10 with a temporary token suspension.</em></li>



<li><em>Trading remains unaffected; technical aspects are managed by Binance.</em></li>



<li><em>No new tokens; deposits and withdrawals resume post-stability confirmation.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In an announcement <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-support-the-bnb-smart-chain-bep20-network-upgrade-hard-fork-81b4b634c80c47fea8cffd1e1dfa7998" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">addressed</a> to the users, Binance has revealed its plans to back the upcoming BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) network upgrade and subsequent hard fork.binance-preparing-to-support-bep20-network-upgrade-amp-hard-fork.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-1024x576.png" alt="Binance Preparing To Support BEP20 Network Upgrade &amp; Hard Fork" class="wp-image-209033" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-1536x864.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-441.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Binance Preparing To Support BEP20 Network Upgrade &amp; Hard Fork 21"></a></figure></div>


<p>This development is set to transpire at the block height of 30,720,096, estimated around August 10 at 02:00 (UTC). To facilitate the process, the suspension of token deposits and withdrawals on the BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) will initiate approximately on August 10 at 01:45 (UTC).</p>



<p>Formerly recognized as Binance Smart Chain, the BNB Smart Chain is an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)-compatible platform designed for executing general-purpose smart contracts. As a Layer 1 (L1) base layer within the broader <a href="https://coincu.com/202608-bnb-chain-launches-hackvolution-event/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BNB Chain</a> ecosystem, it has garnered renown for its expeditious transaction speeds and economical transaction fees.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s vital to acknowledge that despite the network upgrade and hard fork, trading for tokens accessible on the BNB Smart Chain will remain unaffected. The enhancement is slated for the aforementioned block height, though the specified time serves as a mere estimate for user reference.</p>



<p>With users&#8217; convenience in mind, Binance will oversee all necessary technical aspects for a seamless transition. Importantly, the upgrade will not lead to the creation of new tokens.</p>



<p>Upon confirming the stability of the upgraded network, Binance will reopen token deposits and withdrawals for the BNB Smart Chain. No additional notifications will be issued to users regarding this matter.</p>



<p>This step by <a href="https://coincu.com/208056-binances-encountered-a-zero-transfer-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a> underscores the exchange&#8217;s commitment to technological progress, ensuring its platform remains at the forefront of efficiency and innovation. Recently, the exchange has <a href="https://coincu.com/208211-binance-reaches-150-million-users/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">shown</a> its extraordinary durability and development by achieving the astonishing milestone of 150 million registered users.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/209011-binance-preparing-to-support-network-upgrade/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/image-440-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
