<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:36:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Targets 1M Users at Launch as Twitter Wavers on Verification</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluesky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jack dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252205</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Targets 1M Users at Launch as Twitter Wavers on Verification</a></p>
<p>Bluesky allows users to use domain names as handles to help achieve decentralized verification and give users more control over their identity.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Targets 1M Users at Launch as Twitter Wavers on Verification</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Targets 1M Users at Launch as Twitter Wavers on Verification</a></p>
<p>Bluesky, a social media platform created by former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a> boss <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jack-dorsey/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jack Dorsey</a>, has gained significant traction even before its official launch. The official Bluesky Twitter account has more than 252k followers without a solid protocol to showcase to the users. Nevertheless, the Bluesky application has been downloaded more than 245k times by iPhone users according to data provided from Data.ai.</p>
<p>After Musk acquired Twitter late last year for a whopping $44 billion, Dorsey increased his focus on Bluesky which has since developed AT protocol, a social networking technology. The Bluesky began making headlines after hiring former Zcash blockchain developer and contributor Jay Graber as the Chief Executive Officer. Additionally, the social platform announced about 30k signups for the waitlist in just two days.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the social engineering protocol has been accepting invites to the private beta and recently announced the launch of its Android version.</p>
<h2>Can Bluesky Outperform Twitter?</h2>
<p>Built as an alternative to Twitter, Bluesky is on a mission to disrupt the Musk-backed platform and attract Web3 enthusiasts. Twitter has more than 200 million monetizable daily active users. The platform recently eliminated the free blue check verification mark for a monthly fee of about $8. The move significantly disrupted the global Twitter community that had a challenging time deconstructing fake and real accounts.</p>
<p>Moreover, media houses, journalists, artists, and other prominent people significantly relied on Twitter’s free blue check verification mark for notability and authenticity. Without blue check verification, Twitter users are compelled to blindly search for accounts representing public figures and hope it is not impersonation.</p>
<p>“I’m going to continue to browse Twitter to the extent I can as long as other people in the tech community are still using it, but will have to take everything I read there with an even bigger grain of salt than I did previously because I can’t easily verify that an account representing a public figure or media outlet is actually from that person or institution,” Anita Ramaswamy, a technology and finance opinion columnist at Reuters, <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/twitter-ends-legacy-blue-checks-222939614.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Bluesky on the other hand came up with a unique way of making sure only verified accounts run under prominent naming. Notably, Bluesky allows users to use domain names as handles to help achieve decentralized verification and give users more control over their identity.</p>
<p>“Domain name handles help you determine which accounts are authentic based on the website they&#8217;re associated with. For example, the Financial Times, whose website is ft.com, can use the handle “@ft.com” to verify itself as the official account,” Graber explained.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Bluesky allows users to keep the same domain handle even after switching services.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/">Jack Dorsey-Backed Bluesky Targets 1M Users at Launch as Twitter Wavers on Verification</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jack-dorsey-bluesky-1m-users-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>McDonald’s Releases Q1 2023 Results that Beat Earnings &amp; Revenue Estimates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mcd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mcd stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mcdonald's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mcdonald's stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/">McDonald&#8217;s Releases Q1 2023 Results that Beat Earnings &#038; Revenue Estimates</a></p>
<p>Leading hamburger purveyor McDonald's experienced earnings growth for Q1 2023 despite sporting a pricier menu. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/">McDonald&#8217;s Releases Q1 2023 Results that Beat Earnings &#038; Revenue Estimates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/">McDonald&#8217;s Releases Q1 2023 Results that Beat Earnings &#038; Revenue Estimates</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mcdonalds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">McDonald&#8217;s Corporation</a> (NYSE: MCD) has published its Q1 2023 <a href="https://corporate.mcdonalds.com/corpmcd/investors/financial-information.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings results</a> which beat the consensus estimate. For the year&#8217;s first quarter, the fast food restaurant chain pulled in revenue of $5.9 billion versus the $5.59 billion expected by analysts. In addition, the prominent Chicago-based company realized earnings per share (EPS) of $2.63 adjusted versus $2.33 expected.</p>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s also experienced an increase in US customer traffic despite hiking the price of its products to remain competitive in a challenging economy. US traffic surged for the third straight quarter, which bucked the industry trend of waning traffic amid pricier menus. The McDonald&#8217;s factor is contrary to the industry trend because its meals are comparatively cheaper than those of its contemporaries. During economic downtime, consumers tend to patronize more affordable options. This trend considerably helped the fast food chain.</p>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s shares rose 1% in pre-market trading.</p>
<p>Beyond the US, McDonald&#8217;s also experienced commendable sales for Q1 2023, with markets in Europe and Australia beating estimates. According to reports, these internationally operated markets surpassed StreetAccount estimates of 8.5% same-store sales growth.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, McDonald&#8217;s international developmental licensed markets segment in countries like China and Japan surpassed the 10.5% same-store sales expectations.</p>
<h2>Other Noteworthy Information from McDonald&#8217;s Q1 2023 Outing</h2>
<p>All three McDonald&#8217;s divisions, including the US, International Operated Markets, and International Developed Licensed Markets, reported same-store sales growth of 12.6%. Elsewhere, the fast food chain reported a Q1 net income of $1.8 billion, or $2.45 per share. These figures represented an increase from the $1.1 billion, or $1.48 per share; the multinational food and real estate company made the year before.</p>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s also stressed that its reported $2.63 earnings per share excludes $180 million in restructuring charges and other items. Meanwhile, the company&#8217;s net sales grew by 4% to $5.9 billion for the period ended March 31st.</p>
<p>Commenting on McDonald&#8217;s first-quarter performance, company President and Chief Executive Officer Chris Kempczinski said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our strong first quarter results demonstrate that our Accelerating the Arches strategy is working, as comparable sales grew 12.6% through a healthy balance of strategic menu price increases and positive traffic growth.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the CEO of the world&#8217;s largest hamburger chain also added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Running great restaurants is fundamental to our business momentum. We have refocused on operational excellence through our global Performance and Customer Excellence (PACE) initiative, and we&#8217;ve seen significant customer satisfaction improvement around the world. Amidst a challenging operating environment, customer demand for McDonald&#8217;s Brand remains strong.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>McDonald&#8217;s Reports Quarterly Earnings in Tech-Dominated Week</h2>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s latest quarterly report comes amid slated releases by several corporations in various industries. Last week was dominated by the earnings of household names in the global banking sector, and this week sees <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-earnings-q1-reports/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tech stocks take center stage</a>. Investors will be paying close attention to tech stocks as cues regarding the health of the economy. The reason is that the tech industry appears set to chart a new path for the global economy amid the banking crisis. Furthermore, artificial intelligence and its surging popularity have raised the stakes for the tech space.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/">McDonald&#8217;s Releases Q1 2023 Results that Beat Earnings &#038; Revenue Estimates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/mcdonalds-q1-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FinTech Firm Klarna Overhauls App with TikTok-like Discovery Feed amid AI Hype</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 13:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[klarna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tiktok]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/">FinTech Firm Klarna Overhauls App with TikTok-like Discovery Feed amid AI Hype</a></p>
<p>Klarna seeks to leverage the power of AI for offering curated shopping experiences to customers while also introducing TikTok features and new tools for advertisers. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/">FinTech Firm Klarna Overhauls App with TikTok-like Discovery Feed amid AI Hype</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/">FinTech Firm Klarna Overhauls App with TikTok-like Discovery Feed amid AI Hype</a></p>
<p>The artificial intelligence (AI) revolution is taking over and has only accelerated over the past few months. As a result, companies are making quick pivots to hop on the trend and adopt the prowess of this new tech revolution. Recently, fintech firm Klarna announced a massive redesign of its app while adding an AI-powered TikTok-inspired discovery feed. Besides, it also introduces customized shops for social media content creators, along with the ability to sell second-hand goods.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, April 25, the Swedish fintech firm said that the design overhaul is to help users find the items that they want by using some advanced AI recommendation algorithms. This would also help the merchants target their customers more effectively.</p>
<p>Based on the shopping behaviors of the shoppers and the brand they like, the AI will build a personal profile for shoppers. Thus, the shoppers shall receive recommendations from Klarna&#8217;s 500,000 retailers including some of the top players like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nike</a>, H&amp;M, and others. Fintech platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/klarna/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Klarna</a> currently caters to more than 150,000 users globally.</p>
<p>David Sandstrom, Klarna’s chief marketing officer, said that the decision comes following inspiration from Chinese tech firms. Top Chinese shopping platforms have been leveraging the power of algorithm driven-shopping. Sandstrom <a href="https://worldnewsera.com/news/finance/fintech-firm-klarna-overhauls-its-app-with-a-tiktok-like-discovery-feed-as-a-i-hype-swirls/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In China, a couple of years ago, 90% of transactions started with a search. Nowadays, less than 50% of purchases start with a search because recommendations are so tailored to them. Our ambition is to basically offer people products and brands before they knew they wanted them”.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Klarna Taking Inspiration from TikTok and ChatGPT AI</h2>
<p>Short video-sharing platform TikTok has been leading currently in terms of introducing new features and almost every other competitor wants to copy them. Furthermore, its advanced targeting features have made TikTok the preferred choice of e-commerce business to advertise on the platform.</p>
<p>Kalrna is looking to make a similar move, however, Sandstrom admits the fact that it is no close to being as sophisticated as TikTok. “It would be naïve to compare us to TikTok’s recommendation engine. It would be a blatant lie to say we’re close to that,” he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/25/klarna-overhauls-app-with-tiktok-like-discovery-feed-amid-ai-buzz.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>. “But we have the prerequisites to do that.”</p>
<p>But like other tech firms, Klarna doesn&#8217;t want to hold itself back from incorporating AI software to tailor its content in a much better way for its users. Previously, Klarna also launched the ability to integrate OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT into its service along with a plugin that allows users to ask the popular chatbot platform for shopping inspiration.</p>
<p>But instead of relying on AI alone, Klarna looks to personalize its services further and recently launched the &#8220;Ask Klarna&#8221; feature. This allows shoppers to chat with or seeks video advice from specialists.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Klarna is launching a tool that will allow content creators to set up their own storefronts while promoting items from brands with whom they have affiliate deals. Dubbed &#8220;Creator Shop&#8221;, Klarna will launch this service in the US.</p>
<p>Besides, Klarna also plans to launch a self-service tool for advertisers dubbed “Ads Manager,” which will allow marketers to track paid product listings. With advertising, Klarna is planning to reduce its dependence on fees from merchants.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/">FinTech Firm Klarna Overhauls App with TikTok-like Discovery Feed amid AI Hype</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-hype-fintech-klarna/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>California Lawmaker Introduces Bill to Incorporate DAOs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 13:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAOs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252161</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/">California Lawmaker Introduces Bill to Incorporate DAOs</a></p>
<p>With Matt Haney taking a very bold step that is backed by the industry, seeing DAOs function as businesses will be a matter of time.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/">California Lawmaker Introduces Bill to Incorporate DAOs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/">California Lawmaker Introduces Bill to Incorporate DAOs</a></p>
<p>A California lawmaker Matt Haney has introduced Assembly Bill 1229 which seeks to re-engineer and expand the state’s corporate to include Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAO). As <a href="https://decrypt.co/137767/daos-could-get-official-standing-under-california-law" target="_blank">reported</a> by Decrypt, the proposed Bill, if passed, will enable DAOs, blockchain networks and smart contracts to register as businesses in the state.</p>
<p>This registration will enable the protocols to function like a regular business with the ability to file taxes and be compliant with other state and federal regulations. Per the report, the proposed Bill has received backing from industry giant Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) as well as the Crypto Council for Innovation.</p>
<p>While the pace at which regulations are being approached at the Federal level as it concerns the digital currency ecosystem is slow, many states are notably pushing forth new momentum with respect to integrating cryptocurrencies. California has been particularly progressive in this regard and while there is optimism with respect to Bill 1229, the first order will be to educate other AssemblyMembers and bring them up to speed about the technology underpinning DAOs.</p>
<p>“Our goal is to educate our colleagues on blockchain basics, California corporations, and the workings of Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAOs),” a spokesperson for AssemblyMember Matt Haney revealed to Decrypt. “By establishing a legal framework around DAOs, we can create certainty, legitimize this organizational type, and ensure appropriate taxation in California.”</p>
<p>As a state that is positively tilted toward technology, the goal remains to formulate and pass laws that will help its evolution in no small measure.</p>
<p>“We have to make sure that our laws are keeping up with technology,” the spokesperson said. “For us, we’ve seen only three paths forward, environmental tech, biotech, and we think that Web3 needs to be firmly rooted in California. And that’s what this bill is about.”</p>
<h2>California Lawmaker Considers DAOs and Web 3.0 as the Future</h2>
<p>The world has seen a number of technological breakthroughs over time and despite the resistance to crypto and its underlying technology, California Lawmaker believes DAOs and the broader Web 3.0 is the future of innovative technology.</p>
<p>“Whatever you call this new technology—blockchain, web3, or crypto—we know that it’s the future of tech,” Assemblymember Haney said in a statement. “It would be devastating to both our economy and our identity as a state to lose California’s place as the world’s tech leader because our laws are not keeping up with the times.”</p>
<p>The laws are even more needed at a time when the clamor from the industry has reached a whole new pedestal with growing calls for regulation. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) has recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-action-sec-regulatory/">sued</a> the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for keeping a long silence in providing clear guidelines for the industry.</p>
<p>With Matt Haney taking a very bold step that is backed by the industry, seeing DAOs function as businesses will be a matter of time.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/">California Lawmaker Introduces Bill to Incorporate DAOs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/california-bill-daos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PepsiCo Reports Q1 2023 Earnings, $17.85B Revenue Beats Wall Street Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coca cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pep stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepsi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepsico]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepsico stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252149</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/">PepsiCo Reports Q1 2023 Earnings, $17.85B Revenue Beats Wall Street Expectations</a></p>
<p>Beverage giant PepsiCo raised its full-year outlook following its commendable Q1 2023 performance, beating analysts' expectations.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/">PepsiCo Reports Q1 2023 Earnings, $17.85B Revenue Beats Wall Street Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/">PepsiCo Reports Q1 2023 Earnings, $17.85B Revenue Beats Wall Street Expectations</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/pepsico/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PepsiCo</a> (NASDAQ: PEP) has raised its 2023 yearly outlook following its better-than-expected <a href="https://investor.pepsico.com/docs/default-source/investors/q1-2023/q1-2023-earnings-release_wfvmt94lzqbm92aw.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q1 performance</a>. On Tuesday, the multinational food, snack, and beverage corporation posted earnings and revenue that surpassed expectations. For the first quarter of the year, PepsiCo reported $17.85 billion in revenue compared to the $17.22 billion analysts expected. In addition, the New York-based corporation reported earnings per share (EPS) of $1.50 adjusted versus Wall Street’s projected $1.39.</p>
<p>In Q1 2023, PepsiCo realized $1.93 billion in net income, or $1.40 a share. However, the net income paled in comparison year-over-year (YoY) to the $4.26 billion, or $3.06 a share, realized in 2022.</p>
<p>PepsiCo’s beverage business volume increased by 1% in the last quarter, while the food segment declined by 3%. Altogether, all the company’s categories sustained a 2% drawdown in Q1, while prices surged 16% overall.</p>
<h2>PepsiCo CEO Content with Q1 2023 Results Believes Company Is on the Right Track</h2>
<p>PepsiCo Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Ramon Laguarta expressed satisfaction with the company’s latest quarterly performance. As Laguarta put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are very pleased with our performance and business momentum as our categories and geographies remained resilient during the first quarter.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The CEO also touched on PepsiCo’s increased full-year 2023 guidance, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Given our strong start to the year, we now expect our full-year 2023 organic revenue to increase 8% (previously 6%) and core constant currency EPS to increase 9% (previously 8%).”</p></blockquote>
<p>Laguarta reiterated his belief that PepsiCo is on the track for sustained success in a dynamic business environment. “Our results demonstrate that the investments we have made to become an even Faster, even Stronger, and even Better organization by Winning with pep+ are laying the foundation for durable and sustainable growth,” said he.</p>
<p>The PepsiCo CEO concluded that the company remains committed to its “strategic agenda” and looks to keep investing in core resources. These include people, brands, supply chains, go-to-market systems, and digitization initiatives.</p>
<p>Earlier in the month, PepsiCo embarked on an agenda to sport ‘greener’ and more eco-friendly product packaging by 2025. According to the company behind the popular Pepsi soft drink, 100% of its product packaging will be recyclable in two years. In addition, PepsiCo said packaging for its beverage and snack brands will be compostable, biodegradable, or reusable by 2025. Claiming this goal is “not easy,” PepsiCo Foods North America CEO Steven Williams said the company remains “fully committed to it.”</p>
<h2>Coca-Cola Q1 Performance</h2>
<p>PepsiCo’s latest quarterly report comes on the heels of beverage rival <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coca-cola/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coca-Cola’s</a> (NYSE: KO) Q1 2023 outing. Less than 24 hours ago, the company behind the Coke brand <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coca-cola-q1-2023-results/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">also beat estimates</a> and doubled down on its yearly outlook.</p>
<p>For the first quarter of the year, Coca-Cola pulled in revenue of $10.96 billion adjusted compared to the $10.8 billion analysts expected. In addition, the beverage giant reported a $3.11 billion, or 72 cents per share in quarterly net income attributable to shareholders.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/">PepsiCo Reports Q1 2023 Earnings, $17.85B Revenue Beats Wall Street Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pepsico-q1-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Backs NFT ‘Stand with Crypto’ Campaign</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 12:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Backs NFT &#8216;Stand with Crypto&#8217; Campaign</a></p>
<p>Coinbase emphasized that all proceedings related to Stand with Crypto NFT collection launched through ZORA will be donated to vetted organizations.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Backs NFT &#8216;Stand with Crypto&#8217; Campaign</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Backs NFT &#8216;Stand with Crypto&#8217; Campaign</a></p>
<p>The biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> has recently filed a lawsuit against top financial regulators Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). The move comes after months of embittered relations between the two parties over SEC&#8217;s stringent regulatory policies for all companies dealing with crypto. As the crypto exchange chooses the legal path to get regulatory clarity, Coinbase CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> minted an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> recently and asked the community to &#8220;Stand with Crypto&#8221;.</p>
<p>Coinbase&#8217;s CEO <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1650664062848753664" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweeted</a> recently about minting a Non-Fungible Token and asking everyone to stand together in unity among the crypto community to seek a feasible crypto mandate. Presently, more than 11,247 NFTs have been minted in allegiance to the exchange&#8217;s recent undertaking.</p>
<p>As per <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/228065/coinbase-stand-with-crypto-campaign-sec" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">details</a>, the NFT is featuring a blue shield that represents a cumulative stand to protect and encourage the crypto industry. The “Stand with Crypto” is an NFT holding with no utility or value. Coinbase emphasized that all proceedings related to Stand with Crypto NFT collection launched through ZORA will be donated to vetted organizations. But this will be completed through a crypto advocacy round.</p>
<p>In the lawsuit, the company has requested the commission to publicly provide answers to an old petition about regulation of the crypto space. The petition that was filed in July 2022, asks about the commission&#8217;s proposal and assumed rules to administer the regulation of securities. Paul Grewal, who is the Chief Legal Officer of Coinbase, claimed that the SEC should be answerable to petitions by legislation and should answer petitions in a decent time.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the commission hasn&#8217;t replied to any inquiries since July.</p>
<p>Armstrong&#8217;s minted NFT image is of a shield on a Zora marketplace. Following the minting of NFT, the company official has not taken the next step to show solidarity towards the movement, which is the addition of a shielded emoji with the Twitter name.</p>
<p>Coinbase hasn&#8217;t been responsive to the queries of media outlets seeking clarity on whether the Stand with Crypto campaign has been designed by the exchange or is unassociated with it.</p>
<p>Coinbase&#8217;s request in July did not receive a reply, moreover, SEC actively reopened custody and exchange regulations to specifically convey that they apply to virtual assets. The SEC has also proactively been involved in multiple enforcement activities against crypto organizations, which obviously includes an investigation on Coinbase.</p>
<p>Coinbase has had a long past of trying to impact US policy with massive lobbying campaigns. Recently, in February, it announced an effort to promote the crypto advocacy community and share resources to make their voices heard.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Backs NFT &#8216;Stand with Crypto&#8217; Campaign</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-nft-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ByteDance Pushes Lemon8 in US as TikTok Faces Possible Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 12:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bytedance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lemon8]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tiktok]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/">ByteDance Pushes Lemon8 in US as TikTok Faces Possible Ban</a></p>
<p>Lemon8 growth in the US could also get the attention of US regulators, especially due to its relationship with ByteDance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/">ByteDance Pushes Lemon8 in US as TikTok Faces Possible Ban</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/">ByteDance Pushes Lemon8 in US as TikTok Faces Possible Ban</a></p>
<p>Chinese tech giant and TikTok developer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bytedance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ByteDance</a> is pushing another social media app, Lemon8, into the US market as TikTok faces a possible ban. The popular short video app is under pressure in the US due to concerns over the handling of users’ data. Already, more than 24 states in the country have banned TikTok on government-issued devices. US lawmakers have referred to laws that allow the Chinese government to secretly demand data from Chinese companies and citizens for intelligence-gathering operations. Last month, Congress <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tiktok-ceo-us-congress-security-threat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">questioned</a> TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew on the app’s ability to operate independently of influences on its parent company.</p>
<p>Hence, they are worried that ByteDance may give out sensitive user data to the Chinese government. Amid the intense pressure of a possible ban of TikTok in the US, ByteDance has devised a business strategy by pushing Lemon8.</p>
<p>Notably, Lemon8 is a combination of Instagram and Pinterest and was first rolled out in Japan in 2020. In March, the tech company invited US creators onto the new platform ahead of its official launch in the country. According to the message sent to creators, ByteDance asked that they become “launching creators” on Lemon8.</p>
<h2>ByteDance Is Pushing Lemon8 as a Potential Alternative to TikTok</h2>
<p>A senior fellow for emerging tech at the German Marshall Fund, Lindsay Gorman, said it appears the technology company is introducing Lemon8 as a potential alternative to TikTok.</p>
<blockquote><p>“You could see this as the competitive move of a company that’s trying to expand into different consumer markets and segments with more image-based and longer-form written content as opposed to only short-form videos.</p></blockquote>
<p>As TikTok is about to bid farewell to the US market, the possible alternative app has gained momentum and increased adoption. Analytics firm data.ai <a href="https://www.data.ai/en/apps/ios/top/downloads/united-states/lifestyle/ios-phone/?topchart=last-month" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shows</a> that Lemon8 jumped 693 positions to become the second most downloaded lifestyle app in the US in the last 30 days. At its current position, the ByteDance app pushed Zillow Real Estate &amp; Rentals down and stands next to Pinterest, which tops the chart. Also, Apptopia revealed that the new social media app had garnered 17 million downloads globally since its launch.</p>
<p>A senior advisor at the Center for Strategic and International Studies, Glenn Gerstell, explained that some of the algorithms Lemon8 uses are similar to or the same as TikTok’s. In his speech, this process will make both apps popular as they feed users what they want to see.</p>
<p>Lemon8 growth in the US could also get the attention of US regulators, especially due to its relationship with ByteDance. The analysts stated that developing an app to replace TikTok is not the solution to the challenges ByteDance is facing in the US. However, Gorman and Gerstell agreed that TikTok content creators could fall back on Lemon8 if the US eventually bans the short video-sharing app stateside.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/">ByteDance Pushes Lemon8 in US as TikTok Faces Possible Ban</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bytedance-lemon8-us-tiktok-ban/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fox Corp Loses Nearly $1B Announcing Tucker Carlson Departure </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 12:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fox]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fox corporation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/">Fox Corp Loses Nearly $1B Announcing Tucker Carlson Departure </a></p>
<p>Fox Corporation stock suffered a massive dent in value less than a day after announcing the departure of longtime TV host Tucker Carlson. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/">Fox Corp Loses Nearly $1B Announcing Tucker Carlson Departure </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/">Fox Corp Loses Nearly $1B Announcing Tucker Carlson Departure </a></p>
<p>Shares of Fox Corporation (NASDAQ: FOXA) <a href="https://www.businessinsider.in/stock-market/news/fox-corporation-sheds-930-million-in-market-value-after-announcing-tucker-carlson-is-leaving-the-news-network/articleshow/99739557.cms" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">declined</a> 5% on Monday following <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/04/24/media/tucker-carlson-fox-news/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Tucker Carlson’s exit</a>. The mass media company previously announced that Carlson was leaving the Fox News network for his involvement in a string of controversies.</p>
<p>During the early trading session, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-news-corporation-fox-stock-merger/">Fox Corporation</a> shed nearly a billion ($962 million) of its market value. However, the media syndicate’s Class A recovered marginally to trade at $32.65 at 1:32 pm Eastern Time (ET).</p>
<p>Fox and Tucker Carlson parted ways just days after the media group settled a mammoth $787 million Dominion lawsuit. The settlement is the largest of its kind in an American defamation case.</p>
<p>Dominion Voting Systems accused Fox News of disseminating election fabrications in the lawsuit. The electronic voting company also claimed that Carlson permitted debunked election-fraud claims regarding Dominion to air on his popular TV show. In addition to disseminating election lies on the “Tucker Carlson Tonight” show, the conservative political commentator also allegedly questioned the plausibility of Dominion’s denial in private messages. These messages, which emerged in legal filings, also exposed Carlson disparaging colleagues.</p>
<p>Another lawsuit filed in March against Carlson by his former top booker, Abby Grossberg, accused him of stoking sexism on his show. In addition to promoting a hostile working environment, Grossberg claimed that Fox coerced her testimony in the Dominion lawsuit. According to the TV producer, the network’s lawyers pressured her into providing misleading testimony in the case.</p>
<h2>Fox News Announced the Departure of Tucker Carlson despite His Raving Popularity</h2>
<p>Although Carlson had been one of Fox News’ most popular hosts, thanks to his widely watched politically charged TV show, the channel announced his departure on Monday, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“FOX News Media and Tucker Carlson have agreed to part ways. We thank him for his service to the network as a host and, prior to that, as a contributor.”</p></blockquote>
<p>An inside source claimed that at least three senior Fox Corporation executives decided to drop Carlson on Friday evening. These included Fox Corp Chairman Rupert Murdoch, his son, and Fox Corp chief executive officer Lachlan Murdoch, and Fox News chief executive Suzanne Scott. Meanwhile, Carlson, whose last appearance was Friday on his nighttime show, learned of his ousting via telephone Monday morning. According to a person with inside information, the embattled television personality and his team had spent the weekend crystallizing plans for summer shows.</p>
<p>Carlson had held the Fox News 8 pm time slot for his “Tucker Carlson Tonight” piece since April 2017. The political commentator joined Fox as a contributor in 2009, eventually rising through the ranks to earn his own show. According to the <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/media/2023/04/24/tucker-carlson-leaves-fox-news/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Washington Post</a>, Carlson became the most-watched host in America, averaging 3.32 million total viewers. In addition, the TV host also attracted the most viewers in the coveted 25-54 age demographic.</p>
<p>Fox has yet to officially state a reason for its decision to dismiss Carlson and the show’s executive producer, Fox has yet to state a reason officially. Instead, the company said it would fill the 8 pm hour slot with a rotation of personalities until it names a new TV host.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/">Fox Corp Loses Nearly $1B Announcing Tucker Carlson Departure </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fox-1b-tucker-carlson-departure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Popular Tech Investor Chamath Palihapitiya Says ‘Crypto Is Dead in America’</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 12:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chamath palihapitiya]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252096</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/">Popular Tech Investor Chamath Palihapitiya Says &#8216;Crypto Is Dead in America&#8217;</a></p>
<p>Chamath Palihapitiya blamed the US regulators for their heavy crackdown recently on the US crypto industry and all associated players. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/">Popular Tech Investor Chamath Palihapitiya Says &#8216;Crypto Is Dead in America&#8217;</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/">Popular Tech Investor Chamath Palihapitiya Says &#8216;Crypto Is Dead in America&#8217;</a></p>
<p>In the latest regulatory developments taking place in the United States, popular tech investor <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/chamath-palihapitiya/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chamath Palihapitiya</a> shared a very cautious move about crypto assets. Over the last few years, Palihapitiya has been sharing bullish views about Bitcoin stating that it has replaced gold and that the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> price would shoot to $200,000.</p>
<h2>Chamath Palihapitiya and His Opinion on Crypto</h2>
<p>During the latest interview on the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WvTTDxMuAis" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">All-In podcast</a>, the tech investor blamed the demise of crypto on US regulators. The regulatory action in the United States has recently turned a lot more aggressive following the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX in November 2022. Since then, the US SEC has been going hammer and tongs after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> chief <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gary Gensler</a> stating that crypto firms should strictly abide by the securities laws.</p>
<p>Interestingly, during his recent testimony, Gary Gensler blamed crypto as the reason behind the recent banking crisis. Of course, it has received a severe backlash from the crypto community. Palihapitiya said: “You had Gensler even blaming the banking crisis on crypto. The United States authorities have firmly pointed their guns at crypto.”</p>
<p>The SEC has been ramping up its enforcement of the crypto industry while alleging that most companies and projects have been selling digital assets as unregistered securities. Earlier this year, the SEC proposed rules that would determine which companies can custody of customers&#8217; digital assets. Referring to the crypto companies facing the regulatory backlash, Palihapitiya said:</p>
<blockquote><p>They “were probably the ones that were the most threatening to the establishment. And they were the ones that, in fairness to the regulators, did push the boundaries more than any other sector of the startup economy. Now they’re paying the price for that. The bill has come due for them.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin at $200,000?</h2>
<p>Chamath Palihapitiya is one of those investors who have been very bullish about the long-term prospects for Bitcoin (BTC). Back in early 2021, just ahead of the mega bull run, Chamath said that the BTC price would rise from $39,000 at the time to $100,000 and then up to $200,000.</p>
<p>However, he didn&#8217;t mention any specific timeline for the same but added: “Five years, 10 years, but it’s going there. And the reason is that every time you see all of this stuff happening, it just reminds you that, wow, our leaders are not as trustworthy and reliable as they used to be.”</p>
<p>By the end of 2021, when BTC was trading close to its all-time high, Palihapitiya said that Bitcoin had effectively replaced gold.</p>
<p>In the latest development, banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a> noted that the BTC price <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-hit-100000-2024-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">can climb</a> all the way to $100,000 adding that the &#8220;crypto winter&#8221; is now over.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/">Popular Tech Investor Chamath Palihapitiya Says &#8216;Crypto Is Dead in America&#8217;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chamath-palihapitiya-crypto-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UBS Stock Falls 2% after Record of Slump in Q1 2023 Net Profit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 10:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit suisse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ubs stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252097</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/">UBS Stock Falls 2% after Record of Slump in Q1 2023 Net Profit</a></p>
<p>The turmoil in the banking ecosystem from the United States as it concerns Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) stirred a ripple effect that was felt in Switzerland.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/">UBS Stock Falls 2% after Record of Slump in Q1 2023 Net Profit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/">UBS Stock Falls 2% after Record of Slump in Q1 2023 Net Profit</a></p>
<p>The shares of Swiss multinational banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ubs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UBS Group AG</a> (SWX: UBSG) are seeing a mild slump today after the firm revealed that its net profit for the first quarter took a significant hit. While still largely profitable, UBS said the net profit for the quarter dropped by 52% over the past year to $1.03 billion.</p>
<p>UBS said the drop in revenue was fueled by the more prolonged US residential mortgage-backed securities litigation matter. The legal tussle cost the firm a total of $660 million in the quarter. While many may see the litigation and its accruing costs as a negative one, UBS CEO Sergio Ermotti believes the case is just about getting set to be closed.</p>
<p>“We are in advanced discussions. Hopefully, we can close this 15-year-old chapter very soon,” he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/25/ubs-q1-2023-results-post-deal-to-buy-credit-suisse.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<p>UBS impressed on some of its key growth metrics for the quarter in consideration of the outlook of the global financial ecosystem in Q1. The Swiss giant said it generated total revenue of $8.75 billion as against the $9.38 billion scored in the year-ago period. However, UBS revealed its operating expenses for the quarter soared from $6.6 billion a year ago to $7.2 billion in the past quarter.</p>
<p>According to Ermotti, the performance of the company in the quarter is “very solid,” a testament to the bank’s ranking as one of the dominant commercial banks in Switzerland and in the European Economic Area (EEA). The company said its Global Wealth Management unit reported as much as $28 billion in new money, an influx that can be described as a vote of confidence from asset managers on the firm’s stability.</p>
<p>UBSG dropped by 2.64% over the past 24 hours and is changing hands at 17.72 Swiss Francs.</p>
<h2>UBS Profit Unhindered by Credit Suisse</h2>
<p>The turmoil in the banking ecosystem from the United States as it concerns Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) stirred a ripple effect that was felt in Switzerland, ending the more than 160-year solvency of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/credit-suisse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Credit Suisse Group AG</a> (SWX: CSGN).</p>
<p>Seeing the harsh bank run Credit Suisse was facing, Swiss regulators <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-shares-deal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">quickly initiated</a> an acquisition of the firm by UBS. In the current performance report, Ermotti noted that it is believed that investors and the bank’s customers understood that UBS is part of the solution to Credit Suisse and not the profit, and as such, its profit was relatively unaffected by the takeover deal.</p>
<p>“We saw some inflows coming from Credit Suisse, but, most importantly, we continue to see even after the transaction, we saw inflows, so the demonstration that our clients believe we are a source of stability,” he said in an interview with CNBC. “We are part of the solution and not part of the problem.”</p>
<p>The takeover is set to be completed by the end of this year and full system absorption is billed for 2-4 years from now.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-franklin-onchain-money-fund/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/">UBS Stock Falls 2% after Record of Slump in Q1 2023 Net Profit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-stock-q1-2023-net-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=PhpRedis metric#hits=4577 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1272436 metric#prefetches=197 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=15 metric#store-hits=203 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=111.82 metric#ms-cache=7101.30 metric#ms-cache-median=0.00 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6,350.7 -->