<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:55:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Flare Inks Partnership with aiPX to Debut New Perpetual Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/flare-aipx-perpetual-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aiPX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/flare-aipx-perpetual-exchange/">Flare Inks Partnership with aiPX to Debut New Perpetual Exchange</a></p>
<p>In addition to its focus on risk management and liquidity solutions, aiPX, the perpetual DEX built on Flare blockchain, offers a range of features designed to enhance the trading experience for users.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/flare-aipx-perpetual-exchange/">Flare Inks Partnership with aiPX to Debut New Perpetual Exchange</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/flare-aipx-perpetual-exchange/">Flare Inks Partnership with aiPX to Debut New Perpetual Exchange</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an exciting development within the blockchain space, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flare</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a data-centric <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/flare-launches-layer-1-oracle-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Layer 1 blockchain</a>, has announced a partnership with aiPX to launch a decentralized non-custodial perpetual exchange on the Flare network. According to a press release shared with Coinspeaker, Flare&#8217;s native network will serve as the underlying infrastructure for aiPX, providing a robust and efficient foundation for the decentralized exchange. </span></p>
<h2><b>Benefits of Flare and aiPX Partnership</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leveraging Flare&#8217;s capabilities, aiPX will ensure that users can connect their wallets seamlessly to the platform, eliminating the need for additional steps or third-party intermediaries. Furthermore, by utilizing Flare&#8217;s native network, aiPX gains access to the blockchain&#8217;s scalability and high transaction throughput. This ensures that users have a quick and efficient trading experience with little to no delays or congestion.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the other hand, aiPX is expected to offer innovative solutions for risk management and liquidity provision. One of the key components enabling this functionality is the integration of Flare Time Series Oracle (FTSO) price feeds. By leveraging FTSO price feeds for collateral calculations and liquidation thresholds, aiPX ensures accurate and reliable data, enabling effective risk management within the platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to its focus on risk management and liquidity solutions, aiPX, the perpetual DEX built on Flare blockchain, offers a range of features designed to enhance the trading experience for users. These features include leverage trading, token swaps, staking for protocol revenue share, and user governance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Remarkably, aiPX will be launching with an initial set of liquidity pools that include WUSDC, WFLR, and WUSDT. These pools provide traders with immediate access to a range of assets, allowing them to begin trading and interacting with the platform from the start. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the project progresses and fresh bridging models are introduced on Flare, more tokens are expected to become available, expanding the options for users and further enhancing the liquidity ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is worth noting that the team behind aiPX has a track record of success in the DeFi space. The team previously developed Takepile, a decentralized perpetual exchange, on the Fantom network. This experience and expertise serve as a strong foundation for aiPX&#8217;s development, ensuring that the team understands the intricacies of building and maintaining a decentralized trading platform.</span></p>
<h2><b>The Rise of Data-Centric Layer 1 Blockchains</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data-centric Layer 1 blockchains have emerged as a crucial component of the blockchain ecosystem. These platforms prioritize the availability and integrity of data, making them ideal for hosting Decentralized Applications (dApps) that rely on accurate and transparent data. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flare, as a data-centric Layer 1 blockchain, aligns perfectly with the goals of the partnership, ensuring a solid foundation for the decentralized non-custodial perpetual exchange. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Recently, the platform </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-atriv-flare-layer-1-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">collaborated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with Atriv to provide the network with Atriv’s no-code NFT platform. The collaboration intends to create a free market in which collectors and digital artists can easily make art and tokenize it.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/flare-aipx-perpetual-exchange/">Flare Inks Partnership with aiPX to Debut New Perpetual Exchange</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Group’s Freshippo Expands Brick and Mortar Presence in China Ahead of Its IPO</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[freshippo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261234</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/">Alibaba Group&#8217;s Freshippo Expands Brick and Mortar Presence in China Ahead of Its IPO</a></p>
<p>Freshippo's expansion comes three months after its parent company Alibaba revealed its restructuring plans.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/">Alibaba Group&#8217;s Freshippo Expands Brick and Mortar Presence in China Ahead of Its IPO</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/">Alibaba Group&#8217;s Freshippo Expands Brick and Mortar Presence in China Ahead of Its IPO</a></p>
<p>Freshippo, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group&#8217;</a>s retail grocery subsidiary, has opened 12 new stores across Mainland China. The stores are strategically located in key cities such as Beijing, Shanghai, and Guangzhou, aiming to cater to the growing demand for high-quality products and exceptional service in the highly competitive grocery market.</p>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://www.media-outreach.com/news/hong-kong/2023/06/30/229896/freshippo-accelerates-expansion-with-same-day-launch-of-12-new-stores-across-8-cities-in-mainland-china/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> on June 30, seven of the newly launched stores feature a new Freshippo logo that offers an extensive range of products, an expanded delivery area, spacious shopping environments, and enhanced customer service.</p>
<p>The grocery company is headquartered in Shanghai and runs more than 300 stores across 27 cities in mainland China. With its unique blend of e-commerce prowess, logistics capabilities, and traditional shopping experiences, Freshippo offers customers the convenience of online ordering with home delivery and the option to visit their physical stores renowned for their high-quality fresh produce, including items like lobsters.</p>
<p>Through the latest expansion, the company aims to cater to the diverse needs of customers, whether they reside in commercial or residential areas through the expansion.</p>
<h2>Freshippo Ranks among Top Ten Chain Stores in China for the First Time</h2>
<p>In addition to the newly launched stores, the company has also introduced five new Freshippo Outlets in Shanghai. These outlets focus on delivering quality products at attractive prices, making them an appealing option for a broader segment of consumers. With these latest additions, the grocery company now operates 68 outlets across 14 cities in Mainland China, solidifying its presence in the retail landscape.</p>
<p>Freshippo&#8217;s expansion comes as China&#8217;s consumer market is witnessing a strong recovery fueled by the increasing demand from young customers, particularly in emerging first-tier cities.</p>
<p>According to a recent Chinese Chain Store &amp; Franchise Association report, Freshippo ranked among the top 10 in 2022 China&#8217;s TOP 100 Chain Stores. The Alibaba-owned company took eighth position among the top 100 chain stores for the first time since its launch and sixth among the leading 100 supermarkets in Mainland China.</p>
<h2>Freshippo Plans to Become a Publicly Traded Company</h2>
<p>Freshippo&#8217;s expansion comes three months after its parent company Alibaba revealed its restructuring plans. The Chinese e-commerce giant divided its company into six business units to revive growth as competition among e-commerce companies heightens in China.</p>
<p>These newly formed units have the flexibility to raise external capital and eventually go public. However, it is worth noting that while Freshippo operates as an independent business under the Alibaba umbrella, it is not part of the six newly formed business groups.</p>
<p>Last month, Alibaba approved an initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) for Freshippo to become a publicly traded company. However, a specific timeline for the offering has not been disclosed.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Freshippo has been actively exploring global sourcing opportunities and forging strategic partnerships to strengthen its supply chain.</p>
<p>On a recent <a href="https://www.alibabagroup.com/en-US/document-1606000993504329728" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">trip to Australia</a> earlier this month, the company engaged with over 40 Australian brands for potential collaboration. The visit was part of Freshippo&#8217;s accelerated import business development strategy for 2023.</p>
<p>During the trip, the Freshippo team targeted Victoria and New South Wales, aiming to establish new partnerships and explore collaboration opportunities with Australian brands.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s global supply chain strategy, announced mid-May, has already led to strategic partnerships with 13 renowned retailers, brands, associations, and consulting firms worldwide.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/">Alibaba Group&#8217;s Freshippo Expands Brick and Mortar Presence in China Ahead of Its IPO</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC vs Coinbase Case Slated for July 13</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261226</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/">SEC vs Coinbase Case Slated for July 13</a></p>
<p>In the Coinbase defense that triggered a new hearing date in July, the exchange noted that many of the tokens SEC highlighted in its allegations are outside the Commission’s purview.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/">SEC vs Coinbase Case Slated for July 13</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/">SEC vs Coinbase Case Slated for July 13</a></p>
<p>The long-awaited legal battle between crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has been scheduled to hold on the 13th of July. Coinbase is just one of the crypto companies under the radar of the US financial watchdog. The Commission <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-102" target="_blank" rel="noopener">alleges</a> that the exchange has been operating its crypto asset trading platform as an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency. It also accused the company of not registering its staking-as-a-service program. The charges dial back to 2019, claiming that Coinbase has unlawfully generated profits.</p>
<h2>SEC and Coinbase Case Set for July 13</h2>
<p>The date was moved to July following the exchange’s defense strategy, involving submitting its first <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-sec-exchange-lawsuit-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">response</a> 40 days before the 7th of August deadline. Coinbase deployed a “creative” defense tactic, resulting in the July court date with the US SEC.</p>
<p>Per the rules, the SEC must file a response to Coinbase following the crypto company’s strategic defense. While the expected response date was supposed to be the 3rd of July, the watchdog requested an extensive considering the independence day holiday on the 4th of July. The court granted the request. Furthermore, the pre-trial conference, which was originally slated for the 24th of August is now a pre-motion conference happening on the 1st of July. At a pre-motion conference, the presiding judge and attorneys meet to evaluate the necessary steps to move a case to trial. They also fix dates for specific tasks.</p>
<p>In the <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.599908/gov.uscourts.nysd.599908.23.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coinbase defense</a> that triggered a new hearing date in July, the exchange noted that many of the tokens SEC highlighted in its allegations are outside the Commission’s purview. The company’s counsel wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Coinbase has answered the SEC’s Complaint with numerous defenses, including that this action violates due process and constitutes an abuse of discretion. But there is a more fundamental problem with the SEC’s case &#8211; one that the Chair recognized two years ago and that entitles Coinbase to judgment on the pleadings now: The subject matter falls outside the SEC’s authority.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Coinbase&#8217;s Defense</h2>
<p>The exchange argued further that the regulator could only push further if the transactions in the digital assets and services highlighted in the Complaint are considered “investment contracts. This would mean that they are “securities” per the Securities Act and the Exchange Act. Coinbase added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Because as a matter of law none of them are, the claims must be dismissed.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Lawyer and Twitter legal commentator, MetaLawman, likened the exchange’s tactic of sending its response 40 days earlier to a typical “creative strategy”. He explained that &#8220;Coinbase appears to be using this creative strategy to get documents helpful to its cause in front of the Judge through the Answer”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-coinbase-case-july-13/">SEC vs Coinbase Case Slated for July 13</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea Passes First Independent Crypto Bill to Strengthen Investor Protection</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vaup]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/">South Korea Passes First Independent Crypto Bill to Strengthen Investor Protection</a></p>
<p>As per the VAUP legislation, the Financial Services Commission (FSC) will get the authority to oversee crypto operators as well as crypto custodians. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/">South Korea Passes First Independent Crypto Bill to Strengthen Investor Protection</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/">South Korea Passes First Independent Crypto Bill to Strengthen Investor Protection</a></p>
<p>South Korea has now implemented the first independent bill for digital assets in order to boost investor protection in the region. The development comes one year after the country&#8217;s biggest implosion of the Terra ecosystem last year which triggered the $2 trillion crypto market rout.</p>
<p>On Friday, the South Korean parliament passed the Virtual Asset User Protection legislation, integrating a total of 19 crypto bills. The legislation establishes clear definitions for digital assets and sets penalties for various violations, including the use of nonpublic information, market manipulation, and unfair trading practices.</p>
<p>Under the legislation, the top financial regulator &#8211; the Financial Services Commission (FSC) &#8211; gets the power to oversee crypto operators along with crypto custodians. Also, the Bank of Korea will have the right to probe such platforms. Furthermore, this act would require reserve funds, insurance coverage, and other necessary record-keeping. The rule will cover digital assets such as Bitcoin, however, existing capital-market laws will be applicable to tokens deemed securities.</p>
<p>Upon the violation of the new rules, individuals may face a minimum of one year of imprisonment or significant fines. For instance, the Financial Services Commission has the authority to impose fines that are double the amount of the profits obtained through unfair trading practices.</p>
<h3>Reforming South Korea&#8217;s Crypto Industry</h3>
<p>Last year, the implosion of Terraform Labs led to the erosion of $40 billion in investors&#8217; wealth. Terra founder Do Kwon is now facing a period in jail in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-extradition-custody-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Montenegro</a>.</p>
<p>Apart from the fallout involving Kwon, investors were also reminded of the ongoing risks in the digital asset sector when two crypto lenders associated with South Korea temporarily suspended withdrawals in June, one after the other.</p>
<p>In March, a well-known murder case in Seoul that was connected to losses in crypto investments further emphasized the need for politicians to expedite the implementation of new regulations. Speaking on the development, Lee Suh Ryoung, chief secretary general of the Korea Blockchain Enterprise Promotion Association in Seoul <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/south-korea-passes-inaugural-standalone-crypto-bill-after-spate-of-scandals-1.1939911" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We welcome the authorities’ attempt to build order. But the law in general remains stuck in the perspective of traditional finance in terms of regulating crypto.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In April, South Korea experienced a significant decline in its monthly spot crypto trading volume, dropping to around $38 billion compared to its peak of nearly $200 billion two years ago, as per data from CCData. However, the country continues to be known for occasional virtual asset frenzies.</p>
<p>Countries worldwide are intensifying their efforts to regulate digital assets. Regions such as Hong Kong and Dubai are striving to attract crypto investments, while the European Union recently passed its groundbreaking Markets in Cryptoassets (MiCA) regulation. US agencies have also taken action following a series of incidents, including the bankruptcy of the FTX exchange.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-independent-crypto-bill/">South Korea Passes First Independent Crypto Bill to Strengthen Investor Protection</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skybridge Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
<p>Scaramucci highlights the importance of patience when considering Nvidia as an investment opportunity.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
<p>Investing in Artificial Intelligence (AI) stocks has become increasingly popular as the technology continues to reshape industries. However, concerns about a potential bubble in the AI industry have emerged. In a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-30/scaramucci-says-ai-stocks-are-a-bubble-but-buy-them-anyway#:~:text=%E2%80%9CThere%20are%20boom%2Dbust%20cycles,'ll%20probably%20be%20OK.%E2%80%9D" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Anthony Scaramucci, the Founder of SkyBridge Capital, advised AI stock investors to concentrate on long-term investments amidst these concerns.</p>
<p>He highlights the presence of high-quality AI companies that offer long-term value to investors. While some AI stocks may be overvalued in the short term, Scaramucci emphasizes that owning them over an extended period could still yield favorable returns.</p>
<p>Scaramucci used <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corp</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA), a major leader in the AI industry, as an example. Notably, Nvidia has established itself as a prominent participant in the AI market, supplying sophisticated Graphics Processing Units (GPUs) and other hardware solutions critical for AI training and inference.</p>
<p>He believes Nvidia is currently overvalued, which aligns with concerns about the current condition of the AI market. However, Scaramucci adds that owning Nvidia stock for the next 15 years could still prove to be a profitable decision.</p>
<p>According to reports, Nvidia has witnessed an astounding surge in its share price this year. With investors banking on its essential role in the advancement of AI, Nvidia&#8217;s shares have soared by 179% in 2023 and are trading at 53 times analysts&#8217; estimates of adjusted earnings for the current fiscal year.</p>
<p>Despite the seemingly high valuation, Scaramucci highlights the importance of patience when considering Nvidia as an investment opportunity. Drawing parallels to early internet winners, Scaramucci reminds investors that long-term success often requires perseverance.</p>
<h2>Besides AI: Anthony Scaramucci Nursing Losses</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Scaramucci&#8217;s SkyBridge Capital has faced significant challenges in 2022 due to its investment positions in crypto and exposure to the now-bankrupt platform FTX Derivatives Exchange. According to previous reports, SkyBridge&#8217;s largest fund lost 39% at the time, prompting the establishment of new withdrawal limits for clients.</p>
<p>SkyBridge Capital was one of the trading firm&#8217;s early supporters and one of the hardest-hit venture capital firms when the platform crumbled last year. In a previous <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-capital-founder-scaramucci-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Scaramucci stated that the failure of FTX had harmed his reputation. He stated this in part because he considered himself Sam Bankman-Fried’s friend.</p>
<p>Despite the betrayals and fund losses, Scaramucci stated that he will continue to take chances in the digital currency ecosystem because he believes in the blockchain technology that is fueling the broader sector. Additionally, Scaramucci reflects on the nature of short-term losses, emphasizing the importance of maintaining a long-term perspective as an investor.</p>
<p>Overall, SkyBridge Capital&#8217;s experience offers valuable lessons, emphasizing the importance of diversification, diligent research, risk management, patience, and adaptability. By understanding the nature of investment cycles and maintaining a long-term perspective, investors can navigate short-term losses and position themselves for potential long-term success.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[upbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261183</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
<p>Since BCH became one of the four cryptocurrencies traded on EDX, its price has continued to rise. In the last 24 hours, the crypto has spiked more than 30%, reaching $325 for the first time since April 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a> (BCH) is experiencing a major increase in price and trading volume due to different reasons. One of the significant factors that have been said to affect its price is that Fidelity, Charles Schwab, and Citadel-backed EDX Markets introduced BCH as part of the assets available for trading on their platform on June 20 at its launch.</p>
<p>EDX Markets only made four cryptocurrencies available for trading when the exchange was launched. The cryptos are Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a>, Ethereum, and Litecoin. According to Jamil Nazarali, CEO of EDX Markets, as reported by <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/30/bitcoin-cash-tops-300-amid-surge-in-trading-volumes-in-south-korea/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coindesk</a>, this was done because they are believed to be, to a great extent, safe cryptocurrencies, and they are also compliant with US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) regulations.</p>
<p>Lawrence Lewitinn, The Tie&#8217;s Director of Content, stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Nazarali explained that they felt confident that Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash, as derivatives of bitcoin, were not securities. While there is some interest, it is not substantial.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Some have also said the price rise could be due to the hard fork upgrade that the cryptocurrency recently went through. However, since the hard fork got completed in mid-May, and the significant price rise didn&#8217;t start till June 20, it couldn&#8217;t have been the leading cause. Nevertheless, we cannot deny that it can increase the attention given to BCH as the fork improved its network security and privacy measures.</p>
<p>Since BCH became one of the four cryptocurrencies traded on EDX, its price has continued to rise. In the last 24 hours, the crypto has spiked more than 30%, reaching $325 for the first time since April 2022. Overall, BCH&#8217;s price has risen by 150%, from $106 on June 20 to $325 today.</p>
<h2>Rise in Bitcoin Cash Trading Volume among South Korean Users of Upbit</h2>
<p>Another factor pushing the price upward is an increase in trading volume in South Korea. As more people trade BCH, its demand increases, thereby pushing the price up.</p>
<p>There is a large BCH trading volume in South Korea, as can be seen from the data by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/upbit" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinGecko</a> on BCH trading volume on Upbit, one of the popular exchanges in South Korea. Coingecko revealed that the Bitcoin Cash-Korean Won (BCH/KRW) pair on Upbit had a trading volume of $658.25 million in the last 24 hours. Which is more than three times bigger than the $166.93 million volume that the Bitcoin-Korean won (BTC/KRW) pair has on the exchange.</p>
<p>Considering all the points above, we can conclude that the significant rise in the price of BCH is a result of different factors like introducing the asset on the EDX exchange, which increased its trading volume, and the increased demand for Bitcoin Cash among South Korean users of Upbit.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salesforce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[typeface]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
<p>The funding round conducted only a few months after its public launch puts Typeface in fierce competition with similar tools.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
<p>Typeface, a generative artificial intelligence (AI) content creation platform for enterprises, announced it has concluded a Series B funding round. Typeface received $100 million in funding from a round led by Salesforce Ventures, the arm of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/salesforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Salesforce Inc</a> (NYSE: CRM) that provides funding, support, and mentorship to startups. The round brings Typeface’s total funding to $165 million and puts the company’s valuation at $1 billion.</p>
<p>Other participants in the funding round include Google Ventures, the M12 venture fund from Microsoft, Madrona, Menlo Ventures, and Lightspeed Venture Partners.</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/typeface-announces-100m-in-new-funding-to-fuel-global-expansion-of-its-personalized-generative-ai-platform-for-enterprises-301866644.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official release</a>, Typeface founder and CEO Abhay Parasnis said the company provides businesses with “enterprise-ready solutions” to adequately harness the transformative power of AI for content creation. According to Parasnis, “by combining the strengths of generative AI platforms with our brand-specialized knowledge, we have eliminated the barriers for enterprises to harness generative AI. Typeface empowers every enterprise to create high-quality, personalized content that aligns with its unique voice.”</p>
<p>Parasnis, a former Adobe CTO, founded Typeface in June 2022, along with former personnel from Microsoft and Meta. Typeface launched publicly in February and has garnered interest from several companies, including LG Electronics, one of Typeface’s customers. The platform integrates several AI tools into its business, including OpenAI’s GPT-4, Google Vertex AI, Microsoft Azure AI, and Stable Diffusion.</p>
<h2>Typeface Partnerships Before Funding Round</h2>
<p>Typeface successfully secured two major partnerships with tech giants. Google Cloud and Typeface announced a partnership to scale its AI content for businesses. A <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/typeface-and-google-cloud-announce-strategic-partnership-to-provide-ai-generated-personalized-content-at-scale-for-enterprises-worldwide-301844358.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> explained that Typeface will integrate Google Cloud’s large language models (LLMs) and launch a Google Workspace Marketplace plugin. Businesses can use the plugin to create quick, customized, compelling content for use across different channels.</p>
<p>Last week, Typeface <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/typeface-and-salesforce-partner-to-bring-personalized-generative-ai-capabilities-into-salesforce-marketing-gpt-301856067.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> another partnership with Salesforce. The partnership integrates Typeface’s AI tools with the Salesforce Marketing GPT to provide customers with customized content. Marketers will be able to use their own brand, messaging, and style guides to create engaging and creative content to drive productivity.</p>
<h2>How Does Typeface Work?</h2>
<p>Parasnis <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/06/29/typeface-which-is-building-generative-ai-for-brands-raises-100m-at-a-1b-valuation/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a> to TechCrunch that Typeface functions with three major components. The first is a content hub that applies guidelines the user provides for content (text and image) generation. Typeface also has the Blend tool, which uses AI to customize the user’s content to a particular brand’s style or voice. Finally, Parasnis explains Flow, a tool offering users various workflows and templates they can install with existing programs for on-brand content creation.</p>
<p>Speaking on the need for Typeface, Parasnis said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Enterprise leaders are telling us across the board that they want to embrace generative AI, but they need a solution that meets their unique requirements and is ready for the enterprise.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Specific Typeface use may include helping a marketer create an Instagram post, including an image and a caption. The user can specify specific brand wording and imagery to launch a product or advertise a feature based on the brand’s image and style.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261167</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
<p>Google said the decision by Canada exposes the company to “uncapped financial liability”.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) is removing all Canada news links from its search due to a new <a href="https://www.parl.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/bill/C-18/third-reading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Online News Act</a>. The tech giant said it would block all Canadian news, meaning users will no longer find any report linked to the country on the search engine. The decision was in response to a new law that required tech companies to pay media outlets for content.</p>
<p>Last week, the Canadian government’s controversial C-18 legislation in Canada passed parliament despite Google noting that it was “unworkable”. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> (NASDAQ: META) also criticized the bill on the grounds that it was unfair to impose compensation on tech companies. Google and Meta have been battling with the government over the law forcing them to pay media outlets in Canada for distributing links to news stories. The Canadian government explained that the legislation is to offer fair compensation to struggling news outlets. The officials also emphasized the need “to enhance fairness in the Canadian digital news market”. The bill supporters wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Digital platforms and social media are now the gateways where people find, read and share news. Because of this, advertising revenues have shifted away from local news and journalists to these gatekeepers, who profit from the sharing and distribution of Canadian news content.”</p></blockquote>
<p>There is a prediction that the law could generate up to $329 million for the Canadian news industry. Although the Online News Act has already been passed in Canada, it would take months to take effect. When it does, Google has already decided to remove links to “Canadian news from our Search, News, and Discover products and will no longer be able to operate Google News Showcase in Canada”.</p>
<h2>Google Will Block All Canada News Links</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://blog.google/intl/en-ca/company-news/outreach-initiatives/an-update-on-canadas-bill-c-18-and-our-search-and-news-products/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">news blog</a>, Google said the decision by Canada exposes the company to “uncapped financial liability”. It reiterated that it is not the proper approach and could impact its products. According to the tech giant, it contributed to Canadian journalism via programs and partnerships and is willing to do more. Google revealed linking to Canadian news publications over 3.6 billion times last year at no charge. According to the company, it helped publishers generate profits via ads and new subscriptions without expecting anything in return. Despite the willingness to do more, the multinational technology company said it will not be able to do that “in a way that breaks the way that the web and search engines are designed to work, and that creates untenable product and financial uncertainty”.</p>
<p>Canadian minister Pablo Rodriguez was surprised by Google’s decision to remove all Canadian links from its platform. The politician said they still had a conversion with the tech company shortly before. Google also confirmed that it discussed with the government where it requested clarity on financial expectations. Google seemed to be dissatisfied with the chat with Canada officials, as it announced removing the links not long after the meeting.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
<p>The UK government wants to adopt the nascent crypto asset industry to enable exponential growth to its economy away from the Brussels shackles.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
<p>Having successfully secured its independence from the European Union through Brexit, the United Kingdom (UK) continues to reorganize its internal policies to attract international investors and streamline bilateral trade. In the latest developments under the leadership of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, the UK government announced the Financial Services and Markets Act 2023 was granted Royal Assent on Thursday. Under the economic legislation, the UK government passed to safely adopt the crypto assets.</p>
<p>The move comes after the European Union recently passed a comprehensive crypto adoption framework dubbed Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation.</p>
<p>According to Economic Secretary to the Treasury, Andrew Griffith, the country is keen to reform its financial laws to accommodate the fast-growing trillion-dollar market in a regulated manner.</p>
<p>“This landmark piece of legislation gives us control of our financial services rulebook, so it supports UK businesses and consumers and drives growth. By repealing old EU laws set in Brussels it will unlock billions in investment – cash that can unlock innovation and grow the economy,” Griffith <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/rocket-boost-for-uk-economy-as-financial-services-and-markets-bill-receives-royal-assent" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The United Kingdom wants to become a stronghold for IPOs as more companies reach global markets through the use of technologies like blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI). The country wants to unlock a £100 billion market through the Financial Services and Markets Act 2023 with the help of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>“Today’s ground-breaking Act also establishes ‘sandboxes’ that can facilitate the use of new technologies such as blockchain in financial markets,” the announcement noted.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at UK and Crypto Market</h2>
<p>With London being a strategic financial hub, the United Kingdom has attracted significant investors especially those fleeing hostile regulatory scrutiny in the United States. In the past few months, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> has visited the country and made several official meetings with Griffith.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Great meeting today with UK Economic Secretary and City Minister <a href="https://twitter.com/griffitha?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@griffitha</a>.</p>
<p>The UK is moving fast on sensible crypto regulation to both drive economic growth AND consumer protection. Excited to keep investing in the UK. 🇬🇧 <a href="https://t.co/478PQSLmDe">pic.twitter.com/478PQSLmDe</a></p>
<p>— Brian Armstrong 🛡️ (@brian_armstrong) <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1648013189437595909?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>However, Armstrong pointed out that some UK-based banks are blocking fiat payments to crypto companies, which has been a huge impediment to mainstream adoption in the country. Nonetheless, Armstrong insisted that the company will continue investing in the country amid positive crypto-focused policies.</p>
<p>Similarly, crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> has made a significant entrance into the UK market amid hostile developments in the United States. According to the Winklevoss twins, the UK is well slated to be a Web3 hub in the near future.</p>
<p>According to PM Sunak, the UK is implementing various plans to become a crypto asset hub. As the Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>) narrows down to the CBDC rollout, the country remains receptive to the stablecoin market. Additionally, the FCA-led ‘CryptoSprint’ continues to work with the Royal Mint on an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>, establishing a Crypto Asset Engagement Group.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[didi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shein ipo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
<p>Even if the IPO rumors were true and Shein wanted to list in the US, the company would need to clear the air about environmental, social, and governance concerns.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
<p>Fast-rising Chinese fashion giant Shein has denied the widespread rumors that it has filed for an initial public offering (IPO) in the US. Rumors had it that the company was planning to go public in the US before the end of the year. At the time, A Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/shein-ipo/exclusive-chinas-shein-files-for-u-s-ipo-sources-idUKL4N38L313" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> said Shein was considering the New York Stock Exchange (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nyse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NYSE</a>) for its IPO, but market volatility caused by the Russia-Ukraine war made it suspend its plans. The report cited people with knowledge of the matter and added that the listing could make Shein the most valuable Chinese company to go public in the US since Didi’s IPO in 2021.</p>
<h2>Shein Turns Down Alleged US IPO Filing</h2>
<p>However, a Shein spokesperson told CNBC:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Shein denies these rumors.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This comes shortly after it was accused of exploiting trade loopholes to import goods into the US. A committee exploring economic competition between China and the US, The Select Committee on the CCP, released a <a href="https://selectcommitteeontheccp.house.gov/sites/evo-subsites/selectcommitteeontheccp.house.gov/files/evo-media-document/fast-fashion-and-the-uyghur-genocide-interim-findings.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> saying that the Chinese fast fashion retailer and Temu did not pay import fees in 2022. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/committeeonccp/status/1672239571147390976?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1672233037864525824%7Ctwgr%5Ee3ff8ead16e211ec869512f02014c556f5ed874d%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnbc.com%2F2023%2F06%2F30%2Fshein-denies-us-ipo-rumors.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>, the Committee wrote that the companies avoid tax and inspection by the US Customs and Border Protection, “making it impossible to determine if their products are made with Uyghur forced labor in Xinjiang.”</p>
<p>According to the report, both Shein and Temu are responsible for more than 30% of daily shipped packages to the US. The brands process this under the minimis provision of Section 321 of the Tariff Act of 1930. This helps them avoid import tariffs if the fair retail value of the shipment is not over $800. Per the findings, the import accounted for almost 600,000 shipments daily in 2022, which means that it could be higher this year. Hence, lawmakers opined that the tariff violations unfairly placed Shein and Temu over US retailers. While Temu’s valuation is said to be over $100 billion, Shein was recently valued at $64 billion.</p>
<h2>Shein&#8217;s Allegations</h2>
<p>Before denying <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/e-retailer-shein-us-ipo-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US IPO plans</a>, Shein was accused of human rights abuses. The company faces allegations over forced labor of its supplier factories in the Uyghur region. Even if the IPO rumors were true and Shein wanted to list in the US, the company would need to clear the air about environmental, social, and governance concerns. There have been <a href="https://www.businessoffashion.com/news/retail/report-shein-violating-labour-laws/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ill reports</a>, including allegedly poor working conditions.</p>
<p>Many said the Chinese company was violating labor laws and slaving away employees. An investigation found that employees in some Shein partner factories worked 12 to 14 hours daily with only 24 hours off every month. Meanwhile, Chinese labor laws say workweeks cannot be more than 40 hours, and overtime should not exceed 36 hours monthly. Also, workers are entitled to one day off every week under the law.</p>
<p>However, a Shein representative told CNBC in May:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have zero tolerance for forced labor.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite dismissing the US IPO news, many believe that Shein will eventually list in the US sometime.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3903 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1061926 metric#prefetches=196 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=202 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=103.30 metric#ms-cache=4.78 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2389 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.6 -->