<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:38:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lawyers Argue that Plans of SBF to Plead Not Guilty May Not Be in His Best Interest</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/">Lawyers Argue that Plans of SBF to Plead Not Guilty May Not Be in His Best Interest</a></p>
<p>SBF remains under house arrest after posting a $250 million bail bond back in December.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/">Lawyers Argue that Plans of SBF to Plead Not Guilty May Not Be in His Best Interest</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/">Lawyers Argue that Plans of SBF to Plead Not Guilty May Not Be in His Best Interest</a></p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>) the embattled founder and former Chief Executive Officer of bankrupt FTX Exchange is set to appear in court today to start the criminal proceedings on his fraud charges where he is expected to plead not guilty. As <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/bankman-fried-set-enter-not-guilty-plea-ftx-fraud-case-2023-01-03/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Reuters, his court session is set to commence by 2 p.m. EST (1900 GMT) before US District Judge Lewis Kaplan in Manhattan.</p>
<p>From earlier reports, SBF is billed to enter into a not-guilty plea before Judge Lewis, a move that has been under intense analysis by lawyers observing the case. Indeed, it may seem a surprising move to the general public that SBF has been advised to plead not guilty by his lawyers considering the fact that his co-executives Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang have both <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ellison-wang-guilty-ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">pleaded guilty</a> to their 7 and 4 count charges respectively.</p>
<p>As for Sam Bankman-Fried, the count charges levied on him by Federal prosecutors sum up to 8, and should he be convicted for them, he could face as much as 115 years in prison. The bottom line of his fraud case hinges on the fact that he misappropriated  FTX customers’ funds to fund operations at Alameda Research.</p>
<p>SBF entered into some indulgences such that he went on luxury real estate acquisitions as well as making political donations that have notably riled up Washington DC since the bankruptcy filing became public. Bankman-Fried has made attempts to apologize to customers, creditors, and investors of the defunct trading platform which has a liability of over $8 billion to refund to investors.</p>
<p>According to the embattled crypto innovator, he made mistakes while running the trading platform but he did not believe that his actions had any criminal undertones at the time.</p>
<h2>Not Guilty Plea May Not Favor SBF</h2>
<p>According to a former federal prosecutor Danya Perry who served as a former assistant US attorney for the Southern District of New York, the Department of Justice (DoJ) has a very good advantage with respect to the current SBF case.</p>
<p>According to her, the DoJ has a lot of witnesses that are ready to testify should the case drag on to trial but she <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-fraud-charges-bankruptcy-arraignment-plea-deal-2023-1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">believed</a> the not-guilty plea if made will be an attempt for SBF and his lawyers to negotiate a better deal with the amount of time that will be freed up.</p>
<p>&#8220;They have a mountain of paper evidence, and in fact, admissions by the defendant himself,&#8221; Perry said, adding; So they&#8217;re not going to be in any particular rush, and they&#8217;re not going to be welcoming of any sweetheart plea deal.&#8221;</p>
<p>The situation at hand makes pleading not guilty a fair one as the plea can be changed later on as the proceedings progress. With Bankman-Fried sitting at the echelon of affairs of the bankrupt trading firm, he may not see anyone to provide evidence against as is customary to suspects who plead guilty as explained by another former Federal prosecutor, Ian McGinley.</p>
<p>In all, there is a belief that the not-guilty plea can give prosecutors ample time to dig out more anomalies attached to the exchange and its operators. SBF remains under house arrest after posting a $250 million bail bond back in December.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/">Lawyers Argue that Plans of SBF to Plead Not Guilty May Not Be in His Best Interest</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawyers-sbf-plans-plead-not-guilty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gold Price Climbs to Six-Month High as Analysts Anticipate Further Growth in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Commodities & Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231164</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/">Gold Price Climbs to Six-Month High as Analysts Anticipate Further Growth in 2023</a></p>
<p>Gold price is on a steady rise, and analysts opine it could further benefit from a string of 2023 fiscal policies. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/">Gold Price Climbs to Six-Month High as Analysts Anticipate Further Growth in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/">Gold Price Climbs to Six-Month High as Analysts Anticipate Further Growth in 2023</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinspeaker-advent-gold-price-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">price of gold</a> has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/03/gold-surges-to-6-month-high-and-analysts-expect-new-records-in-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">surged to a six-month high</a>, even as analysts predict it will rise further as 2023 begins.</p>
<p>In the early hours of Tuesday, spot gold peaked just shy of $1,850 per troy ounce. However, the precious metal eventually eased off to trade at $1,834 per ounce late morning in Europe. Meanwhile, US gold futures were trading up 0.72% at $1,839.40 by 6 am Eastern Time.</p>
<h2>Gold on Incline Since Early November 2022</h2>
<p>Gold prices have been on a generally upward trajectory since the beginning of November. A combination of macro and microeconomic factors has fueled this rally. They include market turbulence, increasing recession expectations, and a rise in gold purchases from central banks. Echoing analyst projections that gold price will attain record highs in 2023, Ole Hansen, head of the commodity strategy at Saxo Bank, offered:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In general, we are looking for a price friendly 2023 supported by recession and stock market valuation risks — an eventual peak in central bank rates combined with the prospect of a weaker dollar and inflation not returning to the expected sub-3% level by year-end — all adding support.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Hansen also pointed out that last year’s global de-dollarization could further spur the precious metal to new heights. As he put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The de-dollarization seen by several central banks last year when a record amount of gold was bought look set to continue, thereby providing a soft floor under the market.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Hansen also suggested that upcoming US data could influence gold price key events for future forecasts. These include Wednesday’s latest Fed Reserve meeting minutes and Friday’s jobs report. According to Hansen, “above $1842, the 50% [mark] of the 2022 correction, gold will be looking for resistance at $1850 and $1878 next.”</p>
<p>Last month, Eric Strand, manager of the AuAg ESG Gold Mining ETF, also suggested that a more dovish fiscal stance could aid gold prices. According to him, at the time, 2023 could yield a new record high for gold. In addition, Strand stated that this year could witness the beginning of a new bull market. In his opinion, the price of gold could surpass $2,100 per ounce.</p>
<h2>Projected Record Gold Price Contingent on Fiscal Policy Trajectory</h2>
<p>The likelihood that the price of gold will crest at a new all-time high in 2023 largely depends on the monetary policy trajectory. These fiscal decisions are crucial because they come when central banks look to ease off the aggressive interest rate hikes of 2022. Due to inflation, the governing banks of developed nations, including the US and the Eurozone, embarked on steep rate hikes last year. However, their relentless drive to rein in inflation stifled economic growth and threatened to bring about a recession.</p>
<p>Many economic discussions center around whether a looming recession could result in prevalent rate cuts by the end of 2023. As it stands, the consensus is that inflation will far exceed the target range in most developed economies.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/">Gold Price Climbs to Six-Month High as Analysts Anticipate Further Growth in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-price-six-month-high-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moroccan Central Bank to Release Crypto Regulatory Bill ‘in the Following Days’</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto ban morocco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation morocco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morocco bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morocco crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morocco crypto ban]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/">Moroccan Central Bank to Release Crypto Regulatory Bill &#8216;in the Following Days&#8217;</a></p>
<p>For finalizing the bill, BAM collaborated with the International Monetary Fund and the World Bank. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/">Moroccan Central Bank to Release Crypto Regulatory Bill &#8216;in the Following Days&#8217;</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/">Moroccan Central Bank to Release Crypto Regulatory Bill &#8216;in the Following Days&#8217;</a></p>
<p>After a series of numerous discussions, Morocco is ready for introducing its crypto regulatory bill. According to the Governor of Moroccan Central Bank, Bank Al-Maghrib (BAM), Abdellatif Jouahiri, the country might see the release of the final crypto bill &#8220;in the following days.&#8221;</p>
<p>Abdellatif Jouahiri <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-morocco-central-bank-governor-says-crypto-draft-law-now-ready/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For cryptocurrencies, I can assure you that the project is ready. We worked with the World Bank and the consultant to make it happen. The different chapters are completed. Now we are engaged in the discussion with the different stakeholders. It is long, but necessary to allow everyone to adhere to this project.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>For finalizing the bill, BAM collaborated with the International Monetary Fund and the World Bank. Currently, it is in talks with Morocco’s capital market and insurance watchdogs, which are the Moroccan Capital Markets Authority (AMMC) and the Insurance Supervisory Authority and Social Security (ACAPS).</p>
<p>Abdellatif Jouahiri added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Discussions are to be held with all stakeholders, including the Moroccan Capital Markets Authority (AMMC) and the Insurance and Social Security Supervisory Authority (ACAPS),” said the BAM Chief. We proceeded to a specific definition of the cryptocurrency and prepared a general public survey that details the specifics and use of this virtual currency in Morocco.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Kingdom of Morocco started working on crypto regulation in the summer of 2022. In June, it was the first time Morocco&#8217;s central bank announced its intention to establish a regulatory framework for the crypto market. At that time, BAM’s governor Abdellatif Jouahri said that the institution engaged with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) and the World Bank on specific benchmarks. While the Ministry of Finance and the Moroccan Capital Market Authority repeatedly warned of the risks associated with the use of cryptocurrencies, Morocco keeps growing in terms of crypto users number. It is now becoming the fastest-growing crypto market in Northern Africa.</p>
<h2>Moroccan Situation: Status of Crypto</h2>
<p>Until 2017, the Moroccan government did not acknowledge the existence of crypto assets. However, with the rapid growth of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), the authorities decided to impose a ban on cryptocurrency transactions. Currently, there is no way for Moroccans to acquire Bitcoin or any other cryptocurrency. This is because there is no cryptocurrency exchange in Morocco due to the ban and the lack of entrepreneurial ventures in this area. But even with the ban, the ownership of cryptocurrencies is steadily increasing in Morocco.</p>
<p>In 2022, Morocco became the fastest-growing crypto market in Northern Africa. It saw growth from 2.4% of the population owing digital assets in 2021 to 3.1% a year later. The number of people owning cryptocurrencies in Morocco reached 1.15 million people in 2022, generating an $8,612 GDP per capita.</p>
<p>As a result of this growth, the Moroccan government realized there is a need for a proper crypto bill. We might see the regulatory framework in the upcoming days, which will give clear guidance on dealing with crypto for Moroccans.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/">Moroccan Central Bank to Release Crypto Regulatory Bill &#8216;in the Following Days&#8217;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/moroccan-central-bank-crypto-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>December 2022 Crypto Attacks Constituted Relatively Low $62M Loss</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[axie infinity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lodestar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ronon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/">December 2022 Crypto Attacks Constituted Relatively Low $62M Loss</a></p>
<p>Despite 2022 being the worst year for crypto attacks, December's spate came in at the lowest, rendering it the least harmful month last year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/">December 2022 Crypto Attacks Constituted Relatively Low $62M Loss</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/">December 2022 Crypto Attacks Constituted Relatively Low $62M Loss</a></p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/03/2022-crypto-attacks-were-least-in-december-with-62m-lost-in-heists-certik-says/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coindesk report</a>, December had the least number of crypto attacks for 2022. However, the report, citing blockchain audit firm CertiK, noted that scams and hacks accounted for a massive $3.7 billion loss throughout last year. This fact makes 2022 the worst year for criminal activities in the history of the crypto and blockchain sectors.</p>
<p>Despite 2022 being an uneventful year by way of crypto attacks, the month of December provided a few cheer-worthy instances for market participants. There was $62 million worth of stolen tokens, scams, or hacks last month, which made it the least harmful month. By contrast, an overwhelming $595 million worth of crypto-based attacks happened in November 2022.</p>
<h2>Closer Analysis of December 2022 Crypto Attacks</h2>
<p>The two most notable crypto attacks in December 2022 were the Defrost Finance $12 million hack and Helio Protocol $15 million exploit. Defrost Finance&#8217;s attack allegedly came from a <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/12/30/defrost-finance-denies-rug-pull-allegations-amid-12m-exploit/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">&#8216;rug pull&#8217;</a> that saw developers disappear with investor money. However, the team behind the initiative pushed back on those claims and referred to them as defamatory and inaccurate.</p>
<p>Other relatively minor attacks that occurred at the end of last year include a flash loan exploit that resulted in a $7.6 million loss. Flash loans pose a popular means via which attackers gain funds to carry out exploits on decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) systems. The loans enable traders to borrow unsecured funds from lenders through smart contracts instead of third parties. Furthermore, no collateral is required because the contract deems the transaction complete only after the lender&#8217;s repayment. Therefore, the implication of this process suggests that defaulting on a flash loan would trigger the smart contract to cancel the transaction. The said transaction&#8217;s cancellation would also see the money returned to the lender.</p>
<p>Of the previously mentioned $7.6 million flash loan figure, a single Lodestar attack constituted an overwhelming $6.5 million.</p>
<p>Several other crypto projects also experienced similar attacks, with losses ranging from $50,000 to $300,000.</p>
<p>Although attackers made away with $3.2 billion in 2021, the following year experienced an even more inauspicious start. For instance, there was the $325 million hack of the popular cross-chain platform Wormhole. This exploit was followed by the far more substantial $625 million cyber assault on Axie Infinity&#8217;s Ronin bridge. 2022 also saw a significant $200 million attack on the Nomad bridge.</p>
<h2>Ways to Hack</h2>
<p>There are several ways in which miscreants carry out exploits and attacks within the crypto and blockchain industry. These include exploiting bridges, flash loans, and market manipulation.</p>
<p>Blockchain bridge exploitation sees hackers attack the blockchain-based tool that facilitates user transactions between different networks. Meanwhile, a typical market manipulation hack sees rogue traders deploy large sums of money to influence thinly traded markets in their favor. The usual end goal of such market manipulation is to pocket multiples far in excess of the initial capital deployed.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/">December 2022 Crypto Attacks Constituted Relatively Low $62M Loss</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/december-2022-crypto-attacks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uncertain 2023 Outlook Causes Treasury Yields to Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury yield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231149</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/">Uncertain 2023 Outlook Causes Treasury Yields to Fall</a></p>
<p>As the new year kicks off and 2023 trading begins, investors' fingers are crossed on key economic metrics expected to be available in the coming week.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/">Uncertain 2023 Outlook Causes Treasury Yields to Fall</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/">Uncertain 2023 Outlook Causes Treasury Yields to Fall</a></p>
<p>Investors are worried about the 2023 outlook and looking forward to new economic data releases due this week, causing treasury yields to fall. It happened at about 4:19 a.m. ET on the 3rd of January, with the 10-year Treasury note <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/03/us-treasury-yields-as-uncertainty-about-2023-outlook-lingers.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">dropping</a> more than seven basis points to 3.7577%. Also, the 2-year Treasury went down almost four basis points and traded at about 4.3637% earlier.</p>
<h2>Gloomy 2023 Affects Treasury Yields</h2>
<p>As the new year kicks off and 2023 trading begins, investors&#8217; fingers are crossed on key economic metrics expected to be available in the coming week. The key economic data could give indicators on the state US economy and Federal Reserve policy plans. While there was preliminary data of December&#8217;s S&amp;P Global Manufacturing Purchasing Managers&#8217; Index published last month, the final ready is due today. The initial publication suggested a shrinking in factory activity through December.</p>
<p>Moreso, investors are looking forward to gaining insights into the labor markets via JOLTS job openings data. The JOLTS job openings is a survey by the US Bureau of Labor Statistics to measure job vacancies. The summary from the Fed&#8217;s December meeting is also due, and investors are hoping to get some clues on future monetary policy from it.</p>
<p>Furthermore, many believe that the Federal Reserve may slow down on its continuously increasing interest rates. There were four consecutive 75 basis point increases in increase rates last year before it slightly dropped in December. In December, the central bank announced a 50 basis point hike in interest rates as the fight against inflation lingers. As the Feds passed another interest rate hike as 2022 was about to come to an end, it sent some fears among investors who were hoping for good news in 2023.</p>
<p>A few hours into 2023, US treasury yields rose as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/treasury-yields-better-market-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">investors anticipated a better market in 2023</a>. The 10-year Treasury yields jumped about 2 basis points to 3.8520% on the 30th of December, while the 2-year Treasury increased over 2 basis points to 4.4009% around 5:00 a.m. ET. The last-minute performance was in line with earlier suggestions that the Treasury yield could pop before the new year. At the time of the prediction, the 10-year Treasury yield was up by one basis point to 3.6856%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/">Uncertain 2023 Outlook Causes Treasury Yields to Fall</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bithumb’s Former Chairman Found Not Guilty by Seoul Court</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lee Jung-Hoon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/">Bithumb’s Former Chairman Found Not Guilty by Seoul Court</a></p>
<p>When Terraform Labs and its associated tokens collapsed, Bithumb was one of the exchanges that were raided by the authorities in the search for evidence that could help the investigation.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/">Bithumb’s Former Chairman Found Not Guilty by Seoul Court</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/">Bithumb’s Former Chairman Found Not Guilty by Seoul Court</a></p>
<p>Bithumb&#8217;s former Chairman Lee Jung-Hoon of the South Korean cryptocurrency trading platform has been declared not guilty of fraud charges dating back to 2018 in relation to the acquisition of the exchange from Kim Byung-Gun. The Not Guilty verdict was <a href="https://www.hankyung.com/finance/article/202301038848B" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">pronounced</a> at the Seoul Central District Court&#8217;s 34th Division of the Criminal Agreement.</p>
<p>The verdict on the Bithumb&#8217;s former chairman puts an end to the legal strain on Jung-Hoon whose trial was focused on allegations of the violation of the Act on the Aggravated Punishment Of Specific Economic Crimes due to fraud. The sum in question was pegged at around 100 billion won ($70 million) and had he been found guilty, he would have been <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/prosecutors-8-year-jail-owner-bithumb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sentenced to 8 years in prison</a>.</p>
<p>Like the United States, South Korea has seen a number of high-profile legal cases involving cryptocurrency entities over the past few years. Known as one of the most vibrant crypto hubs in the Asian region, South Korea boasts of exchanges like Bithumb that have been under the constant watch of regulators for scores of misconduct.</p>
<p>Bithumb as an exchange has come out to accept the verdict of the court and the trading platform reiterated that while the legal case involving its brand name is over, Jung-Hoon no longer plays an active role in the daily operations of the platform. According to the exchange, it has been under the directives of “Professional Managers” for some time now.</p>
<p>The discharge of Jung-Hoon speaks to the flexibility of the South Korean justice system and the decision comes barely a week after another Bithumb-linked executive committed suicide following allegations of embezzlement and manipulation of stock prices. As <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bithumb-s-largest-shareholder-executive-found-dead-following-allegations-of-embezzlement" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Cointelegraph, the executive, Park Mo, who doubles as Bithumb’s largest shareholder was found dead in his home.</p>
<h2>Bithumb and Impossible Situations</h2>
<p>While not the biggest trading platform in South Korea, in reality, Bithumb has found itself in many impossible situations over the past years with respect to its visible engagement in the digital currency ecosystem.</p>
<p>When Terraform Labs and its associated tokens collapsed, Bithumb was one of the exchanges that were <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/15-entities-terra-collapse-south-korea/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">raided</a> by the authorities in the search for evidence that could help the investigation into the startup at the time. The raid was not necessarily new to Bithumb as the exchange had recorded more than two police raids in less than three years as authorities cracked down on its operations across the board.</p>
<p>The not-guilty verdict received by Lee Jung-Hoon comes off as one visible win for the exchange in recent times. While it is unclear whether Jung-Hoon’s attornies did a good job or not, the exchange’s former chairman may now focus on his health as he reportedly missed a Parliamentary Hearing back in October last year as he said he had a mental health disorder at the time.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/">Bithumb’s Former Chairman Found Not Guilty by Seoul Court</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bithumbs-former-chairman-not-guilty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Promotes China Boss Tom Zhu to Highest-Profile Executive Role after Elon Musk</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tom zhu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/">Tesla Promotes China Boss Tom Zhu to Highest-Profile Executive Role after Elon Musk</a></p>
<p>Tesla China boss Zhu becomes the company’s highest-profile executive, second only to Musk, and looks to strengthen global operations. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/">Tesla Promotes China Boss Tom Zhu to Highest-Profile Executive Role after Elon Musk</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/">Tesla Promotes China Boss Tom Zhu to Highest-Profile Executive Role after Elon Musk</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/01/03/cars/tom-zhu-promotion-tesla-north-america-sales-intl-hnk/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">promoted</a> its Chinese outlet boss Tom Zhu to the role of the highest-profile executive after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>. According to reports, Zhu will take direct oversight over the electric vehicle maker’s US assembly plants and sales operations in Europe and North America. Interestingly, the Tesla China chief still retains his former job description and responsibilities at the company. These include the title of vice president of Greater China and the most senior executive for sales throughout the rest of Asia.</p>
<h2>Zhu Highest-Profile Executive Appointment Comes amid Musk Twitter Exertions</h2>
<p>Zhu’s appointment to the second highest-profile executive global role at Tesla comes when Musk seems distracted by his new <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a> obligations. It also appears to be a response by Tesla to deepen its senior executive hierarchy for better operational and stock focus. The appointment grants Zhu superior management over deliveries in all of Tesla’s major markets and key production hub operations. Zhu’s reporting lines would separate Tesla’s vehicle design and development while deputizing to Musk on global sales and output management. An organizational chart posted internally by Tesla and confirmed by two unnamed inside sources reflected this shakeup.</p>
<p>A host of Tesla managers situated across various regions would start reporting to Zhu following his promotion. These include Jason Shawhan, director of manufacturing at the Gigafactory in Texas, and Joe Ward, vice president of Europe, the Middle East, and Africa. Meanwhile, previously-established reporting lines to Zhu, featuring Tesla country managers in China, Japan, and the Australian region, would continue.</p>
<p>Expectations that Zhu was being primed for a more significant role began late last year. At the time, Tesla deployed its China boss and a team of his reports to address production constraints in the United States. According to recent data compiled by Refinitiv, the company delivered 405,278 vehicles during the fourth quarter. Although this figure fell short of the consensus estimate, it is almost 100,000 more deliveries in the year-ago period.</p>
<h2>Strong Management Track Record</h2>
<p>Under Zhu’s watch in China, Tesla’s Shanghai facility strongly rebounded from Covid lockdowns. During the two-month lockdown, Zhu demonstrated a commendable work ethic and dedication to his role. According to reports, the Tesla China chief began sleeping in the factory to keep operations running.</p>
<p>Zhu’s pragmatic approach to work also extends to his physical presentation and way of life. The Tesla China boss reportedly sports a minimalist appearance and once resided in a government-subsidized apartment close to the Shanghai Gigafactory. Whether or not he will move following his promotion remains unclear.</p>
<p>Born in China, Zhu now holds New Zealand citizenship. The executive is one of several workers recently seen celebrating the Texas plant production milestone. Before joining Tesla in 2014, Zhu worked as a production manager at a company established by his Duke University MBA classmates. While there, he advised Chinese contractors working on infrastructure projects in Africa.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/">Tesla Promotes China Boss Tom Zhu to Highest-Profile Executive Role after Elon Musk</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-china-highest-profile-executive/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Developers Loses Staggering $3.3M in PGP Exploit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/">Bitcoin Developers Loses Staggering $3.3M in PGP Exploit</a></p>
<p>The PGP keys were reportedly compromised for the hacker to gain access to more than 200 Bitcoins lying in the developers wallet. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/">Bitcoin Developers Loses Staggering $3.3M in PGP Exploit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/">Bitcoin Developers Loses Staggering $3.3M in PGP Exploit</a></p>
<p>In the latest development of a crypto wallet hack, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> developer Luke Dashjr lost a staggering $3.3 million due to a Pretty Good Privacy (PGP) key compromise. Last week on December 31, Dashjr&#8217;s wallet had several outgoing transactions totaling over 200 Bitcoins and an estimated $3.3 million as of the current BTC price.</p>
<p>In a message on Twitter this Sunday, January 1, Luke Dashjr <a href="https://twitter.com/LukeDashjr/status/1609621375349555204" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;PSA: My PGP key is compromised, and at least many of my bitcoins stolen. I have no idea how. Help please. Looks like some of it is coinjoined to 1YAR6opJCfDjBNdn5bV8b5Mcu84tv92fa&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a message later on Monday, the Bitcoin developer stated that it was &#8220;basically all gone&#8221;. The funds of the Bitcoin developer were lost due to the PGP or Pretty Good Privacy which is a cryptographic method to encrypt or decrypt data. This method can be used to encrypt information that is stored on the server. PGP helps to protect against unauthorized access or tampering. Keys generated through PGP can be useful to verify a specific piece of data like the legitimacy of a software download.</p>
<p>However, it isn&#8217;t clear yet what exactly led to the exploit. Many in the crypto community feel that the hacker may have gotten access to the server used by Dashjr in order to steal data. This also includes the private key to access his Bitcoin wallet. Back in November 2022, Dashjr acknowledged that his server was compromised.</p>
<h2>Crypto Community Weighs In</h2>
<p>The crypto community has weighed in on the recent incident indicating what might have led to a possible hack. Gustavo Gonzalez, solutions developer at OpenZeppelin noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The hack is still pretty fresh, so there is still not much clarity on what might have happened, besides PGP keys compromised and speculation that private keys might have been stolen from a previous server hack&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>Banteg, the pseudonymous developer of Yearn Finance <a href="https://twitter.com/bantg/status/1609740686298841090" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a> on Dashjr&#8217;s post stating that it might be a potential &#8220;supply chain attack&#8221;. Such attacks usually take place when a hacker enters and modifies software by injecting malicious code into the system.</p>
<p>The incident has got many eyeballs. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> chief <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a> stated that his team is monitoring the assets and that they would freeze them if sent to a centralized exchange.</p>
<p>The last year of 2022 witnessed several cryptocurrency hacks taking place in the market. Several billions of dollars worth of investors&#8217; money were lost last year. The decentralized finance (DeFi) market was the most affected.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/">Bitcoin Developers Loses Staggering $3.3M in PGP Exploit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-developers-3-3m-pgp-exploit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foxconn’s iPhone City Plant Runs at 90% Capacity</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231077</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/">Foxconn&#8217;s iPhone City Plant Runs at 90% Capacity</a></p>
<p> The factory's unflinching efforts to manufacture products will turn out to be profitable for the upcoming lunar New Year shopping season.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/">Foxconn&#8217;s iPhone City Plant Runs at 90% Capacity</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/">Foxconn&#8217;s iPhone City Plant Runs at 90% Capacity</a></p>
<p>The Foxconn group has suddenly become a center of attraction as its iPhone plant is allegedly <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-03/iphone-city-is-back-at-90-capacity-after-covid-turmoil-subsides" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">operating</a> at ninety percent of capacity, even when the world is struggling with the resurgence of COVID and the increased number of victims. The news indicates the ability of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a>&#8216;s major production associate to gather enough workers in the backdrop of the latest employee upheaval.</p>
<p>Hon Hai Precision Industry Co Ltd, which also operates as Foxconn globally, is a Taiwanese multinational electronic contract manufacturer founded in 1974 with an office in Tucheng, New Taipei City, Taiwan.</p>
<p>Foxconn owns a plant in the central Chinese city of Zhengzhou, which is presently functioning at a capacity of ninety thousand people, similar to any normal day number, as reported by Henan Daily while citing a company&#8217;s executive Vic Wang.</p>
<p>According to the report, on December 30th, the factory was exporting ninety percent of its peak manufacturing products at the beginning of the year. The factory&#8217;s unflinching efforts to manufacture products will turn out to be profitable for the upcoming lunar New Year shopping season.</p>
<p>China suffered a pan-country COVID resurgence as the government unceremoniously dropped all the related precautions. This made plans extremely uncertain for manufacturers like Foxconn whose entire operation is centered around collecting a large number of workers to run its factories.</p>
<p>The latest outbreak of COVID also gave rise to some of the most oppressive COVID precautionary measures by the administration, which was significantly condemned by citizens of China. Zhengzhou, which is also known as the iPhone city, produces a large number of high-end iPhone 14 Pro and Pro Max devices. It made news a month ago when several workers staged protests against the government demanding improved COVID curbs. The movement was massively supported by the people of the country and resonated with everyone suffering from the government&#8217;s aggression.</p>
<p>Foxconn has eased most of the regulations and offered multiple benefits to the employees and staff working in the plant.</p>
<p>The unwanted halt of the manufacturing business could have led to a massive loss in iPhone production before the upcoming shopping season. Apple, at one point, could have suffered a loss worth six million iPhones as a consequence of the obstruction.</p>
<p>On Saturday, the government-run broadcaster of the Henan region, where the plant is situated, stated that the factory was presently running at a stable number of around twenty thousand employees and that it had also smoothened its supply chain, allowing production capacity to rejuvenate.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/">Foxconn&#8217;s iPhone City Plant Runs at 90% Capacity</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-iphone-city-plant-capacity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Popularity Dominance Was Unshaken in 2022 but Ethereum (ETH) Outperformed in Total Transactions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/">Bitcoin (BTC) Popularity Dominance Was Unshaken in 2022 but Ethereum (ETH) Outperformed in Total Transactions</a></p>
<p>The Ethereum network has significantly benefited from the merge event, which reciprocated to higher on-chain activity on layer 2 protocols. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/">Bitcoin (BTC) Popularity Dominance Was Unshaken in 2022 but Ethereum (ETH) Outperformed in Total Transactions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/">Bitcoin (BTC) Popularity Dominance Was Unshaken in 2022 but Ethereum (ETH) Outperformed in Total Transactions</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>, Ethereum, and meme networks continued to lead the cryptocurrency market in 2022. According to statistical analysis from Google search trends, Bitcoin’s global monthly searches topped 28.4 million whilst <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> came in the fourth position with approximately 3.8 million. In between were <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dogecoin</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/shiba-inu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shiba Inu</a> with a total of approximately 5.8 million and 4.4 million respectively. However, ETH <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-transactions-338-higher-in-2022-but-bitcoin-remains-most-popular" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">outstripped</a> Bitcoin in the number of transactions in blockchain per day.</p>
<p>According to aggregate data from bitinfocharts.com, the number of transactions in a blockchain per day on ETH averaged approximately 1.2 million. On the other hand, the number of transactions in a blockchain per day on the Bitcoin network averaged about 200k in 2022.</p>
<p>In percentage points, there were approximately 338 percent more Ether transactions than Bitcoin in 2022.</p>
<p>The Ethereum network has significantly benefited from the merge event, which reciprocated to higher on-chain activity on layer 2 protocols. Furthermore, Ether’s proof-of-stake (PoS) &#8211;  introduced through the beacon chain- has significantly opened Ethereum’s overall throughput.</p>
<p>On the social media corridors, Twitter, for instance, Bitcoin outstretched Ethereum in tweets per day. Whereby Bitcoin recorded between 100k and 300k tweets per day whereas Ethereum posted less than 100k tweets per day.</p>
<p>In the United States Google monthly searches, Bitcoin ranked top with approximately 4.57 million while Ethereum recorded about 611,000 monthly searches. Other top ten digital assets ranked by Google trends in 2022 include Avalanche, Litecoin (LTC), Cardano (ADA), XRP, Safemoon, and Nexus.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at Bitcoin, Ethereum  and Entire Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market has sustained the ongoing bear market for more than twelve months. Thereby leading to liquidations of over $2.2 trillion in 2022. According to our latest crypto price oracles, Bitcoin price exchanged about $16,713 on Tuesday, with a market capitalization of approximately $321 billion. Ethereum price, on the other hand, traded at about $1,214 on Tuesday, with a market capitalization of approximately $146 billion. As a result, Bitcoin and Ethereum enjoyed a market dominance of approximately 38.3 percent and 17.4 percent respectively.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is struggling to recover from the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> and Alameda implosion, which has affected millions of users globally. For instance, Digital Currency Group &#8211; the parent company of Grayscale, Genesis Trading, CoinDesk, TradeBlock, LunoGlobal, and FoundryServices &#8211; announced significant exposure to the FTX and FTT market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Will you, or will you not, commit to solving this by January 8th in a manner that treats the $1.1 billion promissory note as $1.1 billion?</p>
<p>&mdash; Cameron Winklevoss (@cameron) <a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1609944270315868160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>While the SBF case is active in United States courts, more attention has been given to the Ripple vs SEC lawsuit. Furthermore, Hinman’s emails, which are likely to be revealed to the public, are expected to have profound implications on most DeFi tokens in the industry.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bahamian-securities-ftx-funds/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/">Bitcoin (BTC) Popularity Dominance Was Unshaken in 2022 but Ethereum (ETH) Outperformed in Total Transactions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/btc-popularity-eth-transactions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>