<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:59:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[animoca brands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitmain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moonpay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
<p>Companies like Circle, Ripple, and the non-fungible tokens (NFTs) marketplace OpenSea have happier employees.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
<p>Employee happiness is a crucial aspect of any industry, and the cryptocurrency space is no exception. However, recent data derived from Glassdoor indicates that staff satisfaction at popular crypto exchanges such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a>, Binance, and Coinbase is relatively low.</p>
<p>The tech recruitment firm TrueUp <a href="https://www.trueup.io/crypto/trends#layoffs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">collected</a> data from Glassdoor to assess employee happiness and growth in 27 prominent crypto firms. The results were presented in a quadrant chart, which revealed that bankrupt crypto lender Celsius, digital assets trading platform Amber Group, and virtual asset service provider Gemini had the least happy employees based on reviews from 80, 139, and 42 individuals, respectively. Binance and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> were also positioned on the left side of the chart, indicating lower employee satisfaction, with a total of 1,257 <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Gemini-Reviews-E1400858.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reviews</a>.</p>
<p>It is important to note that Glassdoor does not provide a specific happiness metric. Instead, it evaluates employee sentiment through indicators such as the likelihood of recommending the company, approval of the CEO, and overall outlook. These metrics offer valuable insights into employee satisfaction within the crypto industry and serve as a basis for further analysis.</p>
<p>In the past year, Coinbase CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> responded strongly to employees expressing dissatisfaction, suggesting they should consider quitting. The response came after a group of staff filed a petition calling for the removal of certain executives, including chief operating officer Emilie Choi, chief product officer Surojit Chatterjee, and chief people officer LJ Brock, citing unrealistic demands from the executives as the reason for their request.</p>
<p>&#8216;We, the employees at Coinbase, believe that the executive team has recently been making decisions that are not in the best interests of the company, its employees, and its shareholders,&#8221; the petition read.</p>
<h2>Circle, Ripple, and OpenSea: Higher Staff Satisfaction</h2>
<p>However, not all companies in the digital asset sector face employee dissatisfaction. According to the TrueUp data, companies like Circle, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a>, and the non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) marketplace OpenSea have happier employees. Other virtual asset service providers, such as Chainalysis, Fireblocks, Ava Labs, and Immutable, also rank in the same category.</p>
<p>When it comes to growth, companies like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, Coinbase, Blockchain.com, Bitpanda, and Gemini have experienced significant expansion over the years. These crypto service providers have established themselves as key players in the emerging economy, attracting users and investors from around the world. The TrueUp data also identified Animoca Brands, MoonPay, and Bitmain as crypto firms that have experienced rapid growth.</p>
<h2>Binance Responds to the Data Claim</h2>
<p>In response to the data, Binance emphasized its commitment to hiring individuals who excel in high-performance environments and are dedicated to delivering for users. The company&#8217;s spokesperson <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-coinbase-gemini-staff-among-least-happy-glassdoor" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> Cointelegraph that not all employees may align with their &#8220;hardcore&#8221; values, which could contribute to negative reviews stating that Binance sees feedback as an opportunity for growth and continuously strives to enhance the employee experience.</p>
<p>&#8220;It also means that sometimes, we have some who are not able to thrive in this unique, brutally fast environment, and we have to accept some negative reviews as a result,&#8221; the Binance spokesperson explained.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/">Unhappy Staff: Binance, Coinbase, and Gemini Rank Low in Job Satisfaction</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/unhappy-staff-binance-coinbase-gemini/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alex mashinsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius bankruptcy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>CFTC investigators claim that they have reasons to believe that the bankrupt lender and its former CEO violated the rules of the agency.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>It appears that yet another trouble may be lurking around the corner for failed crypto lender Celsius Network and its former CEO Alex Mashinsky. According to a recent Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/cftc-probe-concludes-crypto-lender-celsius-ex-ceo-mashinsky-broke-rules?sref=3REHEaVI#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) might already be building a case against the firm and Mashinsky. The report also claims that the case may even surface as early as this July, per inside sources.</p>
<h2>Celsius CEO Allegedly Misled Investors</h2>
<p>Bloomberg reports that CFTC investigators claim that they have reasons to believe that the bankrupt lender and its former CEO violated the rules of the agency. That is, in terms of misleading investors. So, if a majority of the CFTC’s commissioners can agree to pursue a case, then there will be a case.</p>
<p>The new submission by CFTC is similar to the report of former prosecutor Shoba Pillay. After Celsius <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-files-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for US bankruptcy last July, US Bankruptcy Judge Martin Glenn, who is overseeing the bankruptcy proceedings, appointed Pillay as an independent examiner.</p>
<p>Her duty was to find out if there was any truth to Celsius customers&#8217; claims that the firm was indeed a Ponzi scheme. She was also tasked with reporting on Celsius&#8217; handling of cryptocurrency deposits.</p>
<p>However, the examiner&#8217;s report wasn&#8217;t exactly conclusive at the time. Pillay determined that there were times when Celsius truly operated like a Ponzi scheme. She said Celsius did not exactly disclose to its customers, the risks it took with their crypto assets. The report read in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“How Celsius ran its business differed significantly from what Celsius told its customers.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As of publication, the CFTC is yet to make an official statement regarding the potential case, whereas efforts to reach Celsius’ press have also proved abortive.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it might also be worth noting that the Securities and Exchange Commission and federal prosecutors in Manhattan are also looking into Celsius. That is according to bankruptcy <a title="bankruptcy court filing" href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11827/PLEADINGS/1182710062280000000010.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filings</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/">Celsius Ex-CEO Risk to Face CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-ex-ceo-cftc-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samsung’s Profits Likely to Tank to 14-Year-Low as Chip Sales Slow Down</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261860</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/">Samsung&#8217;s Profits Likely to Tank to 14-Year-Low as Chip Sales Slow Down</a></p>
<p>Amid a major slowdown in the semiconductor market, Samsung's operating profits for the April-June quarter could be the lowest since 2008. Samsung is focusing on expanding its presence in the field of artificial intelligence (AI).</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/">Samsung&#8217;s Profits Likely to Tank to 14-Year-Low as Chip Sales Slow Down</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/">Samsung&#8217;s Profits Likely to Tank to 14-Year-Low as Chip Sales Slow Down</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung Electronics</a> could see a major dip in its profits likely to tank as much as 96% on a year-on-year basis. It means that the profits for the company will be the lowest this quarter, in the last 14 years.</p>
<p>The major dent in the company&#8217;s bottom line comes as the tech giant&#8217;s cash cow business of chip sales is seeing a major slowdown. Samsung is the world&#8217;s largest chip manufacturer currently and the slowdown in the chips business has been eating majorly into the company&#8217;s profits.</p>
<p>Analysts at Refinitiv SmartEstimate note that the in the April-June quarter, the operating profit for Samsung shall drop to 555 billion won ($427 million). This would be a significant drop in the operating profits of 14.1 trillion won during the same quarter last year.</p>
<p>This is because the chip division, which has historically been the company&#8217;s main source of profit, is likely to experience losses of approximately 3 to 4 trillion won in the quarter. These losses can be attributed to the declining prices of memory chips and the reduction in inventory values.</p>
<p>If so, it would mean that Samsung will be recording the lowest quarterly profit since the fourth quarter of 2008. Back in that year, Samsung Electronics had reported a consolidated profit of 740 billion won.</p>
<h2>Samsung Faces Brunt of Falling Chip Prices</h2>
<p>During the last quarter, the price of DRAM memory chips &#8211; widely used in PCs, smartphones, and servers &#8211; continued to drop by 13-18%, as per TrendForce. This is because chip buyers refrained from purchasing new chips as well as used-up inventories, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-profit-likely-lowest-more-than-14-years-chip-glut-persists-2023-07-05/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> Reuters.</p>
<p>However, the decrease in prices of memory chips has slowed down compared to previous quarters. Experts predict that the prices will reach the lowest point around the third quarter and a significant recovery might not happen until 2024.</p>
<p>Despite the challenging market conditions, Samsung is focusing on expanding its presence in the field of artificial intelligence (AI). This includes areas like high bandwidth memory (HBM) and chip contract manufacturing.</p>
<p>In terms of its mobile business, Samsung is expected to report an operating profit of around 3.3 trillion won. This is because cost-cutting measures have offset a slight decline in smartphone shipments compared to the first quarter when Samsung released its latest flagship model.</p>
<p>Later this month in July, Samsung will be unveiling its latest foldable smartphone in Seoul. Analysts expect it to dominate the premium smartphone market at least until <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> releases its next iPhone version.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/">Samsung&#8217;s Profits Likely to Tank to 14-Year-Low as Chip Sales Slow Down</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsungs-profits-low-chip-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO Expects Heavy Trading Volumes in Next 6-18 Months, Prepares Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/">Binance CEO Expects Heavy Trading Volumes in Next 6-18 Months, Prepares Exchange</a></p>
<p>Binance chief Changpeng Zhao said that he continues to remain bullish on crypto for the long term, and as per historical trends, the next bull run should happen in 2025. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/">Binance CEO Expects Heavy Trading Volumes in Next 6-18 Months, Prepares Exchange</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/">Binance CEO Expects Heavy Trading Volumes in Next 6-18 Months, Prepares Exchange</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, July 5, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a> said that he&#8217;s expecting heavy trading volumes in the crypto space over the next few months. As a result, he has been preparing the crypto trading p[latform in this regard.</p>
<p>CZ&#8217;s comments came during a Twitter Spaces &#8220;ask me anything&#8221; event stating that the company has been doing a lot of preparations to ready its systems during the possible surge in trading activity. &#8220;If we look at historical patterns, we want to be prepared for higher volumes,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Volumes have been increasing in recent weeks, marking a shift from the low activity seen since the collapse of the FTX exchange in November. Zhao mentioned various factors contributing to this recent surge, including the filing of new spot Bitcoin ETFs and the upcoming Bitcoin halving event anticipated to take place in April or May of 2024.</p>
<p>On the other hand, institutional interest in the crypto space is also growing as trading activity in Bitcoin derivative products shoots up. In June, the trading volume of Bitcoin futures on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME) rose by 28.6% to reach $37.9 billion. Additionally, the value of Bitcoin Micro Futures increased by 21.1% to $702 million, as per <a href="https://ccdata.io/reports/exchange-review-june-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CCData</a>.</p>
<p>There was also a notable increase in Ethereum-based instruments, with over 97,000 ETH Futures contracts traded, representing a 10.8% increase. The trading volume for these contracts reached $46.8 billion, marking a 24.6% increase when valued in USD.</p>
<h2>Binance Chief Is Bullish on Crypto</h2>
<p>Zhao said that as per the historical patterns, there&#8217;s a bull run every four years in the market. As a result, he expects that the next bull run could happen in 2025, as &#8220;the year after Bitcoin halving is usually the bull year&#8221;.</p>
<p>Although he admitted that it&#8217;s hard to predict the future, Zhao said that he remains bullish for the long term. &#8220;We&#8217;re still very early. I think the industry still has a lot of room to grow,&#8221; Zhao <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/237907/binance-cz-crypto-trading-volumes" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>. &#8220;So I&#8217;m always bullish. I&#8217;m a builder, so I always have a positive outlook on things.&#8221;</p>
<p>Binance is currently involved in a legal dispute with U.S. regulators, including the Commodity Futures Trading Commission and the Securities and Exchange Commission. The allegations suggest that Binance, as well as Zhao, violated federal laws. Regarding these lawsuits, Zhao expressed Binance&#8217;s intention to find a swift and fair resolution that satisfies all parties involved.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/">Binance CEO Expects Heavy Trading Volumes in Next 6-18 Months, Prepares Exchange</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-trading-volumes-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of England Partners with Nuggets to Boost CBDC Privacy and Security</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of england]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital pound]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuggets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261719</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/">Bank of England Partners with Nuggets to Boost CBDC Privacy and Security</a></p>
<p>Nuggets is also working with the European Commission's Joint Research Centre to develop a privacy-preserving solution for cross-border payments.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/">Bank of England Partners with Nuggets to Boost CBDC Privacy and Security</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/">Bank of England Partners with Nuggets to Boost CBDC Privacy and Security</a></p>

<p>The Bank of England is a step closer to issuing a digital pound, thanks to its partnership with Nuggets, a blockchain-based identity and payments platform. The duo will work together to design a privacy layer for the UK&#8217;s proposed retail <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>.</p>
<p>Nuggets has previously worked with the Bank of International Settlements and the Bank of England on Project Rosalind. The project explored the use of self-sovereign identity (SSI) for CBDCs. Based on this work, the Bank of England asked Nuggets to investigate and design the identity and privacy layer for its proposed digital pound.</p>
<h2>What to Expect</h2>
<p>According to Nuggets co-founder Alastair Johnson, the feature would use anonymous connections to swap and verify credentials without revealing the user&#8217;s identity. He added that the layer is &#8220;an important step in ensuring that the CBDC is both secure and privacy-preserving&#8221;. Thus, it will use Zero-Knowledge proofs to allow users to control and keep their data private. Again, the layer will be designed to meet strict anti-fraud and anti-money laundering standards.</p>
<p>The Bank of England has been exploring the possibility of issuing a digital pound for several years. In 2020, it published a discussion paper on the topic. Later in 2021, it launched a public consultation on the issue. However, the financial services minister Andrew Griffith has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-financial-services-minister-urges-caution-over-central-bank-digital-currency-2023-07-04/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">warned</a> against issuing a digital pound because of privacy and security issues. Nuggets&#8217; privacy layer could be the critical component to ensure the currency is secure and privacy-preserving.</p>
<h2>Nuggets’ Privacy Solutions: A Game Changer?</h2>
<p>As central banks around the world pursue CBDC development, a key concern in many quarters is how to balance privacy with the need for financial transparency. Nuggets&#8217; privacy solutions could very well be what helps to address this key challenge.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Nuggets is also working on other projects to enhance privacy and security. It is working with the European Commission&#8217;s Joint Research Centre (JRC) to develop a privacy-preserving solution for cross-border payments. It has also partnered with the University of Oxford to develop a data protection solution for healthcare data. Furthermore, Nuggets is collaborating with the World Economic Forum to shape the future of digital identity and payments in the post-pandemic era.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/">Bank of England Partners with Nuggets to Boost CBDC Privacy and Security</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-england-nuggets-cbdc-privacy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Exec Finds and Returns $322K Worth of Lost Crypto to User Unaware of Its Existence</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/">Coinbase Exec Finds and Returns $322K Worth of Lost Crypto to User Unaware of Its Existence</a></p>
<p>According to the Coinbase exec, the owner likely got the lost crypto from a 2018 ETC airdrop when the Ethereum blockchain forked.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/">Coinbase Exec Finds and Returns $322K Worth of Lost Crypto to User Unaware of Its Existence</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/">Coinbase Exec Finds and Returns $322K Worth of Lost Crypto to User Unaware of Its Existence</a></p>
<p>A Coinbase exec has surprised a lucky person with lost crypto they never knew existed. Conor Grogan, Coinbase’s head of product, revealed that he found lost crypto worth hundreds of thousands and successfully found the owner of the assets.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/jconorgrogan/status/1676689354071199744?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1676689354071199744%7Ctwgr%5E9a8faa7f2aeb28fe01ad0235ae98ba10716b1ab4%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fcoinbase-conor-grogan-uncovers-thousands-lost-etc" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a> posted on Wednesday, Grogan said he “found 322K for a stranger who previously lost their life savings in a hack”. He attached a screenshot showing address details and the $322,873 balance in Ethereum Classic (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum-classic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETC</a>).</p>
<p>The Coinbase exec then explained how the lost crypto came about. Back in 2016, a hard fork occurred on the Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) blockchain and created Ethereum Classic. At the time, anyone with an ETH balance received a 1:1 airdrop of the new ETC. According to Grogan, many had no idea they received ETC tokens and likely have money they don’t know exists.</p>
<p>&#8220;Forgetting you have funds onchain (or not keeping track of airdrops) is common. I’ve found 6+ figures for people previously,&#8221; <a href="https://www.theblock.co/amp/post/237996/coinbase-director-finds-lost-crypto-worth-320000-for-stranger" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> he.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Exec Grogan Provides Details on Locating the Lost Crypto</h2>
<p>Grogan then explained how he found the assets. The Coinbase exec said he combed the “ETC rich list” to find accounts with unmoved ETC balances. This process resulted in about 20 accounts holding balances of at least $250,000 without any corresponding activity. Although he began trying to trace them, Grogan said he ran into dead ends.</p>
<p>The saving grace for the one he eventually found was a connection to an EOSDAC coin. Apparently, EOS holders received an EOSDAC airdop via Ethereum back in 2018, using their registered ETH addresses. Grogan then used the amount and snapshot date to find the EOS wallet. He then used this information to find the legal name of the person who owns the ETH address and reached out. The Coinbase exec ended the thread with a screenshotted reply from the account owner, who didn’t know the lost crypto existed and didn’t know the same address applied at the time of the airdrop.</p>
<p>As part of the thread, Grogan <a href="https://twitter.com/jconorgrogan/status/1676689372534505473?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tagged</a> Tron founder and Poloniex owner Justin Sun, informing that several Poloniex wallets have “significant untouched ETC balances”.</p>
<h2>Lost Assets are not Uncommon</h2>
<p>Crypto investors may regularly lose access to their assets for different reasons. In many cases, crypto assets are lost due to user mistakes. A user may send crypto from one wallet to another and mistype the receiving wallet address. In other cases, users may mistakenly choose a different network as the receiving address, forgetting to confirm that the sending and receiving networks are the same. According to a 2018 Chanalysis conclusion referenced in a Wall Street Journal (WSJ) <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-fifth-of-all-bitcoin-is-missing-these-crypto-hunters-can-help-1530798731" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">article</a>, 20% of all Bitcoin is lost, with most unrecoverable.</p>
<p>However, hacks are responsible for most lost crypto. Since its inception, the crypto industry has suffered its fair share of hacking attempts, many of which are successful for hackers. According to blockchain security firm Beosin, hacks and other types of schemes and scams account for <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1674618821766971392" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">$656 million in lost crypto</a> for Q1 of 2023.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/">Coinbase Exec Finds and Returns $322K Worth of Lost Crypto to User Unaware of Its Existence</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-exec-322k-lost-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Three US States Give Twitter Money Transmitter Licenses, More to Come?</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[venmo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261843</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/">Three US States Give Twitter Money Transmitter Licenses, More to Come?</a></p>
<p>Although there are no specific details on what to expect from Twitter following the money transmitter licenses, insiders believe that Twitter Payments will start offering fiat currency services.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/">Three US States Give Twitter Money Transmitter Licenses, More to Come?</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/">Three US States Give Twitter Money Transmitter Licenses, More to Come?</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s vision to create new pathways for revenue is gradually coming to fruition as Twitter Payments LLC received its first set of <a href="https://www.nmlsconsumeraccess.org/EntityDetails.aspx/COMPANY/2404946#RegulatoryActions" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">money transmitter licenses</a> in three US states. Reports revealed in January that the social networking service provider had started submitting applications for regulatory licenses in the US. People with knowledge of the matter revealed that Twitter’s Esther Crawford was working with a team on the requirements to facilitate payments on the platform. The company applied for licenses in all 50 states in the US and is looking forward to their responses.</p>
<h2>Twitter Gets Money Transmitter Licenses from Three US States</h2>
<p>After completing regulatory checks, Michigan, New Hampshire, and Missouri have issued money transmitter licenses to Twitter. The company can now offer transfer services or payment instruments, another profit stream. Missouri gave Twitter a sale of checks and money transmitter licenses, which typically provides consumer protection for businesses that process money transmission.</p>
<p>Since the billionaire took over the company in October, its advertising business, which was a major source of income, had declined. The $5 billion-a-year ad business got hit due to marketers’ concerns over management and content moderation. However, it appears Twitter is set for a fresh pipeline of profits. Elon Musk has been vocal about his visions, including his desire for Twitter to offer fintech services. The chief executive said he wants the social network company to offer fintech services like P2P transactions, debit cards, savings, accounts, and more. All his plans are towards his vision of an “everything app” combining payments, messaging, and commerce.</p>
<p>Although there are no specific details on what to expect from Twitter following the money transmitter licenses, insiders believe that Twitter Payments will start offering fiat currency services. The people familiar with the matter stated that the company may roll out similar operations with Venmo, Stripe, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL).</p>
<h2>Musk&#8217;s Visions for Twitter</h2>
<p>Furthermore, Musk’s vision for Twitter goes beyond getting the money transmitter licenses. The company reportedly plans to expand the platform to accommodate crypto services. This does not come as a surprise as Musk is a known crypto fanatic, and his influence on a particular cryptocurrency has caused the asset to surge exponentially. In addition to the crypto service, another rumor is that Twitter Payments wants to launch a project dubbed “Twitter Coin”. More so, reports revealed that Twitter will unveil its own wallet.</p>
<p>Already, Musk had hinted that “Twitter would do lots of dumb things”, which is now evident in its successful push for money transmitter licenses in the US. The billionaire has made multiple changes within the company, including the most recent view limits on all users.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/">Three US States Give Twitter Money Transmitter Licenses, More to Come?</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-money-transmitter-licenses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta’s Threads App Goes Live on Apple App and Google Play Stores</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261866</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/">Meta’s Threads App Goes Live on Apple App and Google Play Stores</a></p>
<p>The app is primarily geared towards text-based conversations, and users will have the ability to publish Threads posts with up to 500 characters.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/">Meta’s Threads App Goes Live on Apple App and Google Play Stores</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/">Meta’s Threads App Goes Live on Apple App and Google Play Stores</a></p>
<p>In an age where social networking platforms abound, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), Facebook&#8217;s parent company, has launched Threads. The new app caters to users’ desire for a more streamlined and visually appealing messaging experience.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/amp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">much-anticipated</a> Threads, now available for free on the Apple App Store and Google Play online store in over 100 countries, offers a unique combination of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a>’s visual aesthetic and a text-based social messaging interface.</p>
<p>Announced in a <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2023/07/introducing-threads-new-app-text-sharing/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> by Meta, Threads aims to enhance the way people connect and communicate with each other. By integrating elements from Twitter&#8217;s visual style, the app provides a refreshing departure from traditional messaging applications.</p>
<p>According to screenshots available on the Apple App Store, Threads allows users to post short messages, which can be liked, shared and commented on by others. This format encourages concise and focused communication, facilitating meaningful interactions among users.</p>
<p>With Threads, Meta introduces a new way to communicate on Instagram, expanding beyond the realm of images and videos. The app embraces the concept of text-based conversations, resembling the structure of Twitter, where concise messages take the center stage.</p>
<p>While Threads is closely linked to Instagram and allows users to use their existing Instagram usernames, it is important to note that it is a separate app that users will need to download.</p>
<p>In a remarkable feat, the newly launched Threads app by Meta has already garnered tremendous attention and user adoption. As stated by Meta’s CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a> within four hours of its introduction, the app has recorded over 5 million sign-ups, an extraordinary achievement that highlights the strong appeal and interest surrounding the new social media application.</p>
<h2>Factors Contributing to the Success of Threads Launched by Meta</h2>
<p>Notably, the release of Threads by Meta coincides with a period of challenges and criticisms being faced by Twitter under the ownership of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>. The CEO of Tesla Inc (NASDAQ: TSLA), recently decided to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-daily-tweet-views-ceo-efforts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">impose</a> a temporary “rate limit” on Twitter, restricting the number of tweets users can see per day.</p>
<p>With its combination of concise text-based conversations and visual appeal, Threads offers a unique proposition that may attract users who are dissatisfied with the temporary limitations imposed by Twitter.</p>
<p>Additionally, its connection to Meta and the larger Facebook ecosystem inspires confidence and comfort. Its rapid adoption is facilitated by users&#8217; propensity to use new apps from well-known developers.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the distinctive features of Threads have likely contributed to its early adoption and success. One of the notable features mentioned is the inclusion of &#8220;threads&#8221; in users&#8217; individual feeds. These threads are posts made by other users that the individual follows, ensuring that users can stay updated on the content shared by their connections.</p>
<p>The app is primarily geared towards text-based conversations, and users will have the ability to publish Threads posts with up to 500 characters. However, Meta recognizes the importance of multimedia content and allows users to share links, photos, and videos with a duration of up to 5 minutes.</p>
<p>This versatility enables users to express themselves in various formats and enrich their conversations. Additionally, Meta has incorporated tools for content filtering, user management, and privacy control, promoting a safe and enjoyable user experience within the app.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/">Meta’s Threads App Goes Live on Apple App and Google Play Stores</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-threads-app-goes-live/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMF Seeks Ways to Tax Crypto Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/">IMF Seeks Ways to Tax Crypto Assets</a></p>
<p>To tax crypto, the IMF explained that the distributed ledger technology could be helpful.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/">IMF Seeks Ways to Tax Crypto Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/">IMF Seeks Ways to Tax Crypto Assets</a></p>
<p>According to the International Monetary Fund (IMF), tens of billions of dollars of crypto tax are still out there. The financial agency noted that governments are yet to address all the possible ways to tax <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto</a>. Even if the crypto tax has no hindrances, the IMF noted the challenges in processing the action. The group released a paper on “taxing cryptocurrencies” to discuss the problems with accommodating crypto assets within the tax systems. The research did not fail to mention that the tax system is not designed for crypto, causing a significant struggle to home them. Notably, the tax systems were in place way before the emergence of blockchain technology, which has given birth to several assets.</p>
<h2>IMF Investigates Crypto Tax and Suggests How to Gather the Pending Taxes</h2>
<p>In the paper, the IMF noted that the “semi-anonymity” of crypto makes it difficult to tax the asset. The group also referred to its dual nature, which includes an investment vehicle and means of payment. In addition, high volatility is common to cryptocurrencies, and this is a major challenge for tax collections. As a matter of fact, there is no consensus on how to tax cryptocurrency &#8211; whether as gambling, capital gains, or income. The paper stated that crypto is not specifically influential in evading taxes considering its high fees and volatility. It noted the exploration of green taxation but called for more mechanisms to help the current situation.</p>
<p>Summarizing the challenges policymakers face to tax crypto, the IMF <a href="https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WP/Issues/2023/06/30/Taxing-Cryptocurrencies-535510" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The greatest challenges are for implementation: crypto’s quasi-anonymity is an inherent obstacle to third-party reporting. Design problems arise from cryptocurrencies’ dual nature as investment assets and means of payment: more straightforward is a compelling case for corrective taxation of carbon-intensive mining. Ownership is highly concentrated at the top, but many crypto investors have only moderate incomes. The capital gains tax revenue at stake worldwide may be in the tens of billions of dollars, but the more profound risks may ultimately be for VAT/sales taxes.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The financial group added that the high adoption of crypto in growing economies where there is a limit to collection technology is another setback. The category of crypto holders &#8211; the smallholders and the whales also causes the IMF not to tax crypto. The retail crypto holders require a different approach compared to the whales that hold larger portions. Hence, there is a need for a proper tax design. The agency also spoke of anonymous transactions, noting that that could result in anonymous transactions.</p>
<p>To tax crypto, the IMF explained that the distributed ledger technology could be helpful too. It referred to the technology’s transparency, which could help trace transaction history and eventually be used in administering the due taxes. It added that “the use of smart contracts (self-executing programs) within blockchains, for example, might in principle help secure chains of VAT compliance and enforce withholding”.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/">IMF Seeks Ways to Tax Crypto Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-tax-crypto-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>General Motors Announces 19% Increase in Vehicle Deliveries YoY in Q2 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[general motors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mary barra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261840</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/">General Motors Announces 19% Increase in Vehicle Deliveries YoY in Q2 2023</a></p>
<p>General Motors is expected to release detailed Q2 earnings results on July 25.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/">General Motors Announces 19% Increase in Vehicle Deliveries YoY in Q2 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/">General Motors Announces 19% Increase in Vehicle Deliveries YoY in Q2 2023</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">General Motors Co</a> (NYSE: GM), a Detroit-based automaker with several vehicle subsidiaries, announced its second-quarter sales on Wednesday, July 05. According to the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/05/gm-second-quarter-2023-new-vehicle-sales.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, General Motors delivered 691,978 vehicles in the United States during the second quarter, up approximately 19 percent Year over Year. The company announced that all its four subsidiaries delivered double-digit increases in sales YoY. During the second quarter, GM announced that its EV section delivered about 15,652 units to the market.</p>
<p>However, the company recorded a significant decline in first-quarter sales, which resulted in a mixed reaction on its stock market. During the first quarter of 2023, General Motors reported total vehicle sales of about 1.3 million including more than 36k electric vehicles. As a result, GM shares closed Wednesday trading at $39.42, up approximately 1.18 percent from the day’s opening price. However, GM shares dropped approximately 0.15 percent during the after-hours trading session. Nonetheless, the company’s stock market has gained approximately 17 percent YTD.</p>
<h2>General Motors and Its Market Performance</h2>
<p>Undeniably, the company has lagged behind the electric vehicle industry compared to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) which has significantly dominated the American market. As a result, the company has been blamed for not ramping up production of EVs amid the global transition. For comparison purposes, Tesla produced nearly 480k electric vehicles during the second quarter alone and delivered more than 466k units to customers.</p>
<p>The slow transition of General Motors from combustion engines to electric vehicles has seen its global market share decline as more countries champion greener energy.</p>
<p>In the company’s defense, GM CEO Mary Barra highlighted that its EV sector has significantly been hampered by battery production that has been taking longer than expected. Notably, its competitor Tesla has an in-house battery production site that has significantly streamlined its supply chain.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the company is expected to significantly increase its EV production especially after Tesla confirmed that its charging spots can be used by other EV companies including General Motors. The move is in line with the Biden administration&#8217;s to help struggling electric vehicle companies rise and create more jobs.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Thanks to the Bipartisan Infrastructure Law, we’ve already announced over 25,000 infrastructure projects in 4,500 towns across America.</p>
<p>Union workers are building roads and bridges, laying internet cable, and installing 500,000 electric vehicle chargers throughout America.</p>
<p>— Joe Biden (@JoeBiden) <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeBiden/status/1670579899625603072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>During the second half of the year, General Motors has planned to unveil several electric vehicle models including the Chevrolet Silverado, Blazer,  Equinox, and a $300,000-plus bespoke Cadillac EV dubbed the Celestiq. Previously, the company heavily relied on Chevrolet Bolt models in its EV sales but announced the model will be discontinued during the second half of 2023.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the company is expected to release detailed Q2 earnings results on July 25.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-web3go-4m-seed-funding/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/">General Motors Announces 19% Increase in Vehicle Deliveries YoY in Q2 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/general-motors-deliveries-q2-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4111 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1098118 metric#prefetches=204 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=99.74 metric#ms-cache=5.06 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2412 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.1 -->