<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:14:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance.US Hires Former SEC Director In Defence to Fraud and Manipulation Charges</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-us-hires-former-sec-director-in-defence-to-fraud-and-manipulation-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After strong allegations from the US SEC last week, Binance.US is now preparing its defense and has recently hired four lawyers from Milbank LLP, along with George Canellos, the co-director of the Securities and Exchange Commission’s enforcement division. Binance.US faces charges of operating as an illegal securities exchange. Canellos is currently the global head of <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-hires-former-sec-director-in-defence-to-fraud-and-manipulation-charges/" title="Binance.US Hires Former SEC Director In Defence to Fraud and Manipulation Charges"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-hires-former-sec-director-in-defence-to-fraud-and-manipulation-charges/">Binance.US Hires Former SEC Director In Defence to Fraud and Manipulation Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="640" height="384" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07102744/binance.us_.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Binance.US" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>After strong allegations from the US SEC last week, Binance.US is now preparing its defense and has recently hired four lawyers from Milbank LLP, along with George Canellos, the co-director of the Securities and Exchange Commission’s enforcement division.</p>
<p>Binance.US faces charges of operating as an illegal securities exchange. Canellos is currently the global head of the litigation and arbitration group at Milbank. He has previously supervised over 1,300 attorneys at the SEC on several investigations. Commenting on hiring George Canellos, John Reed Stark, former head of SEC’s Office of Internet Enforcement <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/binance-us-hires-former-sec-enforcement-co-director-as-it-fights-charges-1.1932139" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Canellos possesses a rare and remarkably special combination of skill sets — having served as both an SEC prosecutor and a DOJ prosecutor. Think Liam Neeson meets Perry Mason&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>As said, three other attorneys will also be joining the defense team for Binance.US. On June 5, the SEC filed a lawsuit against Binance.US, the global Binance exchange, and its owner Changpeng Zhao. The lawsuit accuses them of breaking securities laws in the US by mishandling customer funds and misleading investors and regulators. To protect customer funds, the SEC asked the court to freeze Binance.US&#8217;s assets temporarily. Binance has denied the allegations made by the SEC.</p>
<p>Following the SEC action, several banks showed the intent to <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-signals-cutting-off-from-banking-partners-liquidity-crisis-ahead/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cut ties with Binance.US</a> after which it decide to suspend USD deposits.</p>
<h3>Binance.US Defends Fraud and Manipulation Charges</h3>
<p>On Monday, Binance.US submitted a new court filing wherein they noted that the exchange has “made significant efforts” in order to cooperate with the US SEC since December 2020.</p>
<p>It is the first time the company has disputed the claims made by the SEC, which accused Binance.US and its parent company of redirecting over $12 billion in customer assets to funds controlled by Changpeng &#8216;CZ&#8217; Zhao, the owner and founder.</p>
<p>The US SEC has also accused Zhao of commingling customer assets along with funds controlled by the Binance chief. Responding to it, lawyers representing Binance.US&#8217;s parent company, BAM Trading, said it &#8220;<span id="page41R_mcid4" class="markedContent"><span dir="ltr" role="presentation">maintains its customers’ fiat currency in segregated accounts maintained </span><span dir="ltr" role="presentation">with its banking partners, separate from any corporate funds.&#8221;</span></span></p>
<p>Binance.US acknowledged that Changpeng &#8216;CZ&#8217; Zhao owns the bank account of BAM Trading but denied that he has signatory authority over the account. The SEC, on the other hand, argues that Zhao has control over those bank accounts, which indicates a lack of separation between Binance and Binance.US. It is believed that Zhao owns a controlling stake in both entities.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a glimpse into the share of Binance.US has tanked over the last two months, now at just 4.8%.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In just 2 months, <a href="https://t.co/pup2WYms9R">https://t.co/pup2WYms9R</a>&#39;s market share has fallen from more than 20% to just 4.8% relative to its closest U.S. competitors <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/Rm2DxJ9fAL">pic.twitter.com/Rm2DxJ9fAL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Kaiko (@KaikoData) <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1668357755885764611?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-hires-former-sec-director-in-defence-to-fraud-and-manipulation-charges/">Binance.US Hires Former SEC Director In Defence to Fraud and Manipulation Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/07102744/binance.us_.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US Seeks To Revoke US SEC&#8217;s Request To Freeze Its Funds</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-us-seeks-to-revoke-us-secs-request-to-freeze-its-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Pratap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance.US has urged a federal judge to reject the US SEC’s request to freeze assets on the cryptocurrency exchange during a legal fight with the regulator. Binance’s US arm has argued that freezing its assets would cripple its business and hurt customers, Bloomberg reported. “Operations would quickly grind to a halt” Without the ability to <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-seeks-to-revoke-us-secs-request-to-freeze-its-funds/" title="Binance.US Seeks To Revoke US SEC&#8217;s Request To Freeze Its Funds"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-seeks-to-revoke-us-secs-request-to-freeze-its-funds/">Binance.US Seeks To Revoke US SEC&#8217;s Request To Freeze Its Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06122903/Binance-Outflows-Remain-Within-Historical-Levels-Amid-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="binance sec lawsuit" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Binance.US has urged a federal judge to reject the US SEC’s request to freeze assets on the cryptocurrency exchange during a legal fight with the regulator. Binance’s US arm has argued that freezing its assets would cripple its business and hurt customers, Bloomberg <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-12/binance-us-says-asset-freeze-sought-by-sec-will-cripple-exchange?leadSource=uverify%20wall#xj4y7vzkg">reported</a>.</p>
<h2>“Operations would quickly grind to a halt”</h2>
<p>Without the ability to pay employees, vendors, suppliers and professionals or to maintain the trading platform, the operations will quickly grind to a halt, Binance.US attorneys said Monday in a court filing. “With a freeze of all corporate assets, banking partners would most likely cease to honor requests to transfer funds for any purpose, including customer redemptions,” the exchange added.</p>
<p>The SEC had <a href="https://coingape.com/sec-asks-to-freeze-binance-us-assets-funds-are-safu-says-binance/">requested the federal court to seize assets</a> of  Binance.US, after it sued Binance entities and founder Changpeng Zhao last week, alleging “blatant disregard of US securities laws” and “years of violative conduct” that puts customer funds at risk.</p>
<h2>Binance assures US customer assets are safe</h2>
<p>Binance.US attorneys further argued in their court filing that US customer assets are safe and said “there is no need for the draconian relief sought by the SEC.” As reported earlier, the US SEC had filed an emergency action application for a temporary restraining order to freeze Binance.US’s assets in an attempt to protect customer funds, including through repatriation of client investments held abroad. Binance has aggressively disputed the allegations.</p>
<h2>Proposed Bill Seeks To Fire SEC Chair</h2>
<p>On Monday, Republican lawmaker Warren Davidson <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-republicans-introduce-bill-remove-sec-chair-gary-gensler">introduced</a> the “SEC Stabilization Act” into the House of Representatives. One of the bill’s main provisions is to fire the SEC chair Gary Gensler. Along with removing the SEC chair Gary Gensler, the bill would redistribute the power between SEC chair and commissioner. Though the Republican lawmakers did not specifically mention cryptocurrencies in their statements, both the lawmakers Warren Davidason and Tom Emmer have a positive stance on crypto.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-us-seeks-to-revoke-us-secs-request-to-freeze-its-funds/">Binance.US Seeks To Revoke US SEC&#8217;s Request To Freeze Its Funds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06122903/Binance-Outflows-Remain-Within-Historical-Levels-Amid-SEC-Lawsuit.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon 2.0 Released As the Value Layer of the Internet, MATIC Price Up 2.5%</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/polygon-2-0-released-as-the-value-layer-of-the-internet-matic-price-up-2-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon MATIC News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151536</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s Layer-2 scalability platform Polygon recently faced major headwinds as the SEC named its native cryptocurrency MATIC, a security. But looking past that, the Polygon team has recently unveiled Polygon 2.0 to build the Value Layer of the Internet. Thus, Polygon 2.0 will serve as a fundamental layer to create, exchange, as well as program <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/polygon-2-0-released-as-the-value-layer-of-the-internet-matic-price-up-2-5/" title="Polygon 2.0 Released As the Value Layer of the Internet, MATIC Price Up 2.5%"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/polygon-2-0-released-as-the-value-layer-of-the-internet-matic-price-up-2-5/">Polygon 2.0 Released As the Value Layer of the Internet, MATIC Price Up 2.5%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1080" height="539" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13095149/Polygon-2.0-Value-Layer-of-Internet.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Ethereum&#8217;s Layer-2 scalability platform Polygon recently faced major headwinds as the SEC named its native cryptocurrency MATIC, a security. But looking past that, the Polygon team has recently unveiled Polygon 2.0 to build the Value Layer of the Internet.</p>
<p>Thus, Polygon 2.0 will serve as a fundamental layer to create, exchange, as well as program value. The team claims that Polygon 2.0 will help democratize the global economy just as the internet helped in democratizing information access.</p>
<p>Polygon 2.0 brings decentralized finance, digital ownership, and innovative coordination methods to the forefront. It fills the gap in creating an Internet that prioritizes users rather than gatekeepers, rent-seekers, or intermediaries.</p>
<p>The new and upgraded Polygon version will serve as the blueprint for building the Value Layer. It features a set of proposed upgrades bringing a major shift in the protocol&#8217;s architecture, tokenomics, and governance.</p>
<p>The team shall reveal more details regarding Polygon 2.0 in the coming weeks. They will detail the future of the Polygon PoS chain, as well as the utility and the evolution of the MATIC token.</p>
<p>Also, the upgraded Polygon network will transition to greater community governance of the protocol and treasury. The team shall unveil a roadmap of how Polygon 2.0 will become the Value Layer of the internet while offering unified liquidity using ZK technology and unlimited scalability.</p>
<p>After facing a <a href="https://coingape.com/ada-sol-and-matic-tank-10-each-after-robinhood-delisting-will-more-exchanges-follow/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">heavy correction</a> last week, the MATIC price is finally up by 2.5% in the last 24 hours. Still, it is 22 negative on the weekly chart.</p>
<h3>More About Polygon 2.0 &#8211; The Value Layer of the Internet</h3>
<p>The Ethereum blockchain network was the first to demonstrate the concept of a value layer by allowing users to create, exchange, as well as program value in a secure and seamless way. As said, Polygon 2.0 will adopt the concepts of infinite scalability and unification from the internet.</p>
<p>Polygon 2.0 is a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://polygon.technology/blog/introducing-polygon-2-0-the-value-layer-of-the-internet" target="_blank" rel="noopener">special network</a> made up of different chains that work together. It&#8217;s a network of ZK-powered Layer-2 chains to make it seem like there&#8217;s only one chain for users. Thus, it can handle several chains at once such that they can interact with each other quickly and easily.</p>
<p>Polygon 2.0 doesn&#8217;t need extra security or trust because everything is already built in. This means the network can handle a lot of things at the same time and keep everything working smoothly.</p>
<p>The Polygon team hasn&#8217;t yet unveiled the specific timeline for the release of the newly upgraded network.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/polygon-2-0-released-as-the-value-layer-of-the-internet-matic-price-up-2-5/">Polygon 2.0 Released As the Value Layer of the Internet, MATIC Price Up 2.5%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13095149/Polygon-2.0-Value-Layer-of-Internet.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Balaji Srinivasan: US Dominance In Crypto Market Not Same Anymore</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/balaji-srinivasan-crypto-news-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 22:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Balaji Srinivasan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: Former Coinbase chief technology officer and crypto investor Balaji Srinivasan once again made a claim about the state of the crypto market. Earlier, in March 2023, he made a sensational claim about Bitcoin price reaching $1 million shaking not just the crypto market but also the wider financial markets. Meanwhile, the investor <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/balaji-srinivasan-crypto-news-bitcoin/" title="Balaji Srinivasan: US Dominance In Crypto Market Not Same Anymore"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/balaji-srinivasan-crypto-news-bitcoin/">Balaji Srinivasan: US Dominance In Crypto Market Not Same Anymore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/20153605/Balaji-Srinivasan-Bitcoin.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Balaji Srinivasan Bitcoin news price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: Former Coinbase chief technology officer and crypto investor Balaji Srinivasan once again made a claim about the state of the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>. Earlier, in March 2023, he made a sensational claim about <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> reaching $1 million shaking not just the crypto market but also the wider financial markets. Meanwhile, the investor believes that the United States&#8217; global veto over technology is no longer the same, just as the global distribution of power is not dominated by the US. Hence, going by Srinivasan&#8217;s argument, the crypto ecosystem is bound to grow faster if market participants look beyond the US as much earlier as possible.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bill-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-crypto-news" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>US Congressman Files Bill To Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler</strong></a></p>
<p>In the recent times, top US based crypto exchange Coinbase announced plans to expand its presence beyond the United States. This came after its repeated attempts to obtain clear path to regulatory framework from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Meanwhile, he feels that US administration&#8217;s plans to have a CBDC-led surveillance environment would not have the same effect globally as it had earlier.</p>
<h2>&#8220;CBDC Surveillance State In The US&#8221;</h2>
<p>The crypto investor responded to a tweet by Josh Swihart about the US lawmakers&#8217; plans to &#8220;diligently working to shut off all crypto from the mainstream, including Bitcoin.&#8221; Srinivasan, however, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1668304162206121985" target="_blank" rel="noopener">explained</a> that it would not have a widespread effect on the crypto market as Washington DC does not have a global veto over tech anymore. Interestingly, the back to back lawsuits against top <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchanges</a> Coinbase and Binance draw parallel to the US government&#8217;s string resistance to the digital assets ecosystem.</p>
<p>Yet, despite the many obstacles and legal attacks, Bitcoin price is still 54% higher when compared to the closing price in 2022. This makes the case even more stronger to migrate to new crypto hubs like Dubai and Singapore.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripple-lawsuit-sec-hinman-docs" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC’s Strongest Argument In XRP Case At Risk Amid Hinman Docs Disclosure</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/balaji-srinivasan-crypto-news-bitcoin/">Balaji Srinivasan: US Dominance In Crypto Market Not Same Anymore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/20153605/Balaji-Srinivasan-Bitcoin.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price: Former US Fed Official Hints At FOMC-Led Limitations</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/us-fed-bitcoin-price-fomc-interest-rate-hike-pause-crypto-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOMC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: Ahead of the crucial Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting scheduled for June 14, 2023, the financial markets are widely anticipating that the US Federal Reserve halt interest rate hikes again. A clear indication to this is seen in the S&#38;P 500 Index behavior, which is at the cusp of closing at <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/us-fed-bitcoin-price-fomc-interest-rate-hike-pause-crypto-news/" title="Bitcoin Price: Former US Fed Official Hints At FOMC-Led Limitations"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/us-fed-bitcoin-price-fomc-interest-rate-hike-pause-crypto-news/">Bitcoin Price: Former US Fed Official Hints At FOMC-Led Limitations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="US Fed bitcoin price FOMC crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520.jpg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520-768x512.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520-391x260.jpg 391w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520-150x100.jpg 150w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520-272x182.jpg 272w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: Ahead of the crucial Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting scheduled for June 14, 2023, the financial markets are widely anticipating that the US Federal Reserve halt interest rate hikes again. A clear indication to this is seen in the <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.google.com/search?q=sp500" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> behavior, which is at the cusp of closing at a 13 month high on Monday, largely due to the expectation of the central bank pausing the rate hike spree. The S&amp;P 500 rose 0.86% on Monday while the Nasdaq Composite Index jumped 1.3%. However, it remains to be seen whether the markets will have any real deviation if and when the rate hike pause is announced.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bill-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-crypto-news" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>US Congressman Files Bill To Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler</strong></a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, former Fed Vice Chair Roger Ferguson believes the ongoing market optimism resulted in the pricing in of the Fed rate hike pause already. Hence, it may be argued that there may not be much room for bullish environment in the financial markets. However, the same may not necessarily be said about Bitcoin price and crypto markets.</p>
<h2>Former Fed Vice Chair: Rate Hike Pause Already Priced In</h2>
<p>Speaking to CNBC on Monday, former Fed official Roger Ferguson agreed that the market is right about the Fed pause expectation. However, he said not all is fine about the quantitative easing of the Fed&#8217;s monetary policy. Citing tight labor market and rising wages, Ferguson <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/squawkcnbc/status/1668225689877635074" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> there was likelihood of further rate hikes in the remaining of 2023, as against the market expectation of a downward path in terms of easing the policy. Hence, this could potentially translate to increased volatility in the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>, as risky assets like Bitcoin may be preferred by traders in an uncertain environment.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I think the market has priced in a pause. Where I disagree with the market is I see not one but a possibility of two more hikes after this one with no reversal this year. I think the market&#8217;s generally correct but a little optimistic.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The CME FedWatch Tool <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shows</a> that the likelihood that the Fed will change the Federal target rate just around 21%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-151531" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13005947/ING.png" alt="ING dollar prediction" width="711" height="218" /></p>
<p>In yet another positive indication for rise in <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> in the rest of 2023, banking and financial services company ING predicted that the US Dollar could end up in a relatively lower position by the end of the year, as shared by Twitter handle Walter Bloomberg. This is based on a contrarian view that the Fed may cut rates in the fourth quarter.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-crypto-market-regulation-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Gary Gensler Warns Crypto Market: “Not Liking Not Same As Not Receiving”</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/us-fed-bitcoin-price-fomc-interest-rate-hike-pause-crypto-news/">Bitcoin Price: Former US Fed Official Hints At FOMC-Led Limitations</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12121722/Bitcoin-Major-Cryptos-Slide-as-Markets-Digest-Hawkish-Powell-Remarks-e1665582241520.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Successor Reveals Real Reason She Chose Twitter</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/elon-musk-successor-reveals-real-reason-she-chose-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk BTC News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linda Yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151526</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Yaccarino, the new Twitter Chief Executive Officer (CEO) who was appointed by the former Elon Musk has opened up on the reason why she took up the appointment.  Yaccarino, who used to work with NBCUniversal claimed that she has been getting a lot of questions from people about why she chose Twitter. She made <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-successor-reveals-real-reason-she-chose-twitter/" title="Elon Musk Successor Reveals Real Reason She Chose Twitter"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-successor-reveals-real-reason-she-chose-twitter/">Elon Musk Successor Reveals Real Reason She Chose Twitter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="890" height="500" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/12154500/linda-yaccarino-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="linda-yaccarino" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">Linda Yaccarino, the new Twitter Chief Executive Officer (CEO) who was </span><a href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-names-new-twitter-ceo-linda-yaccarino/"><span style="font-weight: 400">appointed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by the </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-elon-musk-becomes-twitter-ceo-will-reverse-bans/"><span style="font-weight: 400">former</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Elon Musk has opened up on the reason why she took up the appointment. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Yaccarino, who used to work with NBCUniversal claimed that she has been getting a lot of questions from people about why she chose Twitter. She made a Twitter </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/lindayacc/status/1668300211591188480"><span style="font-weight: 400">thread</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for this purpose and also included the details in the first memo which she sent out to employees. She titled the memo &#8220;Building Twitter 2.0 Together&#8221;.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Hello Twitter. <br />People keep asking me: Why Twitter? <br />So, I’ll tell you. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Linda Yaccarino (@lindayacc) <a href="https://twitter.com/lindayacc/status/1668300211591188480?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">She began her explanation by reminding her more than 447,000 followers that the former CEO who is an automobile expert saw the need for transformation in the space exploration and electric vehicles sector, and he went for it. This time around, Twitter which she referred to as the &#8220;global town square&#8221; echoing Musk&#8217;s stated goal for the company, needed transformation and here she is. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&#8220;It’s also becoming clear that the global town square needs transformation—to drive civilization forward through the unfiltered exchange of information and open dialogue about the things that matter most to us,&#8221; the new Twitter CEO said. &#8220;Have you ever been talking with someone particularly insightful and thought, you should have the freedom to speak your mind. We all should. Enter Twitter 2.0.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><b>Yaccarino Becomes Responsible for Twitter Ad Business</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Before coming to Twitter to take over from Elon Musk, Yaccarino was a long-time advertising executive at NBCUniversal. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">During her time there, she led global and sales for the media house. Upon her joining Twitter, Musk decided to oversee the operations of Twitter’s product and engineering teams while Yaccarino leads everything else. He decided to </span><a href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-might-step-down-as-twitter-ceo-heres-why/"><span style="font-weight: 400">step down</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> after coming under different policy changes on Twitter that led to a few account suspensions and sine other chaos. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Since the Tesla boss bought the bluebird app in a </span><a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-elon-musk-cites-whistleblower-to-end-44-billion-twitter-deal/"><span style="font-weight: 400">$44 billion bid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Twitter’s ads business has seen a relapse. Hence, Yaccarino&#8217;s major responsibility will be to rebuild that sector. Speaking to Twitter employees, Yaccarino reminded them that Twitter is currently on a mission to become the &#8220;world’s most accurate real-time information source and a global town square for communication.&#8221; </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-successor-reveals-real-reason-she-chose-twitter/">Elon Musk Successor Reveals Real Reason She Chose Twitter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/12154500/linda-yaccarino-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC’s Strongest Argument In XRP Case At Risk Amid Hinman Docs Disclosure</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripple-lawsuit-sec-hinman-docs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151522</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP News: The crypto industry is eagerly waiting for the release of the infamous Hinman Ethereum speech linked emails and documents in the XRP Lawsuit. The date decided by both parties, U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple Labs, to release the crucial documents has finally arrived. Also Read: Hinman Docs Reveal In XRP <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripple-lawsuit-sec-hinman-docs/" title="SEC’s Strongest Argument In XRP Case At Risk Amid Hinman Docs Disclosure"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripple-lawsuit-sec-hinman-docs/">SEC’s Strongest Argument In XRP Case At Risk Amid Hinman Docs Disclosure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13003409/ripple1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ripple xrp news lawsuit price hinman speech SEC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>XRP News:</strong> The crypto industry is eagerly waiting for the release of the infamous Hinman Ethereum speech linked emails and documents in the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP Lawsuit</a>. The date decided by both parties, U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple Labs, to release the crucial documents has finally arrived.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-news-crypto-fomc-cpi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hinman Docs Reveal In XRP Case To Congressional Hearing; Why This Week Is Crucial For Crypto?</a></strong></p>
<h2>A Turning Point In XRP Lawsuit?</h2>
<p>As per the court orders, Ripple and SEC filed a joint letter seeking <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-extension-to-reveal-hinman-docs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">one week extension</a> until June 13, 2023, for the public release of the unredacted Hinman Speech documents. However, with speech linked memos, unredacted versions of cross motions for summary judgment of both parties will be made public.</p>
<p>Finally, the Crypto industry will gain clarity that why then SEC Director of Corporation Finance, Bill Hinman concluded that Ether (ETH) was not a security.</p>
<p>Attorney John Deaton, Amicus curiae in the XRP lawsuit suggests that June 13, 2023, will make it clear how strong or weak the SEC’s assertions linked to several specific sales stands. He highlighted that just the “offer” can violate Section 5 of the Securities Act. It is important to note that this appears to be the commission’s strongest argument in the case. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More XRP News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<h2>Ripple Wanted To Hide Sales Data</h2>
<p>Deaton mentioned that the cross motions filed by both parties will be released to the public. This will allow us to see some specific evidence offered against Ripple and the defendants. However, Ripple was seeking to redact evidence linking to its revenue with XRP sales offered to Coinbase crypto exchange and others to list XRP. This also included the amount of sales that were targeted at investors via programmatic sales.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance To Face US DOJ’s Criminal Charges Or It&#8217;s Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints</a></strong></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the court ordered that this evidence cannot be redacted as Ripple’s native crypto XRP sales and its payment to 3rd parties to list it pertains to the Howey analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-ripple-lawsuit-sec-hinman-docs/">SEC’s Strongest Argument In XRP Case At Risk Amid Hinman Docs Disclosure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13003409/ripple1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Price Analysis: $SHIB Price Gaze Relief Rally to $0.0000786; Is this a Good Buy?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/shiba-inu-price-analysis-shib-price-relief-rally-to-0-0000786-is-it-a-good-buy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu price analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=151528</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu Price Analysis: Amid last weekend&#8217;s altcoin crash, the Shiba Inu coin price witnessed a heavy sell-off and printed a long red candle on June 10th. Amid this downfall, the prices breached crucial support of $0.00000783, and $0.0000072 and reached a two-year low of $0.00000543. Though the support breakdown fueled the overall bearish view <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/shiba-inu-price-analysis-shib-price-relief-rally-to-0-0000786-is-it-a-good-buy/" title="Shiba Inu Price Analysis: $SHIB Price Gaze Relief Rally to $0.0000786; Is this a Good Buy?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/shiba-inu-price-analysis-shib-price-relief-rally-to-0-0000786-is-it-a-good-buy/">Shiba Inu Price Analysis: $SHIB Price Gaze Relief Rally to $0.0000786; Is this a Good Buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13001815/jbnE1mwK-e1686595729792.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Shiba Inu price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13001815/jbnE1mwK-e1686595729792.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13001815/jbnE1mwK-e1686595729792-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13001815/jbnE1mwK-e1686595729792-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13001815/jbnE1mwK-e1686595729792-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shiba Inu Price Analysis: Amid last weekend&#8217;s altcoin crash, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu coin price</a> witnessed a heavy sell-off and printed a long red candle on June 10th. Amid this downfall, the prices breached crucial support of $0.00000783, and $0.0000072 and reached a two-year low of $0.00000543. Though the support breakdown fueled the overall bearish view for this memecoin, the daily low created at the aforementioned low indicates the SHIB price is likely to go below it.</span></p>
<p>Also Read- <a href="https://coingape.com/registered-crypto-exchange-lists-shiba-inu-shib-ecosystems-bone-token/">Registered Crypto Exchange Lists Shiba Inu (SHIB) Ecosystem’s BONE Token</a></p>
<h2><b>Shiba Inu Price Daily Chart: </b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The long-tail rejection at $0.0000056 support suggests the buyers are actively defending this level0</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A potential upswing in the SHIB price could raise a temporary recovery of 20%</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume of the Shiba Inu coin is $120.5 Million, showing a 68% loss.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/j/jbnE1mwK.png" alt="Shiba Inu Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1105" />Source- Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On June 10th, the aggressive selling was swiftly countered by buyers, who managed to recover the losses incurred during the day. The resulting long-tail rejection indicated that the buyers are aggressively accumulating at this discounted price and projected a suitable level to revert the price higher.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By the press time, the SHIB coin traded at $0.00000665 and showed another long-tail rejection candle indicating the buying pressure persists. If the bullish momentum rises further, the coin price will witness a minor relief rally to retest the breached support of $0.0000072, and $0.00000783 as potential resistance. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the higher possibility of sellers defending two resistances, the Shiba price is likely to stay in a downtrend or consolidation phase for the remaining days of June.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Will Shiba Inu&#8217;s Price Recover to $0.000008?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the upside side, the Shiba Inu coin shows a downsloping trendline which has been carrying a steady downtrend for the past four months. Even if the coin price shows a significant recovery in the coming days, the buyers will get a better conviction for long-term recovery if the prices breach the overhead trendline. A breakout above the overhead trendline will boast the buying momentum and surpass $0.000008. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Vortex Indicator: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The wide gap showcased as the VI- slope moves up above the V+ reflects an established downtrend.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Bollinger Band: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The <a href="https://coingape.com/education/bollinger-band/">BB indicator</a> challenged on the downside is another sign of intense selling pressure which is unstable and may lead to a swift rebound in the near future</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/shiba-inu-price-analysis-shib-price-relief-rally-to-0-0000786-is-it-a-good-buy/">Shiba Inu Price Analysis: $SHIB Price Gaze Relief Rally to $0.0000786; Is this a Good Buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/13001815/jbnE1mwK-e1686595729792.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Congressman Files Bill To Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bill-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-crypto-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151527</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: US Congressman Warren Davidson on Monday announced filing of the sensational SEC Stabilization Act to restructure the regulatory agency and also to fire Chair Gary Gensler. The bill, aimed at streamlining US capital markets, comes at a time when Gensler is facing heavy criticism for his style of enforcing laws on the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bill-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-crypto-news/" title="US Congressman Files Bill To Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bill-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-crypto-news/">US Congressman Files Bill To Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1201" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/17151938/Gary_Gensler.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Gary Gensler crypto news SEC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: US Congressman Warren Davidson on Monday announced filing of the sensational SEC Stabilization Act to restructure the regulatory agency and also to fire Chair Gary Gensler. The bill, aimed at streamlining US capital markets, comes at a time when Gensler is facing heavy criticism for his style of enforcing laws on the crypto market. In a latest, CoinGape <a href="https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-crypto-market-regulation-news" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> his warnings to crypto investors, in that he reiterates that the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> businesses are informed of the existing laws, although most of the industry participants dislike the status quo.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-crypto-news-coinbase" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Elon Musk Sides With Coinbase ‘Crypto Regulation’ Stance</strong></a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the XRP community, which has been long fighting the SEC in the Ripple lawsuit, awaits the June 13 public release of the Hinman documents. The Ripple lawsuit is currently the most important conflicts with the SEC as the outcome is expected to be right around the corner with Judge Analisa Torres likely to deliver the all important Summary Judgement any time now.</p>
<h2>The SEC Stabilization Act To Fire Gary Gensler</h2>
<p>Warren Davidson, a Congressman from Ohio, filed the SEC Stabilization Act aiming to restructure the agency as well as fire Chair Gensler. He <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/WarrenDavidson/status/1668305460368121857?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a> that there was a need to fix the ongoing abuse of power and to ensure protection that is in the best interest of the market for years to come.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;U.S. capital markets must be protected from a tyrannical Chairman, including the current one. It’s time for real reform and to fire Gary Gensler as Chair of the SEC.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Davidson was joined with support by House Majority Whip Tom Emmer, who argued that the US investors and the industry deserve clear and consistent oversight, not political gamesmanship. The SEC Stabilization Act includes firing Gensler as the first step, followed by revamping the rulemaking process, enforcement and investigations.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-galaxy-digital-wins-in-1-2b-acquisition-lawsuit-against-bitgo" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Galaxy Digital Wins in $1.2B Acquisition Lawsuit Against BitGo</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bill-to-fire-sec-chair-gary-gensler-crypto-news/">US Congressman Files Bill To Fire SEC Chair Gary Gensler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/17151938/Gary_Gensler.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pakistan Ditches US Dollar, Embraces Yuan for Russian Oil Import</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/pakistan-ditches-us-dollar-embraces-yuan-for-russian-oil-import/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRICS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chinese Yuan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us dollar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151515</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pakistan has made a major step towards achieving de-dollarization by completing its first government-to-government import of Russian oil in the Chinese local currency Yuan. This deal was specifically struck between Islamabad and Moscow and the first cargo has arrived in Karachi since Sunday and is still being offloaded at the port.  The country&#8217;s Petroleum Minister <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/pakistan-ditches-us-dollar-embraces-yuan-for-russian-oil-import/" title="Pakistan Ditches US Dollar, Embraces Yuan for Russian Oil Import"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/pakistan-ditches-us-dollar-embraces-yuan-for-russian-oil-import/">Pakistan Ditches US Dollar, Embraces Yuan for Russian Oil Import</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="630" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12220821/Pakistan-China.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">Pakistan has made a major step towards achieving de-dollarization by </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.samaaenglish.tv/news/40038755"><span style="font-weight: 400">completing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> its first government-to-government import of Russian oil in the Chinese local currency Yuan. This deal was specifically struck between Islamabad and Moscow and the first cargo has arrived in Karachi since Sunday and is still being offloaded at the port. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The country&#8217;s Petroleum Minister Musadik Malik disclosed this information to Reuters on a phone call. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the minister, the entire transaction involves 100,000 tonnes of oil, but only 45,000 tonnes has been deposited at Karachi with the others on the way. He did not divulge details of the discount which Pakistan received from Russia or the commercial features of the deal. Still, he suggested that the oil importation is certainly a good buy for Pakistan. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">&#8220;We’ve run iterations of various product mixes, and in no scenario will the refining of this crude make a loss,” Malik announced. “We are very sure it will be commercially viable.”</span></p>
<h2><b>BRICS Nations to Ditch the U.S. Dollars</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Importantly, the change in currency notes is a clear effort to inactivate the dominance of the United States dollars as regards international trades. More so, it is a milestone for BRICS foundation member countries; Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa, that have been pushing for de-dollarization amongst themselves. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Many member countries, as well as non-members of BRICS have also joined in the drive against U.S. dollar dominance. In April, Indonesia hinted at plans to </span><a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/ndonesia-looking-to-move-away-from-the-u-s-dollar/"><span style="font-weight: 400">replace</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the dollar with an alternative mode of payment. At the time, Indonesia was considering reducing its reliance on the U.S. dollar by introducing Rupiah for cross-border transactions, at least amongst Asian countries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A few weeks later, Brazil president Luiz Lula da Silva, proposed that the country </span><a href="https://coingape.com/brazil-president-proposes-ditching-us-dollar-trading-currency/"><span style="font-weight: 400">ditch</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the dollar for another currency. Apart from using their local currencies, some of these nations are considering Bitcoin (BTC) as a safer alternative to the U.S. dollar, especially now that the cryptocurrency has recovered reasonably from the bear market of last year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Noteworthy, Max Keiser, the advisor to El Salvador President Nayib Bukele is positive that if the BTC alternative is accepted, it will be </span><a href="https://coingape.com/super-hyper-bitcoinization-will-kill-us-dollar-dominance-el-salvador-advisor/"><span style="font-weight: 400">fast track</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to de-dollarization. </span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/pakistan-ditches-us-dollar-embraces-yuan-for-russian-oil-import/">Pakistan Ditches US Dollar, Embraces Yuan for Russian Oil Import</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12220821/Pakistan-China.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler Warns Crypto Market: &#8220;Not Liking Not Same As Not Receiving&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-crypto-market-regulation-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151514</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler reiterated his stance on crypto regulation, in the wake of the recent lawsuits against crypto exchanges Coinbase and Binance. He made some interesting remarks before Piper Sandler Global Exchange &#38; Fintech Conference. Gensler once again drew a link between the digital assets market <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-crypto-market-regulation-news/" title="Gary Gensler Warns Crypto Market: &#8220;Not Liking Not Same As Not Receiving&#8221;"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-crypto-market-regulation-news/">Gary Gensler Warns Crypto Market: &#8220;Not Liking Not Same As Not Receiving&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06203738/gary-gensler.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="gary gensler SEC crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler reiterated his stance on crypto regulation, in the wake of the recent lawsuits against <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchanges</a> Coinbase and Binance. He made some interesting remarks before Piper Sandler Global Exchange &amp; Fintech Conference. Gensler once again drew a link between the digital assets market and the securities laws, stating that trust in capital markets in the United States was built on compliance with the laws. He also warned that <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> like bankruptcies can continue to happen without compliance, although he failed to address how exactly crypto businesses are to comply.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-to-rise-amid-positive-us-fed-inflation-data-or-fall-as-market-makers-exit" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Bitcoin, Ethereum To Rise Amid Positive US Fed &amp; Inflation Data or Fall As Market Makers Exit</strong></a></p>
<p>Interestingly, the SEC Chair spoke about the need to protect investors, saying the <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto markets</a> should not be allowed to harm them. In his speech, Gensler mentioned a 2018 conversation by Binance&#8217;s then Chief Compliance Officer Samuel Lim with a colleague about how the crypto exchange is operating as an unlicensed securities exchange in the the United States. The same was included in the SEC&#8217;s recent complaint against Binance, which alleged it of lying to regulators.</p>
<h2>Gary Gensler Warns Crypto Market, Again</h2>
<p>Gensler reiterated in his opening remarks that most cryptocurrencies qualify as securities by the virtue of meeting the investment contract test. However, the SEC Chair made it a point to warn that lack of compliance could lead to more and more anti-crypto enforcement actions. He <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.sec.gov/news/speech/gensler-remarks-piper-sandler-060823" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>, &#8220;not liking the message is not the same thing as not receiving it,&#8221; indicating that the market participants are well informed about the status quo. Apparently, this is an attempt to shield the SEC&#8217;s arguments in the many crypto lawsuits that may involve the stance of &#8216;lack of clarity&#8217; over regulations.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;When crypto asset market participants go on Twitter or TV and say they lacked “fair notice” that their conduct could be illegal, don’t believe it. They may have made a calculated economic decision to take the risk of enforcement as the cost of doing business.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, the digital assets market participants will be anticipating the public release of Hinman documents in the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP Vs SEC lawsuit</a>, on June 13, 2023.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Binance To Face US DOJ’s Criminal Charges Or Its Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-crypto-market-regulation-news/">Gary Gensler Warns Crypto Market: &#8220;Not Liking Not Same As Not Receiving&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/06203738/gary-gensler.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Classic Price Analysis: $LUNC Price Exhibits Coiling Pattern Before Potential Surge; Buy Now?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/terra-classic-price-analysis-lunc-price-coiling-pattern-surge-buy-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra classic price analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=151518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Terra Classic Price Analysis: The LUNC price showed a significant downturn last week, as the crypto market witnessed a heavy sell-off in altcoins. From the peak of $0.000115, the coin price tumbled nearly 24.5% to reach the current price of $0.000086. As the downsloping trendline is currently carrying this correction phase, the sellers could plunge <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/terra-classic-price-analysis-lunc-price-coiling-pattern-surge-buy-now/" title="Terra Classic Price Analysis: $LUNC Price Exhibits Coiling Pattern Before Potential Surge; Buy Now?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/terra-classic-price-analysis-lunc-price-coiling-pattern-surge-buy-now/">Terra Classic Price Analysis: $LUNC Price Exhibits Coiling Pattern Before Potential Surge; Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12214803/gob2DIKS-e1686586702457.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Terra Classic Price Analysis" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12214803/gob2DIKS-e1686586702457.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12214803/gob2DIKS-e1686586702457-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12214803/gob2DIKS-e1686586702457-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12214803/gob2DIKS-e1686586702457-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Terra Classic Price Analysis: The <a href="https://coingape.com/price/terra-luna-classic/">LUNC price</a> showed a significant downturn last week, as the crypto market witnessed a heavy sell-off in altcoins. From the peak of $0.000115, the coin price tumbled nearly 24.5% to reach the current price of $0.000086. As the downsloping trendline is currently carrying this correction phase, the sellers could plunge the price back to the $0.00007 mark.</span></p>
<p>Also Read- <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-luna-classic-staking-officially-hits-1-trillion-lunc-burn-63-billion/">Terra Luna Classic Staking Officially Hits 1 Trillion, LUNC Burn 63 Billion</a></p>
<h2><strong>LUNC Price Daily Chart</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The LUNC price is likely to witness high volatility in a narrow range.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A breakdown below $0.000082 could tumble the prices by 15%.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the LUNC coin is $82 Million, indicating a 27% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/g/gob2DIKS.png" alt="Terra Classic Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1105" />Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On June 10th, the LUNC price experienced a heavy sell-off and printed a long-red candle in the daily chart. This sell-off showed an attempt to break the local support of $0.000082 but the sellers failed to sustain lower levels.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, the long-wick rejection candle validates the aforementioned level as a high accumulation zone, indicating the price is likely to fall below. Similarly, on the flip side, the overhead trendline will constantly pressurize the LUNC price and undermine bullish attempts.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, the coin price is likely to coil between the mentioned until either of the levels is breached. Thus, the breakout will release the trapped momentum and trigger a direction move on the respected side.</span></p>
<h2><b>Will LUNC Price Fall to $0.00007?</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The near future trend for LUNC price depends on the range formation between the downsloping trendline and $0.000082 support. With the current market condition bearish, the LUNC price is likely to break below $0.000082 support which will intensify the selling pressure and push the coin to $0.00007. Conversely, a breakout above the overhead trendline will provide buyers with a suitable footing to lead the price to $0.0001.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Pivot levels: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">This support/resistance indicator reflects the demand zone at $0.000073 and $0.00006, and on the flip side, it shows the supply zone at $0.000092 and $0.000103.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Relative Strength Index: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bullish divergence in the daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> reflects increasing buying pressure at lower prices. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/terra-classic-price-analysis-lunc-price-coiling-pattern-surge-buy-now/">Terra Classic Price Analysis: $LUNC Price Exhibits Coiling Pattern Before Potential Surge; Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12214803/gob2DIKS-e1686586702457.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hinman Docs Reveal In XRP Case To Congressional Hearing; Why This Week Is Crucial For Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-news-crypto-fomc-cpi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151496</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP Lawsuit News: The digital asset market took a massive hit last week as the U.S. top financial watchdog, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), sued two of the world’s biggest crypto exchanges. However, It is expected that the crypto market might witness even more volatility in this week due to scheduled mega events ahead. <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-news-crypto-fomc-cpi/" title="Hinman Docs Reveal In XRP Case To Congressional Hearing; Why This Week Is Crucial For Crypto?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-news-crypto-fomc-cpi/">Hinman Docs Reveal In XRP Case To Congressional Hearing; Why This Week Is Crucial For Crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/23152921/ripple-sec.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ripple sec XRP news lawsuit john deaton" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>XRP Lawsuit News:</strong> The digital asset market took a massive hit last week as the U.S. top financial watchdog, the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/securities-and-exchange-commission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC), sued two of the world’s biggest crypto exchanges. However, It is expected that the crypto market might witness even more volatility in this week due to scheduled mega events ahead.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance To Face US DOJ’s Criminal Charges Or It&#8217;s Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints</a></strong></p>
<h2>Hinman Docs To Unseal In XRP Lawsuit</h2>
<p>The crypto community can anticipate a roller coaster ride in the market charts this week as much anticipated <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-extension-to-reveal-hinman-docs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crucial documents in the XRP lawsuit</a> will be released amid the recently filed legal dispute between U.S. SEC and Binance.</p>
<p>As per the<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/DaanCrypto/status/1668140076017111041" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> schedule</a>, the world’s largest crypto exchange, Binance and its U.S. arm need to respond to the U.S. SEC’s application for a temporary restraining order by Monday. The commission asked a federal court to issue a temporary restraining order to freeze Binance.US’s assets.</p>
<p>Tuesday will be marked as the biggest day for Ripple Labs and other defendants in the U.S SEC Lawsuit. The infamous speech was given by then SEC Director of Corporation Finance, Bill Hinman stated in his view, Ethereum (ETH) was not security. It is expected that the sealed documents will disclose what internal discussion led the executive to suggest the nature of Ethereum. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Read More XRP lawsuit News Here&#8230;</strong></a></p>
<h2>CPI Data, FOMC Meeting Remains Main Focus</h2>
<p>The US Core <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/consumer-price-index-cpi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Consumer Price Index</a> (CPI) will be the main focus this week followed by the crucial FOMC meeting. US CPI data will be announced on June 13, while the crucial FOMC meeting will be held from June 13-14. However, US Fed Chief Jerome Powell will give out market moving statement on June 14.</p>
<p>The market needs to brace itself as ECB is expected to raise interest rates by 25 basis points on June 15 amid inflation pressure. Reports suggest that due to persistent inflationary pressures, the central bank might halt the hike for the rest of the year.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-verdict-might-prove-crucial-for-coinbase-binance-attorney/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP Lawsuit Verdict Might Prove Crucial For Coinbase, Binance, Says Attorney</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-news-crypto-fomc-cpi/">Hinman Docs Reveal In XRP Case To Congressional Hearing; Why This Week Is Crucial For Crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/23152921/ripple-sec.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Galaxy Digital Wins in $1.2B Acquisition Lawsuit Against BitGo</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/breaking-galaxy-digital-wins-in-1-2b-acquisition-lawsuit-against-bitgo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey Benjamin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitgo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[galaxy digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>American crypto investment and asset management firm, Galaxy Digital will be walking away unscathed in its legal battle with custody service provider, BitGo. According to reports, the case was dismissed, giving Galaxy Digital the much needed relief over the case. BitGo filed the lawsuit against Galaxy Digital back in September last year following the failure <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-galaxy-digital-wins-in-1-2b-acquisition-lawsuit-against-bitgo/" title="Breaking: Galaxy Digital Wins in $1.2B Acquisition Lawsuit Against BitGo"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-galaxy-digital-wins-in-1-2b-acquisition-lawsuit-against-bitgo/">Breaking: Galaxy Digital Wins in $1.2B Acquisition Lawsuit Against BitGo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="499" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12204436/Galaxy-Digital.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400">American crypto investment and asset management firm, Galaxy Digital will be walking away unscathed in its legal battle with custody service provider, BitGo. According to reports, the case was </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitgo-lawsuit-against-galaxy-digital-140403325.html"><span style="font-weight: 400">dismissed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, giving Galaxy Digital the much needed relief over the case.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">BitGo </span><a href="https://coingape.com/bitgo-sues-galaxy-digital/"><span style="font-weight: 400">filed the lawsuit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against Galaxy Digital back in September last year following the failure of the latter to make good on the deal to acquire the former for $1.2 billion as agreed earlier. The latter firm </span><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/galaxy-announces-termination-of-bitgo-acquisition-806604223.html"><span style="font-weight: 400">backtracked</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on the deal at the time on account that BitGo failed to share its audited financial records as of July 31 last year.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The period of the negotiations also coincided with the heat of the crypto winter that saw the collapse of top crypto platforms including Celsius Network and Voyager Digital which fueled cautionary investments amongst firms. With the expectations the deal generated, BitGo sued the Mike Novogratz led firm for more than $100 million in damages.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">With the ruling, Galaxy Digital will no longer be liable to pay any damages and it will be able to focus on its business moving forward.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We’re pleased with the court’s decision to dismiss BitGo’s claims. Now is the time for all of us to work together and focus on the task at hand: Upgrading the global financial system in a manner that promotes innovation and protects investors and consumers alike,” Galaxy Digital said in a statement shared on Twitter.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><b>Galaxy Digital vs BitGo: The Way Forward</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The lawsuit and the way it ended appears acceptable to Galaxy Digital and moving forward from here appears straightforward. However, the case is not the same for BitGo who as of the time of writing has not commented on the court’s decisions on the matter.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As noted, the latest tweet from BitGo is the affirmation of its legality as a crypto custody service provider, a confirmation that appears necessary to prevent the bout of panic withdrawals that is typically characteristic of the volatile cryptocurrency ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Whether or not BitGo will be appealing the case remains unknown, but for now, supporters of the Galaxy Digital firm appear elated for now.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-galaxy-digital-wins-in-1-2b-acquisition-lawsuit-against-bitgo/">Breaking: Galaxy Digital Wins in $1.2B Acquisition Lawsuit Against BitGo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12204436/Galaxy-Digital.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Sides With Coinbase &#8216;Crypto Regulation&#8217; Stance</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/elon-musk-crypto-news-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk tweet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151510</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Market News: The recent rise of artificial intelligence (AI) integration in mainstream businesses in naturally attracting the question of regulating AI usage, as already pointed by the likes of billionaire Elon Musk. However, the US regulators have been waging a parallel war against crypto market since the beginning of 2023, as the U.S. Securities <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-crypto-news-coinbase/" title="Elon Musk Sides With Coinbase &#8216;Crypto Regulation&#8217; Stance"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-crypto-news-coinbase/">Elon Musk Sides With Coinbase &#8216;Crypto Regulation&#8217; Stance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/14142358/never-tweet-how-elon-musk-is-ruining-the-promise-of-crypto_pd62.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="elon musk crypto news coinbase" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto Market News</strong>: The recent rise of artificial intelligence (AI) integration in mainstream businesses in naturally attracting the question of regulating AI usage, as already pointed by the likes of billionaire Elon Musk. However, the US regulators have been waging a parallel war against <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> since the beginning of 2023, as the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/securities-and-exchange-commission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> continues to target crypto businesses operating in the United States. In this context, there is an interesting situation wherein there are conflicting arguments in terms of regulating the AI space versus the digital assets space.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-to-rise-amid-positive-us-fed-inflation-data-or-fall-as-market-makers-exit" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Bitcoin, Ethereum To Rise Amid Positive US Fed &amp; Inflation Data or Fall As Market Makers Exit</strong></a></p>
<p>Recently, the US SEC filed back to back lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance, which are the world&#8217;s top crypto exchanges in terms of trading volumes. However, the <a href="https://coingape.com/sec-sues-coinbase-exchange-day-after-binance-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase lawsuit</a> came as a direct contradiction to the exchange&#8217;s demand for clear regulatory framework for crypto assets from the reguatory agency. The regulator claimed that Coinbase had been operating as an unregistered broker since at least 2019, whereas it was in the same year that the SEC approved SEC&#8217;s IPO application.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk Responds To Crypto Vs AI Regulatory Concerns</h2>
<p>Although Coinbase had in recent times moved court over its request to compel the SEC to respond to a crypto rulemaking petition, it can also be argued that the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto exchange</a> actually never wanted any regulation. It is, however, widely agreed that regulation of digital assets under the existing rules is accepted by hardly any crypto market participants. Hence, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://companies.coingape.com/coinbase" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coinbase</a> may be open to regulation as and when there are clear rules for the crypto space, which it appears will be a distant plan in near future, considering the upcoming US presidential election 2024 and the possibility of a regime change, including at the SEC.</p>
<p>Whereas on the other side, Sam Altman, the chief executive officer of OpenAI, recently called for the United States administration to regulate the artificial intelligence space. In this context, Musk <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1668080415293206530" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">responded</a> to the double puzzle on regulating the two emerging markets.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/registered-crypto-exchange-lists-shiba-inu-shib-ecosystems-bone-token" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Registered Crypto Exchange Lists Shiba Inu (SHIB) Ecosystem’s BONE Token</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-crypto-news-coinbase/">Elon Musk Sides With Coinbase &#8216;Crypto Regulation&#8217; Stance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/14142358/never-tweet-how-elon-musk-is-ruining-the-promise-of-crypto_pd62.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Finds Support for a Potential Rally to $0.745; Good Time to Buy?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-finds-support-for-a-potential-rally-to-0-745-good-time-to-buy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 14:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MACD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=151500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The recent altcoin crash fueled the ongoing downtrend in MATIC price and plunged to yearly support of $0.518. From the peak of $0.95, this downfall tumbled the price by nearly 45% within a week. However, the daily chart shows a sharply lower price rejection at $0.518 on June 10th, revealing a high accumulation zone for <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-finds-support-for-a-potential-rally-to-0-745-good-time-to-buy/" title="MATIC Price Finds Support for a Potential Rally to $0.745; Good Time to Buy?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-finds-support-for-a-potential-rally-to-0-745-good-time-to-buy/">MATIC Price Finds Support for a Potential Rally to $0.745; Good Time to Buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="681" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12191339/422D2L03-1-e1686577478590.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Matic price" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12191339/422D2L03-1-e1686577478590.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12191339/422D2L03-1-e1686577478590-300x170.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12191339/422D2L03-1-e1686577478590-768x436.png 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12191339/422D2L03-1-e1686577478590-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The recent altcoin crash fueled the ongoing downtrend in <a href="https://coingape.com/price/polygon/">MATIC price</a> and plunged to yearly support of $0.518. From the peak of $0.95, this downfall tumbled the price by nearly 45% within a week. However, the daily chart shows a sharply lower price rejection at $0.518 on June 10th, revealing a high accumulation zone for buyers; Can coin buyers kickstart a fresh recovery from this level?</span></p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/delisted-matic-price-plummets-as-whales-dump-tokens/">Delisted MATIC Price Plummets as Whales Dump Tokens</a></p>
<h2><strong>MATIC Price Daily Chart</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A potential reversal in MATIC price may face intense supply at $0.687 and $0.744</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The oversold RSI indicator reflects the coin price is trading at a heavy discount </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the MATIC is $364.5 Million, indicating an 8.67% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/4/422D2L03.png" alt="MATIC Price " width="1946" height="1105" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Long-tail rejection candle at $0.518 support indicates the aggressive accumulation from buyers at lower levels. The coin price is 24% higher from the bottom support to current trade at $0.644.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The discounted MATIC price could attract more buyers and trigger a temporary pullback to $0.745. The potential rally could surge the price by 15%-18% to meet the long-coming resistance trendline(red).</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aforementioned resistance has maintained a steady downtrend in MATIC price and the potential traders seeking long-entry opportunities must wait for a breakout above this trendline.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Will MATIC Price Rise above $0.745?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The current relief rally in MATIC is likely triggered by the accumulation of this <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoin</a> at discounted market value. Thus, with the overall trend still bearish, a recovery above $0.745 is less likely. If buyers face supply pressure at the in-between resistance of $0.68, the price may revisit $0.518 support.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Exponential Moving Average: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coin price stretched far from its <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">exponential moving average</a>(20, 50, 100, and 200) reflecting instability in the current downtrend.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><b>Moving Average Convergence Divergence: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The wide gap between the bearishly aligned <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/macd-moving-average-convergence-divergnece/">MACD</a>(blue) and signal(orange) highlights an aggressive downtrend in MATIC.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/matic-price-finds-support-for-a-potential-rally-to-0-745-good-time-to-buy/">MATIC Price Finds Support for a Potential Rally to $0.745; Good Time to Buy?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12191339/422D2L03-1-e1686577478590.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum To Rise Amid Positive US Fed &#038; Inflation Data or Fall As Market Makers Exit</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-to-rise-amid-positive-us-fed-inflation-data-or-fall-as-market-makers-exit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin(BTC) News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CPI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151474</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum prices showing resilience amid positive macro factors. However, the market conditions remain bleak due to US SEC lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase and selling pressure on Cardano, Solana, and Polygon (MATIC). Investors are bracing for the big week ahead with key events including US CPI, PPI data, and the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-to-rise-amid-positive-us-fed-inflation-data-or-fall-as-market-makers-exit/" title="Bitcoin, Ethereum To Rise Amid Positive US Fed &#038; Inflation Data or Fall As Market Makers Exit"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-to-rise-amid-positive-us-fed-inflation-data-or-fall-as-market-makers-exit/">Bitcoin, Ethereum To Rise Amid Positive US Fed &#038; Inflation Data or Fall As Market Makers Exit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21183759/bitcoin-ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Crypto Slides As Fitch Puts US Rating Watch Negative On Debt Ceiling Standoff" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Bitcoin and Ethereum prices showing resilience amid positive macro factors. However, the <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-market-crash-heres-why-bitcoin-ethereum-altcoins-are-falling-sharply/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market conditions remain bleak</a> due to US SEC lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase and selling pressure on Cardano, Solana, and Polygon (MATIC).</p>
<p>Investors are bracing for the big week ahead with key events including US CPI, PPI data, and the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/federal-reserve-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US Federal Reserve&#8217;s</a> monetary policy decision, as well as interest rate decisions by the European Central Bank and Bank of Japan.</p>
<p>Stock markets are inching toward fresh 52-week highs after new market forecasts indicate inflation cooled in May and the <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-recover-on-debt-ceiling-deal-us-fed-pause-easing-jobs-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US Fed plans to &#8220;skip&#8221; rate hike</a> in June. Chair Jerome Powell and key Fed officials also support skipping rate hikes. The <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CME FedWatch Tool</a> shows an 80% probability of the Fed keeping its policy rate unchanged.</p>
<p>Moreover, US treasury yields remain firm and the US dollar slides, bringing some upward momentum in Bitcoin price. US Dollar Index (<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/index/dxy" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DXY</a>) fell below 103.50 on Monday.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="LUNC News: Terra Luna Classic Developer L1TF All Set For v2.1.1 Parity Upgrade" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-luna-classic-developer-l1tf-all-set-for-v2-1-1-parity-upgrade/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Terra Luna Classic Developer L1TF All Set For v2.1.1 Parity Upgrade</a></strong></p>
<h2>Internal Problems Still Haunts Bitcoin and Ethereum Price</h2>
<p>Despite positive developments on the macro front, Bitcoin and Ethereum prices fail to show strong price action due to uncertainty surrounding Binance and Coinbase lawsuits.</p>
<p>The key events for the crypto include a <strong>US House</strong> hearing on the digital asset industry and the <a href="https://coingape.com/us-house-releases-stablecoin-bill-bring-clarity-giving-fed-authority/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">draft stablecoin bill</a>, <strong>Hinman documents</strong> becoming public, SEC&#8217;s Coinbase rulemaking response, and the Binance.US hearing on assets freeze. All are scheduled for Tuesday, June 13.</p>
<p>According to Kaiko <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1668206152377663488" target="_blank" rel="noopener">data</a>, Binance.US market depth is down a staggering 78% since the SEC lawsuit. Marker makers pulled out liquidity after Binance.US ended USD support on the exchange.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FyaoMqCWYAAUiEw?format=jpg&amp;name=large" width="754" height="403" /></p>
<p>Moreover, Bitcoin and Ethereum prices will remain under pressure as the <strong>US Treasury Dept</strong> is expected to <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-crypto-under-selloff-pressure-as-us-treasury-dept-start-issuing-t-bills/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">issue $1 trillion in treasury bills</a> by the end of the third quarter.</p>
<p>BTC price is expected to bounce, but it will unlikely cross <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-prediction-for-the-week-amid-binance-coinbase-saga-dormant-btc-move/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>$30,000 before August</strong></a> due to several factors. <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC price</a> jumped 1% in the last 24 hours, with the price currently trading near $26,000.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/Ethereum" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH price</a> currently trades at $1747. The 24-hour low and high are $1722 and $1776, respectively. (<a href="https://coingape.com/price/converter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto Price Converter</a>)</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="Just-In: Registered Crypto Exchange Lists Shiba Inu (SHIB) Ecosystem’s BONE Token" href="https://coingape.com/registered-crypto-exchange-lists-shiba-inu-shib-ecosystems-bone-token/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Registered Crypto Exchange Lists Shiba Inu (SHIB) Ecosystem’s BONE Token</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-to-rise-amid-positive-us-fed-inflation-data-or-fall-as-market-makers-exit/">Bitcoin, Ethereum To Rise Amid Positive US Fed &#038; Inflation Data or Fall As Market Makers Exit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21183759/bitcoin-ethereum.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance To Face US DOJ&#8217;s Criminal Charges Or Its Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance.US]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CZ Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151470</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange and its executive’s legal troubles seems to be intensifying from here as the U.S. top financial watchdogs decide to go after Binance. However, the former Chief executive of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) suggests that the Department of Justice (DOJ) is likely to file criminal charges <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news/" title="Binance To Face US DOJ&#8217;s Criminal Charges Or Its Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news/">Binance To Face US DOJ&#8217;s Criminal Charges Or Its Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/08160005/Top-Altcoins-Crash-by-Over-20-As-US-Court-Summons-Binance-CEO.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Binance CZ crypto crash news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p><strong>Crypto News:</strong> The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange and its executive’s legal troubles seems to be intensifying from here as the U.S. top financial watchdogs decide to go after Binance. However, the former Chief executive of the U.S. <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/securities-and-exchange-commission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) suggests that the Department of Justice (DOJ) is likely to file criminal charges against Binance.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/custodia-case-ripple-xrp-lawsuit-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Custodia Bank Case More Important Than Ripple Lawsuit, Says XRP Lawyer</a></strong></p>
<h2>Binance In Big Trouble?</h2>
<p>John Read Stark, ex-head of SEC’s office of internet enforcement, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1668015011896205315" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hinted</a> that the U.S. DOJ will fill or has already filed a Binance linked criminal indictment under seal. He mentioned that both CFTC and SEC complaints read more like criminal indictments to him. However, the complaint also alleges the crypto exchange of fraud, deception of law, and money laundering.</p>
<p>As per the U.S. CFTC complaint, Binance’s CEO Changpeng Zhao and three of its executives that operated the crypto exchange allegedly violated the agency’s statutes and regulations. It is important to note that the CFTC charged Binance’s former Chief compliance officer, Samuel Lim for assisting and abetting the exchange’s violations. <strong><a href="https://coingape.com/tag/Binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read More Crypto News Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Stark highlighted that the CFTC presented evidence that the former COO was aware of the situation that Binance customers were there for a crime. The watchdog further alleged that the defendants assisted US VIP users in evading Binance’s compliance control.</p>
<h2>DOJ Working With SEC, CFTC?</h2>
<p>The U.S. SEC recently alleged that Binance and its CEO commingled billions of dollars with customer funds, which was later secretly sent to a different company controlled by CZ. However, the commission in a memorandum of support has mentioned that it has been widely reported that the world’s largest crypto exchange and CZ are under criminal authorities investigation.</p>
<p>This directs that the commission might be working with criminal prosecutors and the FBI, the former U.S. SEC executive suggests. He claimed that the DOJ is working with CFTC, SEC and several other whistleblowers.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/binance-ceo-cz-sec-lawsuit-crypto-news-letter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance CEO Refers SEC’s Chat Evidence In Internal Staff Letter</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-doj-sec-fud-crypto-news/">Binance To Face US DOJ&#8217;s Criminal Charges Or Its Just A FUD: Ex-SEC Exec Hints</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/08160005/Top-Altcoins-Crash-by-Over-20-As-US-Court-Summons-Binance-CEO.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: UK PM Rishi Sunak Welcomes a16z Crypto First Expansion Amid US Woes</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/uk-pm-rishi-sunak-welcomes-a16z-first-expansion-amid-us-woes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rishi Sunak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The largest venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) to open its first international office in London amid an increasingly hostile environment towards crypto in the US. The company will also host the next Crypto Startup School accelerator program in the country in 2024. UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak welcomes the move as the country looks <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/uk-pm-rishi-sunak-welcomes-a16z-first-expansion-amid-us-woes/" title="Breaking: UK PM Rishi Sunak Welcomes a16z Crypto First Expansion Amid US Woes"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/uk-pm-rishi-sunak-welcomes-a16z-first-expansion-amid-us-woes/">Breaking: UK PM Rishi Sunak Welcomes a16z Crypto First Expansion Amid US Woes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/25192145/Andreessen-Horowitz-j.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: UK PM Rishi Sunak Welcomes a16z Crypto First Expansion Amid US Woes" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>The largest venture capital firm <strong>Andreessen Horowitz (a16z)</strong> to open its first international office in London amid an increasingly hostile environment towards crypto in the US. The company will also host the next <strong>Crypto Startup School</strong> accelerator program in the country in 2024.</p>
<p>UK Prime Minister <strong>Rishi Sunak</strong> welcomes the move as the country looks to empower <strong>blockchain</strong> and <strong>Web3</strong> space. The UK Prime Minister and policymakers promise to provide clear regulations and guidelines to foster <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/web-3-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web3</a> development and the <strong>digital asset industry</strong>.</p>
<h2 class="epi-fontLg"><b>Andreessen Horowitz Opens First International Office in London</b></h2>
<p>According to an official <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://a16zcrypto.com/posts/announcement/expanding-uk-andreessen-horowitz/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, Andreessen Horowitz&#8217;s <strong>a16z crypto</strong> will open its first international office in London later this year. Venture capital fund a16z crypto is the largest investor in crypto and web3 startups and manages $7.6 billion in committed capital.</p>
<p>The move comes amid the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) continuing <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-market-defies-us-sec-bitcoin-ethereum-and-coinbase-coin-rally/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crackdown against the crypto industry</a>, suing crypto exchanges Coinbase (<a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-stocks/COIN/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">COIN</a>) and Binance last week for allegedly violating securities laws.</p>
<p><strong>Chris Dixon</strong>, founder and managing partner at a16z crypto, asserts the Biden administration is trying to kill crypto and UK has deep pools of talent, world-leading academic institutions, and a strong entrepreneurial culture. The London office will be led by general partner Sriram Krishnan. He also <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/cdixon/status/1668031650028986368" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shared</a> why the UK is best for its first expansion.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The UK is on the right path for crypto regulation:<br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Working with industry on unique attributes of blockchain tech<br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Laying a foundation for future blockchain apps<br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Innovative sandbox approach to regulation<br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Outcomes-based regulation<br /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f449.png" alt="👉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Consumer protection front-and-center</p>
<p>&mdash; cdixon.eth (@cdixon) <a href="https://twitter.com/cdixon/status/1668031650028986368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“As we cement the U.K.’s place as a science and tech superpower, we must embrace new innovations like Web3, powered by blockchain technology, which will enable start-ups to flourish here and grow the economy,” Sunak said in a statement shared with CoinGape Media.</p>
<blockquote><p>“That’s why I am thrilled world-leading investor, Andreessen Horowitz, has decided to open their first international office in the UK — which is testament to our world-class universities and talent and our strong competitive business environment.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Rishi Sunak is an advocate for crypto and blockchain technologies. Other policymakers such as MP Lisa Cameron are pushing for digital asset regulation while protecting consumers, foster innovation, and allow start-ups turn to the UK flourishing web3 hub.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/top-10-web-3-games-to-explore-in-2023-here-list" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Top 10 Web3 Games To Explore In 2023; Here List</a></strong></p>
<h2>a16z crypto Initiatives in the UK</h2>
<p>a16z crypto has already invested in UK-based crypto companies including Arweave, Aztec, and Improbable. Moreover, blockchain-based AI compute protocol <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/alive_eth/status/1668030741098233857" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Gensyn</a> today closed $43 million series A funding round led by a16z.</p>
<p>The VC firm also plans to start its a16z Crypto Startup School accelerator program in London in spring 2024 to attract web3 startups in the UK. Recent program enticed 8,000 applicants with 26 companies selected to receive investments from a16z.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a title="LUNC News: Terra Luna Classic Staking Officially Hits 1 Trillion, LUNC Burn 63 Billion" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-terra-luna-classic-staking-officially-hits-1-trillion-lunc-burn-63-billion/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Terra Luna Classic Staking Officially Hits 1 Trillion, LUNC Burn 63 Billion</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/uk-pm-rishi-sunak-welcomes-a16z-first-expansion-amid-us-woes/">Breaking: UK PM Rishi Sunak Welcomes a16z Crypto First Expansion Amid US Woes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/25192145/Andreessen-Horowitz-j.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Subreddits Go Dark In Protest</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-subreddits-go-dark-in-protest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai Pratap]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reddit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=151477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Several communities on the popular social media platform Reddit, including popular crypto subreddits, unanimously decided to go private for 48 hours to protest controversial charges to developers of third-party apps. A total of 3,489 subreddits have gone dark in protest, including five of the 10 most popular communities on the site &#8211; r/gaming, r/aww, r/Music, <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-subreddits-go-dark-in-protest/" title="Crypto Subreddits Go Dark In Protest"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-subreddits-go-dark-in-protest/">Crypto Subreddits Go Dark In Protest</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12173544/Crypto-Subreddits-Go-Dark-In-Protest.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="crypto subreddits" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /><p>Several communities on the popular social media platform Reddit, including popular crypto subreddits, unanimously decided to go private for 48 hours to protest controversial charges to developers of third-party apps.</p>
<p>A total of 3,489 subreddits have gone dark in protest, including five of the 10 most popular communities on the site &#8211; r/gaming, r/aww, r/Music, r/todayilearned and r/pics &#8211; which each have memberships of more than 30 million people.</p>
<h2>Reddit starts charging for APIs</h2>
<p>Reddit heavily relies on moderators to run smoothly. However, the social media company announced in April that it would make some changes to its website. The changes include preventing users from freely accessing APIs and tools.</p>
<p>Third-party apps such as Apollo, Reddit is Fun, Sync and ReddPlanet were set up as a way for people to access the platform on their mobile devices before Reddit launched its own app in 2016.</p>
<p>Now, Reddit has introduced a series of charges to the developers who wish to continue using its Application Programming Interface (API) &#8211; the behind-the-scenes code which allows third-party apps to find and show the content on Reddit. All four of these apps have said they will be shutting down as a result of Reddit&#8217;s new API pricing.</p>
<h2>Crypto subreddits join the protest by going dark</h2>
<p>Popular crypto subreddits protesting against the change include <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/">r/Bitcoin</a>,<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/"> r/CryptoCurrency</a> and <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.reddit.com/r/cardano/">r/cardano</a>. These and other thousands of subreddits will remain private or in read-only modes between June 12 and 14 to protest the changes.</p>
<p>Reddit, which is also planning for an IPO, is asking developers to pay $12,000 per every 50 million requests. The Apollo developer said that it would cost him 20 million US dollars per year to use Reddit’s APIs.</p>
<p>BBC <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-65877280">reported</a> that the protest could go on longer that 48 hours on some subreddits as the community demands Reddit to roll back the changes.</p>
<p>Read More: <a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-support-reddits-bold-move-against-ai-giants/">Elon Musk Supports Reddit In Pricing APIs</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-subreddits-go-dark-in-protest/">Crypto Subreddits Go Dark In Protest</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/12173544/Crypto-Subreddits-Go-Dark-In-Protest.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
