<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:40:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US President Unveils $42B Initiative for High-Speed Internet Initiative in America</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260487</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/">US President Unveils $42B Initiative for High-Speed Internet Initiative in America</a></p>
<p>White House infrastructure coordinator Mitch Landrieu emphasized that high-speed internet is a necessity in today’s society and should be accessible to every household in America.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/">US President Unveils $42B Initiative for High-Speed Internet Initiative in America</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/">US President Unveils $42B Initiative for High-Speed Internet Initiative in America</a></p>
<p>The incumbent and 46th president of the United States (US) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Joe Biden</a> has announced a high-speed internet initiative worth $42 billion in America. The scheme is his next push to invest in the country as he prepares for his re-election bid. The president is launching the project, targeted at offering high-speed internet to all households in America by 2030. Notably, Congress has already allocated the required funds via the Bipartisan Infrastructure Law. In addition, the allocation, which the US Department of Commerce is also overseeing, will be spread over the next couple of years via the Broadband Equity, Access, and Deployment program.</p>
<h2>High-Speed Internet Is Coming to America</h2>
<p>Under the high-speed internet program, each state in America will receive at least $107 million. While Texas will get over $3.3 billion, 19 other states are slated to receive more than $1 billion.</p>
<p>Commenting on the initiative in America for Americans, vice-president Kamala Harris said at the White House that a fast internet connection is not a luxury. She added that such is necessary in this 21st century. Per the Secretary of Commerce Gina Raimondo, the development will contribute to economic growth. Raimondo connected high-speed internet to better living standards in America, noting:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Whether it’s connecting people to the digital economy, manufacturing fiber optic cable in America or creating good-paying jobs building internet infrastructure in the states, the investments we’re announcing will increase our competitiveness and spur economic growth across the country for years to come.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Similarly, White House infrastructure coordinator Mitch Landrieu emphasized that high-speed internet is a necessity in today’s society and should be accessible to every household in America. He added that the president and the vice president are committed to committing all citizens without leaving any community behind.</p>
<p>In America, over 8.5 million homes and small businesses are considered to be underserved regarding internet access. This set of people, consisting of more than 7% of the country, have internet speed below the official standard. The government standard for internet speed is at least 25 megabits per second for downloads and 3 Mbps for uploads.</p>
<p>Additionally, the $42 billion investment in high-speed internet in America is part of the president’s Bipartisan Infrastructure Bill signed into law in November 2021. White House officials compared the project to Franklin D. Roosevelt’s (FDR) effort to extend electricity to rural America in the 1930s. FDR, who was the 32nd president of the United States between 1933 and 1945, had that as part of his New Deal legislation during the Great Depression.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/">US President Unveils $42B Initiative for High-Speed Internet Initiative in America</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/42b-high-speed-internet-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IBM Buying Vista Equity Partners’ Apptio for $4.6 Billion</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apptio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ibm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salesforce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vista equity partners]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260485</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/">IBM Buying Vista Equity Partners&#8217; Apptio for $4.6 Billion</a></p>
<p>The news from IBM on its plans to acquire Apptio came at a time organizations are digitally transforming their business operations faster than before.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/">IBM Buying Vista Equity Partners&#8217; Apptio for $4.6 Billion</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/">IBM Buying Vista Equity Partners&#8217; Apptio for $4.6 Billion</a></p>
<p>Amid the increasing use of cloud architecture, technology corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ibm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IBM</a> (NYSE: IBM) said it would acquire software company Apptio from Vista Equity Partners. According to a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/ibm-to-acquire-apptio-inc-providing-actionable-financial-and-operational-insights-across-enterprise-it-301862671.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, IBM is purchasing Apptio SaaS solutions which help organizations to plan, analyze, optimize, control, and collaborate with other investments as they make smart decisions, after entering into a definitive agreement with Vista Equity Partners. Per the deal, the technology corporation will buy the software for $4.6 billion.</p>
<p>As a leader in financial and operational IT management and optimization (FinOps), Apptio will help IBM accelerate its application management, optimization, and observability offerings. Also, enterprise leaders can deliver enhanced business value across technology investments. As a fast-growing technology business management and FinOps leader, Apptio offers services to over half of the Fortune 100. The company boasts more than 1,500 clients. Some of its partners include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/salesforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Salesforce</a> (NYSE: CRM), Amazon Web Services (AWS), Oracle, Google Cloud Platform, and more.</p>
<h2>IBM Announces Plans to Buy Apptio</h2>
<p>The news from IBM on its plans to acquire Apptio came at a time organizations are digitally transforming their business operations faster than before. Since the coronavirus outbreak, companies have adopted IT tools to expand across clouds. Hence, many turned to Apptio solutions to integrate into technology. As IBM acquires the software, it will help businesses manage and optimize enterprise IT spending and derive tangible financial value and operational improvement.</p>
<p>The CEO and chairman of IBM, Arvind Krishna, commented on the latest development with Apptio, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Technology is changing business at a rate and pace we&#8217;ve never seen before. To capitalize on these changes, it is essential to optimize investments which drive better business value, and Apptio does just that. Apptio&#8217;s offerings combined with IBM&#8217;s IT automation software and watsonx AI platform, gives clients the most comprehensive approach to optimize and manage all of their technology investments.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The combination of the companies&#8217; automation software will provide a full technology platform for businesses. The combined capabilities will result in a &#8220;virtual command center&#8221;, useful across the client&#8217;s technology landscape. Furthermore, Apptio is bringing $450 billion of anonymous IT spend data to IBM.</p>
<p>IBM&#8217;s announcement to purchase Apptio for billions of dollars reflects its continued efforts and investments toward a hybrid cloud. The software is also positioned to benefit from the technology company&#8217;s extensive client base across over 175 countries.</p>
<p>Expressing his excitement Apptio co-founder, and CEO Sunny Gupta stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are so excited to be joining IBM and combining our industry leading offerings with IBM&#8217;s global presence and strong portfolio across AIOps, automation and hybrid cloud offerings.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>While IBM will buy Apptio with Cash on hand, the transaction is still subject to regulatory approvals. Nevertheless, the companies expect to close the deal before the end of the year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/">IBM Buying Vista Equity Partners&#8217; Apptio for $4.6 Billion</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ibm-buying-apptio-4-6b/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Mario Forever Game Installs Crypto Mining Malware on User Devices and Steals Personal Data</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nintendo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[super mario]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xmr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/">Super Mario Forever Game Installs Crypto Mining Malware on User Devices and Steals Personal Data</a></p>
<p>A recent report from a research and intelligence firm reveals that the Super Mario Forever remake from Buziol Games contains heavy malware.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/">Super Mario Forever Game Installs Crypto Mining Malware on User Devices and Steals Personal Data</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/">Super Mario Forever Game Installs Crypto Mining Malware on User Devices and Steals Personal Data</a></p>
<p>Hackers have hijacked a Super Mario game and are using it to install crypto-mining malware on unsuspecting Windows devices. Several PC gamers may be helping unscrupulous players that mine crypto and also steal user information.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://blog.cyble.com/2023/06/23/trojanized-super-mario-game-installer-spreads-supremebot-malware/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from Cyble Research &amp; Intelligence Labs (CRIL), a legitimate installer for Super Mario 3: Mario Forever carries additional payload that contains malware. The intelligence firm reports that the malware can run crypto-mining software that requires heavy computing resources, and steals data from the device. Cyble’s report states:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Recently, CRIL identified a trojanized Super Mario Bros game installer that delivers multiple malicious components, including an XMR miner, SupremeBot mining client, and the Open-source Umbral stealer. The malware files were found bundled with a legitimate installer file of super-mario-forever-v702e.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Initially launched in 2003 and developed by Buziol Games, Super Mario 3: Mario Forever is an unofficial free-to-play remake of the original Super Mario from Japanese gaming giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nintendo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nintendo</a>. The game became a hit with several million downloads and was applauded by the general public. Gamers loved it because it contained better graphics and improved sound while retaining all of the classic mechanics from the original version. Buziol Games continued to improve the game and released updated versions for at least ten years.</p>
<h2>The Super Mario Malware</h2>
<p>Cyble researchers state that hackers have now published an adjusted version of the game that features a Trojan Horse. Also known as “Super Mario Forever,” the game has an installer archive with three executables. One of these is the legitimate Super Mario game, while the others are malware. Running the executables installs the malware into the user’s Windows AppData directory.</p>
<p>Upon execution, the installer runs an XMR (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/monero/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Monero</a>) miner and a SupremeBot mining client. The Monero miner steals data from the system and then starts mining after connecting to a mining server.</p>
<p>The other executable duplicates itself into a hidden folder and then deletes the first file to ensure the process is discreet. The duplicated copy runs every 15 minutes with a fake name disguised as a legitimate process. Upon installation, the malware transmits information and pulls remote configuration information for XMR mining.</p>
<p>According to Cyble, the Super Mario malware can take screenshots, capture webcam images, and pull passwords and cookies from a user’s browser. The malware can also steal Discord tokens and session files from Telegram, as well as collect system files connected to crypto wallets.</p>
<h2>CRIL’s Recommendations</h2>
<p>Cyble’s report includes a few recommendations for people who have installed Super Mario as they may be exposed to malware. According to CRIL, all users should periodically monitor their CPU usage and system performance, and activate automatic software updates for Windows. The recommendations also include using a strong antivirus software or internet security program on the device and other connected devices.</p>
<p>According to a Protos <a href="https://protos.com/mamma-mia-crypto-malware-hidden-in-super-mario-game/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, this is not the first time hackers have infected Super Mario with malware. Protos says that researchers found “a mess of viruses” associated with Super Mario Forever in the late 2010s.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/">Super Mario Forever Game Installs Crypto Mining Malware on User Devices and Steals Personal Data</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/super-mario-crypto-mining-malware/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Launch New Products Including iPhone 15 and Watch Ultra This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 15:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone 15]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vision pro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260469</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/">Apple to Launch New Products Including iPhone 15 and Watch Ultra This Year</a></p>
<p>Apple would likely go ahead with a fall release for the iPhone 15, along with a few other new products slated for this year and 2024.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/">Apple to Launch New Products Including iPhone 15 and Watch Ultra This Year</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/">Apple to Launch New Products Including iPhone 15 and Watch Ultra This Year</a></p>
<p>Apple has a few new products in its roadmap for 2023 and well into 2024. The expected new products include the iPhone 15 and a new Apple Watch, among others.</p>
<p>A Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-06-25/apple-2023-and-2024-road-map-iphone-15-m3-macs-ipad-air-vision-pro-headset-ljbftjwx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> has highlighted products Apple lovers should expect following the company’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-mixed-reality-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vision Pro mixed-reality headset debut</a>. For instance, Apple intends to release the iPhone 15 sometime in the fall of this year. While there is no official word from Apple on specs, several rumors are already floating through the grapevine.</p>
<p>MacRumors earlier <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that the iPhone 15 will include four models with two at 6.1 inches and two at 6.7 inches, like the iPhone 14 releases. The report also suggests that all four iPhone 15 models will feature USB-C ports instead of Lightning ports. Prices are expected from $799.</p>
<p>Apple lovers can also expect a new iMac with a 24-inch screen. The company is also reportedly developing a new 30-inch iMac. In addition to the iPhone and iMac, Apple should refresh the iPad Pro and iPad Air as well.</p>
<p>Furthermore, expected Apple products include new MacBook Pro models. The MacBook Pro will come in different sizes &#8211; 13, 14, and 15 inches. All three models will feature Apple’s M3 chip.</p>
<p>At its recent Apple Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC), Apple <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-series-products-wwdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> a new 15-inch MacBook Air priced at $1,299. Users can choose one of four colors, all powered by Apple’s M2 chipset. In addition, Apple announced software updates, including the WatchOS 10 with new features like hiking and cycling for complete tracking. Furthermore, users should expect a software update for iOS 17.</p>
<h2>New Apple Products to Precede Vision Pro Headset</h2>
<p>Some of the products expected from Apple will likely be available before the recently-launched <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-mixed-reality-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vision Pro headset</a> ships to the market. Apple announced the headset at the WWDC, with several interesting features.</p>
<p>For instance, the device comes with an EyeSight feature that switches between transparent and opaque modes for the benefit of people around the user. Owners can also control their devices with hands and eyes, as the headset has 12 cameras that track user movement.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Bloomberg’s report states that there’s still a lot left for Apple to figure out before releasing the Vision Pro. Reportedly, the showcase at the WWDC only featured the best parts of the device. Several features, including in-air typing, are not yet ready. The report also states that Apple is not done integrating several interface elements, and adapting core iPad apps for the new device.</p>
<p>Apple also hasn’t figured out support for third-party apps and might still have trouble with the EyeSight feature. In addition, there is still some uncertainty about the device working well with users who wear prescription lenses.</p>
<p>Consequently, Apple has reportedly expanded device testing and involved a few thousand extra employees. Apple initially only allowed senior executives and engineers to take the new device home. However, the company may now provide more developers with increased access so the device is ready as scheduled.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/">Apple to Launch New Products Including iPhone 15 and Watch Ultra This Year</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-new-products-iphone-15/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan’s National Tax Agency Says Crypto Startups Will Not Pay for Unrealized Gains</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260464</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/">Japan&#8217;s National Tax Agency Says Crypto Startups Will Not Pay for Unrealized Gains</a></p>
<p>The move is expected to attract crypto investors who had fled the country following the heavy burdens caused by taxations of unrealized profits.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/">Japan&#8217;s National Tax Agency Says Crypto Startups Will Not Pay for Unrealized Gains</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/">Japan&#8217;s National Tax Agency Says Crypto Startups Will Not Pay for Unrealized Gains</a></p>
<p>Undeniably, the cryptocurrency and blockchain markets have turned out to be a huge backbone for the development of economic growth prospects in many markets around the world. By now, it is safe to bet that countries have a clear understanding that the cryptocurrency and blockchain industries are here to stay and thus prudent to tap into their prowess to rebuild their economies following the devastations of Covid-19. Japan has been a key growth factor to most crypto projects, especially those fleeing the United States due to punitive regulatory aspects. Crypto projects like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> have made a significant entrance into the market of Japan through its cross-border payment solutions including RippleNet.</p>
<h2>Japan Regulators Open Doors Wide for Crypto Projects</h2>
<p>Following the meteoric growth of the cryptocurrency market through the Decentralized Financial (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) industry, the Japanese government is keen to attract investors to tap into its vast local market. In the recent crypto update in Japan, the country’s National Tax Agency via the ruling Liberal Democratic Party (LDP) tax committee approved a proposal to exempt digital asset projects from paying unrealized gains on their products.</p>
<p>Essentially, crypto projects operating in the Japanese market were obligated to pay unrealized taxes of about 35 percent on digital tokens issued to the local market. The document added that the tax exemptions will be applicable to unrealized gains from holding applicable crypto assets continuously from the date of issuance or from taking certain technical measures to prevent its transfer to other persons.</p>
<p>The Japanese government only <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/26/japanese-crypto-issuers-wont-pay-taxes-on-unrealized-gains-govt-clarifies/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wants</a> to tax crypto traders after they take profit in fiat currencies, which will be done through regulated digital asset exchanges. According to the country’s prime minister Fumio Kishida, the crypto market has the chance to alter the financial market for the betterment of the future. The narrative is evident through the fact that Kishida reassured investors through a parliament speech last year that the country will continue to focus on supporting the social implementation of digital technology.</p>
<p>Earlier last year, the current ruling party in Japan Liberal Democratic Party (LDP) released an NFT White Paper that referred to the Web3 industry as the new frontier of the digital economy and outlined plans to advance the national strategy on mainstream adoption.</p>
<h2>Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The crypto market in Japan has significantly rebounded since the collapse of FTX and the local subsidiary returned cash to traders. As a means to attract investors of all kinds, Japan has initiatives to use NFTs and DAOs in various governance aspects. Moreover, government officials in Japan are closely looking into how the metaverse industry could revolutionize overall governance.</p>
<p>Moreover, government officials are able to meet virtually in a secure platform through blockchain technology thus increasing the overall efficiency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/">Japan&#8217;s National Tax Agency Says Crypto Startups Will Not Pay for Unrealized Gains</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-tax-agency-crypto-startups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Classic Engineers Working on Major Revival Plan with ‘Six Samurai’ Proposal</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lunc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terrausd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdtc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/">Terra Classic Engineers Working on Major Revival Plan with ‘Six Samurai’ Proposal</a></p>
<p>The 'Six Samurai' proposal presents roadmap to important components such as the migration from Columbus-5 to Columbus-6 and an upgrade to the Cosmos SDK.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/">Terra Classic Engineers Working on Major Revival Plan with ‘Six Samurai’ Proposal</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/">Terra Classic Engineers Working on Major Revival Plan with ‘Six Samurai’ Proposal</a></p>
<p>Six engineers working on the Terra Classic ecosystem have proposed a &#8216;Six Samurai&#8217; plan for the complete revival of the blockchain ecosystem. This development comes as some community members of Terra have been looking to break away entirely from the shadows of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/do-kwon-extradition-custody-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">disgraced</a> founder Do Kwon and bring new life to the LUNC ecosystem.</p>
<p>Terra Classic, the original network developed by Terraform Labs, has remained as an autonomous blockchain instead of transitioning to Terra 2.0, which emerged as a separate version following Terra&#8217;s downfall. As of Monday, June 26, the LUNC tokens on Terra Classic are currently valued at $580 million.</p>
<p>Terra Classic engineers co-led by “Solid Snake&#8221; and “Bilbo Baggins” submitted a governance proposal to the Terra Classic community with a $116,000 three-month spend. If approved by the community, these engineers would work part-time on the project.</p>
<p>The proposal represents an ambitious roadmap put forward by passionate LUNC holders. The roadmap includes important components such as the migration from Columbus-5 to Columbus-6 and an upgrade to the Cosmos SDK. Additionally, the proposal outlines plans to list Terra Classic on Keplr&#8217;s Web Interface, which offers analytic visualizations, as well as on Mintscan, a block explorer for Cosmos. In the proposal, the Samurai Six engineers noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“LUNC has limitless upside potential, and we want to help realize it by leveraging our skills to bring value to the blockchain and all its investors in order to accomplish a true revival of the ecosystem. We&#8217;re here to provide value to the ecosystem on its road to revival, and we see ourselves as contributors to the Terra Classic blockchain, both as developers and long-time community members/investors.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Six Samurai Propose a Plan for Testnet for TerraUSD (USTC)</h2>
<p>Some additional tasks that the proposal includes are upgrading the network in order to reduce the syncing times between the nodes. It also includes building a testnet for the TerraUSD (USTC) stablecoin for testing financial services.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there&#8217;s a plan for building an application for generating yield to token holders along with a plan to reward developers for the user activity that their applications generate.</p>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<p>The Terra Luna Classic community is currently voting on a proposal called &#8220;USTC / Stable Algo Quant Team.&#8221; The proposal aims to incrementally adjust and simulate the TerraClassicUSD (USTC) repeg. Initial voting shows support from the community and the Quant team developers who will be working on setting the USTC repeg to $1. The Joint L1 Task Force (L1TF) developer team will also assist the Quant team in this repeg process.</p>
<p>A team member named RedlineDrifter <a href="https://twitter.com/RedlineDrifter/status/1673107790787739651" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shared</a> on Twitter that Proposal 11597 is up for voting. This proposal is crucial for the Terra Luna Classic chain, and other community members are also spreading awareness about the USTC repeg proposal.</p>
<p>According to the proposal, the Quant team requires a payment of $20,000 in LUNC for the first month. The Quant team consists of members like RedlineDrifter, Faffy, Alex, Bilbo Baggins, and Kyjack. Additionally, Terra Classic&#8217;s core developer and professor Edward Kim will volunteer to contribute to the team by assisting in AI research related to backtesting and USTC repeg.</p>
<p>The Quant team&#8217;s objective is to improve an existing tool, conduct a thorough analysis, and provide valuable insights into the strengths and weaknesses of the algorithm.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/">Terra Classic Engineers Working on Major Revival Plan with ‘Six Samurai’ Proposal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-classic-revival-plan-six-samurai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore’s Central Bank Proposes Interoperable Network Design for Tokenizing Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[project orchid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbi digital asset]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/">Singapore&#8217;s Central Bank Proposes Interoperable Network Design for Tokenizing Assets</a></p>
<p>Singapore's MAS created the report with 11 banking giants to run several pilots improve market issuance by tokenizing assets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/">Singapore&#8217;s Central Bank Proposes Interoperable Network Design for Tokenizing Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/">Singapore&#8217;s Central Bank Proposes Interoperable Network Design for Tokenizing Assets</a></p>
<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) is proposing a framework to develop open and interoperable networks for tokenizing assets. On Monday, the central bank <a href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/publications/monographs-or-information-paper/2023/project-guardian-open-interoperable-networks" target="_blank" rel="noopener">published</a> a report containing details of its proposal, called Project Guardian.</p>
<p>The publication states that the MAS is already collaborating with 11 organizations working to develop and test tokenization across multiple asset categories. The test will feature foreign exchange, fixed income, and wealth management asset classes powered by a few financial services companies.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the MAS is not very supportive of most cryptocurrencies because of their highly speculative nature. However, the central bank said it is interested in the benefits obtainable from the digital asset world. According to MAS deputy managing director of markets and development Leong Sing Chiong, “while MAS strongly discourages and seeks to restrict speculation in cryptocurrencies, we see much potential for value creation and efficiency gains in the digital asset ecosystem.”</p>
<p>Some of the banks part of the initial testing and proposal are DBS, Standard Chartered, Citi, and HSBC. Standard Chartered is already working on a platform that develops asset-backed tokens for trading on the Singapore Exchange. Speaking on the pilot, Standard Chartered’s global head of trade and working capital, Kai Fehr, said the test has already confirmed the advantages available to investors. According to Fehr, “the initial pilot trade conducted in collaboration with Singapore Exchange and Linklogis proves the viability of assets-backed tokenization as an innovative originate-to-distribute structure, and the potential opportunities it presents to investors to participate in financing real-world economic activity.”</p>
<h2>Further Details of Singapore’s Project Guardian Framework for Tokenizing Assets</h2>
<p>In addition to the participating banking giants, the MAS developed the report with the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) Committee on Payments and Market Infrastructure (CPMI).</p>
<p>As part of the project, HSBC, Marketnode, and UOB, have concluded a technical pilot for issuing a digitally native structured product. MAS says this pilot proves that the structured product chain can offer faster issuance and settlements at lower costs.</p>
<p>Another pilot carried out by UBS Asset Management explores Variable Capital Company (VCC) fund issuance on digital asset networks. The aim of this pilot is to improve trading VCC fund shares on the secondary market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, DBS Bank, UBS AG, and SBI Digital Asset Holdings are working on a repurchasing agreement with digital bonds. This is to introduce more flexibility, efficiency, and speed for cross-border distribution and settlement.</p>
<h2>Singapore’s CBDC Project</h2>
<p>The MAS’ general reluctance toward CBDCs has not kept it from exploring non-speculative digital currencies. Singapore joined several countries working on central bank digital currencies (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a>) and completed the first phase of its CBDC project. Called <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-phase-1-project-orchid/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Project Orchid</a>, the MAS initially began working on it in November 2021.</p>
<p>Project Orchid set out to examine the design and technicalities of a CBDC system in Singapore. The central bank also examined how well a CBDC would function with existing payment frameworks. The bank revealed:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Though MAS has assessed that there is non urgent need for a retail CBDC in Singapore at this point in time, MAS seeks to facilitate ongoing learning and advance the financial infrastructure in Singapore.”</p></blockquote>
<p>At launch, the MAS called Project Orchid a “multi-year, multi-phase exploratory project” without providing a time frame.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/">Singapore&#8217;s Central Bank Proposes Interoperable Network Design for Tokenizing Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-central-bank-tokenizing-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HSBC Approves Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Trading in Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hsbc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/">HSBC Approves Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Trading in Hong Kong</a></p>
<p>In conjunction with its decision to allow Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF trading, HSBC has launched the Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/">HSBC Approves Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Trading in Hong Kong</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/">HSBC Approves Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Trading in Hong Kong</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hsbc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">HSBC Holdings plc</a> (LON: HSBA), the largest bank in Hong Kong, has made history by becoming the first bank in the region to offer crypto trading services to its customers.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1673266576370577408" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revealed</a> by Independent Chinese Journalist, Wu Blockchain, customers can now buy and sell <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/ethereum-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH) Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) listed on the Hong Kong exchange. This move comes as a response to the growing demand for digital assets and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-hsbc-standard-chartered-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">pressures</a> on banks from Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA), the country’s banking regulator, to accept crypto exchanges as clients.</p>
<p>Currently, the Hong Kong Exchanges and Clearing Limited (HKEX) has listed three crypto exchange-traded funds on its platform. These ETFs include the CSOP Bitcoin Futures ETF, CSOP Ethereum Futures ETF, and Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF.</p>
<p>These crypto ETF listings on the Hong Kong exchange provide several advantages to investors. Firstly, it offers a regulated framework that ensures investor protection, enhancing the credibility of the crypto market. Additionally, ETFs provide ease of access, as they can be bought and sold on the exchange like traditional stocks, offering convenience and liquidity to investors.</p>
<p>As more investors gain exposure to cryptocurrencies through regulated channels such as ETFs, the mainstream adoption of digital assets is projected to accelerate, perhaps attracting institutional investors who have been waiting for more established investment vehicles.</p>
<p>HSBC&#8217;s decision to offer crypto trading services to Hong Kong investors is indeed a strategic move that aligns with the growing importance of the cryptocurrency industry in the region. Hong Kong has witnessed significant developments in crypto innovation, attracting a wide range of investors, entrepreneurs, and blockchain enterprises.</p>
<p>The move by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/">open</a> crypto trading activities to retail investors further underscores the increasing acceptance and recognition of digital assets in the financial sector.</p>
<h2>HSBC Launches Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre</h2>
<p>In conjunction with its decision to allow Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF trading, HSBC has launched the Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre. This strategic placement ensures that investors who engage with virtual asset-related products through these platforms have easy access to the educational resources and risk disclosures provided by the education center.</p>
<p>Remarkably, HSBC has made the Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre available to its customers via a variety of channels, including the HSBC HK Easy Invest app, the HSB CHK Mobile Banking app, and online banking.</p>
<p>By providing educational resources and requiring customers to acknowledge the associated risks, HSBC is empowering individuals to make informed investment decisions when engaging with digital asset-related products. This educational initiative contributes to the overall maturity and integrity of the crypto market while fostering a culture of responsible investing in Hong Kong, a stance that many other regions may learn from.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/">HSBC Approves Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Trading in Hong Kong</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-etf-hong-kong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Rescinds Decision to Delist Privacy Coins as It Complies with EU Regulations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[beam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decred]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[firo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[horizon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mob]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mobilecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nav]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[navcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pivx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scrt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[secret]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[verge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xmr]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XVG]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zcash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/">Binance Rescinds Decision to Delist Privacy Coins as It Complies with EU Regulations</a></p>
<p>Binance will not delist privacy coins in Europe, opting instead to review its classification of assets in line with EU law.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/">Binance Rescinds Decision to Delist Privacy Coins as It Complies with EU Regulations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/">Binance Rescinds Decision to Delist Privacy Coins as It Complies with EU Regulations</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has reviewed its decision to delist several privacy coins in Europe. The exchange will no longer delist these coins as it works to comply with regulations stipulated by European authorities.</p>
<p>Binance will now reclassify privacy coins to satisfy regulations. In a recent comment, Binance <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-relists-privacy-coins-in-europe" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“After carefully considering feedback from our community and several projects, we have revised how we classify privacy coins on our platform to comply with EU-wide regulatory requirements.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance also noted that it must comply with regulations in several individual EU jurisdictions since it is registered in these places. The exchange said these jurisdictions have specific laws that expect Binance to “monitor transactions for coins listed on our platform.”</p>
<h2>Binance Planned to Delist Multiple Privacy Coins in Europe</h2>
<p>Last month, Binance announced it would suspend access to privacy coins, making them unavailable for trading in Poland, France, Spain, and Italy. At the time, Binance said at least a dozen coins would stop trading.</p>
<p>The exchange named Dash (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DASH</a>), Zcash (ZEC), BEAM, Verge (XVG), Monero (XMR), PIVX, and MobileCoin (MOB). Other named coins are Horizon (ZEN), Firo (FIRO), Decred (DCR), Navcoin (NAV), and Secret (SCRT). Binance said it took the decision “as part of Binance’s ongoing compliance processes.”</p>
<p>The Binance announcement met with some resistance. For instance, Guy Zyskind, the co-founder and CEO of Secret Labs, said Secret has tried to rectify what it considers a misclassification. Zyskind <a href="https://decrypt.co/142973/binance-delist-monero-zcash-4-european-countries" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told Decrypt</a> that only data contained in smart contracts are confidential, while transactions remain public. According to him, “Secret is much more appropriate for GDPR-type applications in the blockchain setting.”</p>
<p>Privacy coins provide users with a lot more anonymity than is ordinarily available. These coins obscure user transactions such that surveillance becomes nearly impossible. Consequently, authorities have become considerably averse to privacy coins as they believe these assets are easily used for money laundering and other illegal transactions.</p>
<h2>The European Union and MiCA</h2>
<p>In April, the EU <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-parliament-passes-mica/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed</a> the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) bill to regulate the digital currency sector. The bill was first introduced in 2020 to provide much-needed clarity for Virtual Assets Service Providers (VASPs). While there are several arguments against MiCA, privacy coins may be more affected than other types of digital assets. For instance, MiCA would require exchanges to only support privacy coins if they verify user identities.</p>
<p>The EU Parliament voted 517-38 in favor of MiCA after multiple deliberations. For instance, Parliament postponed a final vote for the second time due to translation issues. A postponement in January followed a previous delay in November 2022 because the legal document had to be translated into all 24 official languages.</p>
<p>With MiCA, the EU has pioneered comprehensive crypto regulations and provided clarity that may be absent in other places like the US. Crypto firms in the US have been at loggerheads with authorities like the SEC for what many have described as a deliberate attempt to avoid providing clarity.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/">Binance Rescinds Decision to Delist Privacy Coins as It Complies with EU Regulations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-privacy-coins-eu-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berkshire Hathaway Sells 2.53 Million of China’s BYD Shares</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[berkshire hathaway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[byd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=260390</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/">Berkshire Hathaway Sells 2.53 Million of China’s BYD Shares</a></p>
<p>Berkshire Hathaway purchased 225 million of the EV maker’s shares for $230 million in 2008.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/">Berkshire Hathaway Sells 2.53 Million of China’s BYD Shares</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/">Berkshire Hathaway Sells 2.53 Million of China’s BYD Shares</a></p>
<p>American multinational conglomerate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/berkshire-hathaway/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Berkshire Hathaway</a> (NYSE: BRK.B) sold 2.52 million shares of Chinese EV maker BYD listed in Hong Kong on the 19th of June. A stock exchange filing revealed that the investment company sold the shares for HKUS$ 675.80 million, equaling $86.3 million.</p>
<h2>Berkshire Cuts China&#8217;s BYD Shares Holdings</h2>
<p>Following the sale of the BYD share, Berkshire Hathaway’s holdings in the Chinese company’s issued H-shares reduced from 9.21 % to 8.98%. Notably, Berkshire Hathaway is not new to selling part of its shares. As a matter of fact, it is not the first time this year the investment company will be selling its shareholdings in other companies. Before its move on BYD, Berkshire Hathaway traded most of its Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TSMC</a>) stock. It performed a major cut, reducing its holdings by 86%. Meanwhile, it bought the shares around three months prior to the sale.</p>
<p>The American multinational conglomerate purchased the shares in November 2022, causing TSMC’s stock to surge. Shortly after the $5 billion investment, the semiconductor manufacturing company saw its stock decline 4% in Taipei amid broader market losses. Berkshire’s decision to offload TSMC’s stock came as a surprise to the market, including the co-president of Taishin Securities, Tony Huang, who said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s surprising that Berkshire cut its holdings so much in just a quarter, which differs from its past practice of long-term investment and continuing to add shares.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Berkshire&#8217;s Selloffs</h2>
<p>As Huang said, the investment company typically holds on to its acquired shares on a long-term basis. It also buys more shares from the same company after the initial acquisition. However, the recent decision concerning TSMC is a deviation from the usual practice. As for BYD, Berkshire Hathaway purchased 225 million of the EV maker’s shares for $230 million in 2008. Since the acquisition, the American company’s investment has boomed. The last time the shares of BYD peaked in June 2022, Berkshire Hathaway’s investment was worth $9.5 billion.</p>
<p>In February, the South China Morning Post (SCMP) <a href="https://www.scmp.com/business/china-business/article/3209740/buffetts-berkshire-reports-2nd-biggest-byd-stake-take-us26-billion-table-six-month-selling-spree" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> the second biggest of nine publicly disclosed transactions since Berkshire began to trim its BYD stake in August 2022. The SCMP noted that the cutback on the 3rd of February took $2.6 billion off the table within a six months selling spree. The spree included a $1.33 million BYD shares sold-off <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-reduces-stake-byd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> by Coinspeaker. At the time, the sale was worth $34.43 million, and the company’s holdings dropped from 15.07% to 14.95% on the 8th of December, 2022.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spot-bitcoin-etf-bernstein/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/">Berkshire Hathaway Sells 2.53 Million of China’s BYD Shares</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/berkshire-hathaway-2-53m-byd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4213 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1020950 metric#prefetches=208 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=214 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=94.08 metric#ms-cache=4.45 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2223 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.7 -->