<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:37:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvda stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
<p>China manufactures nearly 80 percent of global gallium and germanium products used in making chips that are critical in AI developments.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
<p>The Xi Jinping-led government has once again pushed the People&#8217;s Republic of China to arise against the enemy’s gunfire after being left with few moves to play. Notably, the government of China has issued a stern warning against the exportation of gallium and germanium products, which are mostly used in the manufacture of semiconductor chips. On July 3, the Chinese Ministry of Commerce issued a joint statement with the General Administration of Customs requiring all gallium and germanium metal exports to have a government license.</p>
<p>Citing national security interests, the Chinese government <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-to-tighten-control-on-exports-of-ai-chip-making-materials" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that there will be no excess exportation of gallium and germanium starting from August 1. Reportedly, the government has put in place punitive actions against persons caught going against the issued orders.</p>
<p>Some of the metal products highlighted in the recent export restrictions include gallium antimonide, gallium arsenide, gallium metal, gallium nitride, gallium oxide, gallium phosphide, gallium selenide, and indium gallium arsenide.</p>
<p>Others are germanium products including germanium dioxide, germanium epitaxial growth substrate, germanium ingot, germanium metal, germanium tetrachloride, and zinc germanium phosphide.</p>
<h2>China Checkmates US Sanctions on AI Chips</h2>
<p>Undeniably, the Chinese government has outwitted the United States government in taking control of futuristic technologies by restricting the exportation of key materials. Moreover, a 2023 report from the European Commission and the European Association of Critical Raw Materials Alliance (CRMA), shows that the Republic of China is home to over 80 percent of global gallium supply. The Chinese tech experts are now working on scaling the production of their modern semiconductor chips to remain a major global hub for tech companies in the future.</p>
<p>Notably, Chinese tech companies have suffered a low supply of American emerging technologies since the Trump administration began issuing sanctions. The situation has over the years worsened after the Biden administration issued similar sanctions and pushed its allies including Japan to cut China off the semiconductor supply.</p>
<p>Since the Artificial Intelligence (AI) boom, related stocks and products have skyrocketed amid heavy speculations. For instance, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corp.</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) saw its market capitalization rally towards $1 trillion earlier this year following the demand vs supply choke. According to the latest stock market data, NVDA shares have rallied about 19 percent YTD to trade around $424 on Tuesday. Interestingly, nearly 50 Wall Street analysts expect the NVDA stock market to rally further in the coming future with an average rating of Buy.</p>
<p>The response from the White House on the matter is expected to escalate or calm down the situation after Chinese officials earlier requested nations to work together on technology for humanity’s future. Nonetheless, the ongoing war between Russia and Ukraine has complicated the relationship between the West and China.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/">China Seeks Global Tech Control via Issuing Stern Restrictions on Exporting Semiconductor-Making Materials</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-global-tech-semiconductor/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluesky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jack dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mastodon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TweetDeck]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
<p>The competition in the social media industry is heating up, and Twitter is finding itself in the midst of a dynamic landscape with various rivals vying for user attention and engagement.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
<p>In a recent announcement, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a> confirmed that a change is forthcoming regarding the accessibility of TweetDeck. According to recent <a href="https://www.nottinghampost.com/news/uk-world-news/twitter-says-tweetdeck-soon-only-8572133" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, starting in 30 days, TweetDeck will only be accessible to users who have obtained verified status on the platform.</p>
<p>TweetDeck has long been regarded as a helpful resource for social media enthusiasts, professionals, and corporations. Its unique features, such as the ability to handle various feeds and searches, have made it a go-to platform for people looking for a more simplified way to manage their Twitter activities.</p>
<h2>The Release of TweetDeck 2.0</h2>
<p>Notably, TweetDeck 2.0 introduces numerous major features and changes to the popular social media management application.</p>
<p>While users can expect new features such as video docking and enhanced Tweet composer functionality, one significant adjustment is the temporary disabling of TweetDeck Teams. However, Twitter has reassured users that TweetDeck Teams will be reintroduced in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>This announcement comes just days after <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>, Twitter’s Chairman made another significant change by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-daily-tweet-views-ceo-efforts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">limiting</a> unverified users to reading only 1000 posts per day. Since assuming ownership of the company, Musk has maintained an active and vocal presence, implementing various changes aimed at improving user experience and tackling longstanding issues plaguing the platform.</p>
<p>Twitter&#8217;s recent updates and changes continue to make waves in the social media landscape. In a recent development, verified users on Twitter, who have either subscribed to Twitter Blue or are considered “notable,” have seen an increase in their daily post limit.</p>
<p>Initially set at 6,000 posts, verified users can now read up to 10,000 posts per day, allowing for a more extensive engagement with the platform. As of now, all users, regardless of their Twitter Blue status, are able to access the new version of TweetDeck. This means that there is no immediate restriction on accessing TweetDeck for verified or unverified users.</p>
<h2>Competition Heats Up for Twitter</h2>
<p>The competition in the social media industry is heating up, and Twitter is finding itself in the midst of a dynamic landscape with various rivals vying for user attention and engagement.</p>
<p>One of the significant competitors that Twitter faces is Facebook from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), which has a massive user base and an established ecosystem of platforms and services.</p>
<p>Facebook&#8217;s recent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> of a rival app dubbed Threads adds another layer of competition to the mix. With its extensive resources and user reach, Facebook has the potential to pose a significant challenge to Twitter&#8217;s market position.</p>
<p>Other microblogging platforms have also emerged as formidable contenders in the social media space. Following Musk&#8217;s announcement, Bluesky, a platform backed by Jack Dorsey, the co-founder and former CEO of Twitter, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bluesky-record-traffic-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">experienced a surge</a> in traffic. Users flocked to Bluesky, leading to “record-high traffic” on the same day the announcement was made.</p>
<p>Another platform that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-mastodon-user-base/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">witnessed</a> a significant increase in traffic is Mastodon, a decentralized social network. Eugen Rochko, CEO of Mastodon revealed that the platform experienced a surge in its active user base by at least 110,000 on Sunday, July 2.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/">Twitter Subscribers to Gain Exclusive Access to TweetDeck</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-subscribers-tweetdeck/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[g7]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
<p>Inflation in the UK is still on the rise despite continuous hikes in interest rates and inflation reductions in other G7 countries.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
<p>Inflation in the United Kingdom (UK) is still rising despite continuous efforts from the country’s central bank. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/04/uk-is-now-the-only-major-economy-where-inflation-is-still-rising.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Data</a> from the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) states that inflation in all other G7 countries is falling.</p>
<p>According to the OECD, G7 inflation dropped from 5.6% in April to 4.6% in May. The organization noted that this reduction, the lowest in more than 6 months, was true of G7 countries outside the UK. The OECD said there are noted reductions in inflation in Japan, Canada, Germany, the US, France, and Italy.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the OECD said inflation dropped in all observed nations in May, from April, excluding the UK, Norway, and the Netherlands. In the UK, consumer prices rose 7.8% between April and May, and 7.9% compared to last year.</p>
<h2>Bank of England Still Fighting UK Inflation</h2>
<p>The Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>) recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-raises-interest-13th-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> an interest rate hike by 50 basis points. The announcement came after the Monetary Policy Committee voted 7-2 in favor, marking the 13th consecutive hike.</p>
<p>The BoE increased rates in response to inflation as the annual consumer price index climbed 8.7% in May, higher than the 8.4% economists had predicted. Core inflation, excluding alcohol, tobacco, and food, also climbed to 7.1% from the 6.8% recorded in April. Back in March, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-double-digit-march-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UK inflation was at 10.1%</a> according to the Office for National Statistics, higher than the 9.8% expected by a Reuters poll of economists. UK inflation hit <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-inflation-soars-highest-41-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">11.1% in November</a>, the highest level in 41 years.</p>
<p>Speaking on the hike, BoE governor Andrew Bailey said the increase was necessary. Bailey admitted that although the economy is improving, hiking interest rates is important as inflation is “still too high and we’ve got to deal with it.” Bailey warned that any delay in increasing these rates could worsen the economy in the near future.</p>
<p>Despite the poor figures, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) has a bullish outlook on the UK’s inflation. According to the IMF, the UK will likely escape a recession in 2023 and see positive growth this year. However, the IMF warns that although it expects growth, this outlook is “subdued”. Essentially, the Fund does not expect large growth margins. The IMF had previously <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-global-growth-forecast-us-eurozone-gdp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">predicted</a> that growth in the UK would contract by 0.3%</p>
<h2>More Hikes Coming?</h2>
<p>A Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-england-hikes-rates-5-surprise-move-tackle-stubborn-inflation-2023-06-22/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> states that markets predict a 50% chance that the rate would peak at 6.25% this year. The recent hike had pushed rates to 5%.</p>
<p>Generally, the UK’s economy has suffered a few setbacks that may have worsened inflation over time. In addition to Brexit and COVID-19, the country has experienced quite an increase in gas prices because of Russia’s war against Ukraine. Although many countries have suffered their fair share of problems caused by the same factors, the UK is still struggling.</p>
<p>Bailey said while the BoE is not expecting a recession, the rate hike was “absolutely imperative”, and the bank will continue to do whatever is required to reduce inflation.</p>
<p>A BoE forecast puts growth in the UK for 2023 at 0.25%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/">OECD Data: UK Is Only G7 Country where Inflation Is Still Rising</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-g7-inflation-oecd-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telescope labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
<p>Apart from setting the bar with the first-of-its-kind solution, Telescope Labs boasts the plugin's integration with artificial intelligence for advanced real-time analysis. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
<p>Launched in 2022, data analytics startup Telescope Labs has launched an advanced tool for analyzing and grading web3 games. The company provides support for web3 gaming outfits and uses predictive models and machine learning to cater to users. According to an official announcement on July 4th, the newly-unveiled plugin is powered by OpenAI&#8217;s GPT-4. The tool is a unique solution that utilizes <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI</a> to access thousands of web3 games.</p>
<h2>Telescope Labs Rolls Out AI Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</h2>
<p>Telescope Labs deploying the advanced reasoning abilities of GPT-4 means that the new tool for analyzing and grading web3 grams goes beyond the traditional analysis tools. It will help its users conduct daily analyses and compare the growth performance of multiple games. In addition, the Telescope Labs web3 game analytics powered by GPT-4 can be used to predict future trends.</p>
<p>Following the launch, users of the Telescope Labs tool can use it for grading and analyzing over 2,000 web3 games. Also, there are 37 distinct Key Performance Indicators (KPIs) available to them to make smarter choices. The KPIs have been optimized for web3 and are accessible to all users.</p>
<p>The CEO and co-founder of Telescope Labs, Semih Gilan, is excited about the announcement of the grading tool. He added that &#8220;the plugin&#8217;s blend of voluminous and varied data, sophisticated reasoning, user-friendliness, and real-time responsiveness is a game-changer for web3 gaming and blockchain.&#8221;</p>
<p>Notably, the plugin is the first-of-its-kind solution, and this means that Telescope Labs has set a standard for future developments. Already, OpenAI disrupted the markets with its ChatGPT before releasing GPT-4 months ago. Since its release on March 14th, 2023, the latest version of OpenAI&#8217;s multimodal larger language model has caught the attention of many companies like Telescope Labs. With Telescope Labs launching a GPT-4-backed web3 games grading tool, there will be a higher understanding of web3 gaming and blockchain game analysis.</p>
<h2>Telescope Labs Sets Bar for Future Developments</h2>
<p>Telescope Labs spoke about the push behind the development of the grading tool. The data analytics startup said the plugin is responding to the blockchain gaming industry&#8217;s call for advanced analysis tools. It added that blockchain gaming community members have been demanding user-friendly data analysis tools. Hence, the unveiling of the plugin.</p>
<p>Apart from setting the bar with the first-of-its-kind solution, Telescope Labs boasts the plugin&#8217;s integration with artificial intelligence for advanced real-time analysis. It also said the tool is easy to use and sets the benchmark regarding data access.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/">Telescope Labs Unveils GPT 4-Backed Advanced Tool for Analyzing and Grading Web3 Games</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/telescope-gpt-web3-grading-tool/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Luminex Announces BRC-69 Standard to Simplify Recursive Inscriptions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 12:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luminex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/">Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Luminex Announces BRC-69 Standard to Simplify Recursive Inscriptions</a></p>
<p>According to ordinals launchpad Luminex, the BRC-69 standard will make recursive ordinals easy and also create additional enhancements.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/">Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Luminex Announces BRC-69 Standard to Simplify Recursive Inscriptions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/">Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Luminex Announces BRC-69 Standard to Simplify Recursive Inscriptions</a></p>
<p>Luminex has launched a new standard that it calls the BRC-69. The standard will make Recursive Ordinals easier to create and significantly reduce inscription costs by more than 90%.</p>
<p>Luminex says reducing inscription costs can help decongest block space as more inscriptions flood the network. On the need for the BRC-69 standard, Luminex said in a <a href="https://twitter.com/luminexio/status/1675832803488043008?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“As the number of inscriptions grows, Bitcoin block spaces become increasingly scarce and costly. We need innovative approaches to enable creators to manifest their ideas while optimizing efficiency.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Luminex Describes the BRC-69 Recursive Inscription Process</h2>
<p>This process allows minters on the network to inscribe one text line instead of a full image. The network then uses the text line as a reference to create an image using data from other ordinals. Luminex <a href="https://twitter.com/luminexio/status/1675832805123850242?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explains</a> that this is possible through a 4-step process. This includes inscribing traits, deploying the collection, compiling the collection, and then minting assets.</p>
<p>The launchpad further explains the process on a <a href="https://github.com/luminexord/brc69" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">GitHub page</a>. After images of the traits are inscribed on-chain, the deploy operation creates a JSON/Text inscription that contains basic details of the collection, including inscription IDs. This functions as a reference for other parts of the process.</p>
<p>Following deployment, the compile inscription references the deploy inscription for the traits and inscription IDs to be used for the final image. Users can also customize the compile inscription logic depending on preferred specifics. Finally, Luminex says the mint phase for BRC-69 stores the index of traits and references the compile inscription so the image is easily rendered using on-chain data.</p>
<p>Luminex also <a href="https://twitter.com/luminexio/status/1675832810123440128?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">says</a> the introduction of BRC-69 creates opportunities for several other related enhancements:</p>
<blockquote><p>“BRC-69 offers high flexibility and opens the door for more enhancements and features. For instance, it’s now possible to launch collections with an entirely on-chain pre-reveal process. We’re eager to test this feature with our upcoming launches on Luminex.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin Ordinals</h2>
<p>Introduced by developer Casey Rodarmor, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/introduction-to-bitcoin-ordinals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Ordinals</a> are digital assets inscribed with data on the satoshi, essentially transforming a satoshi into a non-fungible token (NFT). Although very similar to traditional NFTs, Bitcoin Ordinals are different. For instance, Bitcoin Ordinals are on-chain, directly written on the Bitcoin network. For traditional NFTs, users newly mint tokens that may connect to other blockchains.</p>
<p>Another difference is regulating the kind of content generated with traditional NFTs is possible. For Bitcoin Ordinals, no censoring is possible with inscription on sats. Anyone can create any type of ordinal at any time.</p>
<p>In May, the Ordinals market and Bitcoin Miladys NFT collection launched the BRC-721E for interconnectivity between Bitcoin and Ethereum. The BRC-721E standard allows users to convert their ERC-721 NFTs to Ordinals, moving the tokens from Ethereum to the Bitcoin blockchain. This process is irreversible as it begins by using an ETH call function to burn the ERC-721 NFT.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/">Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Luminex Announces BRC-69 Standard to Simplify Recursive Inscriptions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ordinals-luminex-brc-69/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Explores Different Options for Video Streaming Platforms Youku, Tudou</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 11:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tudou]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[youku]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/">Alibaba Explores Different Options for Video Streaming Platforms Youku, Tudou</a></p>
<p>Alibaba is reviewing its video platform assets and is also planning restructuring to boost growth while creating separate entities for video streaming platforms. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/">Alibaba Explores Different Options for Video Streaming Platforms Youku, Tudou</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/">Alibaba Explores Different Options for Video Streaming Platforms Youku, Tudou</a></p>
<p>According to sources familiar with the matter, Chinese tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba</a> is currently exploring options for its video streaming and entertainment platforms  &#8211; Youku and Tudou. The latest development comes as part of Alibaba&#8217;s plan to revamp its structure.</p>
<p>Sources familiar with the matter said that the company has been conducting a strategic review of its two video streaming platforms. One of the options under consideration is injecting the assets into Alibaba Pictures Group Ltd. and thus bolstering the business scope of the Hong Kong-listed company.</p>
<p>Alibaba is reviewing its video platform assets while also planning a restructuring to boost growth. They aim to create separate leaders for different businesses like e-commerce, media, cloud, and logistics. Last month, the company made unexpected changes in its leadership by replacing its chief Daniel Zang, who had been with the company for eight years.</p>
<p>In China, video streaming platform Youku has been competing against Baidu Inc.’s iQiyi Inc. and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tencent/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tencent Holdings Ltd</a>. The rivalry has been pretty intense with each of these operators spending billions of dollars for unique content hosting original series. They seem to be following Netflix&#8217;s playbook of gaining market share and overwhelming other startups.</p>
<p>However, this approach triggers a price war that has proved unsustainable leading to losses for companies. Thus, iQiyi has shifted focus to boosting subscriptions with top-notch content as the firm looks to reverse years of losses.</p>
<p>Sources <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-04/alibaba-said-to-weigh-options-for-video-platforms-youku-tudou" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">told</a> Bloomberg that deliberations are at an early stage and Alibaba could be exploring other options including not proceeding with any deals or separate listings from the video platforms.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Pictures and Its Market Dominance</h2>
<p>According to its website, Alibaba Pictures is engaged in various aspects of the entertainment industry, including content production, promotion, distribution, cinema ticketing management, and data services. They have been involved in the production of successful movies in China like Wolf Warrior 2, The Wandering Earth, and Dying to Survive. Additionally, they made an investment in the movie Green Book, which received several awards at the 2019 Oscars.</p>
<p>Over the past year, the shares of Alibaba Pictures have decreased by approximately 45%, resulting in a market valuation of around $1.5 billion for the company.</p>
<p>Once arch-rivals, Youku and Tuduo merged in 2012 in a $1 billion all-stock deal. Later in 2016, Alibaba bought out the US-listed Chinese video site in a $5.1 billion deal. Youku is currently China&#8217;s third-largest long-form video platform, in terms of monthly active users. However, short video apps such as Bytedance’s Douyin have been posing mounting challenges to Youku in recent times.</p>
<p>But Youku&#8217;s investments in content and production capabilities have helped Alibaba narrow its losses for its digital media and entertainment business.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/">Alibaba Explores Different Options for Video Streaming Platforms Youku, Tudou</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-video-streaming-youku-tudou/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yahoo Set to Make Comeback by Going Public via IPO</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 11:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ipo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[softbank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[verizon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yahoo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/">Yahoo Set to Make Comeback by Going Public via IPO</a></p>
<p>The tech industry has witnessed a surge in IPOs this year, reflecting the robust investor appetite for innovative and high-growth companies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/">Yahoo Set to Make Comeback by Going Public via IPO</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/">Yahoo Set to Make Comeback by Going Public via IPO</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/yahoo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Yahoo Inc</a>, the once-dominant internet pioneer, is poised to return to public markets through an Initial Public Offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>). The company&#8217;s CEO, Jim Lanzone, made the announcement in an <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5c8c15ea-e495-4ab4-b535-e0ceef5030dd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with the Financial Times.</p>
<p>This announcement marks a significant milestone for Yahoo, as it seeks to regain its position as a major player in the ever-evolving digital landscape. Despite facing challenges in recent years, Yahoo continues to maintain a prominent position among the top five internet media firms globally, especially in terms of traffic.</p>
<p>According to Lanzone, Yahoo is well-prepared financially, boasting a strong balance sheet that can withstand the scrutiny of public markets. Furthermore, Lanzone highlighted the advantages of operating as a private company during the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-lay-off-workforce-ad-unit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">restructuring phase</a>.</p>
<p>He emphasized that this strategic approach allowed the company to streamline its operations, optimize efficiency, and align its business divisions with specific market segments.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Lanzone revealed that Yahoo plans to invest in strategic partnerships and acquisitions to bolster its capabilities and expand into new areas. Lanzone acknowledges the importance of keeping pace with technological advancements and changing consumer preferences, and he is committed to ensuring Yahoo! remains at the forefront of innovation.</p>
<h2>The Struggles of Yahoo</h2>
<p>Yahoo was started in 1994 by Jerry Yang and David Filo and embodies a long and rich history.  At its peak, the company was a leading search engine and portal, offering a wide range of internet services, including email, news, and advertising. However, Yahoo struggled to adapt to the rise of competitors like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), eventually losing its dominance and market share.</p>
<p>Since then, Yahoo has undergone numerous changes, including a sale to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/verizon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Verizon Communications Inc</a> (NYSE: VZ) in 2017, which resulted in the formation of a new entity called Verizon Media. Despite the rebranding efforts, the company faced ongoing challenges, struggling to keep up with the rapidly evolving digital landscape.</p>
<p>Now, under the leadership of Lanzone, who joined as CEO in 2021, Yahoo is ready to chart a new course. Lanzone, a seasoned executive with deep experience in the technology and media sectors, has ambitious plans to revive the iconic brand and position it for future success.</p>
<h2>Yahoo to Join the IPO Hype</h2>
<p>The tech industry has witnessed a surge in IPOs this year, reflecting the robust investor appetite for innovative and high-growth companies. For example, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/softbank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SoftBank Group Corp</a> (TYO: 9984), with significant investments in technology, is making <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/softbank-arm-ipo-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">preparations</a> for an IPO for its semiconductor subsidiary.</p>
<p>Another notable example is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holding Ltd</a> (HKG: 9988), which has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-split-6-groups-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> plans to split off into six separate business units. Out of these units, five are considering pursuing IPOs. This strategy allows Alibaba to focus on specific areas of its business while unlocking value for shareholders through individual IPOs.</p>
<p>The increased IPO activity in the technology sector reflects a positive market climate and investor interest in technology-driven enterprises. These offerings provide opportunities for investors to participate in the growth potential of innovative businesses and disruptive technologies.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/">Yahoo Set to Make Comeback by Going Public via IPO</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/yahoo-going-public-ipo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager Creditors Receive $5.1M Bill from Law Firm for March-May Services</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 11:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3ac]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[three arrows capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261557</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/">Voyager Creditors Receive $5.1M Bill from Law Firm for March-May Services</a></p>
<p>McDermott Will &#038; Emery has submitted a new bill of $5 million to Voyager creditors for the third interim, leading to a total over $16 million.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/">Voyager Creditors Receive $5.1M Bill from Law Firm for March-May Services</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/">Voyager Creditors Receive $5.1M Bill from Law Firm for March-May Services</a></p>
<p>The law firm representing crypto broker Voyager’s group of creditors has filed a bill for $5.1 million for work done from March to May. According to a summary cover sheet <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x193/11753/PLEADINGS/1175307042380000000001.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">filed</a> at the United States Bankruptcy Court Southern District of New York, this brings the total compensation required to $16.4 million.</p>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery’s filing shows the company has received $8.9 million of the $11.2 million compensation allowed so far. The filing shows that the total compensation bill for Voyager creditors covers 17,948 hours for professional and paraprofessional services rendered. According to the law firm, all services were done efficiently and effectively without any unnecessary duplications. In addition, McDermott Will &amp; Emery assured that it minimized the costs of its services in many areas by using “talented junior attorneys and paraprofessionals”.</p>
<p>The $5.1 million bill covers the third interim fee period. The law firm’s bill for the first interim period, between July and October 2022, was $5.6 million. McDermott Will &amp; Emery also added information on the second interim period, including a $5.5 million bill for November 2022 to February 2023. As of press time, Voyager creditors owe $7.5 million of the total bill.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the law firm included a summary of the services provided. Some of these include advising the creditors of their powers and duties according to bankruptcy law, as well as helping and advising with debtor consultations and negotiations.</p>
<h2>Voyager Creditors Bill Result from Representation Following Bankruptcy Filing</h2>
<p>Days after suspending trading and withdrawals, Voyager Digital <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-digital-chapter-11-bankruptcy-reorganization/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy last July at the Southern District of New York’s bankruptcy court. The company’s filing indicated up to $10 billion in liabilities to more than 100,000 creditors. At the time, Voyager said the reorganization was necessary so clients could access all of their funds in Voyager accounts.</p>
<p>Regardless of the problem, CEO Stephen Ehrlich said all customers with crypto in their accounts would receive compensation. According to Ehrlich, the compensation will combine common shares in the newly organized company, crypto in their accounts, Voyager tokens, and proceeds from the Three Arrows Capital (3AC) recovery. Voyager had loaned 3AC 350 million USDC and 15,250 BTC. 3AC went bankrupt last year and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/three-arrows-capital-plunges-into-liquidation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">began liquidation</a>, a large part of the reason Voyager also plunged into insolvency.</p>
<p>Last week, Voyager’s legal representative Kirkland &amp; Ellis billed the crypto broker $1.1 million for work done in April. The filing indicates some attorneys billed up to $150,000 for the month, while others billed up to $2,000 per hour. The firm’s blended hourly rate was $1,313.18. Interestingly, Kirkland &amp; Ellis <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-3m-legal-fees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">billed</a> Celsius Network $2.6 million for services rendered from July 13 to 31 last year.</p>
<p>In December 2022, Voyager <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-digital-binance-us-bid/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accepted</a> a Binance.US deal for acquisition. Reportedly worth $1.022 billion, the deal was the “highest and best bid for [Voyager’s] assets”. However, Binance.US <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-backs-out-plans-voyager/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eventually backed out</a> of the deal even after approval from relevant stakeholders. Binance said it took this decision because of the “hostile and uncertain regulatory climate in the United States”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/">Voyager Creditors Receive $5.1M Bill from Law Firm for March-May Services</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/voyager-creditors-5-1m-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Takes on Twitter: Facebook Owner Set to Launch Competing App on July 6</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 10:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/">Meta Takes on Twitter: Facebook Owner Set to Launch Competing App on July 6</a></p>
<p>The introduction of Threads by Meta will mark the latest chapter in the ongoing rivalry between the company and Twitter.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/">Meta Takes on Twitter: Facebook Owner Set to Launch Competing App on July 6</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/">Meta Takes on Twitter: Facebook Owner Set to Launch Competing App on July 6</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms</a>, the parent company of Facebook and Instagram, is making waves in the social media landscape with the upcoming launch of its new app called &#8220;Threads&#8221;. The app aims to challenge the dominance of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a> and is set to launch on July 6, this Thursday. Threads are designed as a text-based conversation app that provides users with an engaging and seamless platform for discussions. The new social platform will be integrated with the popular photo-sharing app, Instagram, allowing users to engage with the same accounts they already follow, fostering continuity and expanding their conversational networks.</p>
<p>Meta has launched a countdown website specifically for the new social media platform to create excitement for the launch. According to the company, Threads will be a space where communities can come together to discuss various topics of interest. Users can follow and connect directly with their favorite creators and others who share similar interests. They can also build a loyal following to share their ideas, opinions, and creativity.</p>
<h2>A Rivalry in the Making: Meta vs Twitter</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/03/technology/meta-app-twitter.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduction</a> of Threads by Meta marks the latest chapter in the ongoing rivalry between the company and Twitter. Mark Zuckerberg, the driving force behind Meta, has shown a talent for borrowing successful concepts and integrating them into the company&#8217;s ecosystem. Threads follow in the footsteps of Meta&#8217;s other successful adaptations, such as Reels, inspired by TikTok, and Stories, reminiscent of Snapchat. Meta&#8217;s new social media project features a similar interface to Twitter, with familiar functionalities like liking, commenting, reposting, and sharing. The app, which is already available for pre-order on Apple&#8217;s app store, ensures a smooth transition for users accustomed to the microblogging format, providing them with a user-friendly environment for engaging in discussions.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s introduction of Threads comes as Twitter faces criticism for recent restrictions and rate-limiting errors. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>, the new owner of Twitter, announced these restrictions on July 1, stating that verified accounts are limited to reading 6 million posts per day, while unverified accounts can only read five posts daily. New unverified accounts are limited to reading three posts per day. As a result of these new limits, Twitter competitors like Spill, Bluesky, and Post have witnessed significant growth, indicating a demand for alternative platforms. With its integration of established Instagram communities consisting of millions of users, Threads positions itself as a compelling option for users seeking a fresh social media experience outside of Twitter. This advantage sets Meta&#8217;s upcoming product apart from previous contenders who had to start from scratch.</p>
<h2>Meta Rolls Out New VR Subscription Service Quest+</h2>
<p>In addition to the new social platform scheduled to debut later this week, Meta has been engaging in other product offerings. Last month, the company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-ai-music-generator-musicgen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unveiled</a> MusicGen, a new artificial intelligence (AI) music generator that allows music enthusiasts to create songs using text inputs based on existing melody prompts. This product was introduced on June 27 as part of Meta&#8217;s efforts to explore the AI market.</p>
<p>That same month, the company also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-vr-subscription-quest/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> Meta Quest+, a new service to enhance users&#8217; virtual reality (VR) experience. This subscription service offers users an exciting opportunity to discover fresh gaming experiences without the hassle of searching through Meta&#8217;s extensive catalog. Users will also receive two new monthly titles, ready to be redeemed, enjoyed, and mastered. With the arrival of new games on the first day of every month, subscribers can eagerly anticipate a sense of anticipation and adventure in their gaming routine.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/">Meta Takes on Twitter: Facebook Owner Set to Launch Competing App on July 6</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-twitter-app-july-6/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TON Introduces Messaging Encryption Functionality on Its Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 10:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telegram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ton foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261521</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/">TON Introduces Messaging Encryption Functionality on Its Blockchain</a></p>
<p>When conducting transactions on the TON blockchain, users can include text messages and expect their information to be secure. End-to-end encryption ensures that the messages are not accessible to anyone else.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/">TON Introduces Messaging Encryption Functionality on Its Blockchain</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/">TON Introduces Messaging Encryption Functionality on Its Blockchain</a></p>
<p>The TON Foundation has launched end-to-end messaging encryption features on its blockchain. With the added feature, network users can send private messages to one another without any third parties getting access to the information. The launch was announced on July 3 by the TON Foundation, the team currently developing the network.</p>
<p>Originally, TON was created by the Telegram team as an Open network called <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-telegrams-ton-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Telegram Open Network</a> (TON). However, in 2020, Telegram halted the project due to issues with the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">United States Securities and Exchange Commission</a>.</p>
<p>The source code became freely available to other developers after Telegram&#8217;s withdrawal. By 2021, the TON community had grown to around 30,000 users, and the network began using TON Crystals (also known as TON) to reward contributors to the network.</p>
<p>After <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/telegram/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Telegram</a>&#8216;s departure, TON Labs became the primary developer of the Network. They have continued to work on the project, focusing on improving scalability, transaction throughput, and decentralization to give them an advantage over other Web3 projects.</p>
<h2>Introducing End-to-End Encryption to Strengthen Privacy on TON</h2>
<p>Beyond the network&#8217;s initial features, the newly introduced feature ensures that messages are sent in the most protected manner and are only available to the intended recipients.</p>
<p>When conducting transactions on the TON blockchain, users can include text messages and expect their information to be secure. End-to-end encryption ensures that the messages are not accessible to anyone else, including the developer or the government.</p>
<p>In a press release, the TON Foundation <a href="https://blog.ton.org/ton-wallet-becomes-an-encrypted-messenger" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> that:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;In The Open Network, when sending Toncoin, Jettons, or NFT, you have always been able to include an arbitrary text comment for the recipient. For example, &#8220;For coffee&#8221; or &#8220;Gift! Happy Birthday!&#8221;&#8230;. With the new update, you can now encrypt text when sending messages with transactions. This feature uses end-to-end encryption, so that only the sender and the recipient can view the message.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The developers believe that TON&#8217;s secure messaging solution could be a reliable communication option in case of a problem affecting traditional communication methods. This indicates that the network is ready to seize any opportune moments that could provide the desired exposure.</p>
<p>It still costs as little as 0.006 TON to transact on the network, and wallets like MyTonWallet and OpenMask already support it. It will also be added to TON mobile and Tonkeeper wallets through future app updates.</p>
<p>Many blockchain solutions are new and are still going through different forms of innovation. The addition of end-to-end encryption to the TON network is a good addition to the blockchain ecosystem, and its network could be a useful option when there is a need for secure messaging functionalities for transactions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-mastodon-user-base/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/">TON Introduces Messaging Encryption Functionality on Its Blockchain</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-encryption-messaging-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4092 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1063078 metric#prefetches=201 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=208 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=131.70 metric#ms-cache=6.33 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.3016 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->