<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:26:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>From $400M to $53M: Shutterstock Acquires Giphy from Meta at Fraction of Price</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[giphy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shutterstock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256097</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/">From $400M to $53M: Shutterstock Acquires Giphy from Meta at Fraction of Price</a></p>
<p>Shutterstock will acquire Giphy from Meta for $53 million in cash, complying with the UK regulator's order to divest the animated-images platform due to competition concerns.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/">From $400M to $53M: Shutterstock Acquires Giphy from Meta at Fraction of Price</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/">From $400M to $53M: Shutterstock Acquires Giphy from Meta at Fraction of Price</a></p>
<p>Shutterstock, an American provider of stock photography, footage, music, and editing tools, has announced the acquisition of Giphy Inc, the popular animated image platform owned by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a>.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/shutterstock-acquire-giphy-inc-53-million-cash-2023-05-23/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a>, Shutterstock is acquiring Giphy at an incredible discounted price of $53 million, as Meta had paid $400 million for the platform in 2020. The purchase is being carried out in response to an order from the UK competition regulator, which required Meta to sell the company last year due to concerns about potential access limitations to competition.</p>
<h2>Meta&#8217;s Losses from the Sale of Giphy Exceed $345 Million</h2>
<p>The sale of Giphy is causing Meta multimillion-dollar losses, exceeding $345 million. Reports indicate that the social media giant had been interested in <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2020/05/15/facebook-buys-gif-company-giphy-and-plans-to-integrate-it-with-instagram.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">acquiring Giphy</a> for several years, but the company executives were unwilling to sell it as they were in a &#8220;significant growth phase&#8221;.</p>
<p>Meta failed to leverage the company as expected since the beginning of its acquisition, facing legal problems with regulators due to a possible monopoly. This agreement marks the first time a US technology company is being forced by foreign regulators to sell a company.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-shares-up-170-since-november/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> by Coinspeaker, despite the multimillion-dollar losses generated by the sale of Giphy to Meta, this has been the best quarter for the company since 2012. Year-to-date, Meta&#8217;s shares have increased by over 104%, from $122.30 to $250.47, the current price at the time of writing.</p>
<p>According to Mark Zuckerberg, CEO and co-founder of Meta, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-q1-2023-results/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">growth</a> of Meta&#8217;s shares during Q1 is primarily due to the company&#8217;s work in the field of Artificial Intelligence.</p>
<h2>Shutterstock to Gains Access to Over 1.7 Billion Giphy Daily Users</h2>
<p>The acquisition of Giphy will provide Shutterstock with a significant increase of over 1.7 billion daily users, so the company is content with obtaining &#8220;minimal revenue&#8221; from Giphy during this year.</p>
<p>However, they plan to implement strategies to improve Giphy&#8217;s revenue generation starting in 2024, as the company is known for its vast repository of animated images and stickers used on major social media platforms such as Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, and Microsoft Teams.</p>
<p>Paul Hennessy, CEO of Shutterstock, expressed excitement about the acquisition, considering it an important step in the company&#8217;s evolution &#8220;as an end-to-end creative platform&#8221;.</p>
<p>While the agreement is expected to be finalized next month, Shutterstock&#8217;s shares reacted positively to the news, increasing by up to 4% before market opening.</p>
<p>Therefore, this acquisition represents a strategic move by Shutterstock to expand its creative platform by integrating the extensive collection of GIF images and stickers offered by Giphy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/">From $400M to $53M: Shutterstock Acquires Giphy from Meta at Fraction of Price</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/400m-53m-shutterstock-acquires-giphy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Partners with Broadcom to Develop USA-Made 5G Components</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5G Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[broadcom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/">Apple Partners with Broadcom to Develop USA-Made 5G Components</a></p>
<p>Given the significance of 5G technology in the advancement of consumer electronics and connectivity, Apple said it is spending tens of billions of dollars to develop this field in the US.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/">Apple Partners with Broadcom to Develop USA-Made 5G Components</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/">Apple Partners with Broadcom to Develop USA-Made 5G Components</a></p>
<p>Popular US tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) said it has <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/05/apple-announces-multibillion-dollar-deal-with-broadcom/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">signed</a> a multibillion-dollar agreement with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/broadcom/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Broadcom Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AVGO), a multinational semiconductor and infrastructure software firm to produce 5G components.</p>
<p>Through the partnership, Broadcom will develop 5G radio frequency components, including FBAR filters, and advanced wireless connectivity components that will be utilized by Apple. Notably, the FBAR filters will be designed and created at major US manufacturing and engineering centers, including Broadcom&#8217;s extensive facility in Fort Collins, Colorado.</p>
<p>While commenting on the update, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tim-cook/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tim Cook</a> stated that the firm is excited to commit to initiatives that capitalize on the inventiveness, creativity, and innovative spirit of Americans.</p>
<p>FBAR (Film Bulk Acoustic Resonator) filters are a type of electronic filter that is used in wireless communication systems, specifically radio frequency applications. One of the significant advantages of FBAR filters is their small size and high performance. They can be manufactured with high precision and integrated into compact electronic devices.</p>
<p>Apple wearable devices such as the Apple Watch may use FBAR filters to optimize wireless connections. These filters help improve the efficiency of wireless communication and enable features such as Bluetooth connectivity, cellular connectivity, and wireless data transfer.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the collaboration will help support more than 1,100 jobs at Broadcom&#8217;s FBAR filter manufacturing facility in Fort Collins. This collaboration would demonstrate the firm’s commitment to supporting job growth and investing in automation projects and skills development.</p>
<p>Apple has a significant impact on job creation and the economy in the United States. Through its direct employment, developer ecosystem, and spending with suppliers and manufacturers, Apple supports over 2.7 million jobs across the country. This includes jobs within Apple itself, as well as jobs created through the iOS app economy and the extensive supply chain.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Apple recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> it is ramping up production plans for its next-generation displays to reduce its reliance on South Korean rival <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung Electronics Co Ltd</a> (KRX: 005930).</p>
<h2>Apple Investing in 5G Technology</h2>
<p>Given the significance of 5G technology in the advancement of consumer electronics and connectivity, Apple said it is spending tens of billions of dollars to develop this field in the US.</p>
<p>Remarkably, Apple said these investments are part of its 2021 commitment to invest $430 billion in the US economy over five years. Currently, the company said it is on track to meet the five-year investment goal in the American economy through direct spending with American suppliers, data center investments, capital expenditures, and other domestic spending.</p>
<p>With 5G, consumers can expect improved mobile experiences, such as higher-quality video streaming, augmented reality and virtual reality applications, and immersive content consumption on smartphones and tablets.</p>
<p>Following the introduction of 5G technology to Apple devices in 2020, Apple has helped to expand and accelerate 5G adoption across the country, driving innovation and job growth among companies that support 5G innovation and infrastructure.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/">Apple Partners with Broadcom to Develop USA-Made 5G Components</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-broadcom-usa-5g-components/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Cloud to Downsize Headcount by 7%, with Layoff Signaling Beginning of Its Spinoff Process </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba cloud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/">Alibaba Cloud to Downsize Headcount by 7%, with Layoff Signaling Beginning of Its Spinoff Process </a></p>
<p>Alibaba Cloud has emerged as an early IPO candidate and will reportedly pursue a 7% staff layoff amid its ‘streamlined’ restructuring. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/">Alibaba Cloud to Downsize Headcount by 7%, with Layoff Signaling Beginning of Its Spinoff Process </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/">Alibaba Cloud to Downsize Headcount by 7%, with Layoff Signaling Beginning of Its Spinoff Process </a></p>
<p>The cloud arm of Chinese e-commerce giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group</a> (NASDAQ: BABA) has <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/alibaba-cloud-arm-cut-7-102544044.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">begun</a> a layoff set to affect 7% of its total workforce. Sources describe the downsizing as part of broader measures to prepare Alibaba’s cloud division for a spinoff. Furthermore, sources add that the new standalone company would ultimately pursue an initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>).</p>
<p>In late March, reports stated that Alibaba would <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-split-6-groups-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">split into six business groups</a> capable of pursuing IPOs. The company’s shares dipped marginally in pre-market trading Tuesday on news of the layoff development.</p>
<p>Alibaba has reportedly begun informing affected staff of its cloud division layoff plans. Inside sources stated that the Chinese multinational tech company is offering severance packages to affected staff. The company also plans to transfer some workers to other parts of its business empire as part of the headcount shakeup. However, one of the sources stressed that the transfer scheme is not guaranteed.</p>
<p>Alibaba, which is on course to streamline its cloud unit into a separate company within a year, employed over 235,000 people as of March.</p>
<h2>Alibaba CEO Comments on Cloud Division Shakeup Amid Layoff Plans</h2>
<p>Last week, Alibaba CEO Daniel Zhang detailed the company’s cloud division restructuring for the first time. Zhang explained that the Asian tech giant plans to entirely relinquish control of its once-thriving Alibaba Cloud venture. According to the chief executive, the e-commerce powerhouse views giving up control of the cloud arm as unlocking potential. Free from any potentially stifling Alibaba ownership constraints, the cloud unit can attract more significant growth potential as an independent entity.</p>
<p>Amid Alibaba Cloud’s agenda to operate as a separately-owned business entity, some analysts value the business above $30 billion. The reason is that the cloud business sector appears primed for substantial growth following ChatGPT’s explosive popularity. Furthermore, from a back-end point of view, ChatGPT’s technology relies on cloud-based resources to train next-gen artificial intelligence models.</p>
<p>Despite the positive outlook by experts, Alibaba Cloud’s representatives remained mum on suggestions that the unit would benefit from the AI revolution. Instead, reports stated that the cloud unit was selected as an early IPO candidate due to its more developed business model and customer profile. Furthermore, Zhang pointed out that the business’ spinoff was to establish its overall market structure and growth potential trajectory properly. The Alibaba CEO added that he believes a standalone cloud division could potentially outgrow and outpace Alibaba in size and scale. Zhang doubled down on his belief regarding the business offshoot’s potential if it attracted sound external financing.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Businesses to Branch Out 6 Ways to Maximize Potential, Including Pursuing Separate IPOs</h2>
<p>Approximately two months ago, Alibaba announced plans to split its services into 6 distinct standalone business groups. The company described the move as a way to “unlock shareholder value and foster market competitiveness” amid uncertain economic factors. Furthermore, Alibaba also said the six offshoot business groups revolve around its strategic priorities. The groups are Cloud Intelligence Group, Local Services Group, Tmall Commerce Group, Global Digital Commerce Group, Digital Media and Entertainment Group, and Cainiao Smart Logistics.</p>
<p>Each standalone business division would have its own CEO, board of directors, and potential public listing.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/">Alibaba Cloud to Downsize Headcount by 7%, with Layoff Signaling Beginning of Its Spinoff Process </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMF Predicts Positive Outlook for UK amid Broad Inflationary Worry</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/">IMF Predicts Positive Outlook for UK amid Broad Inflationary Worry</a></p>
<p>Per the IMF outlook, resilient demand in the context of declining energy prices can encourage a positive outlook for the UK economy in several ways.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/">IMF Predicts Positive Outlook for UK amid Broad Inflationary Worry</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/">IMF Predicts Positive Outlook for UK amid Broad Inflationary Worry</a></p>
<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) said it expects the United Kingdom to avoid a recession and maintain positive growth in 2023. According to a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/23/the-imf-now-expects-the-uk-to-avoid-a-recession.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the IMF attributes this positive outlook to resilient demand and declining energy prices, which have encouraged economic growth.</p>
<p>However, the IMF also characterizes the outlook as “subdued”, indicating that while growth is expected, it may not be robust.</p>
<p>In the report, the IMF noted that the economic activity in the UK had fallen sharply with inflation remaining at a “stubbornly high” rate of 10.1% compared to last year. Remarkably, British Finance Minister Jeremy Hunt stated that the task of fighting inflation and improving the UK&#8217;s growth prospects is far from done.</p>
<p>He named high energy prices and high inflation as problems facing both the UK and the rest of the world. However, Hunt admitted in an IMF press conference that the government is working towards prioritizing growth for the economy.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the report follows shortly after the IMF <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-global-growth-forecast-us-eurozone-gdp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">predicted</a> in an earlier review that UK’s growth would contract by 0.3% in 2023, making it the G20&#8217;s worst performer. Interestingly, the most recent release appears to indicate an improvement in the UK&#8217;s growth forecast.</p>
<p>The new forecast predicts that the UK growth will be 0.4% this year, up 0.7 percentage points from the previous forecast. This points to a more upbeat outlook for the UK economy in the near term. Furthermore, according to the IMF, UK GDP is expected to grow by 1% in 2024.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, the IMF projects growth of around 2% in 2025 and 2026. These projections suggest a gradual improvement in the UK&#8217;s economic performance over the medium term.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the IMF report referred to the UK’s continued financial stability as a &#8220;global public good&#8221; and recommended evidence-based reforms for London to address the post-pandemic rise in labor inactivity, regulatory uncertainty surrounding business investment, and accelerating the country&#8217;s green transition.</p>
<h2>IMF Outlook and the UK Economy Growth Twist</h2>
<p>Per the IMF outlook, resilient demand in the context of declining energy prices can encourage a positive outlook for the UK economy in several ways. When energy prices fall, household disposable income typically increases.</p>
<p>This can lead to increased consumer spending on goods and services, boosting economic activity and stimulating economic growth. Increased consumer spending supports businesses, boosts employment levels and contributes to overall economic growth.</p>
<p>In addition, lower energy prices can also improve the competitiveness of UK exporters. Reduced energy costs can increase the competitiveness of UK goods and services in international markets, potentially leading to increased exports and supporting economic growth.</p>
<p>With the UK Government exploring all avenues to bolster its economy, it will take solace in knowing that its biggest ally is also seeing a major meltdown with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/consumer-debt-us-17t-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">debt ceiling conversations</a> permeating the horizon.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/">IMF Predicts Positive Outlook for UK amid Broad Inflationary Worry</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-positive-outlook-uk-inflationary-worry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berenberg: MicroStrategy Shares Give Investors Better Crypto Exposure than Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/">Berenberg: MicroStrategy Shares Give Investors Better Crypto Exposure than Coinbase</a></p>
<p>The report says that macro drivers favor MicroStrategy shares in terms of the de-dollarization of the world economy.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/">Berenberg: MicroStrategy Shares Give Investors Better Crypto Exposure than Coinbase</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/">Berenberg: MicroStrategy Shares Give Investors Better Crypto Exposure than Coinbase</a></p>
<p>The German investment bank Berenberg said that investors seeking exposure to cryptocurrencies are better served if they buy the shares of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy</a> than those of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>A Monday report revealed to the media <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/23/microstrategy-shares-offer-better-exposure-to-crypto-than-coinbase-berenberg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> that macro factors associated with the shares of MicroStrategy Inc (NASDAQ: MSTR) give investors a higher possibility of being in profit than if they went for the shares of Coinbase Global Inc (NASDAQ: COIN). Highlighting its preference for MSTR, the Berenberg report outlined the reasons why investors should look towards MSTR as a better alternative to holding Coinbase shares in their quest to benefit from the potential of the coin market.</p>
<h2>Short on COIN, Long on MSTR</h2>
<p>According to the analysts, there are many investors who are bearish towards Coinbase shares and advised that they look towards MSTR as a viable alternative, not just by shorting COIN but by pairing it with MSTR to build a better-balanced portfolio that gives them the desired exposure to the coin market. It was added that it is an even better deal to short COIN while being long on MSTR.</p>
<p>The report stated that the correlation between MSTR and COIN is 0.96, referencing April 2021, when Coinbase went public through a direct listing. The MicroStrategy advantage stems from the fact that the company’s business model involves the direct acquisition of bitcoins, adding that with the currency regulatory environment, it is a better model than what is obtainable at Coinbase.</p>
<h2><strong>MicroStrategy Owns </strong>140,000 BTC</h2>
<p>MicroStrategy currently owns 140,000 Bitcoins, valued at $3.8 billion based on the current market price. The report says that macro drivers favor the company’s shares in terms of the de-dollarization of the world economy, which the company implies could lead to the weakening of the US economy. It added that the weakening of the USD is beginning to cast <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> in a positive light among many investors.</p>
<p>Despite this, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has maintained that crypto tokens are unregistered securities. The regulator and others in the United States have moved against platforms that trade on these assets in recent months. It is interesting to note that the blanket classification excluded Bitcoin, which the regulators deem a commodity, unlike most other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Coinbase May Face Enforcement Action</h2>
<p>Crypto trading platforms such as Binance.US and, more recently, Coinbase are in the sights of regulators. SEC Commissioner Gary Gensler is of the opinion that Coinbase does not comply with US securities law. The Berenberg report noted that the defiant stance of Coinbase management will not help the company’s cause but will rather accelerate enforcement actions against it.</p>
<p>&#8220;Coinbase’s revenues at risk in the event of an enforcement action are disproportionately profitable relative to its total revenue,&#8221; the report added.</p>
<p>According to the investment bank, Coinbase shares&#8217; hold rating price target is $55, while MicroStrategy shares have a buy rating price target of $340.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/">Berenberg: MicroStrategy Shares Give Investors Better Crypto Exposure than Coinbase</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/berenberg-microstrategy-shares-coinbase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Bitget Secures License to Operate in Poland</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 13:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vasp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256024</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/">Crypto Exchange Bitget Secures License to Operate in Poland</a></p>
<p>Bitget secured regulatory licenses as a virtual asset service provider in Poland and Lithuania, witnessing significant growth and positioning itself among the Top 4 centralized crypto exchanges. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/">Crypto Exchange Bitget Secures License to Operate in Poland</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/">Crypto Exchange Bitget Secures License to Operate in Poland</a></p>
<p>Earlier on Tuesday, May 23, crypto exchange Bitget announced that it has successfully registered as a virtual asset service provider (VASP) in Poland. Securing this regulatory license will allow Bitget to operate legally in the Polish market.</p>
<p>Amid the current market scenario, Bitget has been spreading its footprint fast across different markets. Last month in April 2023, Bitget secured its VASP license in Lithuania which will allow it to offer crypto-based services both from and within the Baltic nation. Speaking on the recent development, Gracy Chen, Bitget&#8217;s managing director, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We understand that regulation is the future of the cryptocurrency industry if mainstream adoption is to be achieved. The recent registrations in the two European countries enhance our foothold and service in Europe.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this month, Bitget released its quarterly transparency report outlining its achievements and growth that it attained during Q1 2023. The exchange&#8217;s website and mobile traffic jumped 35% QoQ to 33.1 million views. Its futures trading volume also saw 27% QoQ growth, reaching 658 billion.</p>
<p>Bitget exchange has experienced significant growth and achieved a position in the Top 4 centralized crypto exchanges due to increased investor activity in the crypto market. With the market capitalization surpassing $1.2 trillion, Bitget has benefited from the bullish wave and witnessed a surge in traffic to its website and mobile applications.</p>
<p>Furthermore, crypto exchange Bitget also grew its staff from 1,000 to 1,300 and it still has 300 openings across compliance, research and development, business development, operations, and customer support.</p>
<h2>Crypto Exchange Bitget&#8217;s User Protection Fund Gains $80 Million</h2>
<p>The recovery in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> price and the broader crypto market this year in 2023 has helped Bitget&#8217;s User Protection Fund to gain $80 million in book value to reach $380 million. Now, the exchange has a presence in more than 100 countries with 8 million registered users.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Poland is also emerging as a preferred destination for crypto firms to set up base. Earlier this year, crypto trading giant binance registered as a VASP in Poland. This was soon after the country introduced new terms and conditions for blockchain companies to continue their operations. Corporate consulting firm Maxcorp <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-secures-regulatory-license-in-poland-reserve-funds-up-80m-in-q1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Traditional Polish banks do not wish to work with crypto companies, thus mostly Lithuanian based financial institutions whom are crypto-friendly can be used, further we can suggest alternative banking options in Europe (Malta, Switzerland, Cyprus etc.).”</p></blockquote>
<p>Under Polish legislation, corporate activities involving cryptocurrencies are considered VAT-exempt, while profits are subject to a standard tax rate of 19%. To ensure the integrity of the exchange, recipients of Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) are obligated to conduct Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) procedures.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/">Crypto Exchange Bitget Secures License to Operate in Poland</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-poland/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reliance JioMart Cuts 1,000 Workers as Part of Broader Sustained Layoff Agenda</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 13:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jiomart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reliance jio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/">Reliance JioMart Cuts 1,000 Workers as Part of Broader Sustained Layoff Agenda</a></p>
<p>Indian retail giant Reliance JioMart has begun its layoff plan, which is expected to last several weeks and impact 10,000 employees. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/">Reliance JioMart Cuts 1,000 Workers as Part of Broader Sustained Layoff Agenda</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/">Reliance JioMart Cuts 1,000 Workers as Part of Broader Sustained Layoff Agenda</a></p>
<p>Reliance Retail&#8217;s versatile online shopping platform JioMart recently <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/22/reliance-jiomart-to-cut-11000-jobs-report-says/?guccounter=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">began a mass layoff</a>, which could affect up to 10,000 workers. This week reports state that JioMart had already laid off 1,000 employees, with another 9,000 more job cuts to follow in the coming weeks. The Indian retail giant opted for this mass downsizing to better its margins amid a contracting economy.</p>
<p>JioMart also plans to shut down more than 50% of its fulfillment centers to improve its profit outlook. These centers house the e-commerce company&#8217;s products (including preparation and storage) from where they are distributed to local stores.</p>
<p>Another reason for closing over half its fulfillment centers is to better withstand the impact of a recently-concluded Reliance Retail acquisition. Less than two weeks ago, the Indian retail company wrapped up its acquisition of the local arm of German retailer Metro AG. The deal cost Reliance $344 million, and it is widely believed that the company could recoup some of this money by shuttering several fulfillment centers. As it stands, over 150 JioMart fulfillment centers supply goods to neighboring stores. Therefore, reducing the required operational costs for these centers would lessen some financial strain as Reliance seeks profitability.</p>
<h2>Layoff Projected to Boost Company&#8217;s Earnings Potential</h2>
<p>JioMart&#8217;s primary focus is improving its bottom line, and the Indian e-commerce giant&#8217;s latest grim approach leaves no doubt. The headcount shakeups follow the Navi Mumbai-based company&#8217;s aggressive pricing strategy, which induced supply disruptions.</p>
<p>Officials with inside knowledge of the JioMart downsizing situation touched on how the company seeks to slash its 15,000-employee headcount. According to these inside sources:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The company has asked over 1,000 people on the ground, including 500 executives at its corporate office, to resign over the past few days. It also plans to have another large round of layoffs with hundreds of employees already put on a performance improvement plan (PIP).&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, one source exposited how downsizing affects workers who manage to dodge the bullet. As the official put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Rest of the sales employees have been put on variable pay structure after Reliance lowered their fixed pay salary.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>With the latest JioMart layoff, Reliance seeks a better position to withstand challenges within the Indian retail space. In addition, the company plans to maximize as many opportunities as it can as its strategy unfolds. However, despite its self-serving goals, Reliance JioMart stressed that keeping customers happy while adapting to changes is essential. The company suggested that a large content customer base remains its ultimate agenda.</p>
<h2>Reliance JioMart as an Indian Retail Industry Leader</h2>
<p>Amid the evolution of the Indian retail space, JioMart has emerged to assume a leading position and play a significant role. The company is a joint venture between Reliance Retail and JioMart and initially focused on online groceries sales. However, with time, JioMart expanded into other product categories, including home essentials, fashion, and lifestyle products.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/">Reliance JioMart Cuts 1,000 Workers as Part of Broader Sustained Layoff Agenda</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/reliance-jiomart-1000-workers-layoff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong to Permit Licensed Crypto Exchanges to Offer Services to Retail Investors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 12:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dasp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sfc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vasp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256026</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/">Hong Kong to Permit Licensed Crypto Exchanges to Offer Services to Retail Investors</a></p>
<p>Hong Kong will open crypto trading activities to retail investors starting June 1, 2023. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/">Hong Kong to Permit Licensed Crypto Exchanges to Offer Services to Retail Investors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/">Hong Kong to Permit Licensed Crypto Exchanges to Offer Services to Retail Investors</a></p>
<p>Hong Kong&#8217;s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has released the results of its consultation paper on regulating crypto assets in the country. In an <a href="https://apps.sfc.hk/edistributionWeb/gateway/EN/news-and-announcements/news/doc?refNo=23PR53" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> on May 23, 2023, the financial watchdog said it received 152 submissions from key players in the industry, professional associations, and consultancy firms, greenlighting its proposal to allow licensed crypto exchanges to serve retail investors in the nation.</p>
<p>The new development enables digital asset service providers (DASP) that demonstrate compliance with the new rulebook to apply for licenses from the appropriate authorities, while those who do not plan to follow the SFC&#8217;s proposed directives are required to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/">close</a> their business dealings in Hong Kong.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong&#8217;s New Crypto Guidelines to Become Effective June 1</h2>
<p>Although the new guidelines are set to take effect starting June 1, 2023, the upcoming regulatory framework will encompass essential aspects, including asset custody safety requirements, avoidance of conflict of interest, customer asset segregation, and cyber security standards.</p>
<p>While the regulator is yet to approve any crypto trading platform to provide its business offerings to retail investors, crypto exchanges such as Huobi Global, OKX, and Gate.io have applied to obtain virtual assets service provider (VASP) licenses from the country.</p>
<p>If approved, the companies can tap Hong Kong&#8217;s crypto market to increase their user base and strengthen their footprints in the industry.</p>
<p>The decision by the SFC to allow authorized exchanges to operate in the country marks a significant step towards enhancing market integrity and building trust within the space. Through this move, Hong Kong has taken a step further towards <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-hub-hong-kong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">achieving</a> its goal of developing a virtual asset hub and becoming a center for technological innovations.</p>
<h2>Protect Consumer Interest</h2>
<p>Aside from allowing crypto trading platforms to operate in the country, the financial regulator is committed to providing <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-sfc-defi-projects-regulatory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">stringent measures</a> to safeguard investors while following the inputs from the results of the consultation paper released in February.</p>
<p>Some of the measures to be implemented in the rulebook include good governance practices, ensuring suitability during the onboarding process, conducting enhanced token due diligence, setting admission criteria, and promoting disclosures.</p>
<p>According to the SFC&#8217;s chief executive officer, Ms. Julia Leung, the upcoming guidelines for operators of digital asset trading platforms align with the same business and rule regulatory measures that aim to provide robust investor protection and manage risks.</p>
<p>&#8220;Providing clear regulatory expectations is key to fostering responsible development. Hong Kong&#8217;s comprehensive virtual asset regulatory framework follows the principles of &#8216;same business, same risks, same rules&#8217; and aims to provide robust investor protection and manage key risks,&#8221; Leung said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/">Hong Kong to Permit Licensed Crypto Exchanges to Offer Services to Retail Investors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-licensed-crypto-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IOSCO Introduces Global Policy Recommendation to Guide Crypto and Digital Assets Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 12:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iosco]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/">IOSCO Introduces Global Policy Recommendation to Guide Crypto and Digital Assets Industry</a></p>
<p>Several jurisdictions have made outstanding efforts to release standard crypto regulations to safeguard citizens and their assets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/">IOSCO Introduces Global Policy Recommendation to Guide Crypto and Digital Assets Industry</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/">IOSCO Introduces Global Policy Recommendation to Guide Crypto and Digital Assets Industry</a></p>
<p>World securities and future market regulator, the International Organization of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) has <a href="https://www.iosco.org/library/pubdocs/pdf/IOSCOPD734.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> a global approach to regulating the crypto market and digital assets. According to the statement made to the press, the proposed recommendation is largely directed toward addressing concerns related to investor protection and market integrity in the digital currency ecosystem.</p>
<h2>IOSCO Crypto Regulation Modalities</h2>
<p>Also, a consultation period for the policy recommendation has been opened for public comments till July 31st. The regulation contains 18 policy recommendations which cut across 6 key areas including market abuse, conflict of interest, client asset protection, disclosures, and risks associated with crypto.</p>
<p>IOSCO plans to achieve this by dictating how crypto clients should be protected and how crypto trading activities should be conducted to “meet the standards that apply in public markets.” Moreso, Jean-Paul Servais, the Chairman of the international regulator, believes that IOSCO is best suited to get the job done seeing that it has already begun some regulation tasks around the world.</p>
<p>IOSCO is recognized for organizing security regulators in over 130 countries including the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), and the United Kingdom Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) which are busy regulating “more than 95pc of the world’s securities markets.”</p>
<p>In 2022, the International agency came up with a Fintech Task Force (FTF) responsible for designing regulatory agendas for both the crypto industry and fintech organizations. The FTF was spearheaded by the Singapore regulator, the MAS with 27 board members. The FCA, which is one of the groups attached to the FTF, was commissioned to release recommendations for the crypto asset industry this year.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the SEC was entrusted with working on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/topics/defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Decentralized Finance</a> (DeFi) ecosystem. Another agency known as the Financial Stability Board intends to publish recommendations for stablecoins later this year. The focus on protecting investors in the crypto space heightened last year following the bear market and the sudden collapse of the Bahamian-headquartered FTX exchange.</p>
<h2>Global Regulators Intensify Efforts towards Crypto Regulation</h2>
<p>Several jurisdictions have made outstanding efforts to release standard crypto regulations to safeguard citizens and their assets. While representing Ajay Seth, the secretary of the Department of Economic Affairs, and Nirmala Sitharaman, the top official in the Indian Finance Ministry, V. Anantha Nageswaran <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulation-priority-g20-india-presidency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mentioned</a> that crypto regulation would be a priority for G20 under India&#8217;s presidency.</p>
<p>Jair Bolsonaro, the Brazilian President has also signed a crypto regulation bill into law which entails that digital asset service providers that intend to do business in the region would first obtain a license from the appropriate agencies. At the same time, anyone who defaults would be penalized and likely face jail time.</p>
<p>Also, Taiwan has increased its hold on the crypto market in its jurisdictions by putting the Financial Supervisory Commission (FSC) in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/financial-supervisory-commission-crypto-taiwan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">charge as</a> the primary regulatory body for crypto.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/">IOSCO Introduces Global Policy Recommendation to Guide Crypto and Digital Assets Industry</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/iosco-global-policy-guide-crypto-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Namada Wants to Form Closer Knit Partnership with Osmosis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 11:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Namada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[osmo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Osmosis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255973</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/">Namada Wants to Form Closer Knit Partnership with Osmosis</a></p>
<p>Namada said it is its Switzerland-based non-profit arm, the Namada Foundation that will be in charge of issuing out the NAM tokens that will be airdropped to OSMO holders.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/">Namada Wants to Form Closer Knit Partnership with Osmosis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/">Namada Wants to Form Closer Knit Partnership with Osmosis</a></p>
<p>Namada Blockchain, a privacy-centric protocol built on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/introduction-cosmos-network-atom-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cosmos Network</a>, is looking at solidifying its presence in the industry with a partnership pitch to Osmosis (OSMO). As <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/22/seeking-grants-deal-with-osmosis-privacy-blockchain-namada-proposes-airdrop/?outputType=amp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Coindesk, Namada co-founder Christopher Goes is exploring a jointly funded grants program to bankroll software “public goods”.</p>
<p>The proposal will also involve the airdropping of NAM tokens to current Osmosis holders, a move that will form an almost unbreakable bond between the two protocols. Namada is looking at pushing these partnerships before it will officially launch on the mainnet.</p>
<p>The proposal is best tagged as a mutually beneficial one for both Namada and Osmosis, and while it will help give Namada a ready-made community, OSMO holders will be gaining more financially in the long term when the airdrop is completed.</p>
<p>As Goes described, the proposed grants program will be funding a lot of research initiatives with a special focus on privacy-centric solutions and development projects. These potential projects will be beneficial to both the Namada and Osmosis protocols respectively. As its first show of legitimacy, the grants program, according to Goes, will be funded by Namada, however, the expectation is that Osmosis will also support in its own best ways.</p>
<p>The collaborations between the duo will also see the use of Namada’s Shielded Actions technology to protect tokens on Namada when they are not in active use on Osmosis.</p>
<p>“It would be pretty boring if you only had assets and couldn&#8217;t do anything with them,” explained Goes. “So we expect that people want to go to Osmosis and decentralized exchanges on other chains to trade their assets,&#8221; he added.</p>
<p>As part of the considerations for the proposed partnership, Namada said it is its Switzerland-based non-profit arm, the Namada Foundation that will be in charge of issuing out the NAM tokens that will be airdropped to OSMO holders.</p>
<h2>Namada and Osmosis Linkup: Possible Timeline</h2>
<p>The Namada push to partner with Osmosis is not one that will come without significant hiccups. One of these hiccups is the pre-approval from the Osmosis community as the request for partnership will still be placed under a robust governance vote.</p>
<p>That Osmosis Labs controls the affairs of the blockchain does not mean the leaders make all crucial decisions. Community input is very crucial, and despite the fact that the community has a lot to benefit from, there is no guarantee as to what the voting outcome will be.</p>
<p>Based on the apparent complications, there is no idea as to what the timeline for the collaboration will be. Going by its history, however, the chances of success with the Osmosis community are high, considering Namada inked a similar partnership with privacy layer-1 protocol <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-zcash-zec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zcash</a> back in April this year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/judge-shareholder-lawsuit-musk-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/">Namada Wants to Form Closer Knit Partnership with Osmosis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/namada-partnership-osmosis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4373 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1196546 metric#prefetches=183 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=13 metric#store-hits=190 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=102.65 metric#ms-cache=6.00 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1765 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.9 -->