<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 20:31:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Genesis could file for bankruptcy this week: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 20:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Genesis Global Capital, a crypto lending platform owned by Digital Currency Group (DCG), is said to be considering filing for bankruptcy. According to a Bloomberg report, Genesis is likely to file for bankruptcy this week. Genesis paused customer withdrawals in November, with over $900 million owed to Gemini Earn customers alone. Troubled crypto lender Genesis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/">Genesis could file for bankruptcy this week: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Genesis Global Capital, a crypto lending platform owned by Digital Currency Group (DCG), is said to be considering filing for bankruptcy.</strong></em></li>
<li><em><strong>According to a Bloomberg report, Genesis is likely to file for bankruptcy this week.</strong></em></li>
<li><strong><em>Genesis paused customer withdrawals in November, with over $900 million owed to Gemini Earn customers alone.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Troubled crypto lender Genesis Global Capital is reportedly looking to file for bankruptcy, according to the latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">cryptocurrency news</a> around the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Genesis is a subsidiary Digital Currency Group, DCG, a crypto company that has over the past few weeks been one of the main topics across Crypto Twitter for its role in the troubles that now beguile its crypto lending unit. DCG also owns Grayscale and crypto publication CoinDesk.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Genesis could file for bankruptcy as early as this week</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Indeed, as we recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/geminis-winklevoss-calls-out-dcg-over-bad-faith-stall-tactics/">reported</a>, crypto exchange Gemini has accused DCG for the difficulty that it has faced since Genesis paused redemptions and loan originations in November last year. And the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/">charged</a> both Gemini and Genesis for violating the securities laws through the offerings linked to the Gemini Earn product.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now, amid the liquidity crunch that&rsquo;s bitten the company, the report is that Genesis could file for bankruptcy protection in the next few days. Sources cited in a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-18/crypto-firm-genesis-said-to-prepare-bankruptcy-filing-as-soon-as-this-week" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> on Wednesday say the bankruptcy filing could happen before the end of the week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Companies use Chapter 11 bankruptcy procedures as a platform that allows the embattled business time in which they can work towards salvaging assets and recouping value for creditors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/">Genesis could file for bankruptcy this week: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deal Box launches $125 milllion venture fund to invest in Web3</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/deal-box-launches-125-milllion-venture-fund-to-invest-in-web3/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/deal-box-launches-125-milllion-venture-fund-to-invest-in-web3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 18:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital assets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/deal-box-launches-125-milllion-venture-fund-to-invest-in-web3/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Deal Box&#8217;s venture arm will invest in blockchain and Web3 startups. Dubbed Deal Box Ventures, the investment unit will target projects in fintech, emerging growth, real estate, funtech and social impact. Thomas Carter, the founder and Chairman of Deal Box, says the fund will also provide the tools and funding ecosystem startups need to succeed. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/deal-box-launches-125-milllion-venture-fund-to-invest-in-web3/">Deal Box launches $125 milllion venture fund to invest in Web3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Deal Box&rsquo;s venture arm will invest in blockchain and Web3 startups.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Dubbed Deal Box Ventures, the investment unit will target projects in fintech, emerging growth, real estate, funtech and social impact.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Thomas Carter, the founder and Chairman of Deal Box, says the fund will also provide the tools and funding ecosystem startups need to succeed.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Deal Box, a US-based capital markets advisory platform, has launched a new venture fund that will invest $125 million in blockchain and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/web-3-0/">Web3</a> technology startups.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/deal-box-launches-venture-arm-to-invest-125m-in-foundational-web-3-technologies-301724423.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> from the token offering firm noted that Deal Box Ventures will look at projects across five key fund areas &ndash; fintech, emerging growth, funtech, real estate and social impact.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Deal Box Ventures is an important milestone in our journey to invest in the most promising and disruptive blockchain startups, providing them with the tools and funding ecosystem they need to be successful by simplifying and reimagining traditional financing models</em>,&rdquo; said Thomas Carter, the founder and Chairman of Deal Box.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Deal Box already invests in three key blockchain projects</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the press release, Deal Box Ventures will target strategic investments aimed at unlocking the full potential of blockchain technology. The venture fund will thus focus on supporting projects leveraging the new technology to reshape and improve everyday lives.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These goals tie in with part of Deal Box&rsquo;s Web3 investments in three key projects whose technology looks to solve issues around device identity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Total Network Services is a platform offering UCID (Universal Communication Identifier), the first blockchain-enabled supply chain security service in the world. Deal Box has also invested in Rypplzz, a project that taps into the benefits of blockchain technology to connect digital and physical objects. Meanwhile, Forward-Edge AI aims to use Artificial Intelligence (AI) to improve human life.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/deal-box-launches-125-milllion-venture-fund-to-invest-in-web3/">Deal Box launches $125 milllion venture fund to invest in Web3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/deal-box-launches-125-milllion-venture-fund-to-invest-in-web3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU postpones final vote on its MiCA regulation</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The European Parliament passed the comprehensive Markets in Crypto-Assets, MiCA legislation in October 2022. The final vote on the bill was originally set for February 2023, but has now been pushed to April. The crypto sector is increasingly in the regulatory spotlight following high profile collapses of crypto companies like FTX. The European Union wants [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/">EU postpones final vote on its MiCA regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The European Parliament passed the comprehensive Markets in Crypto-Assets, MiCA legislation in October 2022.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The final vote on the bill was originally set for February 2023, but has now been pushed to April.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The crypto sector is increasingly in the regulatory spotlight following high profile collapses of crypto companies like FTX.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The European Union wants to see proper crypto regulation across its member states, even as a global push for a harmonized approach gathers pace.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Uniquely, the EU is in the process of finalizing its Markets in Crypto Assets regulation (MiCA), the comprehensive cryptocurrency regulations framework set to usher in a new dawn for crypto in the region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But the final vote on the regulations will not come at least until April this year, the latest <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/202723/eus-final-vote-mica-regulation-postponed-april" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> on the topic suggest.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">EU postpones MiCA vote, again</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This latest delay &ndash; the second for the highly anticipated MiCA rules following the vote&rsquo;s push from November last year to February 2023 &ndash; is down to a snag in the translation of the regulations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, MiCA is a 400-page rule book that needs to be translated into 24 official languages across the EU bloc. The requirement that the document be available in all the official languages before going to a crucial final vote has necessitated the postponement to April 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MiCA bill was first introduced in the European Parliament in September 2020, with lawmakers passing the bill in October 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto remains in the spotlight as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/category/policy-and-regulation/">policymakers and regulators</a> look to harmonize the oversight of the industry following a spate of major bankruptcies in the last year. Among these is the collapse of FTX and multiple other crypto companies tied to disgraced crypto exec Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/">EU postpones final vote on its MiCA regulation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/eu-postpones-final-vote-on-its-mica-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin  now at its pre-FTX collapse level</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-now-at-its-pre-ftx-collapse-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-solana-now-at-their-pre-ftx-collapse-levels/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, bitcoin (BTC) was trading at $21,507.97. Bitcoin price has surpassed where it stood on November 5 just prior to the FTX collapse. It now stands at its highest price since mid-September last year. 2022 was definitely not a very good year for crypto and especially for bitcoin (BTC) which was trading below [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-now-at-its-pre-ftx-collapse-level/">Bitcoin  now at its pre-FTX collapse level</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, bitcoin (BTC) was trading at $21,507.97.</li>
<li>Bitcoin price has surpassed where it stood on November 5 just prior to the FTX collapse.</li>
<li>It now stands at its highest price since mid-September last year.</li>
</ul>
<p>2022 was definitely not a very good year for crypto and especially for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">bitcoin (BTC)</a> which was trading below $20K for quite a while before the year&rsquo;s end. Bitcoin had plunged all the way down to about $15,000 in wake of the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-ftx-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/">FTX collapse</a> before attempting a comeback that saw it stuck close to $16,500 for several weeks before embarking on this current rally since the beginning of 2023.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has now corrected the price dip that was caused by the latest crypto misfortune, the FTX collapse that took place at the beginning of November. Early this morning, the price of bitcoin surged to a daily high of $21,564.50 before slightly pulling back to $21,507.97 at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>What is behind today&rsquo;s BTC price surge?</h2>
<p>While the general cryptocurrency market is on a bullish trajectory, today&rsquo;s sudden surge in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">bitcoin price</a> is largely attributed to this morning&rsquo;s larger-than-expected decrease in the Producer Price Index (PPI) for the just concluded month of December. The retail sales in December also dropped way below their forecast.</p>
<p>December&rsquo;s PPI dropped by about 0.5% bringing the year-to-year rate down from 7.3% to 6.2%. The year-over-year rate dropped by about 5.5% against a forecast of a drop of 5.7%.</p>
<p>On the other hand, December retail sales dropped by 1.1% against a forecast drop of 0.8%. Combined with the decline in November, this marks the first time retail sales have dropped back-to-back by more than 1% post the pandemic.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-now-at-its-pre-ftx-collapse-level/">Bitcoin  now at its pre-FTX collapse level</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An introduction to KYC: the most significant feature in the crypto world</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/an-introduction-to-kyc-the-most-significant-feature-in-the-crypto-world/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/an-introduction-to-kyc-the-most-significant-feature-in-the-crypto-world/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KYC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/an-introduction-to-kyc-the-most-significant-feature-in-the-crypto-world/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The initial level of anti-money laundering (AML) reasonable care is called &#8220;know your customer,&#8221; or KYC for short. The Know Your Client (KYC) processes are initiated as soon as a new customer is accepted by a financial institution (FI). Financial institutions may determine a client&#8217;s potential for financial crime using these procedures. When doing business, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/an-introduction-to-kyc-the-most-significant-feature-in-the-crypto-world/">An introduction to KYC: the most significant feature in the crypto world</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The initial level of anti-money laundering (AML) reasonable care is called &ldquo;know your customer,&rdquo; or KYC for short. The Know Your Client (KYC) processes are initiated as soon as a new customer is accepted by a financial institution (FI). Financial institutions may determine a client&rsquo;s potential for financial crime using these procedures. When doing business, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> are required to have a &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; (KYC) procedure to:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Check the accuracy of the data they have about their clients and customers.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Get a better grasp on the nature of their prospective clients&rsquo; actions and make sure they&rsquo;re above board.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Establish the likelihood that their clients pose a money laundering danger.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">How do VASPs demonstrate KYC compliance?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Many VASPs use a multi-step &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; procedure to guard against scams. Here are the measures to take:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Step 1: Customers&rsquo; identifying information (such as their complete names, birthdates, and addresses) must be collected.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Step 2:&nbsp;Check the information you gave against your government-issued ID (visa, state driver&rsquo;s license) and proof of address (electricity bill).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Step 3:&nbsp;Check the user&rsquo;s data against government records that track politically exposed persons (PEPs) and blacklisted people.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">By adhering to these protocols, banks can determine whether their customers are at risk for money laundering as well as other misappropriation of funds related to their usage of cryptocurrency. When a client&rsquo;s identity and other details are verified, they are given access to a limited set of features on a bitcoin trading platform.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does one keep track of crypto trades?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A cryptocurrency transfer monitoring network provides cryptocurrency marketplaces and financial institutions with assistance in spotting anomalous or questionable behavior that they are required to disclose to government regulators. Additionally, this technology assists law enforcement in their pursuit of criminals. The security of a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">cryptocurrency wallet </a>may be tracked by keeping an eye on its transaction activity. Toolkits developed by firms like <a href="https://the-bitsoft360app.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitsoft360</a>, Crystal Blockchain, Coinfirm, etc. are used by cryptocurrency-related exchanges.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Know Your Customer (KYC) compliance essential for cryptocurrency wallets? </h2>
<p dir="ltr">Since only custodial wallets have access to their users&rsquo; encryption keys, they are the only ones required to follow KYC procedures. The VASP document explains that the Financial Action Task Force (FATF) considers &ldquo;every legitimate or natural entity who swaps, retains, safe-keeps, distributes, transforms, or somehow distributes VAs on account of some other physical or legal entity&rdquo; to be a VASP.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since VASPs are now considered &ldquo;monetary organizations,&rdquo; they too must implement rigorous annual compliance requirements (FYC). &nbsp; To comply with regulations, VASP-related custodial wallet providers must have a &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; (KYC) policy.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">In what ways may cryptocurrency KYC help you?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Here are some of the reasons why cryptocurrency exchanges get a major advantage from operating in conformity with regulatory requirements, even though doing so necessitates certain alterations to their operational procedures and presents some challenges:</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">An increase in consumers&rsquo; faith in business </h3>
<p dir="ltr">Trust in businesses and their products can only increase when their users&rsquo; identities are independently verified. Customers are more inclined to stick with a trading platform if they believe the firm is taking reasonable precautions to keep their funds secure.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Reduced instances of fraud and money laundering&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Nearly one billion dollars in cryptocurrency was reported stolen from over 46,000 customers between January and March 2022. As Fletcher predicted, identity verification procedures that are thorough and accurate could cut down on fraud and improve the market&rsquo;s reputation.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Lessening potential legal trouble</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Strong &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; (KYC) procedures can help organizations stay ahead of changing regulations. By demanding government-issued credentials and tracking payment situations and holdings, KYC approaches allow VASPs to detect and limit false identity cases, avoid financial fraud, and evaluate client risk.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By taking these measures, companies may lessen their exposure to legal and governmental concerns, freeing up resources that can be used toward other goals, such as improving exchange rates, speeding up processes, and ensuring compliance.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Improved market conditions&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Speculative, anonymous transactions are a major driver of the bitcoin market&rsquo;s instability. The industry as a whole benefits from the greater stability and value development enabled by KYC procedures with enhanced identity verification.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is Know Your Customer (KYC) mandatory to purchase cryptocurrency?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">You may buy VAs without completing a &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; check. Examples of non-KYC services are cryptocurrency ATMs and DEXs. Unlike DEXs, which are decentralized, blockchain-based P2P exchanges that allow for large-scale crypto asset trading, crypto ATMs allow customers to acquire bitcoin using cash or debit cards. Instead of serving as financial intermediaries, DEXs rely on algorithmic automation to carry out these functions.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What dangers exist while purchasing cryptocurrency without KYC? </h2>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s quite risky from a regulatory perspective to purchase virtual currencies without first undergoing KYC. Financial authorities, including the Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC), have fined cryptocurrency exchanges for alleged sanctions violations. Black market accounts, which pose a risk to assets, may be flagged as false by a platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lack of &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; in exchanges</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Popular DEXs like Uniswap and Bisq does not require KYC procedures from their users. These marketplaces connect sellers and purchasers of digital money by matching orders according to price and quantity. In the world of cryptocurrencies, a &ldquo;liquidity pool&rdquo; is a collection of commodities that can be quickly and easily converted into cash to settle incoming buy and sell orders. Assets are provided not by banks or other institutions but rather by end users.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; (KYC) connect to the &lsquo;Crypto Travel Rule?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">When discussing cyber safety, &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; and the &ldquo;Crypto Travel Rule&rdquo; are both essential concepts to grasp. While the Travel Rule mandates that FIs and VASPs obtain and communicate opponent information, KYC gathers and transmits data about the persons and institutions that utilize the FI or VASP.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The distinction between &ldquo;Know Your Customer&rdquo; and the &ldquo;Travel Rule&rdquo;&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Before enabling a consumer to use their system, a VASP must do know-your-customer (KYC) checks to ensure that they comply with international rules. The Travel Rule goes even further by requiring that personally identifiable information of consumers be shared and stored when purchases between two VASPs that have already done KYC on their clients exceed a certain level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How come Anti-Money Laundering and Know-Your-Customer measures are so vital to the cryptocurrency sector?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Customers and VASPs alike benefit from strict observance of AML and KYC rules. Virtual currencies, unlike fiat cash, lack a robust regulatory structure.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Criminals are increasingly capitalizing on the ability to send money while concealing its origin and destination. The risks of money laundering, terrorism funding, and other forms of illegal financing may be reduced by standardizing regulatory standards and conducting Know Your Customer and Anti-Money Laundering inspections.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Final thoughts&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency transactions are far more secure when KYC is used. To prevent fraudulent fraud and ensure the safety of financial transactions, Know Your Customer (KYC) measures are essential. Although this post does not provide insights on KYC implementation, it has given you enough details to make a wise plan.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/an-introduction-to-kyc-the-most-significant-feature-in-the-crypto-world/">An introduction to KYC: the most significant feature in the crypto world</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/an-introduction-to-kyc-the-most-significant-feature-in-the-crypto-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Problem of Identity Theft And Blockchain Era &#8211; Ways to Address It</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain, what it is and how it works. The problem of identity theft for blockchain-based businesses. How blockchain helps businesses tackle the issue of identity theft. Blockchain&#8216;s rising popularity may be attributed to its promise of safe monetary operations and the elimination of identity theft.&#160; There will be astronomical yearly expenditure on the blockchain, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/">The Problem of Identity Theft And Blockchain Era &#8211; Ways to Address It</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The blockchain, what it is and how it works.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The problem of identity theft for blockchain-based businesses.</strong></em></li>
<li><strong><em>How blockchain helps businesses tackle the issue of identity theft.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/blockchain/">Blockchain</a>&lsquo;s rising popularity may be attributed to its promise of safe monetary operations and the elimination of identity theft.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There will be astronomical yearly expenditure on the blockchain, estimated at $20 billion, with the banking industry alone contributing about $522 billion. Then why is everyone talking about it? Blockchain is favored by both users and businesses because of its ability to securely store user data.</p>
<p>Visualize the magnitude of identity theft on a worldwide scale. Unfortunately, victims of identity theft often don&rsquo;t find out until they experience severe consequences. If online stores don&rsquo;t take identity theft seriously, they risk losing customers and damaging their image. Blockchain gives individuals more control over their data and a more secure way to avoid identity theft.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The blockchain: What is it?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is a network of technologies designed to securely gather user data and distribute it over the internet in chunks. The blocks are a network of data centers that conduct safe public transactions using encryption. Each transaction in a chain must be recorded in a distributed ledger.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A problem for blockchain-based businesses: Identity theft</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Customers aren&rsquo;t the only ones who suffer from identity theft; internet companies are at risk as well. To achieve their goals, cybercriminals use a wide variety of tactics, such as hacking, account takeovers, and credit card theft. Examples of a few of the most typical forms of identity theft are shown below.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">The scam of fake IDs</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Synthetic identity theft occurs when several victims&rsquo; personal information is used to create a single fraudulent persona. To complete the operation, it is common practice to combine fake information with real user records that have been stolen. Criminals create new identities to engage in other fraudulent schemes. For instance, cybercriminals may create phony profiles in order to seem affiliated with legitimate companies and launder money using these accounts.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Online shopping fraud</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Con artists prey on those who make purchases on digital platforms, making online purchasing dangerous. People of dubious provenance populate these online marketplaces, hoping to mislead customers into giving over their credit card data. With the use of enticing offers and phishing emails, imposter online shops can trick unsuspecting customers into giving over their personal information.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Identity theft in the healthcare industry</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Insurance companies and hospitals must be on the lookout for cunning scammers who steal people&rsquo;s medical identities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The theft of a patient&rsquo;s medical identification information might provide the perpetrator with access to sensitive medical information that can be sold for profit. Since there aren&rsquo;t any foolproof identity verification systems in place when patients register or make insurance payments, this kind of scam often goes undetected.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Theft of social security numbers</h3>
<p dir="ltr">A further method of committing identity theft is through using stolen Social Security numbers (SSNs).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The nine-digit SSN is a form of identification that is typically given to people at birth. Online scams like medical and kid identity theft would be impossible without them. Cybercriminals often use social security numbers to acquire the suspect&rsquo;s accounting transactions and file fraudulent tax returns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Avoiding identity theft with blockchain</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are a few ways in which blockchain technology improves security for user data and prevents fraudulent identities from being accepted into the system. The following are examples of some of these:</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Providing a safe and sound method of financial transactions</h3>
<p dir="ltr">When it comes to fighting identity theft, blockchain is generally seen as a potential cybersecurity solution. Due to the high degree of security it offers, it may aid in preventing private information from falling into the wrong hands. Blockchain&rsquo;s distributed ledger is an electronic database that stores transactional data. Data saved on the blockchain is secured by employing encryption techniques to ensure the privacy of all users&rsquo; data.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We should have safeguards in place to prevent any kind of theft or breach into the system from happening and they are activated the moment they are spotted. As a result, customers of online services may deal with confidence knowing that their personal information is being protected.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Using ID verification tools like <a href="https://btcloopholepro.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin loophole</a> or Chainanalysis, distributed ledger technology (DLP) in blockchain may validate customers&rsquo; identities across different channels.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">The snackable wall against fraud</h3>
<p dir="ltr">An attacker may easily compromise a centralized network and remain undetected for long periods. Identity verification systems are very vulnerable to a single point of failure, which may result in the loss of millions of dollars by giving criminals access to sensitive information such as credit card numbers, Social Security numbers, and other personal details.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With blockchain, the situation is quite different since identity thieves have to physically move from one location to another, which takes a lot of time and energy.</p>
<p>Blockchain employs Public Key Cryptography (PKI) to build a decentralized, digital network comprised of individual blocks of data. PKIs are crucial because they prevent widespread data breaches and safeguard individuals&rsquo; personal information.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Title to individual data</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Synthetic identities are used by cybercriminals to impersonate legitimate businesses and get access to sensitive information, such as credit card and bank account details. Banks lose a significant amount of money due to identity theft every year, and the number of cases is rising.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bad credit, massive credit card debt and flags from financial authorities are all possible outcomes.</p>
<p>To circumvent this issue, blockchain technology provides public keys that may be used to initiate a safe transaction between two parties. Users gain control over their data when, for example, personal details such as their birthdays are recorded in a distributed ledger. This provides an extra safeguard for all of your digital chats.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Last but not least</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Protection against identity theft is crucial for businesses of all stripes. Know your customer (KYC) and anti-money laundering (AML) rules can be easily implemented via client identification verification, which also helps reduce the costs of cybercrime.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Companies in the blockchain industry may use ID verification services to quickly and easily add new users. Identity verification service providers in the blockchain industry may use this to speed up the onboarding process for new customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain companies may meet global KYC and AML criteria and secure their customers&rsquo; loyalty by providing IDV solutions powered by AI.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/">The Problem of Identity Theft And Blockchain Era &#8211; Ways to Address It</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-problem-of-identity-theft-and-blockchain-era-ways-to-address-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Primex Finance Introduces Beta 0.3.0 App With Deployments to Polygon Mumbai and zkEVM Testnets</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/primex-finance-introduces-beta-0-3-0-app-with-deployments-to-polygon-mumbai-and-zkevm-testnets/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/primex-finance-introduces-beta-0-3-0-app-with-deployments-to-polygon-mumbai-and-zkevm-testnets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=99733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kyiv, Ukraine, 18th January, 2023, Chainwire Cross-chain prime brokerage protocol Primex Finance rolls out a major update to its application. Launching in two stages, Beta 0.3.0 introduces a variety of new features, as well as improvements and fixes of existing functionalities. Starting on January 12th, 2023, Phase 1 was exclusively available for Primex Early Users, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/primex-finance-introduces-beta-0-3-0-app-with-deployments-to-polygon-mumbai-and-zkevm-testnets/">Primex Finance Introduces Beta 0.3.0 App With Deployments to Polygon Mumbai and zkEVM Testnets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Kyiv, Ukraine, 18th January, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Cross-chain prime brokerage protocol<a href="https://primex.finance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> <u>Primex Finance</u></a> rolls out a major update to its application. Launching in two stages, Beta 0.3.0 introduces a variety of new features, as well as improvements and fixes of existing functionalities.</p>
<p>Starting on January 12th, 2023, Phase 1 was exclusively available for Primex Early Users, who could be the first to have a hands-on experience with Beta 0.3.0. From now on, Early Users will get privileged access to all major protocol updates in the future (beginning from Beta 0.3.0). In addition to the chance to test new releases before other community members,<a href="https://primex.finance/earlyuser" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> <u>participants of the program</u></a> also enjoy further benefits, such as direct communication with the Primex team and fellow Early Users via Discord, as well as the ability to participate in private challenges and earn exclusive prizes.</p>
<p>On January 18th, 2023, the Primex team will open access for the public to Beta 0.3.0, allowing anyone to<a href="https://app.primex.finance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> <u>launch the application</u></a> and test the new release without restrictions.</p>
<p>Beta 0.3.0 introduces four new core features. As the first and the most important, Primex now deploys to two new blockchains: the Polygon Mumbai and Polygon zkEVM testnets. Consequently, users can now test Primex by trading and lending digital assets on DEXs across four different blockchains (Ethereum Goerli, zkSync 2.0 testnet, Polygon Mumbai, and Polygon zkEVM testnet). With the new multi-chain functionality, traders and lenders can now swap between different networks via a single interface.</p>
<p><i>&ldquo;When we asked our community which chains we should deploy Primex on, Polygon was by far the top choice among voters. While we were happy about the results, they didn&rsquo;t come as a surprise for our team. Mumbai is the testnet of Polygon PoS, the Layer 2 blockchain with the highest DeFi TVL that can achieve up to 7,000 TPS. On the other hand, zkEVM is a newer solution that uses ZK-rollups via the ultra-fast Polygon Zero technology to achieve a 90% fee reduction for users on Ethereum&rsquo;s L2. For these reasons, it makes great sense to deploy Primex on the testnets of these two blockchains,&rdquo;</i> said Vlad Kostanda, Primex Finance&rsquo;s Co-Founder.</p>
<p>Besides the above core features, the Primex team introduced additional changes to the protocol as part of the Beta 0.3.0 update, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Support for the <a href="https://www.okx.com/web3" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>OKX Wallet</u></a>, which users can now utilize to connect their wallets to Primex alongside MetaMask and WalletConnect</li>
<li>The integration of the QuickSwap v2 DEX on Polygon Mumbai</li>
<li>Enhanced trading experience via a new bot that periodically synchronizes asset prices on the testnet with the mainnet</li>
<li>Improved UX for downloading trading history</li>
<li>The ability to see the date and time when an order or position was created on the trading page</li>
<li>Bug fixes related to the translation of the Primex application&rsquo;s certain components and translation delays after a user switches between languages</li>
<li>Additional optimizations and bug fixes</li>
</ul>
<h2><b>About Primex Finance</b></h2>
<p>Founded in 2021, Primex Finance is the first-ever cross-chain prime brokerage protocol that seeks to solve the DeFi market&rsquo;s liquidity fragmentation issue by enabling spot margin trading backed by lenders across numerous DEXs and blockchains with a totally decentralized trade execution mechanism. In September 2022, the team advanced to the next stage of its roadmap by launching the platform&rsquo;s Beta release. Recently, the project rolled out Beta 0.3.0, a major update to the protocol introducing a wide range of important features, functionalities, and fixes. For more information, visit Primex&rsquo;s<a href="https://primex.finance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> <u>website</u></a> and<a href="https://blog.primex.finance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> <u>blog</u></a>.</p>
<h2>Contact</h2>
<p>CMO, Anton Demenko, PrimexLabs O&Uuml;, anton@primex.finance</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/primex-finance-introduces-beta-0-3-0-app-with-deployments-to-polygon-mumbai-and-zkevm-testnets/">Primex Finance Introduces Beta 0.3.0 App With Deployments to Polygon Mumbai and zkEVM Testnets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/primex-finance-introduces-beta-0-3-0-app-with-deployments-to-polygon-mumbai-and-zkevm-testnets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC&#8217;s crypto-related penalties hit $2.6 billion in 2022</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-crypto-related-penalties-hit-2-6-billion-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-crypto-related-penalties-hit-2-6-billion-in-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-crypto-related-penalties-hit-2-6-billion-in-2022/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC&#8217;s first crypto-related enforcement action was in July 2013. The agency has brought 127 such actions since, with 30 of these in 2022 representing a 50% increase from 2021. The monetary penalties across the settlements with the regulator reached $2.61 billion by the end of last year. According to a recent report by Cornerstone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-crypto-related-penalties-hit-2-6-billion-in-2022/">SEC&#8217;s crypto-related penalties hit $2.6 billion in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The SEC&rsquo;s first crypto-related enforcement action was in July 2013.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The agency has brought 127 such actions since, with 30 of these in 2022 representing a 50% increase from 2021.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The monetary penalties across the settlements with the regulator reached $2.61 billion by the end of last year.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">According to a recent <a href="https://www.cornerstone.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SEC-Cryptocurrency-Enforcement-2022-Update.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> by Cornerstone Research, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has overseen 127 crypto-related enforcement actions since 2013. 82 of the actions so far have been litigations and 45 of them administrative proceedings.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC crypto-related fines hit $2.6 billion by 2022</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has recently come under heavy criticism after cryptocurrency exchange FTX collapsed. For the most part, many have questioned the regulatory watchdog&rsquo;s tendency to swing into action after events that see the ordinary public suffer huge losses in the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And no doubt, the SEC swiftly charged former FTX CEO and founder Sam Bankman-Fried following his arrest. Also charged were Alameda&rsquo;s Caroline Ellison and FTX&rsquo;s Gary Wang. Just a few days ago, as we <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-has-filed-charges-against-gemini-and-genesis/">highlighted</a>, the agency filed charges against crypto platforms Gemini and Genesis.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a pattern that falls in line with what has been labelled as &ldquo;regulation by enforcement.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Indeed, even as the crypto market navigates the crypto winter, regulatory clarity remains a long way off. However, enforcement actions have increased rapidly since the SEC&rsquo;s first such move in July 2013.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2022, the securities market watchdog filed 30 enforcement actions touching on 79 market participants, including the February charge against crypto lender BlockFi.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the Cornerstone Research report, the enforcement actions in 2022 were against 56 individuals representing 71% of the allegations and 23 were against firms (29% of the actions). The total enforcement actions over the past year was double the actions filed in 2021, the report noted.</p>
<p>In terms of monetary penalties, settlements with the agency hit $242 million in 2022 &ndash; with the total fines since 2013 amounting to $2.61 billion as of 31 December 2022. As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kim-kardashian-fined-1-3-million-for-scamming-her-instagram-followers-over-crypto-promotion/">reported</a>&nbsp;in October, the SEC fines include the $1.3 million levelled against celebrity Kim Kardashian for her promotion of the crypto project EthereumMax.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-crypto-related-penalties-hit-2-6-billion-in-2022/">SEC&#8217;s crypto-related penalties hit $2.6 billion in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/secs-crypto-related-penalties-hit-2-6-billion-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot’s XCM v3 finally merged after 15-month development</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadots-xcm-v3-finally-merged-after-15-month-development/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadots-xcm-v3-finally-merged-after-15-month-development/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 13:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadots-xcm-v3-finally-merged-after-15-month-development/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XCM works across chains, smart contracts and non-fungible tokens (NFTs). It also supports communication between networks with different consensus mechanisms, like between Bitcoin and Polkadot. Polkadot founder Gavin Wood announced XCM v3 had finally merged on Tuesday, 17 January 2023. Polkadot, the scalable heterogeneous blockchain ecosystem, is currently one of the crypto industry&#8217;s most robust [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadots-xcm-v3-finally-merged-after-15-month-development/">Polkadot’s XCM v3 finally merged after 15-month development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>XCM works across chains, smart contracts and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>It also supports communication between networks with different consensus mechanisms, like between Bitcoin and Polkadot.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Polkadot founder Gavin Wood announced XCM v3 had finally merged on Tuesday, 17 January 2023</em></strong>.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/polkadot/">Polkadot</a>, the scalable heterogeneous blockchain ecosystem, is currently one of the crypto industry&rsquo;s most robust networks, and has a new feature to boot.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Polkadot founder Gavin Wood, the interoperability blockchain&rsquo;s &ldquo;cross-consensus message&rdquo; formar (XCM) version 3 is finally deployed. Wood, who also founded Kusama, Ethereum and Parity Technologies, announced on Tuesday that XCM v3 had been in <a href="https://github.com/paritytech/polkadot/pull/4097" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">development</a> for fifteen months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">After exactly 15 months in development, <a href="https://twitter.com/Polkadot?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@polkadot</a> XCM version 3 is merged. This enables bridges, cross-chain locking, exchanges, NFTs, conditionals, context-tracking and more. <a href="https://t.co/dqcLXOmDa9">https://t.co/dqcLXOmDa9</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gavin Wood (@gavofyork) <a href="https://twitter.com/gavofyork/status/1615363662801428486?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does XCM work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://wiki.polkadot.network/docs/learn-xcm" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">XCM</a> started with cross-chain communication between different chains at its core, before the shift to cross-consensus message &ndash; the aim of which is to avail a language by which different consensus systems can communicate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The XCM design offers instructions on how to compose, send, and interpret messages across chains. The destination chain is the one that executes the instructions, with support for programmable, trustless and rich data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Basically, XCM is standard through which protocol developers can define data and origins that their particular chains can send to or receive from. For instance, a developer can leverage XCM to allow for communication between Bitcoin (<em>a proof-of-work network</em>) and Polkadot (<em>a proof-of-stake network</em>).</p>
<p dir="ltr">But XCM v3 deployment does more than just to enable cross-consensus communication between chains. It can work across smart contracts, bridges, pallets, exchanges, and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">An example is where message format allows interoperability between parachains, removing the need to use bridges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadots-xcm-v3-finally-merged-after-15-month-development/">Polkadot’s XCM v3 finally merged after 15-month development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/polkadots-xcm-v3-finally-merged-after-15-month-development/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
