<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 12:02:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin hits 5-month high as bulls push BTC above $23K</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hits-5-month-high-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 12:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hits-5-month-high-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin hit highs of $23,342 on Binance, with a breakout above $22k extending year-to-date gains. BTC price is up 30% in a month and has recovered 47% since the decline to $15,500 lows. Short liquidations were around $376 million in the past 24 hours. Bitcoin price roared to highs above $23,000 on Saturday morning, rising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hits-5-month-high-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23k/">Bitcoin hits 5-month high as bulls push BTC above $23K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Bitcoin hit highs of $23,342 on Binance, with a breakout above $22k extending year-to-date gains.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>BTC price is up 30% in a month and has recovered 47% since the decline to $15,500 lows.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Short liquidations were around $376 million in the past 24 hours.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price roared to highs above $23,000 on Saturday morning, rising to $23,342 on Binance as the price of the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency by market cap hit levels last seen in mid-August 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BTC was changing hands around $22,900 at the time of writing, about 9% up in the past 24 hours after shedding some of the gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of Bitcoin was, however, still 35% up in the past 30 days, and as crypto trader and analyst Rekt Capital <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1616752893180235780" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">pointed out</a> earlier this morning, BTC had rallied over 47% since falling to lows of $15,500 amid the FTX dump.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/21/1674301360202-5c4a51da-5cb3-4bc1-91fb-cfd196ec6553.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="236"><span class="fr-inner">Bitcoin price chart showing BTC rally to $23,000 on 21 January, 2023. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/84XgTuiZ/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;On-chain data platform Santiment noted just before today&rsquo;s break above $23k that Bitcoin&rsquo;s price rally has come amid a bullish outlook from large BTC investors. As the firm <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1616579880321429504" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">highlights</a> in the chart below, whale addresses with 1,000 to 10,000 BTC have in the past two weeks accumulated over 64,638 bitcoins worth more than $1.46 billion.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128051; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> has now surpassed $22.7k for the first time since August 18, 2022. The price rise has come as the large whale tier group of addresses holding 1,000 to 10,000 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> has collectively accumulated 64,638 ($1.46 billion) <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> in the past 15 days. &#128077; <a href="https://t.co/H6jCsZDgUR">https://t.co/H6jCsZDgUR</a> <a href="https://t.co/RaN2I48ybg">pic.twitter.com/RaN2I48ybg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1616579880321429504?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Over $376 million in shorts liquidated</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As Bitcoin raced to highs near $23,350, l<a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">iquidation data</a> showed that in the past 24 hours, about 80,497 traders had been liquidated.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Coinglass, the largest short liquidation was on Bitmex where an order worth $4.53million was rekt. The total liquidations as of 06:10 am ET on 21 January were $376.61 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, total liquidations are not at the levels seen when BTC/USD broke above $20,000 last week towards erasing all post-FTX losses. Nonetheless, it still shows some traders are convinced this could be a gigantic bull trap.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But as it is, further upside momentum could see bulls target $25,000 or possibly higher if sentiment across risk markets helps bouy buy pressure.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-hits-5-month-high-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23k/">Bitcoin hits 5-month high as bulls push BTC above $23K</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samsung expands mobile wallet app to 8 more countries</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-expands-mobile-wallet-app-to-8-more-countries/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-expands-mobile-wallet-app-to-8-more-countries/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto wallets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-expands-mobile-wallet-app-to-8-more-countries/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Samsung has announced it will roll out its Samsung Wallet mobile app to another eight countries. The Korea firm launched the app in June 2022, and expanded it to 21 countries before the latest announcement. The wallet app integrates with the Samsung Blockchain Wallet for cryptocurrencies. Samsung Electronics has announced that its unified mobile wallet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-expands-mobile-wallet-app-to-8-more-countries/">Samsung expands mobile wallet app to 8 more countries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Samsung has announced it will roll out its Samsung Wallet mobile app to another eight countries.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The Korea firm launched the app in June 2022, and expanded it to 21 countries before the latest announcement.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The wallet app integrates with the Samsung Blockchain Wallet for cryptocurrencies.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Samsung Electronics has announced that its unified <a href="https://coinjournal.net/wallets/">mobile wallet application</a> Samsung Wallet will now be available in eight more countries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The South Korea-based tech giant revealed it would be rolling out the wallet app across Singapore, Australia, Brazil, Hong Kong, Canada, India, Malaysia and Taiwan. Support for the Samsung Wallet in these countries will go live by the end of January.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the company noted in a <a href="https://news.samsung.com/global/samsung-wallet-will-be-available-in-eight-new-markets" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">news release</a> that the exact timing of the launch will vary and depend on user devices and the specific market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Samsung&rsquo;s mobile payments platform grows</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Samsung launched the wallet app in 2022, with support since its unveiling in June having increased from an initial seven countries to 21 countries by the date of the latest announcement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, the Samsung Wallet app is available for Samsung Galaxy users in Korea, UK, the US, Bahrain, China, Denmark, Spain, Finland, France, Germany, Italy, Kazakhstan, Kuwait, Norway, Oman, Qatar, South Africa, Sweden, Switzerland, Vietnam, and the United Arab Emirates.</p>
<p dir="ltr">More than a payments platform, the app also <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-introduce-a-new-blockchain-wallet-app/">integrates</a> with the Samsung Blockchain Wallet and comes with safety features enhanced by Samsung Knox, an inbuilt proprietary security platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, while Samsung&rsquo;s wallet app is not crypto-specific, users with supported devices can leverage it to do things like keeping tabs on their digital assets portfolio. The wallet allows for this via an interface that enables access to cryptocurrency prices across multiple exchanges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-expands-mobile-wallet-app-to-8-more-countries/">Samsung expands mobile wallet app to 8 more countries</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/samsung-expands-mobile-wallet-app-to-8-more-countries/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo to pay $45 million to settle SEC charges</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 17:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nexo reached a $45 million settlement with US regulators, including the SEC. The crypto lender allegedly offered unregistered securities via its Earn Interest Product. Nexo will pay $22.5 to state regulators and the rest to the SEC, with this expected in the next 12 months. Nexo, a Cayman Islands corporation founded in 2018 and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/">Nexo to pay $45 million to settle SEC charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Nexo reached a $45 million settlement with US regulators, including the SEC.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The crypto lender allegedly offered unregistered securities via its Earn Interest Product.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Nexo will pay $22.5 to state regulators and the rest to the SEC, with this expected in the next 12 months.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/nexo/">Nexo</a>, a Cayman Islands corporation founded in 2018 and a leading crypto lender, will pay $45 million as settlement with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the North American Securities Administrators Association (NASAA).</p>
<p dir="ltr">NASAA announced the settlement late Thursday, noting Nexo had agreed to pay the penalties following the outcome of a comprehensive investigation into an interest product the crypto platform allegedly offered to US customers.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Nexo settlement closes multi-year investigation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the <a href="https://www.nasaa.org/67039/nasaa-and-sec-announce-45-million-settlement-with-nexo-capital-over-interest-bearing-account/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> announcing the settlement, the charges related to Nexo&rsquo;s offering and sale of alleged unregistered securities via its Earned Interest Product (EIP). The regulatory watchdog noted 17 US state securities regulators had agreed to the reported settlement, with more set to accept it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>T</em><em>his settlement recognises the important work of state securities regulators and the SEC in making sure that those who are investing their hard-earned money have all the information necessary to understand the risks and rewards of their decisions</em>,&rdquo; said Charlie Clark, Director, Washington Department of Financial Institutions Agency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nexo commented on the landmark settlement via a <a href="https://nexo.io/media-center/nexo-reaches-landmark-resolution-with-us-regulators" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">blog release</a>, confirming it had been reached on a &ldquo;<em>no-admit-no-deny basis</em>.&rdquo; This closes a multi-year probe into Nexo&rsquo;s offerings, particularly its interest bearing accounts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Nexo, the regulators&rsquo; inquiries over the past year or so showed the company had not engaged in any fraud.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Nexo believes that the company has been recognized for what it truly is &ndash; a pioneer, like Uber and Airbnb, providing disruptive solutions in a fast-paced environment.</p>
<p>4/9</p>
<p>&mdash; Nexo (@Nexo) <a href="https://twitter.com/Nexo/status/1616195617574854656?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are content with this unified resolution which unequivocally puts an end to all speculations around Nexo&rsquo;s relations to the United States. We can now focus on what we do best &ndash; build seamless financial solutions for our worldwide audience</em>,&rdquo; said Nexo co-founder Antoni Trenchev.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto lender will pay $22.5 million to state securities regulators and the rest to the SEC, with the payments made over the next 12 months. Notably. Nexo was in the process of a phased out exit from the United States market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nexo&rsquo;s native token NEXO rose in the aftermath of the announcement, and was changing hands around $0.84 on Friday afternoon. The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/nexo/">NEXO price</a> was up by more than 17% in the past 24 hours as at 12:10 pm ET</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/">Nexo to pay $45 million to settle SEC charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/nexo-to-pay-45-million-to-settle-sec-charges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantom launches on-chain funding system Ecosystem Vault</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-launches-on-chain-funding-system-ecosystem-vault/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-launches-on-chain-funding-system-ecosystem-vault/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 16:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-launches-on-chain-funding-system-ecosystem-vault/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fantom Foundation, the platform behind the Fantom (FTM) blockchain announced the launch of Ecosystem Vault on Friday. Vault is a decentralised funding mechanism that will be financed by 10% of FTM transaction fees. The funds in the vault are available to projects that get 55% approval in community-driven governance vote. Fantom, a scalable Layer-1 blockchain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-launches-on-chain-funding-system-ecosystem-vault/">Fantom launches on-chain funding system Ecosystem Vault</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Fantom Foundation, the platform behind the Fantom (FTM) blockchain announced the launch of Ecosystem Vault on Friday.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Vault is a decentralised funding mechanism that will be financed by 10% of FTM transaction fees.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The funds in the vault are available to projects that get 55% approval in community-driven governance vote.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/fantom/">Fantom</a>, a scalable Layer-1 blockchain platform, has officially launched Ecosystem Vault, a decentralised funding pool that will empower and help builders deploy new community-driven projects on the blockchain.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Vault to boost Fantom&rsquo;s dApps ecosystem</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Announcing that Vault was officially live, Fantom noted in a <a href="https://fantom.foundation/blog/ecosystem-vault-now-live/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">blog post</a> that the funding mechanism will encompass governance proposals from the community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project represents Fantom&rsquo;s continuing evolution as the community eyes further decentralisation, the Fantom Foundation team wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Vault&rsquo;s on-chain mechanism allows for a funding profile where projects and developers seeking to build decentralised apps (dApps) in the ecosystem can secure financing. As noted above, the funding pool also gives the Fantom community a chance to contribute to the growth of the blockchain via their funding decisions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per the Fantom Foundation, the Ecosystem Vault will get funds from 10% of transaction fees. The community controls these funds, which are a result of a reduction in the burn rate of native token FTM. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Anyone can apply for the funds in the Vault, a process that requires applicants to create a Fantom Governance proposal (has 100 FTM fee). Afterwards, the proposal will need approval from 55% of the community based on 55% quorum. The Foundation tweeted:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5/ A proposal must receive at least 55% approval with 55% quorum to be considered successful. <a href="https://twitter.com/llamapay_io?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Llamapay_io</a> will be used to distribute all funding. Only wallet addresses included in the application can be paid.</p>
<p>&mdash; Fantom Foundation (@FantomFDN) <a href="https://twitter.com/FantomFDN/status/1616120331478990848?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>As of Friday, 20 January, 2023 at 11:06 am ET, the vault <a href="https://vault.fantom.network/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">held</a> roughly 69,247 FTM tokens valued at just over $21,000.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-launches-on-chain-funding-system-ecosystem-vault/">Fantom launches on-chain funding system Ecosystem Vault</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/fantom-launches-on-chain-funding-system-ecosystem-vault/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin’s recovery will depend on a lot of macro-activities affecting the market, says Dan Ashmore</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-recovery-will-depend-on-a-lot-of-macro-activities-affecting-the-market-says-dan-ashmore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 16:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-recovery-will-depend-on-a-lot-of-macro-activities-affecting-the-market-says-dan-ashmore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinjournal&#8217;s Dan Ashmore says numerous factors, including inflation and rate hikes, have affected the prices of most cryptocurrencies. He told CNBC that Bitcoin&#8217;s recovery would depend on numerous macro events affecting the market. Bitcoin and the broader crypto market have lost more than 65% of their value since the all-time high of November 2021. Bitcoin&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-recovery-will-depend-on-a-lot-of-macro-activities-affecting-the-market-says-dan-ashmore/">Bitcoin’s recovery will depend on a lot of macro-activities affecting the market, says Dan Ashmore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinjournal&rsquo;s Dan Ashmore says numerous factors, including inflation and rate hikes, have affected the prices of most cryptocurrencies.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">He told CNBC that Bitcoin&rsquo;s recovery would depend on numerous macro events affecting the market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and the broader crypto market have lost more than 65% of their value since the all-time high of November 2021.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin&rsquo;s recovery will not happen overnight</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dan Ashmore, a cryptocurrency analyst at Coinjournal,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/01/11/crypto-analyst-breaks-down-decline-bitcoin-millionaires.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>told CNBC</u></a> in a recent interview that the price recovery of cryptocurrencies will not happen overnight. When commenting about the price collapse last year, Ashmore said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Entering 2022, we were at the tail-end of one of the longest and most explosive Bull Runs in recent memory. And then the world is gripped by this inflation crisis post-pandemic. We also experienced one of the swiftest rate hike cycles in recent memories. That sucked the liquidity out of all these risky assets. It is not overly surprising that we have seen this massive pullback.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/20/1674230971916-49ee06fe-a239-4d3b-a34d-e4864740e165.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib fr-fil" width="600" height="334"></em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>The macro climate will play a role in market recovery&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/price/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $21,163, down by more than 60% from the all-time high. While commenting on the possibility of price recovery, Ashmore said the macro climate would play a huge role in that regard. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;In the last month or so, we have seen slightly more positive readings. It still has a long way to go, but it is brighter than it looked a month or two ago. We still have a long way to go before we get back to that $69,000 all-time high. This is not going to be an overnight process.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">He added that the rise depends on a whole range of variables in the macro climate going our way. Furthermore, the avoidance of incidents such as the LUNA, FTX, and Celsius crashes could help boost the market in the long term.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-recovery-will-depend-on-a-lot-of-macro-activities-affecting-the-market-says-dan-ashmore/">Bitcoin’s recovery will depend on a lot of macro-activities affecting the market, says Dan Ashmore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The audit reports of crypto exchanges were anything but an audit, says Dan Ashmore</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-audit-reports-of-crypto-exchanges-were-anything-but-an-audit-says-dan-ashmore/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-audit-reports-of-crypto-exchanges-were-anything-but-an-audit-says-dan-ashmore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 16:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-audit-reports-of-crypto-exchanges-were-anything-but-an-audit-says-dan-ashmore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinjournal&#8217;s Dan Ashmore told CNBC that the audit reports by cryptocurrency exchanges were not really audited reports. The analyst pointed out that the reports only indicated the assets held by the exchanges and didn&#8217;t reveal the liabilities of the companies. Several exchanges, including Binance and OKX, have published their proof of reserve reports in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-audit-reports-of-crypto-exchanges-were-anything-but-an-audit-says-dan-ashmore/">The audit reports of crypto exchanges were anything but an audit, says Dan Ashmore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinjournal&rsquo;s Dan Ashmore told CNBC that the audit reports by cryptocurrency exchanges were not really audited reports.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The analyst pointed out that the reports only indicated the assets held by the exchanges and didn&rsquo;t reveal the liabilities of the companies.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Several exchanges, including Binance and OKX, have published their proof of reserve reports in the last few months.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Proof of reserves didn&rsquo;t include liabilities</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dan Ashmore, a cryptocurrency analyst at Coinjournal,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/01/17/bitcoin-21000-three-arrows-founders-crypto-debt-platform-crypto-world.html"><u>told CNBC</u></a> in a recent interview that the audit reports by cryptocurrency exchanges were not entirely accurate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last month, accounting firm Mazars Group&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/16/mazars-suspends-all-work-with-crypto-clients-including-binance-cryptocom.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>suspended all work</u></a> with its crypto clients, including&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a>, KuCoin and Crypto.com. When asked about the move, Ashmore said the move was a disappointing one for the crypto industry. He stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;It is disappointing, but it is not surprising. When you look at those audit reports, they were anything but an audit. It was essentially a statement of reserves. But there was no mention of liabilities. It is not possible to do an audit without mentioning liabilities. These proof of reserves need to become proper audits.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Ashmore added that third-party entities need to look at these centralised exchanges and make financial assessments. However, due to the lack of in-depth information, it is impossible to do so at the moment.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Centralised exchanges continue to publish proof of reserves</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Since the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange in November 2022, centralised crypto exchanges have been publishing proof of reserves to show their users that they have assets on their platforms.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, the OKX crypto exchange&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-publishes-proof-of-reserves-report-has-assets-worth-7-5b/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>published a proof-of-reserves report</u></a>. The report revealed that the exchange has a total of $7.5 billion worth of assets in reserves which do not include its native token, OKB.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-audit-reports-of-crypto-exchanges-were-anything-but-an-audit-says-dan-ashmore/">The audit reports of crypto exchanges were anything but an audit, says Dan Ashmore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-audit-reports-of-crypto-exchanges-were-anything-but-an-audit-says-dan-ashmore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain uses: The real expansion has just begun!</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-uses-the-real-expansion-has-just-begun/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-uses-the-real-expansion-has-just-begun/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-uses-the-real-expansion-has-just-begun/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain is changing industries and bringing the benefits of the new technology to every day life. Medical innovation and data confidentiality are big trends. Blockchain technology in gaming, supply chain management and digital identity verification are also huge steps. In recent years, application cases for blockchain have extended significantly beyond bitcoin, with various businesses embracing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-uses-the-real-expansion-has-just-begun/">Blockchain uses: The real expansion has just begun!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Blockchain is changing industries and bringing the benefits of the new technology to every day life.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Medical innovation and data confidentiality are big trends.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Blockchain technology in gaming, supply chain management and digital identity verification are also huge steps.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In recent years, application cases for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/blockchain/">blockchain</a> have extended significantly beyond bitcoin, with various businesses embracing the tech in a broad range of industries. These industries include healthcare, transportation, and financial services, to name a few.</p>
<p>However, there are a number of hidden things and the curtains are about to get off. Because blockchains are decentralized, transparent, and boost the capacity of an entire network, they open the door for innovations that require a large amount of computational power to be implemented.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most significantly, they give customers the ability to exercise control over their assets, which may include their data, without having to rely on any outside parties.</p>
<p>As blockchain technology continues to advance, businesses all over the world are collaborating to discover the most effective methods to apply the technology in a variety of contexts. In order to gather deeper insight, we have sought out initiatives that are changing industries and pushing blockchain closer to the lives of people on a daily basis.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The medical innovation &nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For a very long time, physicians or health institutions all over the world have been thought of as the exclusive owners of medical records.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A database in Argentina that contained sensitive data such as governmental IDs including tax ID numbers with over 115,000 persons who filed for COVID-19 circulation licenses was breached in the year 2020. This database contained the information of everyone who applied for the licenses.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Turning the pitiable state of patients into a comfortable one</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Because of this occurrence, ShelterZoom decided to develop a system that would safeguard the medical records of its customers from any future cyber breaches that are comparable to this one.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In order to empower patients with full ownership and control over their medical information, the firm developed a smart-document software-as-a-service supplier and collaborated with a private hospital.</p>
<p>Users are able to access medical record panels and do any and all essential procedures whenever they choose by utilizing a mobile app or extension based on blockchain technology. It also gives patients the ability to monitor email attachments and access privileges to those documents, irrespective of whether the receiver of the email has even opened it.</p>
<p>As a direct result of the agreement, more than 300,000 individuals have permission to the Web3 application. Additionally, there are plans in place to make the service available to other healthcare professionals in Argentina in the near future.</p>
<p>According to the opinions of several experts, projects centered on first-party information will eventually replace analytics in advertising and serve as the basis for personalization. Users are given the ability to monetize their own data through Web3, and consumers stand to gain considerably as a result of this fundamental innovation that is made possible by blockchain technology.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The authority leading to data confidentiality&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In the decades that have passed since the introduction of the internet, data has evolved into an extremely valuable resource.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Traditionally, users have donated their personal data to services and websites for free, and they do not receive any monetary advantage when those businesses sell their personal data to other parties.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Users are able to once again exercise control over their own data and decide for themselves whether or not to commercialize it for their personal advantage when using Web3.</p>
<p>Dimo is a decentralized system for transport data that gives users the ability to produce vehicle data recordings that have been confirmed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Owners have the ability to privately share this information with apps, which provides them with the ability to negotiate cheaper insurance and finance prices. The native DIMO token can be earned as a reward for both referrals and active involvement in the network.</p>
<p>According to the opinions of several experts, projects centered on first-party content will soon overtake cookies in marketing and serve as the basis for personalization.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Users are given the ability to monetize their own data through Web3, and consumers stand to gain considerably as a result of this fundamental innovation that is made possible by blockchain technology.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The luxurious leverages of blockchain&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Customers of high-end brands can now easily confirm the genuineness of their purchases thanks to the Aura Blockchain Consortium.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For instance, Prada is guaranteeing the authenticity and transparency of its recycled gold jewelry and diamonds through a relationship with Aura, allowing customers to track the items from mine to finger.</p>
<p>By the same token, there are certain AI-based <a href="https://coinjournal.net/robots/">trading bots</a> too, <a href="https://the-ethereumcode-pro.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">go URL</a> and know how these bots have turned basic trading mechanisms into luxurious ones.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Louis Vuitton, Christian Dior, and other LVMH labels are also part of the group. The company provides its customers with an Aura-powered diamond certificate detailing the features, history, and travel of each stone.</p>
<p>The jewelry trade has struggled with the issue of traceability for a long time, notably in regard to diamonds, despite the trade&rsquo;s efforts to sell only conflict-free gems.</p>
<p>While ConsenSys developed the blockchain infrastructure and the traceability <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/smart-contract/">smart contracts</a> for Aura, the Ethereum blockchain is the foundation around which Aura is built. Mercedes-Benz and Cartier are two additional members of the funding group.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The silver lining&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain technology is being adopted in a wide variety of industries, from healthcare to gaming to supply chain management to digital identity verification.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With Ethereum as well as other blockchains now able to store and run computer code, the number of potential applications for this cutting-edge technology has skyrocketed.</p>
<p>Over the past year, we&rsquo;ve dispelled the misconceptions that cryptocurrencies serve as a bank for the unbanked, provide a safe haven from inflation and that Decentralized Finance (DeFi) financial engineering can produce higher returns than any other asset class.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recently, though, people have returned to ask about the practical applications of digital assets rather than my forecasts for their <a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/">future prices</a>. And that&rsquo;s making headway.</p>
<p>The recent events may prove to be a blessing in disguise by shifting the blockchain industry&rsquo;s focus from financial engineering to more appealing business applications that actually add value.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-uses-the-real-expansion-has-just-begun/">Blockchain uses: The real expansion has just begun!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-uses-the-real-expansion-has-just-begun/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Mark Yourself Safe From The Flood Of Crypto Frauds?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-to-mark-yourself-safe-from-the-flood-of-crypto-frauds/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-to-mark-yourself-safe-from-the-flood-of-crypto-frauds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/how-to-mark-yourself-safe-from-the-flood-of-crypto-frauds/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Some individuals are under the impression that it will take the place of the conventional financial system and are excited to be a part of the transition. What could possibly go wrong here? Maybe you are not linked with reliable trading bots like bitcoin prime and your investments are con artists who have the intention [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-to-mark-yourself-safe-from-the-flood-of-crypto-frauds/">How To Mark Yourself Safe From The Flood Of Crypto Frauds?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Some individuals are under the impression that it will take the place of the conventional financial system and are excited to be a part of the transition.</p>
<p>What could possibly go wrong here? Maybe you are not linked with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-crypto-trading-bots/">reliable trading bots</a> like bitcoin prime and your investments are con artists who have the intention of using their crypto token holdings to become wealthy very rapidly, and their methods are improving each day.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A cursory glance at crypto fraud, along with some steps you may do to protect yourself, is presented here.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is a crypto scam?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Mining is the process that must be carried out between the two parties. This requires users to execute complex mathematical computations on behalf of everybody on the network, send off some details about themselves, and then wait for their reward.</p>
<p>Few individuals have a firm grasp on how cryptocurrencies function because of their complexity and the emergence of new cryptocurrencies. In other words, you risk losing your money to con artists who are hoping you&rsquo;ll invest in their scheme.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s crucial to know about potential threats before taking any chances, whether they come in the form of phishing schemes or fraudulent apps promising free currency.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Unleashing the reason behind crypto fraud expansion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is a lot of public interest in the crypto market, which is highly volatile. The fact that there are more people to swindle is enough to make this an appealing environment for fraudsters.</p>
<p>The Federal Trade Commission estimates an increase in complaints about cryptocurrency scams from 2021. In 2020, crypto fraud cost consumers a maximum of $130 million. The following year reports skyrocketed, and by 2021, the United States had lost $680 million.</p>
<p>Some frauds may go unreported because as many as 35% of victims didn&rsquo;t realize they could do so. As a result, this year&rsquo;s losses may be considerably greater.</p>
<p>A few of the reasons why scammers stick around in this industry are listed below:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Because cryptocurrencies are digital, hackers need just access to a computer to launch assaults.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When money is transferred, it can&rsquo;t be retrieved unless the recipient cancels the transaction.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>As a decentralized system, cryptocurrencies offer no guarantee of payment to their owners.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A person&rsquo;s identity will not be revealed during this procedure. You can avoid storing sensitive data as the crypto regulatory landscape develops. The source of funds can be traced, however, fraudsters might complicate matters by using several wallets. It&rsquo;s already hard enough to figure out who the wallet owners are.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anyone with cryptocurrency holdings is vulnerable to a crypto scam. To counter this, though, you have a few options for safety.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Protecting your trading account from hackers&nbsp;</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">VPN service</h3>
<p dir="ltr">To protect yourself from intrusions like this, consider signing up for a VPN.</p>
<p>In order to ensure the security of your cryptocurrency transactions, you may wish to sign up for a VPN service. If you invest for a year or more in advance, you can save money on a VPN service that normally costs between $5 to $15 per month.</p>
<p>VPNs offer usefulness outside of the crypto realm, such as when you want to watch foreign TV or hide your online behavior from your ISP.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">A big NO for public Wi-Fi</h3>
<p dir="ltr">There will be occasions when you need to access the internet away from home, and the allure of free public Wi-Fi in a local cafe or restaurant is understandable.</p>
<p>However, you may wish to stay away from free public Wi-Fi if you&rsquo;re conducting cryptocurrency transactions. Anyone in the vicinity can listen in on your web traffic using a program like Wireshark if you&rsquo;re utilizing a free, open Wi-Fi network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>They can usually detect if you are browsing <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">crypto sites</a> based on the data they collect. The possibility exists that they can even see your financial dealings.</p>
<p>While this won&rsquo;t directly lead to the theft of your cryptocurrency, a fraudster may decide to pay much particular examination to you if they notice you making purchases or browsing crypto sites with a big dollar amount. You don&rsquo;t want that type of focus, do you?</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Password&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s tempting to use the same login for your wallet that you use for your favorite website, but you should avoid this.</p>
<p>If you use the same password for your wallet as you do for a site, then the hacker will have access to your key vault if your website password is compromised. (The key vault is typically taken during attacks of this nature.)</p>
<p>An attacker may theoretically use key-logging spyware to track your keystrokes while you type in your password or retrieve your unprotected vault data from your PC&rsquo;s RAM, regardless of how complex your password is.</p>
<p>These methods are quite clever, and to our knowledge, no crypto user has ever had their seed words compromised in this fashion. Unfortunately, this type of crime may become increasingly widespread as cryptocurrency usage grows.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, using a trading bot like <a href="https://bitcoinprimeapp.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">bitcoin prime</a> are others is a must.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Hardware Wallet</h3>
<p dir="ltr">A <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrency-guides/what-is-a-cryptocurrency-hardware-wallet/">hardware wallet</a> is a USB gadget that can contain your key vault and is one of the finest ways to keep your cryptocurrency secure. The device is built in such a way that your seed words remain encrypted even if they are removed.</p>
<p>It is very difficult for a hacker to infiltrate a hardware wallet with malware because it does not have access to the Internet.</p>
<p>You must pair your hardware wallet with your smartphone or tablet via USB or Bluetooth before each transaction. To conduct transactions without disclosing your private key to a potentially malware-infected device, the wallet generates a signature and transmits it to your internet-connected device.</p>
<p>Even if your hardware wallet were taken, the attacker would have a hard time accessing your cryptocurrency because of the PIN code.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Authentication Software</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The security of your online wallet can be bolstered by using a third-party authenticator tool like Google Authenticator for two-factor authentication.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since authenticator apps don&rsquo;t use SMS text communication to give you the pullout code, an attacker who gains access to your phone&rsquo;s service or who is able to mirror your messages will still be unable to obtain your withdrawal code.</p>
<p>Using an authenticator app means the hacker must physically obtain your device in order to access the 2FA code. As an additional safeguard, it outperforms the use of simple text messages.</p>
<p>It is possible for an attacker to circumvent the safety of the exchange even if you have two-factor authentication turned on.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s possible that the exchange&rsquo;s withdrawal hold policy or other safeguards will prevent you from withdrawing your cryptocurrency in the event of a hack.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Summing Up&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is a growth in criminal behavior when the cryptocurrency market reaches new heights because more people are downloading wallets and joining sites for the first time.</p>
<p>As we&rsquo;ve seen, there are many ways to keep your cryptocurrency safe from this new breed of the crook, including two-factor authentication, pulling from an exchange, loading up the seed words, staying away from free public Wi-Fi, and utilizing a virtual private network (VPN).</p>
<p>Scammers will no doubt think of new ways to steal cryptocurrency in the future; we&rsquo;ll be certain to keep this page as necessary. For the time being, these are among the best methods for keeping your crypto safe.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-to-mark-yourself-safe-from-the-flood-of-crypto-frauds/">How To Mark Yourself Safe From The Flood Of Crypto Frauds?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-to-mark-yourself-safe-from-the-flood-of-crypto-frauds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX.US president raises $5 million seed round for new venture Architect</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-ftx-us-president-raises-5-million-seed-round-for-new-venture-architect/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-ftx-us-president-raises-5-million-seed-round-for-new-venture-architect/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 14:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/former-ftx-us-president-raises-5-million-seed-round-for-new-venture-architect/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Former FTX president Brett Harrison has announced his new project has raised $5 million from investors. Backers include Coinbase Ventures, Circle Ventures and SV Angel among others. Architect is buildig new institutional-grade trading technology. Brett Harrison, the former FTX.US president, has raised $5 million in a seed round funding for his new crypto project for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-ftx-us-president-raises-5-million-seed-round-for-new-venture-architect/">Former FTX.US president raises $5 million seed round for new venture Architect</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Former FTX president Brett Harrison has announced his new project has raised $5 million from investors.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Backers include Coinbase Ventures, Circle Ventures and SV Angel among others.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Architect is buildig new institutional-grade trading technology.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Brett Harrison, the former FTX.US president, has raised $5 million in a seed round funding for his new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto project</a> for institutional investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The new platform is a decentralised finance (DeFi) venture dubbed Architect and has been in stealth development since last September.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Architect raises $5 million in seed round</h2>
<p dir="ltr">An announcement Harrison released on Friday stated that Architect had secured the $5 million investment from some of the top venture investors within the crypto space, including Coinbase Ventures and Circle Ventures.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other investors to back the former FTX.US president&rsquo;s startup Architect are SALT Fund, Third King Venture Capital, Motivate Venture Capital and SV Angel. SkyBridge Capital&rsquo;s Antony Scaramucci has also invested in the new crypto software project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ I&rsquo;m very happy to announce the founding of <a href="https://twitter.com/Architect_xyz?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Architect_xyz</a> and the closing of our $5m seed round! <a href="https://t.co/NCMdWwwbA1">https://t.co/NCMdWwwbA1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Brett Harrison (@BrettHarrison88) <a href="https://twitter.com/BrettHarrison88/status/1616438221872701441?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Architect is building <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/hub/">trading</a> software that aims at streamlining the crypto markets. According to Harrison, Architect will make it easier for large investors to enter and explore both centralised and decentralised crypto markets. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Architect will build institutional-grade trading technology that streamlines crypto market structure, making it easier and safer for firms and large traders to access decentralized protocols and centralized exchanges alike</em>,&rdquo; Harrison <a href="https://twitter.com/BrettHarrison88/status/1616438223055556609" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a>.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-20/ex-ftx-us-president-harrison-taps-coinbase-circle-for-new-crypto-firm#xj4y7vzkg" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report </a>by Bloomberg noted that Architect plans to hire some of the talent that worked at FTX as they eye the launch of Architect within the next few months.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-ftx-us-president-raises-5-million-seed-round-for-new-venture-architect/">Former FTX.US president raises $5 million seed round for new venture Architect</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/former-ftx-us-president-raises-5-million-seed-round-for-new-venture-architect/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
