<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:53:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase stock could sink all the way back to $60 – analyst says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-could-sink-to-60-analyst-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Piper Sandler downgraded Coinbase Global Inc on Wednesday. Analyst Patrick Moley cited regulatory uncertainty for dovish view. Coinbase stock has gained close to 60% over the past thirty days. Coinbase Global Inc has been an absolute delight for shareholders over the past thirty days but a sharp downturn is likely moving forward, as per a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-could-sink-to-60-analyst-says/">Coinbase stock could sink all the way back to $60 – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Piper Sandler downgraded Coinbase Global Inc on Wednesday.</li>
<li>Analyst Patrick Moley cited regulatory uncertainty for dovish view.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock has gained close to 60% over the past thirty days.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> has been an absolute delight for shareholders over the past thirty days but a sharp downturn is likely moving forward, as per a Piper Sandler analyst.</p>
<h2>Avoid Coinbase stock due to regulatory uncertainty</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, Patrick Moley downgraded the crypto exchange to &ldquo;neutral&rdquo; and lowered his price target as well to $60 that signals a 25% downside from here.</p>
<p>The analyst turned dovish primarily because the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission sued the Nasdaq-listed firm last month for operating as an unregistered exchange (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">read more</a>).</p>
<p>In a research note today, he attributed the recent surge in Coinbase stock to prominent asset managers filing for a Spot Bitcoin ETF and the consequent benefit to crypto prices but said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Rising crypto prices have not translated to increased trading volumes for COIN in recent quarters and the timing of a Spot Bitcoin ETF approval is anyone&rsquo;s guess.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Coinbase Global will report a weak second quarter</h2>
<p>Moley expects the crypto company to report monthly transacting users and trading volumes at a two-year low in its second financial quarter.</p>
<p>The Piper Sandler analyst agreed that Coinbase Global will eventually emerge as a major player within the crypto space but said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;d like to see more progress on regulatory front and a convincing turnaround in underlying fundamentals of the business before becoming more positive on Coinbase stock.</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite the regulatory crackdown, though, Coinbase increased its <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/coinbases-market-share-is-on-the-rise-in-spite-of-sec-actions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market share</a> last month to a new high since January 2023, as per data from Kaiko &ndash; a digital assets data provider.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-could-sink-to-60-analyst-says/">Coinbase stock could sink all the way back to $60 – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) in 2023. What Are the Best Crypto ICOs To Buy Now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market evolves and matures, many investors seek the next big Initial Coin Offering (ICO) that could offer significant returns. But with so many popping up all the time, which are the best crypto ICOs worth investing in? In this article, you&#8217;ll find 14 hand-picked ICOs with promise. From AI-based projects to layer-1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/">Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) in 2023. What Are the Best Crypto ICOs To Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">As the cryptocurrency market evolves and matures, many investors seek the next big Initial Coin Offering (ICO) that could offer significant returns. But with so many popping up all the time, which are the best crypto ICOs worth investing in? In this article, you&rsquo;ll find 14 hand-picked ICOs with promise. From AI-based projects to layer-1 solutions, you will find something that catches your eye.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coin List</h2>
<ol>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer (CHANCER)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU)</li>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ALINK AI (ALINK)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Vivi (VIVI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">OptionBlitz (BLX)</li>
<li dir="ltr">ASTL (ASTL)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Kryptview (KVT)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Minima (WMINIMA)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Brickken (BKN)</li>
<li dir="ltr">EasyFeedback (EASYF)</li>
<li dir="ltr">WeSendIt (WSI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Mintera (MNTE)</li>
</ol>
<h2 dir="ltr"></h2>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Chancer (CHANCER) &mdash; Revolutionizing the betting industry</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a> is the world&rsquo;s first blockchain-based decentralized predictive markets app. Chancer aims to revolutionize the betting and gambling industry by removing the need for a bookmaker or house entirely. Chancer is a betting facilitator that allows people to make peer-to-peer (P2P) so the odds are equal and never stacked against users. Any type of bet can be made, from a small bet among friends, to viral bets on huge events such as the Superbowl or the Oscars. Unlike traditional bookies, bets aren&rsquo;t limited to just sports.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All bets and pay-outs are made in Chancer&rsquo;s native token, CHANCER. Additionally, users can earn CHANCER simply by using the platform and placing bets, presenting users with a great opportunity to earn a passive income. The rewards don&rsquo;t stop there; users can get discounts on bets, making it cost-efficient for frequent bettors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER has great utility as a token as it fuels Chancer&rsquo;s entire platform. Given that the size of the betting and gambling industry was worth an eye-watering $64 billion last year, there&rsquo;s a real chance that Chancer will disrupt the market and take a sizeable chunk of it through its democratized, decentralized platform that puts bettors first. This makes Chancer a great investment with lots of potential for both betting and crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Chancer </strong><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. Shiba Memu (SHIBA MEMU) &mdash; A meme coin with real utility</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shiba Memu</a> is a brand new meme coin based on the adorable Japanese Shiba Inu dog. However, this deceptively cute coin has a marketing powerhouse behind it and aims to do the work of 100+ marketing agencies in real time. It&rsquo;s leveraging the power of both blockchain and AI technology to transform marketing, taking time-consuming tasks from marketers so they can focus their efforts elsewhere.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu learns from successful marketing strategies, writes its own PR and promotes itself across relevant forums and social networks. It will be able to generate content based on the data that its AI continually analyzes, publishing this on several online platforms. It will then monitor and analyze the success of its marketing efforts and adjust them accordingly, constantly learning and improving content in order to optimize results.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu will undoubtedly benefit from being a cute, funny meme. However, unlike other meme coins in the market which rely on initial hype and then drastically lose value because they have no long-term use, SHIBA MEMU has innate utility as it fuels the entire Shiba Memu platform. Meme fans and crypto enthusiasts looking to invest in a meme coin and see long-term returns should consider Shiba Memu.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Shiba Memu </strong><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. AltSignals (ASI) &ndash; Harnessing AI to Transform the Trading Industry</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a trading signals provider that has established itself as an industry leader. Launched in 2017, AltSignals has issued over 1,500 calls in the forex, crypto, and stock market to over 1,400 VIP subscribers, with an average accuracy of 64%. It consistently produces outstanding returns each month; its Binance Futures signals for February netted a 2,163% return with a 90% win rate, while January generated 2,480% with 92% accuracy!</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; impeccable Trustpilot scores back up these results. It&rsquo;s garnered almost 500 positive reviews, boasting an average star rating of 4.9/5. It&rsquo;s all been made possible by AltSignals&rsquo; team of advanced trading professionals and the cutting-edge <a href="https://www.altsignals.io/indicator" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltAlgo&trade;</u></a> Indicator. AltAlgo&trade; combines over 34 filters and strategies to help the AltSignals team determine the best trading opportunities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now, AltSignals is ready for the next step in its journey. It&rsquo;s launching the ASI token to fund the development of the ActualizeAI algorithm. It aims to leverage a full AI stack to bring the platform&rsquo;s accuracy rate above 80% while offering some incredible benefits to investors. This AI stack will use the latest developments in AI technology, like machine learning and natural language processing, to upgrade the existing <a href="https://www.altsignals.io/indicator" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltAlgo&trade;</u></a> algorithm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By owning ASI, prospective investors will be granted exclusive access to the ActualizeAI algorithm&rsquo;s signals, giving them an edge over others in the financial markets. Those purchasing 20,000 ASI tokens or more will be offered lifetime membership to the signals while gaining free access to the existing AltAlgo&trade; signals service.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI will also offer investors eligibility to join the AI Members Club. This club will allow members to help shape the future of AltSignals and the ActualizeAI algorithm. As members, they can offer feedback, ideas, and contribute to the platform&rsquo;s development, earning additional ASI tokens as rewards. These tokens can be accumulated to upgrade their membership level, which can unlock even more features of the AltSignals AI ecosystem or be held for potential future gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, ASI acts as a governance token, allowing holders to propose changes and decide on future updates made to the platform. This direct community engagement helps to ensure that the platform&rsquo;s goals and values align with the traders using its service. After raising $120k just 2 days after launch, it&rsquo;s safe to say that AltSignals is a crypto project ready for big things. You definitely won&rsquo;t want to miss out on the ASI token presale!</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy AltSignals </strong><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. Metacade (MCADE) &ndash; Playing a Vital Role in the Play-To-Earn Movement</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=23" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a play-to-earn (P2E) community hub aiming to shake up the GameFi landscape with its initial coin offering. It&rsquo;s an all-in-one solution where gamers, crypto enthusiasts, and developers can team up and explore the rapidly-expanding world of P2E gaming. While it&rsquo;ll have everything you&rsquo;d expect from a gaming hub, like sub-communities, spaces for real-time interaction, and game leaderboards, it&rsquo;s harnessing the power of blockchain technology to take things to the next level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, to encourage the top minds in P2E to flock to the platform, it rewards anyone sharing reviews, tips, and other helpful content with MCADE tokens. Advanced players can earn by helping others find their GameFi edge. Meanwhile, players new to the P2E space can open up another source of income by sharing their thoughts on a new title they&rsquo;ve been playing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are also plans for regular tournaments, prize draws, and competitions where gamers can test their luck alongside other community members. Metacade intends to introduce a job and gig board in 2024, where users will discover roles ranging from casual game testing gigs to full-time salaried positions with Web3 and gaming leaders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most excitingly, Metacade is introducing the Metagrant scheme. Metagrants are expected to play a pivotal role in shaping the future of the P2E industry. They allow the community to vote and direct funds to the very best P2E titles in development.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developers will submit their ideas to a pool of competing proposals, and MCADE holders will vote on their favorite. The one that wins is awarded financing from the Metacade treasury, with the final game being added to the platform&rsquo;s virtual arcade for anyone to log on and play. Not only does this foster a unique sense of community engagement, but it also has the potential to make Metacade a household name with P2E gamers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Metacade </strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=23" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong> &lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. ALINK AI (ALINK) &ndash; A Marketplace Ready for the Future of AI</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is ALINK AI?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Following the recent rise of AI applications like ChatGPT, new AI-based crypto projects, and token sales have recently cropped up. One of the premier AI ICO campaigns is <a href="https://alink.ai/"><u>ALINK AI</u></a>, an all-in-one marketplace for AI services. It effectively allows anyone with an internet connection to request and offer services related to artificial general intelligence (AGI) in a blockchain-based marketplace.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These services range from simple speech or image generation to complex predictive model building and industry-specific solutions. Developers can even launch and monetize self-governing AI software that interacts with other aspects of the ALINK network.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ALINK also has a data marketplace built-in, where data can be bought, sold, and traded. Data providers can monetize their information by selling it to marketers, data analysts, research companies, etc. As the need for data to feed to AI solutions grows, ALINK will be ready to act as the intermediary between those with the data and those who need it to train their AI models.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform uses its native digital token, ALINK, as a medium of exchange in its marketplaces to raise money and incentivize its users to provide and improve ALINK&rsquo;s services. While AI tokens have yet to break into the mainstream crypto space, ALINK seems like a promising new cryptocurrency ready to pave the way. As such, it&rsquo;s one of the best crypto ICOs to invest in right now.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">6. Vivi (VIVI) &ndash; Decentralized Short-Form Video Sharing That Pays</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Vivi?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://vivi-tech.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Vivi</u></a> is a decentralized platform that allows creators to share short videos and earn rewards while offering viewers a way to monetize their time spent on social media. Using its decentralized structure, Vivi ensures its users&rsquo; privacy and security while promoting a fair distribution of rewards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Vivi is akin to a decentralized TikTok. Users can post short videos, like makeup or cooking tutorials, making it perfect for TikTok creators looking to move away from centralized social media platforms while maintaining their style.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the unique features of Vivi is the use of non-fungible token (NFT) glasses. Users get a free NFT glasses when signing up and can use them to earn VRV rewards. Users who continue to watch videos and interact on the platform gain VRV, which can be swapped for the platform&rsquo;s governance token, VIVI. VIVI enables users to upgrade their glasses to earn even more VRV for their watch time.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides the main Vivi app, there&rsquo;s also Vivi Live, Vive Spot, and Vivi Academy, which each serve a specific purpose in the live streaming, sports, and educational niches. With the potential to become Web3&rsquo;s go-to decentralized short video platform in the crypto industry, Vivi is certainly a token sale worth considering.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">7. OptionBlitz (BLX) &ndash; A Unique Decentralized Derivatives Trading Platform</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is OptionBlitz?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.optionblitz.co/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>OptionBlitz</u></a> is a decentralized trading platform built on the Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Arbitrum. It specializes in derivatives trading, particularly options trading. It uses Arbitrum to achieve fast transaction settlement times at virtually no cost to traders while maintaining complete decentralization. In its <a href="https://www.optionblitz.co/static/media/optionblitz_whitepaper.ce295a0d387dd3ce94b9.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>whitepaper</u></a>, OptionBlitz also promises zero slippage and zero spreads.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Like other decentralized trading platforms, OptionBlitz allows users to lock up their USDC in a liquidity pool to facilitate transactions for other traders in return for a share of the platform&rsquo;s revenue. OptionBlitz offers traders three distinct products: digital options, classic options, and Turbos, its flagship 200:1 leveraged offering that could be the next step in perpetual futures trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The markets it offers aren&rsquo;t just limited to crypto. Traders can access forex, commodity, and energy markets products, with pricing determined using the Chainlink decentralized oracle for maximum accuracy. Its options are incredibly flexible, with expiration times ranging from 10 seconds to 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Overall, OptionBlitz is setting itself apart from other ICOs with a tremendously innovative offering. Its potential to become the most advanced decentralized derivatives platform can&rsquo;t be understated, so it&rsquo;s one of the best crypto presales to buy right now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">8. ASTL (ASTL) &ndash; Raise Money and Generate Passive Income With ASTL</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is ASTL?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://astl.io/"><u>ASTL</u></a> is a passive income cryptocurrency project that aims to combine AI technology and crypto mining with helping its users generate returns well above what a bank will offer. ASTL uses a fleet of crypto miners, powered by green energy and optimized using AI, to mine the best tokens that maximize user profits.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Investors simply purchase their chosen number of ASTL tokens and then receive a reward in USDT proportional to their purchase. These returns can be as high as 11% APY, thanks to ASTL&rsquo;s mining diversification, and can be paid out daily if users purchase enough tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Effectively, when investors buy ASTL, they buy a portion of the computing power in the project&rsquo;s mining fleet. Unlike regular cloud mining services, the return from ASTL doesn&rsquo;t change depending on the current happenings in the crypto market; the primary difference is that it promises a stable return that won&rsquo;t fluctuate. With its token offering currently underway, ASTL is one to consider if you want to invest in a passive income-focused ICO.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">9. Kryptview (KVT) &ndash; Pioneering Research-To-Earn With a User-Friendly Platform</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Kryptview?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://kryptview.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Kryptview</u></a> is a blockchain-based platform that offers a unique approach to community research and insight-sharing on tokens and other cryptocurrencies. It employs a peer-to-peer model that rewards users for generating in-depth fundamental analysis of the latest cryptocurrencies. The data collected is automatically structured, then reviewed by the community, and posted to the platform for all users to take advantage of.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has built-in fundamental analysis tools that allow users to assign scores to various areas, like a cryptocurrency project&rsquo;s team, competition, sustainability, and community. The reviews generated by Kryptview users are then used to build an overall score for a given token, which provides an at-a-glance view of which cryptocurrency projects are worth picking up.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The reward model of Kryptview is simple but effective. Analysts are ranked based on the quality of their contributions, which allows them to earn more for sharing analysis as they rank up. Meanwhile, reviewers can earn KVT tokens for reviewing research and validating scores. Contributors can post portfolios and generate KVT if their picks outperform the market. As a result, its upcoming ICO is hotly anticipated by many prospective investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">10. Minima (WMINIMA) &ndash; A Mobile-Based Blockchain Focused on Freedom</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Minima?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.minima.global/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Minima</u></a> is one of the latest ICO projects to venture into the layer-1 crypto space. Its goal is to become the world&rsquo;s first fully decentralized network powered by mobile and Internet of Things (IoT) devices. Minima is designed to be accessible by as many participants as possible, meaning anyone with a mobile phone and an internet connection can run a Minima node.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Minima states its core purpose is to build a network that offers freedom to all who use it, where users can come together and create without restrictions or censorship. Like other leading layer-1 networks, it allows anyone to launch custom tokens, NFT projects, and decentralized applications (dApps). Minima also claims to have pending partnerships with companies in the automobile, telecommunications, and file-sharing industries.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While there are fees during periods of high demand on the network, these fees aren&rsquo;t burnt, meaning the tokens are removed from the hard-capped total token supply. This, in turn, makes MNIMA a deflationary token. Minima&rsquo;s presale is for Wrapped Minima, a version of MINIMA that can interface with the Ethereum network.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">11. Brickken (BKN) &ndash; Taking on Traditional Company Fundraising</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Brickken?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.brickken.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Brickken</u></a> is a blockchain-based platform that allows enterprises to tokenize their businesses and raise funds using security tokens. Its vision is to help global asset owners use a decentralized funding model, opening up income streams for companies and investors. Instead of going through an Initial Public Offering (IPO) and issuing stock, companies can undertake Security Token Offerings (STOs) to raise capital without intermediaries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Asset tokenization has been a hot topic amongst crypto investors in recent years. Brickken aims to provide the tools and technology to allow anyone to put their assets on the blockchain, bridging the gap between Web2 and Web3. This is especially important for small-and-medium enterprises (SMEs), which can often only raise funds from venture capitalists. Brickken opens up a world of opportunity for these SMEs, allowing them to tap the vast retail investor market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Brickken uses a proprietary dApp powered by smart contracts to issue and manage token securities while ensuring that every investor and securities issuer meets the regulatory requirements through stringent KYC and anti-money laundering checks. BKN, the project&rsquo;s native digital token, is fuel for Brikken&rsquo;s ecosystem, being used to invest in ongoing projects and issue STOs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">12. EasyFeedback (EASYF) &ndash; Rewarding Users for Their Feedback</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is EasyFeedback?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://easyfeedbacktoken.io/en/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>EasyFeedback</u></a> is a company using blockchain technology to create the world&rsquo;s first feedback-to-earn protocol. Established in 2015, EasyFeedback allows anyone to send suggestions, congratulations, questions, complaints, and claims to any business worldwide &ndash; for free! It offers a suite of templates that can be adapted to the individual company, with feedback sent directly to company heads.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the EASYF token, users sending feedback to companies or institutions can be rewarded based on the feedback&rsquo;s usefulness. These EASYF tokens can be exchanged for products, services, and gift cards in the EasyFeedback marketplace or held in crypto wallets for future gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those with relevant expertise can also become jurors, who evaluate the feedback and decide whether it&rsquo;s worth a reward. These jurors must undergo strict background checks to determine their knowledge and experience in their specialist sector and can earn EASYF tokens for validating feedback. EasyFeedback predicts that the use of its service will increase by 600% following the tokenization of its service, which could bode well for early investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">13. WeSendIt (WSI) &ndash; Established File Sharing Platform Venturing Into Web3</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is WeSendIt?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://wesendit.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>WeSendIt</u></a> is a file-sharing platform that, like AltSignals, has a reputation that precedes its entry into the crypto space. It&rsquo;s a Swiss company that emphasizes data protection and security while making large file transfers and storage simple. Now, WeSendIt is making its foray into Web3 with a custom-built decentralized solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">WeSendIt claims that, through decentralization, it can ensure its clients&rsquo; files stay 100% confidential while costing up to 80% less than regular cloud storage providers. Moreover, it says that data is stored redundantly across thousands of availability zones across the globe, meaning that the risk of losing data due to server failure is virtually eliminated.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Using the WSI digital coin means that users can achieve discounts on its Pro and Premium offers up to 60% cheaper than when paying via credit card or Paypal. Users can also earn WSI rewards for sending data. Finally, there&rsquo;s even a generous referral scheme that pays users in WSI to recruit more users into the ecosystem!</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">14. Mintera (MNTE) &ndash; A Green Project That Generates Passive Income</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Mintera?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://mintera.co/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Mintera</u></a> is a climate-friendly cryptocurrency project that uses blockchain technology to impact the environment positively. While it believes that the development of blockchain-based projects has a beneficial effect on society, Mintera sees a problem with the waste in the crypto space. As a result, it&rsquo;s building an ecosystem of sustainable products, billing itself as &ldquo;the green digital investment bank of the future.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the heart of the Mintera ecosystem is the MNTE token, which offers potential investors access to a net-positive range of green investment products, revenue streams, and perks. One of the most exciting aspects of Mintera is the Green Mining Yield (GMY), which promises to return a stablecoin yield to investors through its long-running green mining operation. Mintera mines <a href="https://www.chia.net/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chia</u></a>, which it terms an eco-friendly alternative to Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Yields depend on Chia&rsquo;s price, but Mintera claims to offer rates of anywhere between 5% and 100% per year. It also dedicates 50% of its profits to environmental organizations and stashes 6.5 million MNTE to fund green innovation. Overall, Mintera is an excellent choice for any ICO investor investing in a climate-positive project.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Buying Into an ICO</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What To Look For in an ICO</h3>
<p dir="ltr">So how do you determine which ICOs are worth investing in? Here&rsquo;s a comprehensive list of what to consider when identifying successful ICOs.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Legal Elements:</strong> Investors should ensure that the ICO complies with relevant regulations in its jurisdictions. Any potential legal risks should also be considered. Some tokens may be regarded as securities by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which could lead to scrutiny and legal action in the future.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Tokenomics:</strong> Evaluating the token economics in an initial coin offering is essential, including the token&rsquo;s supply, distribution, and use case. Pay special attention to how much of the token supply is allocated to the development team: too much or insufficient can be red flags. Around 5-15% is typical.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>White Paper:</strong> Reviewing the white paper is crucial in understanding the project&rsquo;s goals, technology, and roadmap. Assess whether the project has a clear and achievable roadmap with realistic timelines before investing in an initial coin offering.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Partnerships and Terms:</strong> It&rsquo;s a good idea to evaluate any partnerships or collaborations the ICO company has secured and the terms of those agreements. These partnerships can bring value to the project and help it grow.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Team and Advisors:</strong> Assessing the team behind cryptocurrency projects is essential, including their experience and credentials in their specialized industry. Investors should also consider any notable advisors that can bring value to the project.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Community and Engagement:</strong> Evaluating the project&rsquo;s community, including its engagement and support, is essential. A strong community can make all the difference in whether an ICO is successful or not.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 dir="ltr">How Do I Know When New Coins Are Launched?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Staying on top of the latest token sales in the fast-moving world of cryptocurrency and blockchain startups can be challenging. Fortunately, several resources are available that can help investors stay informed. One of the best places to start is on social media platforms such as Twitter and Reddit, where cryptocurrency enthusiasts and industry leaders often post news about new tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some coins are also launched exclusively on centralized exchanges through Initial Exchange Offerings (IEOs) or on decentralized exchanges with Initial Dex Offerings (IDOs). Lastly, there are many lists of active and upcoming ICOs out there. Search &ldquo;ICO list&rdquo; to find websites showcasing the latest token sales.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Advantages of Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs)</h3>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Quick Funding: ICOs provide blockchain startups with a relatively fast and cost-effective way to raise funds. Unlike traditional fundraising methods, like IPOs, ICOs allow private companies to reach a global audience of investors without the need for financial institutions. Blockchain startups can raise funds faster and with fewer restrictions, allowing them to focus on developing their products and growing their businesses.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Potentially High Returns: Since ICOs often involve investing in new and innovative technologies, investors can benefit from being early adopters of new products and services. This can lead to significant price appreciation in the new tokens they hold, translating to high returns on their initial investment.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Community: ICOs typically look to build up a community around their new coins, which can help create a loyal following and promote adopting their new technology. For investors, this can provide an opportunity to connect with like-minded crypto enthusiasts and join a growing community of supporters.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 dir="ltr">Disadvantages of Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs)</h3>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Lack of Regulation: ICOs are still a relatively new fundraising method, so they&rsquo;re largely unregulated. This can make it difficult for investors to assess the legitimacy of a project and opens up a realm of possibility for projects to misuse funds received or even commit outright fraud, often with little repercussion.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Volatility: ICOs are highly speculative investments. Their potential for returns is usually higher than more established projects, which also comes with increased risk. Like many startups, even the best ICOs may face significant challenges in achieving their goals, and the value of their tokens can fluctuate rapidly due to market conditions or unexpected developments.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Technical Risks: ICOs usually involve investing in new and untested technologies, which can present significant technical risks. These risks can include vulnerabilities to hacking or other security breaches and potential flaws or weaknesses in the underlying technology. This can lead to the loss of investor funds and damage the project&rsquo;s future prospects.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Related Crypto FAQs</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What are cryptocurrencies?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies are digital assets that are usually highly decentralized and operate independently of governments and financial institutions. The most valuable cryptocurrency is Bitcoin, which is generally seen as a store of value. The second largest cryptocurrency is Ethereum, which offers smart contracts that can perform incredibly versatile functions.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What does ICO mean?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ICO stands for Initial Coin Offering. It&rsquo;s a fundraising method blockchain startups use to raise capital by issuing digital currency, such as new tokens or coins, to investors in exchange for cryptocurrencies or fiat currency.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Are ICOs illegal?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ICOs are not inherently illegal, but most would face scrutiny under securities laws in many jurisdictions, including by regulators at the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in the US. This means ICOs must comply with relevant regulations to avoid legal issues with regulators.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Are ICO coins a good investment?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The potential return on investment for an ICO coin can be high, but it also comes with increased risk due to the lack of regulation and the potential for volatility. Picking the right ICO can be tricky, and an ICO coin&rsquo;s performance ultimately depends on many factors.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Where can I buy an initial coin offering crypto?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ICOs are usually bought directly from the startup itself or on ICO aggregator websites like Pinksale. Some ICOs take place on exchanges, where they&rsquo;re termed IEOs or IDOs.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What are the next big upcoming initial coin offerings in 2023?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s difficult to predict the next big ICO for 2023, as the market can be highly unpredictable. However, many of the tokens on this list have a strong chance of performing well, especially Chancer and Shiba Memu.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is the main difference between an ICO and an IPO?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The main difference between an ICO and an IPO is that an IPO is a traditional fundraising method established companies use to raise capital by issuing stocks to the public. In contrast, an ICO is used by startups to generate capital by issuing new tokens.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">What happens to an ICO&rsquo;s funds?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Money raised by an ICO is typically used to fund the development and growth of specific features within the project, including hiring developers and marketing the project. The particular use of funds will likely be outlined in the ICO project&rsquo;s white paper.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/initial-coin-offerings-ico-in-2023-what-are-the-best-crypto-icos-to-buy-now/">Initial Coin Offerings (ICO) in 2023. What Are the Best Crypto ICOs To Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash price moved to a bear market: Buy the dip?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-moved-to-a-bear-market-buy-the-dip/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-moved-to-a-bear-market-buy-the-dip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 16:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-moved-to-a-bear-market-buy-the-dip/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash price has moved to a bear market after falling by 22%. The coin has more short-term downside as it moves from the overbought zone. Some investors believe this is a good time to dollar cost average (DCA) Bitcoin Cash price has moved into a bear market as investors start taking profits after the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-moved-to-a-bear-market-buy-the-dip/">Bitcoin Cash price moved to a bear market: Buy the dip?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price has moved to a bear market after falling by 22%.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The coin has more short-term downside as it moves from the overbought zone.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Some investors believe this is a good time to dollar cost average (DCA)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a> price has moved into a bear market as investors start taking profits after the spectacular performance in June. The coin retreated to a low of $250 on Wednesday, about 22% below the highest level in June.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BCH enters a bear market</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash had one of the best period in June as investors moved to proof-of-work cryptocurrencies after the SEC lawsuit on Binance and Coinbase. Investors believe that coins like BCH, Verge, and Litecoin will benefit if the SEC decides to move to war against crypto tokens like Solana and Cardano.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price has now moved into a bear market by falling by over 20% from its highest level in June. This decline is mostly because of profit-taking since BTC was up by more than 250% between the lowest and highest points in June.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Historically, investors tend to exit an asset after rising sharply in a certain period. When it drops, the so-called Fear of Missing Out (FOMO) situation reverses and people who bought during the uptrend starts to exit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BCH price also retreated as&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> price struggled to move above the upper side of the bullish flag pattern that has been forming. BTC is hovering at $30,300 and there is a possibility that it will move below $30,000 soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, BCH also dropped as American stocks retreated after the Independence Day holiday. The Dow Jones index retreated by 50 points while the Nasdaq 100 fell by about 20 points.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688573247977-1d097c7b-0c53-4212-82b6-2d09f67c2e99.png" style="width: 688px;height: 335.369px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="688" height="335.369"></p>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, we see that the BCH price has retreated in the past few days. This retreat started after the coin moved to the extreme greed zone. The coin has now formed three black crows pattern, which happens when three red candles follow each other.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash remains much higher than the 50-day and 100-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) moved below the overbought level. Therefore, I suspect that Bitcoin Cash price has some more downside in the near term before making an eventual comeback.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This pullback will likely see it drop to the next key support at $210, which is the 25-day moving average. Therefore, dollar cost averaging, where a trader buys the coin as it drops could be a good idea since it will ultimately bounce back.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin Cash</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1MjEy&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BCH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    CEX.IO</h3>


<p>
    <a href="/visit/cex-crypto?guid=MTQ1MjEy&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BCH with CEX.IO today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-moved-to-a-bear-market-buy-the-dip/">Bitcoin Cash price moved to a bear market: Buy the dip?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-moved-to-a-bear-market-buy-the-dip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australian regulator searched Binance Australia&#8217;s offices</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-searched-binance-australias-offices/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-searched-binance-australias-offices/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-searched-binance-australias-offices/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Australian Securities and Investments Commission searched Binance Australia&#8217;s office on Tuesday. The cryptocurrency exchange maintains that it is focused on complying with rules.&#160; ASIC searched Binance Australia&#8217;s offices The offices of Binance Australia, the Australian arm of Binance, were searched on Tuesday by the country&#8217;s financial markets regulator. This&#160;latest cryptocurrency news comes as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-searched-binance-australias-offices/">Australian regulator searched Binance Australia&#8217;s offices</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Australian Securities and Investments Commission searched Binance Australia&rsquo;s office on Tuesday.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange maintains that it is focused on complying with rules.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">ASIC searched Binance Australia&rsquo;s offices</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The offices of Binance Australia, the Australian arm of Binance, were searched on Tuesday by the country&rsquo;s financial markets regulator.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes as governments around the world are scrutinising the cryptocurrency exchange&rsquo;s activities. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/binance-australia-offices-searched-by-regulator-as-part-of-derivatives-probe?" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bloomberg report</u></a>, the Australian Securities and Investments Commission searched several Binance Australia locations on Tuesday. The search was part of an ongoing investigation into the cryptocurrency exchange&rsquo;s now-defunct derivatives business, sources close to the matter revealed to Bloomberg.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance has been experiencing crackdowns from governments in Europe and the United States. Last month, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>US SEC sued Binance</u></a> and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, for breaking securities laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On June 22nd, Brazilian authorities revealed that they were&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-brazil-is-being-investigated-for-suspected-pyramid-schemes/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>investigating Binance</u></a> for suspected pyramid schemes. Binance is also being investigated for helping customers get around a restriction on crypto derivatives investments in Brazil.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A few days later,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance dropped its licence application</u></a> in Austria after the German regulators denied its application to operate in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">External pressure is hurting Binance, says CZ</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At a Twitter Space on Wednesday, Binance CEO, CZ, admitted that the external pressure is hurting the company. He stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Many of those things are outside of our control, but short term, they have negative impacts on our business.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the pressure, Binance remains the number one cryptocurrency exchange in the world. However, its global share of crypto spot trading fell for a fourth consecutive month in June. Data obtained from CCData showed that Binance now controls 42% of the global crypto spot trading volume, a 10-month low for the company.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ASIC investigation comes after Binance Australia announced in April that it would wind down the local derivatives exchange while keeping its spot platform open.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time, Binance said it closed the derivative positions of numerous Australian users because they were falsely classified as wholesale investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A spokesperson for ASIC stated that</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We are unable to confirm or deny any operational detail such as possible searches. ASIC&rsquo;s review of the company is ongoing.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange said it is working with local authorities, and its sole focus is to meet local regulatory standards in order to serve its Australian users in a fully compliant manner.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-searched-binance-australias-offices/">Australian regulator searched Binance Australia&#8217;s offices</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-searched-binance-australias-offices/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto spot trading volume rose 16% to $575 billion in June: CCData</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Derivatives]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Spot trading volume across centralised exchanges rose 16.4% to $575 billion in June, the first time volumes rose in three months. Derivatives trading volume on CEXs also rose, with the month seeing a 13.7% spike to $2.13 trillion. Binance saw a decline in both spot and derivatives volumes as OKX registered an increase. According to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/">Crypto spot trading volume rose 16% to $575 billion in June: CCData</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Spot trading volume across centralised exchanges rose 16.4% to $575 billion in June, the first time volumes rose in three months.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Derivatives trading volume on CEXs also rose, with the month seeing a 13.7% spike to $2.13 trillion.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance saw a decline in both spot and derivatives volumes as OKX registered an increase.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">According to the latest &ldquo;Exchange Review&rdquo;&nbsp;<a href="https://ccdata.io/reports/exchange-review-june-2023" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>report</u></a> by research and data platform CCData shows that the spot volumes jumped 16.4% to $575 billion in June as the crypto market experienced increased volatility over the month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the combined CEX volumes across spot and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/derivatives/">derivatives</a> markets hit $2.7 trillion. The monthly trading volume for the two metrics rose 14.2%, while it was 13.7% for derivatives as volumes hit $2.13 trillion &ndash; the first increase for derivatives trading volume in three months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> trading volumes in June rose for the first time in 3 months, following BlackRock &amp; other spot <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> ETF proposals.</p>
<p>&#128200;As per our Exchange Review, spot &amp; derivative trading on centralised exchanges rose 14% to $2.71tn.</p>
<p>Full Story by <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinDesk?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CoinDesk</a> &#128071;<a href="https://t.co/5OVY6fwE8c">https://t.co/5OVY6fwE8c</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CCData (@CCData_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/CCData_io/status/1676575783261708294?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Positive news fuel crypto trading activity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The spike in volatility was fueled by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&rsquo;s lawsuit against leading exchanges <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> and Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also key to this was the positivity that greeted the filing of spot Bitcoin exchange traded funds (ETFs) by major Wall Street asset managers BlackRock and Fidelity, and the launch of Citadel backed crypto exchange EDX Markets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The increase in the market share of spot trading volume hints at the healthy accumulation of crypto following recent positive news in the markets</em>,&rdquo;CCData researchers note in the report.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This outlook was indeed visible in the market. Increased trading activity saw Bitcoin price shoot to a new year-to-date high above $31k, while altcoins like Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash rode the optimistic outlook to break above critical resistance levels. [<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-surges-as-bch-hits-3-month-high-heres-why/">Read more</a>]</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s spot and derivatives volumes decline</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the above increases, the quarterly spot trading volumes on CEXs still hover near &ldquo;historically low levels.&rdquo; For instance, quarterly spot volumes for Q2, 2023 were the lowest since the fourth quarter of 2019.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also notably, the spot market share of Binance declined 41.6% in June to see the leading exchange record a fourth consecutive month of declines, and its lowest market share since August 2022. And although Binance continues to dominate the crypto derivatives trading market with $1.21 trillion, it fell 56.8% in June.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/">OKX</a>, which is the world&rsquo;s second-largest derivatives exchange, recorded a 44.9% increase in its trading volume to hit $416 billion in June. The crypto exchange&rsquo;s market share has now grown to 19.5%, its highest level since April 2022.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/">Crypto spot trading volume rose 16% to $575 billion in June: CCData</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-spot-trading-volume-rose-16-to-575-billion-in-june-ccdata/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saxo Bank ordered to dispose of crypto holdings by Denmark&#8217;s DFSA</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The DFSA ordered the Saxo Bank to dispose of its own holdings in crypto. The Financial regulators in Denmark have said that local banks are not allowed to hold crypto to hedge against trading risks. DFSA&#8217;s order concerning Saxo Bank&#8217;s crypto holdings will have little impact on the bank&#8217;s business. Local investment bank Saxo Bank [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/">Saxo Bank ordered to dispose of crypto holdings by Denmark&#8217;s DFSA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The DFSA ordered the Saxo Bank to dispose of its own holdings in crypto.</li>
<li>The Financial regulators in Denmark have said that local banks are not allowed to hold crypto to hedge against trading risks.</li>
<li>DFSA&rsquo;s order concerning Saxo Bank&rsquo;s crypto holdings will have little impact on the bank&rsquo;s business.</li>
</ul>
<p>Local investment bank Saxo Bank has received a formal order from the Danish Financial Supervisory Authority (DFSA) directing it to dispose of its own cryptocurrency holdings.</p>
<p>According to the regulator, Saxo Bank&rsquo;s cryptocurrency activity &ldquo;lies outside of the legal business area of financial institutions,&rdquo; citing section 24 of the Danish Financial Business Act.</p>
<h2>Cryptocurrency service providers in Denmark</h2>
<p>Danish financial regulators are going after cryptocurrency service providers, saying that local banks are not allowed to hold cryptocurrencies as a form of risk management.</p>
<p>Pinpointing why it singled out Saxo Bank, the DFSA claims that Saxo Bank gives its customers the option to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/">trade a variety of cryptocurrencies</a> on its platform. The regulator stated that the company also provides a number of exchange-traded funds and exchange-traded notes that are linked to cryptocurrencies, adding that &ldquo;it is possible to speculate on crypto assets.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The DFSA also noted that Saxo Bank has its own portfolio of bitcoin assets, which is kept as a hedge to counteract the market risk connected to the bank&rsquo;s cryptocurrency products. The regulator cited Annex 1 of the Financial Business Act in stating that dealing in crypto-assets does not appear to be under the lawful business scope of Danish financial institutions.</p>
<p>Based on the above reasons, the DFSA stated:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Based on the above, Saxo Bank&rsquo;s trading in crypto assets for its own account is found to be outside the legal business area of financial institutions. On this basis, Saxo Bank is ordered to dispose of its own holdings of crypto assets.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>It will be interesting to see how Saxo Bank will move ahead with its crypto offering seeing that their customers do not own underlying cryptocurrencies but instead buys financial products that follow the price of cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/">Saxo Bank ordered to dispose of crypto holdings by Denmark&#8217;s DFSA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/saxo-bank-ordered-to-dispose-of-crypto-holdings-by-denmarks-dfsa/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &#038; macro picture are ominous</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto prices are rising sharply, with Bitcoin up 20% in the last three weeks The filing of a number of high-profile Bitcoin ETFs has pushed optimism in the market Under the hood, liquidity remains low and some worrisome trends emerge, however The regulatory woes are still present, with Coinbase and Binance facing a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/">Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &amp; macro picture are ominous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto prices are rising sharply, with Bitcoin up 20% in the last three weeks</li>
<li dir="ltr">The filing of a number of high-profile Bitcoin ETFs has pushed optimism in the market</li>
<li dir="ltr">Under the hood, liquidity remains low and some worrisome trends emerge, however</li>
<li dir="ltr">The regulatory woes are still present, with Coinbase and Binance facing a murky future</li>
<li dir="ltr">The macro picture also remains uncertain, with the prospect of a lagged impact via tightening monetary policy looming large</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">It wouldn&rsquo;t be like crypto markets to get overly excited. In the past couple of weeks, positivity has returned to the space, led by the seminal filings for a Bitcoin spot ETF by two of the world&rsquo;s biggest asset managers, Blackrock and Fidelity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, Fidelity were among a cohort of large trad-fi operators, including Schwab and Citadel, to back the new exchange EDX, which offers trading for Bitcoin, Ether, Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is up 20% in the last three weeks, breaching past the $30,000 mark, while Ether is up 16% in the same timeframe, approaching the $2,000 mark once more. A glance at the <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/"><u>Fear and Greed</u></a> index, an interesting metric which gauges overall sentiment in the space, shows it is markedly in the &ldquo;greed&rdquo; sector with a score of 61 (0 represents extreme fear, 100 represents extreme greed).&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557574714-e61e6782-a3ef-4b4a-9f4f-a101fbbe3e8d.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="535">And yet, a look under the hood betrays some concern. Firstly, if the filing of the ETFs is the reason for the recent ramp, as it appears to be, is a 20% jump justified? The SEC has declared the recent filings as &ldquo;inadequate&rdquo;, according to the WSJ, informing the Nasdaq and CBOE (who filed the paperwork on behalf of the asset managers) that there is not enough detail with respect to &ldquo;surveillance-sharing agreements&rdquo;. The SEC had previously said that sponsors of a Bitcoin trust are required to enter into a surveillance-sharing agreement with a regulated market of significant size.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the applications can be updated and refiled (and the CBOE did indeed refile theirs since, with Nasdaq likely soon to follow) the development hints at how difficult it has been to get the much-coveted spot ETF over the line. There is no guarantee that these are approved, despite the big names involved &ndash; the SEC even rejected an application from Fidelity in the past, turning it away in January 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, it feels inevitable that Bitcoin spot ETFs will one day be traded freely, but a 20% jump on a mere filing in the last couple of weeks is a massive ramp when considering what else has happened in the space, and the state of markets, which we will delve into now.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Liquidity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Liquidity continues to lag, a factor which cannot be overstated &ndash; and indeed one which the eventual approval of spot ETFs should help.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at centralised exchanges per data from Kaiko as we close out the second quarter of 2023, volume over the past three months was lower again, coming in at the lowest number since 2020, before Bitcoin and crypto embarked on their inexorable price rises and took the financial world by storm.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557591169-492d05de-add9-47cf-86fa-47539ff38e28.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="324"></p>
<p dir="ltr">But with lower liquidity, moves to both the upside and downside are exacerbated. This has perhaps contributed to Bitcoin&rsquo;s steep rise in the past few weeks, and also year-to-date, with it currently up 83%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But liquidity and volumes being so low should be alarming for market participants. Much of the inroads made during the pandemic, with regard to Bitcoin taking its place next to bona-fide asset classes from a trading perspective, have slowed if not reversed &ndash; at least from a liquidity perspective.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As further evidence of this, in the below chart, I&rsquo;ve presented the total balance of stablecoins across exchanges, which has fallen a staggering 60% in the past six months &ndash; an outflow of $26 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14290288">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Having said that, there are pockets of optimism which hint at a brighter future if/when these spot ETFs do get approved. Looking at volume in derivatives markets, it has been rather consistent. In fact, it is markedly up on the second half of 2022. Perhaps this means the spot market has been greater affected by the regulatory crackdown. Either way, it&rsquo;s a less gruesome picture than what we are seeing in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/05/1688557591126-4dee794c-aab5-4225-8275-f59e55c418c3.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="327"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulation</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Right now, with regard to crypto-specific risk, it really all comes back to regulation. We have discussed the ETF filings, but June also brought two seminal moments: formal charges brought against Coinbase and Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The two cases are extremely different, mind you. Binance&rsquo;s lawsuit <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/"><u>could not be less surprising</u></a>, with the exchange constantly skirting guidelines and laws. The charges amount to a laundry list of different offences, including trading against customers, manipulating trade volume, encouraging users to circumvent geographical restrictions and securities violations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is the latter charge which is the centre of the suit against Coinbase, however, and the most pivotal of the lot. It is also why the Coinbase suit is <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-and-cryptos-fate-hangs-by-a-string-a-deep-dive/"><u>far more intriguing</u></a>. Do not forget that the allegations are coming from the SEC, the same body which presided over Coinbase&rsquo;s IPO in April 2021. Why did the SEC let an unregistered securities exchange float on a US stock exchange? You tell me.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But let&rsquo;s get back to the point: what this all means for crypto markets. While Bitcoin appears to be carving its own place out in the eyes of the law, a slew of other tokens were named as securities by the SEC. Despite this, they have risen sharply since off the Bitcoin ETF news. Does this make sense?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Conclusion</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the end of the day, crypto is going to crypto. Prices move, and trying to pinpoint reasons is often a fool&rsquo;s errand. The last month, however, feels like we have seen an extremely aggressive price rise despite some bad news on the regulatory front.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Additionally, the macro picture has not changed much, even with the pause at the last Fed meeting. Fed chair Jerome Powell&rsquo;s comments made it clear that this was a pause rather than an about-turn in policy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Looking ahead, nearly all committee participants view it as likely that some further rate increases will be appropriate this year,&rdquo; Powell said when announcing the pause.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The market believes him. I backed out probabilities from Fed futures in the next chart, which show that there is currently an 86% chance of a 25 bps hike at the next Fed meeting in three weeks time, with only a 14% chance of rates being left unchanged again. I have presented this next to the same probabilities conveyed by the market exactly a month ago (Bitcoin is up 20% in the time since), showing softer forecasts do not explain the sharp price (the chance of no hike has actually come down).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14349271">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">As I said, crypto going to crypto. But with assets as notoriously volatile as what we see in this sector, it would be wise to stop and think about whether the sudden wave of positivity is justified. When considering the liquidity picture and the regulatory trouble, there are plenty of reasons to hesitate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then when one layers in the macro picture, the picture becomes murkier again. Let us not forget that we are in the midst of one of the swiftest rate hiking cycles in modern history, with rates rising all the way from zero to above 5%, and the prospect of them rising even further later this month.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Monetary policy operates with a lag, and the scale of that tightening is enormous. Sentiment may feel like it has flipped dramatically, but there is a long road ahead yet.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/">Crypto prices rising and sentiment flipping but liquidity &amp; macro picture are ominous</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-prices-rising-and-sentiment-flipping-but-liquidity-macro-picture-are-ominous/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance suspends transfers for several Multichain-bridged tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance will cease deposit and withdrawals support for Multichain-bridged tokens Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH), Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) and Travala (AVA. The tokens are minted on BNB Smart Chain, Fantom, Ethereum and Avalanche C-Chain. The exchange says the suspension follows an earlier one taken in May after an incident involving Multichain-bridged tokens. Binance is suspending [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/">Binance suspends transfers for several Multichain-bridged tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance will cease deposit and withdrawals support for Multichain-bridged tokens Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH), Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) and Travala (AVA.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The tokens are minted on BNB Smart Chain, Fantom, Ethereum and Avalanche C-Chain.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The exchange says the suspension follows an earlier one taken in May after an incident involving Multichain-bridged tokens.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> is suspending deposits and withdrawals for several tokens linked to cross-chain router protocol Multichain, according to an <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/updates-on-the-suspension-of-deposits-withdrawals-for-multichain-bridged-tokens-3c7d279dd37043bd8290ac718b5c08a4" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> the crypto exchange published on Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto behemoth states that the suspension of the Multichain-bridged tokens will take effect on July 7 starting at 00:00 UTC and will last &ldquo;until further notice.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/multichain/">Multichain</a> was down nearly 6% in the past 24 hours and traded near $3.14 at the time of writing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> will suspend deposits and withdrawals for a number of Multichain-bridged tokens from July 7, 00:00 UTC until further notice.</p>
<p>More details here &#128071;<a href="https://t.co/CL7V8UeT9l">https://t.co/CL7V8UeT9l</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1676493768856305664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH) among affected tokens</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance says in the notice to users that the deposits and withdrawals pause will impact different networks, including BNB Smart Chain, Fantom, Ethereum and Avalanche C-Chain. In particular, Multichain-bridged tokens that users can no longer transfer via the above chains are:</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polkastarter (POLS), Alchemy Pay (ACH), and SuperVerse (SUPER) and Harvest Finance (FARM) on the BNB Smart Chain; Alpaca Finance (ALPACA) and Beefy.Finance (BIFI) tokens that are minted on Fantom Network; Spell Token (SPELL) on Avalanche C-Chain and Travala (AVA) on the Ethereum bridge.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although the Binance did not provide specific details on why its ceasing support for the above bridge tokens, it highlights that the move as related to the earlier suspension of several Multichain bridge tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On May 24, the crypto giant announced a temporary suspension to multiple tokens after an incident involving Multichain bridge transfers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While deposits and withdrawals for the above tokens are suspended on Binance via the listed chains, users can still access these transfers via other Binance-supported network, the exchange reiterated.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/">Binance suspends transfers for several Multichain-bridged tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-suspends-transfers-for-several-multichain-bridged-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AAVE hikes as holders vote on converting 1,600ETH into rETH and wstETH</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aave holders are voting on a governance proposal to convert 1,600 ether (ETH) to wstETH and rETH. Aave currently earns a yield of 1.69% from the ETH that it has staked on the Aave v2 platform. At press time all the 252,152 votes cast were in favor of the proposal. AAVE&#8217;s Bull Run has gained [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/">AAVE hikes as holders vote on converting 1,600ETH into rETH and wstETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Aave holders are voting on a governance proposal to convert 1,600 ether (ETH) to wstETH and rETH.</li>
<li>Aave currently earns a yield of 1.69% from the ETH that it has staked on the Aave v2 platform.</li>
<li>At press time all the 252,152 votes cast were in favor of the proposal.</li>
</ul>
<p>AAVE&rsquo;s Bull Run has gained momentum as AAVE holders vote on a governance proposal titled &ldquo;<a href="https://app.aave.com/governance/proposal/?proposalId=261">Treasury Managemet &ndash; Acquire wstETH &amp; rETH</a>.&rdquo; The proposal seeks to convert 1,600 ETH to equal amounts of wstETH and rETH to be held in the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> Collector Contract.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/">AAVE token</a> has gained in excess of 26% in the last seven days and today&rsquo;s surge confirms a long-term bullish trend. The token has hit a daily high of $80.28 today although it had pulled back to $76.92 at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Why convert the ETH to wstETH and rETH?</h2>
<p>The majority of the Aave DAO seems to be in agreement seeing that all the voters had voted in support of the proposal at press time. 252,152 votes have been cast so far out of the 320,000 votes required for the proposal to be actioned. But what is the catch?</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/aave/what-is-aave/">Aave</a> is currently the third-largest DeFi protocol and has a total value locked of $6 billion. The Aave DAO currently holds 1,786.51 awETH and 104.548 ETH in the Collector Contract. The awETH deposit yield in Aave v2 earns 1.69%, compared to the 3.8% and 3.13% that Aave DAO would earn if it held wstETH and rETH respectively.</p>
<p>If passed all the unproductive ETH balance, along with aWETH (v2 and v3) will be converted into the same amounts of wstETH and rETH for higher staking yields.</p>
<p>Besides the higher yields, the wrapped staked ether (wstETH) and rocket pool ether (rETH), which are liquid staking derivatives, will allow Aave to stake the tokens for a yield whilst still retaining liquidity.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/">AAVE hikes as holders vote on converting 1,600ETH into rETH and wstETH</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/aave-hikes-as-holders-vote-on-converting-1600eth-into-reth-and-wsteth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
