<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:53:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skybridge Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
<p>Scaramucci highlights the importance of patience when considering Nvidia as an investment opportunity.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
<p>Investing in Artificial Intelligence (AI) stocks has become increasingly popular as the technology continues to reshape industries. However, concerns about a potential bubble in the AI industry have emerged. In a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-30/scaramucci-says-ai-stocks-are-a-bubble-but-buy-them-anyway#:~:text=%E2%80%9CThere%20are%20boom%2Dbust%20cycles,'ll%20probably%20be%20OK.%E2%80%9D" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Anthony Scaramucci, the Founder of SkyBridge Capital, advised AI stock investors to concentrate on long-term investments amidst these concerns.</p>
<p>He highlights the presence of high-quality AI companies that offer long-term value to investors. While some AI stocks may be overvalued in the short term, Scaramucci emphasizes that owning them over an extended period could still yield favorable returns.</p>
<p>Scaramucci used <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corp</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA), a major leader in the AI industry, as an example. Notably, Nvidia has established itself as a prominent participant in the AI market, supplying sophisticated Graphics Processing Units (GPUs) and other hardware solutions critical for AI training and inference.</p>
<p>He believes Nvidia is currently overvalued, which aligns with concerns about the current condition of the AI market. However, Scaramucci adds that owning Nvidia stock for the next 15 years could still prove to be a profitable decision.</p>
<p>According to reports, Nvidia has witnessed an astounding surge in its share price this year. With investors banking on its essential role in the advancement of AI, Nvidia&#8217;s shares have soared by 179% in 2023 and are trading at 53 times analysts&#8217; estimates of adjusted earnings for the current fiscal year.</p>
<p>Despite the seemingly high valuation, Scaramucci highlights the importance of patience when considering Nvidia as an investment opportunity. Drawing parallels to early internet winners, Scaramucci reminds investors that long-term success often requires perseverance.</p>
<h2>Besides AI: Anthony Scaramucci Nursing Losses</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, Scaramucci&#8217;s SkyBridge Capital has faced significant challenges in 2022 due to its investment positions in crypto and exposure to the now-bankrupt platform FTX Derivatives Exchange. According to previous reports, SkyBridge&#8217;s largest fund lost 39% at the time, prompting the establishment of new withdrawal limits for clients.</p>
<p>SkyBridge Capital was one of the trading firm&#8217;s early supporters and one of the hardest-hit venture capital firms when the platform crumbled last year. In a previous <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-capital-founder-scaramucci-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Scaramucci stated that the failure of FTX had harmed his reputation. He stated this in part because he considered himself Sam Bankman-Fried’s friend.</p>
<p>Despite the betrayals and fund losses, Scaramucci stated that he will continue to take chances in the digital currency ecosystem because he believes in the blockchain technology that is fueling the broader sector. Additionally, Scaramucci reflects on the nature of short-term losses, emphasizing the importance of maintaining a long-term perspective as an investor.</p>
<p>Overall, SkyBridge Capital&#8217;s experience offers valuable lessons, emphasizing the importance of diversification, diligent research, risk management, patience, and adaptability. By understanding the nature of investment cycles and maintaining a long-term perspective, investors can navigate short-term losses and position themselves for potential long-term success.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/">Anthony Scaramucci to AI Backers: Bet on Long-Term Investments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/anthony-scaramucci-ai-investments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[upbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261183</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
<p>Since BCH became one of the four cryptocurrencies traded on EDX, its price has continued to rise. In the last 24 hours, the crypto has spiked more than 30%, reaching $325 for the first time since April 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a> (BCH) is experiencing a major increase in price and trading volume due to different reasons. One of the significant factors that have been said to affect its price is that Fidelity, Charles Schwab, and Citadel-backed EDX Markets introduced BCH as part of the assets available for trading on their platform on June 20 at its launch.</p>
<p>EDX Markets only made four cryptocurrencies available for trading when the exchange was launched. The cryptos are Bitcoin, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a>, Ethereum, and Litecoin. According to Jamil Nazarali, CEO of EDX Markets, as reported by <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/30/bitcoin-cash-tops-300-amid-surge-in-trading-volumes-in-south-korea/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Coindesk</a>, this was done because they are believed to be, to a great extent, safe cryptocurrencies, and they are also compliant with US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) regulations.</p>
<p>Lawrence Lewitinn, The Tie&#8217;s Director of Content, stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Nazarali explained that they felt confident that Litecoin and Bitcoin Cash, as derivatives of bitcoin, were not securities. While there is some interest, it is not substantial.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Some have also said the price rise could be due to the hard fork upgrade that the cryptocurrency recently went through. However, since the hard fork got completed in mid-May, and the significant price rise didn&#8217;t start till June 20, it couldn&#8217;t have been the leading cause. Nevertheless, we cannot deny that it can increase the attention given to BCH as the fork improved its network security and privacy measures.</p>
<p>Since BCH became one of the four cryptocurrencies traded on EDX, its price has continued to rise. In the last 24 hours, the crypto has spiked more than 30%, reaching $325 for the first time since April 2022. Overall, BCH&#8217;s price has risen by 150%, from $106 on June 20 to $325 today.</p>
<h2>Rise in Bitcoin Cash Trading Volume among South Korean Users of Upbit</h2>
<p>Another factor pushing the price upward is an increase in trading volume in South Korea. As more people trade BCH, its demand increases, thereby pushing the price up.</p>
<p>There is a large BCH trading volume in South Korea, as can be seen from the data by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/upbit" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CoinGecko</a> on BCH trading volume on Upbit, one of the popular exchanges in South Korea. Coingecko revealed that the Bitcoin Cash-Korean Won (BCH/KRW) pair on Upbit had a trading volume of $658.25 million in the last 24 hours. Which is more than three times bigger than the $166.93 million volume that the Bitcoin-Korean won (BTC/KRW) pair has on the exchange.</p>
<p>Considering all the points above, we can conclude that the significant rise in the price of BCH is a result of different factors like introducing the asset on the EDX exchange, which increased its trading volume, and the increased demand for Bitcoin Cash among South Korean users of Upbit.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/">Bitcoin Cash Surges to Over 1-Year High amid Rising Trading Volume in South Korea</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-south-korea/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salesforce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[typeface]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
<p>The funding round conducted only a few months after its public launch puts Typeface in fierce competition with similar tools.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
<p>Typeface, a generative artificial intelligence (AI) content creation platform for enterprises, announced it has concluded a Series B funding round. Typeface received $100 million in funding from a round led by Salesforce Ventures, the arm of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/salesforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Salesforce Inc</a> (NYSE: CRM) that provides funding, support, and mentorship to startups. The round brings Typeface’s total funding to $165 million and puts the company’s valuation at $1 billion.</p>
<p>Other participants in the funding round include Google Ventures, the M12 venture fund from Microsoft, Madrona, Menlo Ventures, and Lightspeed Venture Partners.</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/typeface-announces-100m-in-new-funding-to-fuel-global-expansion-of-its-personalized-generative-ai-platform-for-enterprises-301866644.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official release</a>, Typeface founder and CEO Abhay Parasnis said the company provides businesses with “enterprise-ready solutions” to adequately harness the transformative power of AI for content creation. According to Parasnis, “by combining the strengths of generative AI platforms with our brand-specialized knowledge, we have eliminated the barriers for enterprises to harness generative AI. Typeface empowers every enterprise to create high-quality, personalized content that aligns with its unique voice.”</p>
<p>Parasnis, a former Adobe CTO, founded Typeface in June 2022, along with former personnel from Microsoft and Meta. Typeface launched publicly in February and has garnered interest from several companies, including LG Electronics, one of Typeface’s customers. The platform integrates several AI tools into its business, including OpenAI’s GPT-4, Google Vertex AI, Microsoft Azure AI, and Stable Diffusion.</p>
<h2>Typeface Partnerships Before Funding Round</h2>
<p>Typeface successfully secured two major partnerships with tech giants. Google Cloud and Typeface announced a partnership to scale its AI content for businesses. A <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/typeface-and-google-cloud-announce-strategic-partnership-to-provide-ai-generated-personalized-content-at-scale-for-enterprises-worldwide-301844358.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> explained that Typeface will integrate Google Cloud’s large language models (LLMs) and launch a Google Workspace Marketplace plugin. Businesses can use the plugin to create quick, customized, compelling content for use across different channels.</p>
<p>Last week, Typeface <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/typeface-and-salesforce-partner-to-bring-personalized-generative-ai-capabilities-into-salesforce-marketing-gpt-301856067.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> another partnership with Salesforce. The partnership integrates Typeface’s AI tools with the Salesforce Marketing GPT to provide customers with customized content. Marketers will be able to use their own brand, messaging, and style guides to create engaging and creative content to drive productivity.</p>
<h2>How Does Typeface Work?</h2>
<p>Parasnis <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/06/29/typeface-which-is-building-generative-ai-for-brands-raises-100m-at-a-1b-valuation/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a> to TechCrunch that Typeface functions with three major components. The first is a content hub that applies guidelines the user provides for content (text and image) generation. Typeface also has the Blend tool, which uses AI to customize the user’s content to a particular brand’s style or voice. Finally, Parasnis explains Flow, a tool offering users various workflows and templates they can install with existing programs for on-brand content creation.</p>
<p>Speaking on the need for Typeface, Parasnis said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Enterprise leaders are telling us across the board that they want to embrace generative AI, but they need a solution that meets their unique requirements and is ready for the enterprise.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Specific Typeface use may include helping a marketer create an Instagram post, including an image and a caption. The user can specify specific brand wording and imagery to launch a product or advertise a feature based on the brand’s image and style.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/">Typeface Valued at $1B Following $100M Series B Funding from Salesforce, Microsoft, Google</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/typeface-1b-100m-series-b-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261167</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
<p>Google said the decision by Canada exposes the company to “uncapped financial liability”.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) is removing all Canada news links from its search due to a new <a href="https://www.parl.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/bill/C-18/third-reading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Online News Act</a>. The tech giant said it would block all Canadian news, meaning users will no longer find any report linked to the country on the search engine. The decision was in response to a new law that required tech companies to pay media outlets for content.</p>
<p>Last week, the Canadian government’s controversial C-18 legislation in Canada passed parliament despite Google noting that it was “unworkable”. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> (NASDAQ: META) also criticized the bill on the grounds that it was unfair to impose compensation on tech companies. Google and Meta have been battling with the government over the law forcing them to pay media outlets in Canada for distributing links to news stories. The Canadian government explained that the legislation is to offer fair compensation to struggling news outlets. The officials also emphasized the need “to enhance fairness in the Canadian digital news market”. The bill supporters wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Digital platforms and social media are now the gateways where people find, read and share news. Because of this, advertising revenues have shifted away from local news and journalists to these gatekeepers, who profit from the sharing and distribution of Canadian news content.”</p></blockquote>
<p>There is a prediction that the law could generate up to $329 million for the Canadian news industry. Although the Online News Act has already been passed in Canada, it would take months to take effect. When it does, Google has already decided to remove links to “Canadian news from our Search, News, and Discover products and will no longer be able to operate Google News Showcase in Canada”.</p>
<h2>Google Will Block All Canada News Links</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://blog.google/intl/en-ca/company-news/outreach-initiatives/an-update-on-canadas-bill-c-18-and-our-search-and-news-products/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">news blog</a>, Google said the decision by Canada exposes the company to “uncapped financial liability”. It reiterated that it is not the proper approach and could impact its products. According to the tech giant, it contributed to Canadian journalism via programs and partnerships and is willing to do more. Google revealed linking to Canadian news publications over 3.6 billion times last year at no charge. According to the company, it helped publishers generate profits via ads and new subscriptions without expecting anything in return. Despite the willingness to do more, the multinational technology company said it will not be able to do that “in a way that breaks the way that the web and search engines are designed to work, and that creates untenable product and financial uncertainty”.</p>
<p>Canadian minister Pablo Rodriguez was surprised by Google’s decision to remove all Canadian links from its platform. The politician said they still had a conversion with the tech company shortly before. Google also confirmed that it discussed with the government where it requested clarity on financial expectations. Google seemed to be dissatisfied with the chat with Canada officials, as it announced removing the links not long after the meeting.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/">Google Says It Will Remove All News Links in Canada in Response to Online News Act</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-news-links-canada/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261162</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
<p>The UK government wants to adopt the nascent crypto asset industry to enable exponential growth to its economy away from the Brussels shackles.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
<p>Having successfully secured its independence from the European Union through Brexit, the United Kingdom (UK) continues to reorganize its internal policies to attract international investors and streamline bilateral trade. In the latest developments under the leadership of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, the UK government announced the Financial Services and Markets Act 2023 was granted Royal Assent on Thursday. Under the economic legislation, the UK government passed to safely adopt the crypto assets.</p>
<p>The move comes after the European Union recently passed a comprehensive crypto adoption framework dubbed Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation.</p>
<p>According to Economic Secretary to the Treasury, Andrew Griffith, the country is keen to reform its financial laws to accommodate the fast-growing trillion-dollar market in a regulated manner.</p>
<p>“This landmark piece of legislation gives us control of our financial services rulebook, so it supports UK businesses and consumers and drives growth. By repealing old EU laws set in Brussels it will unlock billions in investment – cash that can unlock innovation and grow the economy,” Griffith <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/rocket-boost-for-uk-economy-as-financial-services-and-markets-bill-receives-royal-assent" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The United Kingdom wants to become a stronghold for IPOs as more companies reach global markets through the use of technologies like blockchain and artificial intelligence (AI). The country wants to unlock a £100 billion market through the Financial Services and Markets Act 2023 with the help of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>“Today’s ground-breaking Act also establishes ‘sandboxes’ that can facilitate the use of new technologies such as blockchain in financial markets,” the announcement noted.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at UK and Crypto Market</h2>
<p>With London being a strategic financial hub, the United Kingdom has attracted significant investors especially those fleeing hostile regulatory scrutiny in the United States. In the past few months, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> has visited the country and made several official meetings with Griffith.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Great meeting today with UK Economic Secretary and City Minister <a href="https://twitter.com/griffitha?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@griffitha</a>.</p>
<p>The UK is moving fast on sensible crypto regulation to both drive economic growth AND consumer protection. Excited to keep investing in the UK. 🇬🇧 <a href="https://t.co/478PQSLmDe">pic.twitter.com/478PQSLmDe</a></p>
<p>— Brian Armstrong 🛡️ (@brian_armstrong) <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1648013189437595909?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>However, Armstrong pointed out that some UK-based banks are blocking fiat payments to crypto companies, which has been a huge impediment to mainstream adoption in the country. Nonetheless, Armstrong insisted that the company will continue investing in the country amid positive crypto-focused policies.</p>
<p>Similarly, crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> has made a significant entrance into the UK market amid hostile developments in the United States. According to the Winklevoss twins, the UK is well slated to be a Web3 hub in the near future.</p>
<p>According to PM Sunak, the UK is implementing various plans to become a crypto asset hub. As the Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>) narrows down to the CBDC rollout, the country remains receptive to the stablecoin market. Additionally, the FCA-led ‘CryptoSprint’ continues to work with the Royal Mint on an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>, establishing a Crypto Asset Engagement Group.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/">UK Passes Legislation to Support Safe Adoption of Crypto Assets Post Brexit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-passes-legislation-crypto-brexit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[didi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shein ipo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
<p>Even if the IPO rumors were true and Shein wanted to list in the US, the company would need to clear the air about environmental, social, and governance concerns.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
<p>Fast-rising Chinese fashion giant Shein has denied the widespread rumors that it has filed for an initial public offering (IPO) in the US. Rumors had it that the company was planning to go public in the US before the end of the year. At the time, A Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/shein-ipo/exclusive-chinas-shein-files-for-u-s-ipo-sources-idUKL4N38L313" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> said Shein was considering the New York Stock Exchange (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nyse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NYSE</a>) for its IPO, but market volatility caused by the Russia-Ukraine war made it suspend its plans. The report cited people with knowledge of the matter and added that the listing could make Shein the most valuable Chinese company to go public in the US since Didi’s IPO in 2021.</p>
<h2>Shein Turns Down Alleged US IPO Filing</h2>
<p>However, a Shein spokesperson told CNBC:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Shein denies these rumors.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This comes shortly after it was accused of exploiting trade loopholes to import goods into the US. A committee exploring economic competition between China and the US, The Select Committee on the CCP, released a <a href="https://selectcommitteeontheccp.house.gov/sites/evo-subsites/selectcommitteeontheccp.house.gov/files/evo-media-document/fast-fashion-and-the-uyghur-genocide-interim-findings.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> saying that the Chinese fast fashion retailer and Temu did not pay import fees in 2022. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/committeeonccp/status/1672239571147390976?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1672233037864525824%7Ctwgr%5Ee3ff8ead16e211ec869512f02014c556f5ed874d%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnbc.com%2F2023%2F06%2F30%2Fshein-denies-us-ipo-rumors.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>, the Committee wrote that the companies avoid tax and inspection by the US Customs and Border Protection, “making it impossible to determine if their products are made with Uyghur forced labor in Xinjiang.”</p>
<p>According to the report, both Shein and Temu are responsible for more than 30% of daily shipped packages to the US. The brands process this under the minimis provision of Section 321 of the Tariff Act of 1930. This helps them avoid import tariffs if the fair retail value of the shipment is not over $800. Per the findings, the import accounted for almost 600,000 shipments daily in 2022, which means that it could be higher this year. Hence, lawmakers opined that the tariff violations unfairly placed Shein and Temu over US retailers. While Temu’s valuation is said to be over $100 billion, Shein was recently valued at $64 billion.</p>
<h2>Shein&#8217;s Allegations</h2>
<p>Before denying <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/e-retailer-shein-us-ipo-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US IPO plans</a>, Shein was accused of human rights abuses. The company faces allegations over forced labor of its supplier factories in the Uyghur region. Even if the IPO rumors were true and Shein wanted to list in the US, the company would need to clear the air about environmental, social, and governance concerns. There have been <a href="https://www.businessoffashion.com/news/retail/report-shein-violating-labour-laws/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">ill reports</a>, including allegedly poor working conditions.</p>
<p>Many said the Chinese company was violating labor laws and slaving away employees. An investigation found that employees in some Shein partner factories worked 12 to 14 hours daily with only 24 hours off every month. Meanwhile, Chinese labor laws say workweeks cannot be more than 40 hours, and overtime should not exceed 36 hours monthly. Also, workers are entitled to one day off every week under the law.</p>
<p>However, a Shein representative told CNBC in May:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have zero tolerance for forced labor.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite dismissing the US IPO news, many believe that Shein will eventually list in the US sometime.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/">Shein Denies US IPO Rumors</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shein-denies-us-ipo-rumors/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skybridge Founder Anthony Scaramucci Says Increased Regulatory in US Stems from SBF’s Actions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/">Skybridge Founder Anthony Scaramucci Says Increased Regulatory in US Stems from SBF’s Actions</a></p>
<p>When providing his opinion on the regulatory environment for cryptocurrencies in Canada compared to the United States, Anthony Scaramucci stated that Canada had learned from the US.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/">Skybridge Founder Anthony Scaramucci Says Increased Regulatory in US Stems from SBF’s Actions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/">Skybridge Founder Anthony Scaramucci Says Increased Regulatory in US Stems from SBF’s Actions</a></p>
<p>Anthony Scaramucci, Skybridge Capital’s founder, <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-really-hurt-the-industry-anthony-scaramucci" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">voiced</a> his opinion on the increased regulatory environment in the United States, attributing it to the actions of crypto executive Sam Bankman-Fried (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBF</a>).</p>
<h2>Skybridge Founder and His Opinion on SBF</h2>
<p>While speaking at a panel discussion at Collision 2023 in Toronto, Scaramucci acknowledged Bankman-Fried&#8217;s entrepreneurial success. However, he contended that the controversial executive had caused harm to the crypto industry in the United States, particularly from a regulatory perspective.</p>
<p>Scaramucci went on to express his views on the relationship between Bankman-Fried and politicians, including regulatory authorities like Gary Gensler, the chairman of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC).</p>
<p>Scaramucci argued that Bankman-Fried&#8217;s financial contributions and close connections with politicians created a situation in which the distinctions between industry interests and regulatory scrutiny may have been blurred. According to Scaramucci, the aftermath of the collapse of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX Derivatives Exchange</a> has led to what he perceives as over-regulation and “ridiculous prosecutorial oversight” within the industry.</p>
<p>He argued that the pendulum has swung too far, suggesting that the current regulatory landscape may be excessively burdensome, potentially stifling innovation and hindering the growth of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Notably, Scaramucci’s comments suggest that the negative consequences of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s conduct have rippled beyond his own ventures, impacting the broader industry&#8217;s perception and regulatory treatment.</p>
<h2>United States vs. Canada’s Regulatory Landscape</h2>
<p>When providing his opinion on the regulatory environment for cryptocurrencies in Canada compared to the United States, Anthony Scaramucci stated that Canada had learned from the United States and set up its regulatory framework in a manner reminiscent of how things were previously done in the US.</p>
<p>Scaramucci claims Canada took a proactive approach by engaging with industry players to seek input on how to regulate the crypto industry fairly and protect against illicit activities. This collaborative approach involved close cooperation between industry participants and legislators, with both sides working together to establish the guidelines.</p>
<p>Scaramucci&#8217;s words imply that Canada&#8217;s collaborative approach to regulatory activities differs from the current regulatory landscape in the United States. The implication is that the US may have transitioned to a more top-down regulatory approach that is perceived as less inclusive of industry input.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Scaramucci shifted his attention to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng Zhao</a>, the CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>. Specifically, he stated that Zhao could potentially emerge as a key figure in shaping the future of crypto exchanges, particularly in light of the collapse of FTX.</p>
<p>In assessing Zhao’s performance as the CEO of Binance, Scaramucci noted Binance&#8217;s success in terms of execution and growth, claiming that it commands a considerable share (about 65%) of the global crypto market. Scaramucci gives CZ an “A” for these achievements.</p>
<p>However, Scaramucci also mentioned that CZ might receive a &#8220;C+&#8221; or &#8220;B&#8221; grade in terms of transparency. This assessment is probably due to Binance’s ongoing <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-legal-team-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">issues</a> with the US SEC.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/">Skybridge Founder Anthony Scaramucci Says Increased Regulatory in US Stems from SBF’s Actions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/skybridge-founder-us-sbf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inflection AI Completes $1.3B Funding Round, Aims to Develop One of World’s Largest AI Models</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bill gates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflection ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/">Inflection AI Completes $1.3B Funding Round, Aims to Develop One of World&#8217;s Largest AI Models</a></p>
<p>In early 2022, Inflection AI raised $225 million in a first round of funding.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/">Inflection AI Completes $1.3B Funding Round, Aims to Develop One of World&#8217;s Largest AI Models</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/">Inflection AI Completes $1.3B Funding Round, Aims to Develop One of World&#8217;s Largest AI Models</a></p>
<p>Inflection AI may have just completed a $1.3 billion funding round, according to a Thursday <a href="https://inflection.ai/inflection-ai-announces-1-3-billion-of-funding" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> published by the company. The round was led by previous investors <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a>, Reid Hoffman, Bill Gates, and Eric Schmidt, while Nvidia also participated in the round as a new investor.</p>
<p>In early 2022, Inflection AI raised $225 million in the first round of funding.  So, by raising $1.3 billion, Inflection AI has now raised a total of $1.525 billion since it launched in 2022.</p>
<h2>Inflection AI Earmarks Funds for Personal AI Development</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the Palo Alto-based firm has already revealed its plans for the newly-raised fund. According to the firm, a portion of the new capital will be focused on building a 22,000-unit Nvidia H100 Tensor GPU cluster – the largest in the world. And to the firm&#8217;s estimations, these GPUs will help it to build large-scale artificial intelligence models.</p>
<p>The team of developers at Inflection AI is also quite optimistic about the GPU cluster. They wrote in part:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We estimate that if we entered our cluster in the recent TOP500 list of supercomputers, it would be the 2nd and close to the top entry.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the company is also looking to use the remaining portion of the fund to continue the ongoing work on its first product, the adjutant AI system called “Pi&#8221;.</p>
<p>Pi, according to Inflection, is an unusual kind of personal AI. It is &#8220;designed to be a kind and supportive companion offering text and voice conversations, friendly advice, and concise information&#8221;. The firm even says Pi may be accessed directly via social media or WhatsApp.</p>
<p>CEO and co-founder of Inflection, AI Mustafa Suleyman, has also hailed the participation of Microsoft and other investors. He acknowledges that personal AI has the potential to become the most transformational tool of this generation, and is full of optimism for the lengths that the new fund could take the firm. About the newly raised fund, Suleyman said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re excited to collaborate with NVIDIA, Microsoft, and CoreWeave as well as Eric, Bill and many others to bring this vision to life.”</p></blockquote>
<p>You can find other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tech-related news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/">Inflection AI Completes $1.3B Funding Round, Aims to Develop One of World&#8217;s Largest AI Models</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/inflection-ai-1-3b-funding-round/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bed bath beoynd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overstock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[overstock.com]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
<p>Overstock said that it will start operating under the domain of Bedbathandbeyond.com, which offer greater brand awareness and recognition.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, June 29, the price of Overstock.com (NASDAQ: OSTK) shares skyrocketed by 20% and closed the day at $30.57. This happened the day after Overstock announced that it plans to change its website name to Bed, Bath and Beyond.</p>
<p>Overstock.com had paid a sum total of $21.5 million for using the brand Bed, Bath and Beyond, after it filed for bankruptcy in April. The E-commerce retailer announced that it shall stop using its official website and rather operate under the domain of Bedbathandbeyond.com.</p>
<p>This news comes after the federal bankruptcy court approved Overstock&#8217;s demand of taking over the intellectual property assets of Bed Bath &amp; Beyond. Note that this deal doesn&#8217;t include the physical stores of BB&amp;B, which would be closing pretty soon.</p>
<p>Jonathan Johnson, the CEO of Overstock, expressed that the company&#8217;s current product offerings are no longer aligned with its previous liquidation-focused model, and as a result, the name &#8220;Overstock&#8221; no longer accurately represents the nature of the business. Speaking to CNBC&#8217;s The Exchange, he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/29/overstock-shares-spike-after-company-announces-website-rebrand-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We started out 20-plus years ago as a liquidator and became a general merchandiser. Now we’re a home furnishings and furniture company and there [were] a lot of headwinds with the name Overstock, headwinds with customers who were confused who we were and what we were selling, headwinds with suppliers that didn’t want to necessarily sell if it was associated with liquidation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>BB&amp;B Has Strong Brand Awareness and Recall</h2>
<p>Johnson believes that despite the collapse this year and eventual bankruptcy, Bed Bath &amp; Beyond offers a strong brand awareness in the market. He added that both Overstock and BB&amp;B has overlapping customers which will help make the transition smoother.</p>
<p>Johnson added:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’ll do this transition slowly where the Overstock customer will come to the new website and will recognize it, but so will the Bed Bath &amp; Beyond customer. And then over time, we’ll sunset out the Overstock feel.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>During a recent call with analysts, Johnson assured shoppers that Bed Bath &amp; Beyond&#8217;s renowned coupons will continue to be available, at least for a transitional period. However, he also mentioned that the company intends to reduce the frequency and depth of discounts in the long run.</p>
<p>“One thing that Bed Bath &amp; Beyond customers will realize is that our non-coupon price is really good. And I think people will be very surprised with the deals that Overstock and now Bed Bath &amp; Beyond is able to offer and has been offered,” he said.</p>
<p>The relaunch of the Bed, Bath &amp; Beyond website shall happen in Canada by the next week. Later in the coming weeks, there will be a subsequent rollout of a website, mobile app, and loyalty program in the US.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/">Shares of Overstock.com (OSTK) Jump 20% after Announcing Rebrand for Bed Bath and Beyond</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-overstock-ostk-bed-bath-and-beyond/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cme group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
<p>The settlement of the ETH/BTC ratio futures will be linked to the value of CME Group Ether futures final settlement price, divided by the corresponding CME Group Bitcoin futures final settlement price.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, June 29, the world&#8217;s leading derivatives platform CME Group announced plans to launch the ether/bitcoin (ETH/BTC) ratio futures subject to approval from the regulators.</p>
<p>These futures will be cash-settled meaning that the settlement will happen in cash instead of the underlying instrument. Also, the settlement will happen to the value of the CME Group Ether futures final settlement price, divided by the corresponding CME Group <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> futures final settlement price.</p>
<p>The ETH/BTC ratio futures will follow the same settlement cycle as that of the CME Group Bitcoin futures and Ether futures contracts. Speaking of the development, Giovanni Vicioso, CME Group Global Head of Cryptocurrency Products <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cme-group-to-launch-etherbitcoin-ratio-futures-on-july-31-301867241.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Historically, ether and bitcoin have been highly correlated; however, as the two assets have grown over time, market dynamics may affect the performance of one more than the other, creating relative value trading opportunities. With the addition of Ether/Bitcoin Ratio futures, investors will be able to capture ether and bitcoin exposure in a single trade, without needing to take a directional view. This new contract will help create opportunities for a broad array of clients looking to hedge positions or execute other trading strategies, all in an efficient, cost-effective manner.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Major Advantage of Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</h2>
<p>The introduction of Ether/Bitcoin Ratio futures (EBR) enables traders to efficiently engage in relative value trading between Ether futures (ETH) and Bitcoin futures (BTC) contracts within a single trade. This innovative contract provides investors with an opportunity to gain exposure to cryptocurrencies without requiring a specific directional bias.</p>
<p>Ether/Bitcoin Ratio futures offer traders a convenient means to express their perspective on the relative value of the two cryptocurrencies, regardless of their overall cryptocurrency market outlook. The ratio futures are denoted by the ticker EBR on CME Globex, with the ratio being defined as the price of Ether futures divided by the price of Bitcoin futures.</p>
<p>The EBR Final Settlement price is determined by dividing the Final Settlement Price of Ether futures by the Final Settlement Price of Bitcoin futures. The ratio is calculated using the same expiration month for both the underlying Ether and Bitcoin futures contracts. The ratio is always positive and is available for all listed contract months. The contract&#8217;s notional value is derived by multiplying the ratio by $1,000,000.</p>
<p>Crypto industry players have lauded this move from the CME Group stating that it will bring more liquidity into the markets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3iq-coinbase-streamline-eth-staking/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/">CME Group Unveils Plans of Launching Ether/Bitcoin Ratio Futures</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-ether-bitcoin-ratio-futures/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4220 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1072446 metric#prefetches=202 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=209 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=126.97 metric#ms-cache=13.21 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.6292 metric#ms-cache-ratio=10.4 -->