<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin holding $16K amid worst annual performance since 2018</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin was changing hands near $16,600 on Wednesday, about 1% down in the past 24 hours. The cryptocurrency is heading for its worst yearly returns since 2018. Stocks have also hit a brutal patch in 2022, with major US indexes headed for their worst annual returns since 2008. Bitcoin remained uncharacteristically uneventful on Wednesday, trading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/">Bitcoin holding $16K amid worst annual performance since 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Bitcoin was changing hands near $16,600 on Wednesday, about 1% down in the past 24 hours.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The cryptocurrency is heading for its worst yearly returns since 2018.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Stocks have also hit a brutal patch in 2022, with major US indexes headed for their worst annual returns since 2008.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> remained uncharacteristically uneventful on Wednesday, trading around $16,600 as investors weighed an end to a brutal 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The benchmark cryptocurrency was just in the red during early afternoon trading (2:10 pm ET) as Wall Street also turned negative amid fading optimism over China&rsquo;s reopening.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Markets to end 2022 lower</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In crypto, Bitcoin volatility has been at its 2022 low this week, with the surge towards $17,000 cooling off to leave the cryptocurrency 67% down in the past year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In fact, 2022 is shaping as the year with the second-worst returns for BTC since 2010. The digital gold&rsquo;s performance during this markedly bear year has the asset on track for a worst return since the 73% drawdown in 2018.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the 2014 bear market, Bitcoin price fell 58%, with other years with lower returns being +35% in 2015 and +66% in 2021 &ndash; indeed Bitcoin is more than 75% down since its all-time high in 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As Bitcoin struggles to hold onto gains above $16k, the picture across the stock market is similar for the major US indexes. The S&amp;P 500 is down 4.1% this month and over 20% year-to-date, while the Dow and the Nasdaq are -2.5% and -7.1% over the past 30 days respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The historically bullish season for equities has been largely negative, with ongoing investor jitters around inflation and rate hikes, and the overall outlook for the global economy, adding to the downward pressure that has persisted for most of the year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As such, while Bitcoin is set to see its worst yearly performance since 2018, US stocks are poised for their worst annual returns since 2008.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/">Bitcoin holding $16K amid worst annual performance since 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-holding-16k-amid-worst-annual-performance-since-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conflux Network Expands into Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-network-expands-into-hong-kong/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-network-expands-into-hong-kong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 18:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=98932</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Toronto, Canada, 28th December, 2022, Chainwire Dr. Ming Wu, co-founder of Conflux Network, was invited to Hong Kong to speak with various government and private organizations about the digital economy, innovation and technology, and has reached an initial strategic cooperation intention. Conflux is already in the process of registering related entities for the entry into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-network-expands-into-hong-kong/">Conflux Network Expands into Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Toronto, Canada, 28th December, 2022, Chainwire</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Dr. Ming Wu, co-founder of Conflux Network, was invited to Hong Kong to speak with various government and private organizations about the digital economy, innovation and technology, and has reached an initial strategic cooperation intention.</li>
<li>Conflux is already in the process of registering related entities for the entry into Hong Kong, solidifying its role as foundational infrastructure for Web3.</li>
<li>This follows October&rsquo;s announcement of the &nbsp;&ldquo;Policy Declaration on the Development of Hong Kong Virtual Assets&rdquo; which has paved the way for a more hospitable blockchain environment in Hong Kong.</li>
</ul>
<p>Dr. Ming Wu, Co-Founder of <a href="https://confluxnetwork.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Conflux Network</u></a>, &nbsp;was invited by the Hong Kong Government to discuss the rise of tech innovation through Web3 and how the Conflux Network could play a foundational role in these developments. During the visit, Dr. Ming Wu had an in-depth discussion with the heads and reception staff of various institutions under the new &ldquo;Policy Declaration on the Development of Hong Kong Virtual Assets&rdquo; officially released in October.</p>
<p>Over the past several years, stringent COVID-19 travel control measures and regulatory uncertainty saw many Hong Kong blockchain and crypto companies shift their businesses to more hospitable areas. &nbsp;This policy shows a significant refocus on digital assets and coincides with the launch of the first two exchange-traded funds for cryptocurrency in Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Dr. Ming Wu introduced the Conflux Tree-Graph public chain, explaining it is the only compliant, public and permissionless chain in China and has achieved 3000+ TPS, 5000+ nodes and 0.5s block generation. In terms of throughput, confirmation time, and cost of use, it has 2-3 orders of magnitude advantages over the international first-generation public chain &ldquo;Bitcoin&rdquo; and the second-generation public chain &ldquo;Ethereum&rdquo;. The system performance ranks first in the world.</p>
<p>Dr. Mig Wu said &lsquo;Hong Kong&rsquo;s open environment for crypto provides more opportunities for practitioners in Web3 and Metaverse, especially for those from China. People here have more freedom to make the technique and business innovations in a compliant manner. This will also accelerate the integration of Web3 into the traditional internet business and economies to maximally extract its value. By expanding to Hong Kong, Conflux will be able to take a whole different strategy and have the potential to become the foundation to fulfill the Web3 vision of Hong Kong.&rsquo;</p>
<p>The expansion follows Conflux Network being named a potential unicorn, a private startup company valued at over $1 billion, in the <a href="https://assets.kpmg/content/dam/kpmg/xx/pdf/2022/07/emerging-giants-in-asia-pacific.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Emerging Giants in Asia Pacific</u></a> joint report from HSBC and KPMG. &nbsp;One of only five blockchain-related companies to make the prestigious list.</p>
<h3><b>About Conflux</b></h3>
<p>Conflux is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols. Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p>
<p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. In the region, Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p>
<p>To learn more about Conflux, visit <a href="https://confluxnetwork.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">confluxnetwork.org</a></p>
<h5><strong>Contact</strong></h5>
<p>Melissa Tirey<br>
Shift6 Studios<br>
conflux@shift6studios.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-network-expands-into-hong-kong/">Conflux Network Expands into Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/conflux-network-expands-into-hong-kong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Santiment says Cardano sellers are getting exhausted but does price action show it?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/santiment-says-cardano-sellers-are-getting-exhausted-but-does-price-action-show-it/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/santiment-says-cardano-sellers-are-getting-exhausted-but-does-price-action-show-it/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/santiment-says-cardano-sellers-are-getting-exhausted-but-does-price-action-show-it/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano lost 3.22% on Wednesday to hit the lowest in the year at $0.25 Santiment data holds that bears are decreasing in numbers and losing control ADA price action is extremely bearish, and lower prices are possible Cardano (ADA/USD) looked headed for a new low on Wednesday as the price lost 3.22% to trade at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/santiment-says-cardano-sellers-are-getting-exhausted-but-does-price-action-show-it/">Santiment says Cardano sellers are getting exhausted but does price action show it?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cardano lost 3.22% on Wednesday to hit the lowest in the year at $0.25</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Santiment data holds that bears are decreasing in numbers and losing control</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ADA price action is extremely bearish, and lower prices are possible</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/what-is-cardano/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Cardano</u></a> (ADA/USD) looked headed for a new low on Wednesday as the price lost 3.22% to trade at $0.25. The price was the lowest in the year, with ADA still likely falling further. However, Santiment data could revive hopes, although ADA bulls would be disappointed that the price action isn&rsquo;t positive.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Santiment, ADA sellers are getting exhausted, while the cryptocurrency is &ldquo;severely undervalued.&rdquo; As ADA trades on a system of lower lows and lower highs, Santiment points out that there is falling selling power. The insights platform shows that as the token makes one downward movement, fewer coins are marked with a loss on the network. This has been interpreted as the strongest reversal sign as bears are gradually losing power.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides, whale accumulation has been on the rise for Cardano in the last six weeks. But as you are too aware, Cardano has seen whale activity for a larger part of 2021. That has been interpreted to mean that whales are attracted to the low valuation of Cardano. However, this does not tell about the short-term price action since whales are believed to accumulate for the longer term.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ADA on a new low as price weakens on a descending channel</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/28/1672247336747-4d1728ff-be62-4a17-b0ea-4827c3fe8751.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="294"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ADA/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, Cardano has maintained the descending channel with limited price surges. The price has mainly traded at the bottom of the descending channel range, indicating that bulls are keeping off. The RSI shows that ADA is currently oversold.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Which way, Cardano?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">It could be premature to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/buy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy ADA</u></a>, despite Santiment data suggesting bear exhaustion. There is no clear bullish reversal, and we maintain a downtrend bias. From a technical point of view, a clearance of the descending channel is the needed confirmation for a bullish reversal.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy ADA</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5MzA&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg5MzA&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/santiment-says-cardano-sellers-are-getting-exhausted-but-does-price-action-show-it/">Santiment says Cardano sellers are getting exhausted but does price action show it?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/santiment-says-cardano-sellers-are-getting-exhausted-but-does-price-action-show-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy buys another 2,500 BTC to bring total to 132,500</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-buys-another-2500-btc-to-bring-total-to-132500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-buys-another-2500-btc-to-bring-total-to-132500/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy reportedly bought approximately 2,500 BTC between 1 November and 24 December, 2022. The company now holds 132,500 BTC acquired for approximately $4.03 billion. MicroStrategy did however sell 704 BTC for $11.8 million on 22 December for what it termed as tax benefits. MicroStrategy, a publicly traded company that&#8217;s the world&#8217;s largest corporate holder of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-buys-another-2500-btc-to-bring-total-to-132500/">MicroStrategy buys another 2,500 BTC to bring total to 132,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>MicroStrategy reportedly bought approximately 2,500 BTC between 1 November and 24 December, 2022.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The company now holds 132,500 BTC acquired for approximately $4.03 billion.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>MicroStrategy did however sell 704 BTC for $11.8 million on 22 December for what it termed as tax benefits.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">MicroStrategy, a publicly traded company that&rsquo;s the world&rsquo;s largest corporate holder of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>, has reported buying more of the flagship cryptocurrency even as the market hit turbulence beginning early November.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As per the <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/content/dam/website-assets/collateral/financial-documents/financial-document-archive/form-8-k-12-28-2022.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">filing</a> submitted on 28 December to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), MicroStrategy says it purchased an additional 2,500 bitcoins between 1 November and 24 December, 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Altogether, the software analytics and business intelligence firm purchased Bitcoin worth approximately $56.4 million in nearly two months and $4.03 billion in total.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MicroStrategy now holds 132, 500 bitcoins</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As crypto navigated the turmoil caused by FTX&rsquo;s collapse that had crypto price tapping new multi-year lows, MicroStrategy saw an opportunity to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/buy/">buy Bitcoin</a>. In short, the company added 2,395 bitcoins worth $42.8 million to its holdings between 1 November and 21 December, 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total BTC acquisition in this period cost the firm $42.8 million at an average purchase price of $17,871 per coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On 22 December, 2022, MicroStrategy sold 704 bitcoins for $11.8 million. According to the company, the sale was at an average price of $16,776 per coin. Although the sale was at a loss, the company plans to offset the capital losses against capital gains made earlier.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the BTC sale, MicroStrategy went to the market again on 24 December 2022. It bought another 810 bitcoins at an average price of $16,845 and for a total outlay of $13.6 million. By 27 December 2022, the company had added 2,500 bitcoins at a total cost of $56.4 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of this report, MicroStrategy had increased its Bitcoin holdings from 130,000 BTC at the end of October to 132,500 bitcoins by 27 December, 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The recent purchases means MicroStrategy has spent $4.03 billion on acquiring BTC since its first purchase in 2020. The coins&rsquo; average purchase price currently stands at $30,397 per bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/microstrategy-buys-another-2500-btc-to-bring-total-to-132500/">MicroStrategy buys another 2,500 BTC to bring total to 132,500</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink losing $6 will be a bear trigger, but Michaël Van De Poppe is optimistic</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-losing-6-will-be-a-bear-trigger-but-michael-van-de-poppe-is-optimistic/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-losing-6-will-be-a-bear-trigger-but-michael-van-de-poppe-is-optimistic/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Link]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-losing-6-will-be-a-bear-trigger-but-michael-van-de-poppe-is-optimistic/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink has temporarily lost the support at $6 Micha&#235;l Van De Poppe expects the price to rally to $16 next year LINK faces pressure, and the momentum is bearish Chainlink (LINK/USD) was trading $5.74 as of press time. Technical indicators show that the cryptocurrency has lost support at $6, although a bear momentum is yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-losing-6-will-be-a-bear-trigger-but-michael-van-de-poppe-is-optimistic/">Chainlink losing $6 will be a bear trigger, but Michaël Van De Poppe is optimistic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink has temporarily lost the support at $6</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Micha&euml;l Van De Poppe expects the price to rally to $16 next year</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">LINK faces pressure, and the momentum is bearish</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/chainlink/what-is-chainlink/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chainlink</u></a> (LINK/USD) was trading $5.74 as of press time. Technical indicators show that the cryptocurrency has lost support at $6, although a bear momentum is yet to be confirmed. Will the new year spell doom if bulls do not recover above $6?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Potentially yes, since LINK bulls have always defended $6. Any time the price crashes below this level, buyers arrest it quickly, making it an important zone. A loss of $6 will, therefore, be a bear trigger for LINK in early 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto analyst Micha&euml;l Van De Poppe expects Chainlink to be bullish next year. According to Poppe, Chainlink will rally to $16 if bulls reach a resistance area of $7.78. However, Poppe says LINK can fall below $5 before igniting a bullish push.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>LINK price and technical outlook</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">LINK is consolidating within a range of between $6 and $8. Any break below the range low could take the cryptocurrency down. Bulls will gain interest if the cryptocurrency breaks above the range low.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/28/1672245438478-9eb9230e-0f96-4ddf-994f-f1ab5cc56317.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="295"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LINKUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>LINK/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Technically, selling pressure is high on LINK. The RSI points down and remains near the oversold region. A further decline heightens the bear pressure, with LINK now staring at a possible drop below the consolidation. The new few days of trading will be exciting to watch how LINK behaves around the support.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Can LINK recover the $6 level?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Although a price below $6 would be considered bearish for LINK, we need to watch the close of the daily candlestick. A bullish reversal will be confirmed if the candlestick closes with a long wick on the lower side (bullish pin bar).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Conversely, a bear market will be confirmed if LINK closes with a long wick on the upper side and the price breaks further lower. For LINK bulls, it is important to wait for confirmation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy LINK</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5Mjc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg5Mjc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-losing-6-will-be-a-bear-trigger-but-michael-van-de-poppe-is-optimistic/">Chainlink losing $6 will be a bear trigger, but Michaël Van De Poppe is optimistic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-losing-6-will-be-a-bear-trigger-but-michael-van-de-poppe-is-optimistic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xrp Classic develops eco-friendly ReFi blockchain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-classic-develops-eco-friendly-refi-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-classic-develops-eco-friendly-refi-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniela Kirova]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 16:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-classic-develops-eco-friendly-refi-blockchain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ReFi is a regenerative, stable approach to navigating the financial system&#160; In the new financial system, one can address climate change&#160; Xrp Classic has been audited by leading security firm SolidProof After its launch, Xrp Classic is introduced as a carbon-free, environmentally friendly regenerative finance (ReFi) blockchain. ReFi is a regenerative, stable approach to navigating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-classic-develops-eco-friendly-refi-blockchain/">Xrp Classic develops eco-friendly ReFi blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ReFi is a regenerative, stable approach to navigating the financial system&nbsp;</li>
<li>In the new financial system, one can address climate change&nbsp;</li>
<li>Xrp Classic has been audited by leading security firm SolidProof </li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>After its launch, Xrp Classic is introduced as a carbon-free, environmentally friendly regenerative finance (ReFi) blockchain. ReFi is a regenerative, stable approach to navigating the financial system, which is aimed at liberalizing financial service access.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Decentralized ReFi promotes the transition to a financial system where one can address systemic problems such as climate change, according to <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20221228005243/en/Xrp-Classic-Promotes-Eco-friendly-Regenerative-Finance-Using-Blockchain">a press release</a>.</p>
<h2>A flourishing solution&nbsp;</h2>
<p>Xrp Classic aims to be a solution that will thrive as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> mature by representing ReFi sector best practices. Currently, the platform is building its own ReFi blockchain to offer eco-friendly, high-speed transactions combined with minimum trading fees.</p>
<h2>Audited by SolidProof&nbsp;</h2>
<p>Xrp Classic has been audited by leading security firm SolidProof, which confirms its credibility and the authenticity of its contract software. Xrp Classic&rsquo;s ultimate goal is to integrate its ReFi blockchain into all facets to contribute to a decarbonized world.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Greenhouse gas reduction is top investor consideration&nbsp;</h2>
<p>According to a report by PwC, the reduction of greenhouse gas emissions is a leading global investment consideration. Sustainability is becoming more and more important over time. Xrp Classic&rsquo;s ReFi model is an essential part of the transition to low carbon.</p>
<h2>Part of the transition to a low carbon economy&nbsp;</h2>
<p>After its Fair Launch in December, Xrp Classic was advertised on billboards in Times Square and featured on crypto exchange news and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bringing-social-media-into-the-web3-world-interview-ceo-of-cyberconnect/">social media</a> sources. Its ReFi blockchain solution is part of a worldwide transition to a low carbon economy due to a lower environmental impact on the crypto ecosystem. &nbsp;</p>
<p>George Peter, Xrp Classic Community Director, stated:&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>We can use advanced technology to minimize some of the damage we are doing to our environment. Xrp Classic is one type of technology that can transition to a circular economy, facilitating some environmental recovery.</em></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-classic-develops-eco-friendly-refi-blockchain/">Xrp Classic develops eco-friendly ReFi blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-classic-develops-eco-friendly-refi-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum price as cryptocurrency falls below $1,200</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-as-cryptocurrency-falls-below-1200/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-as-cryptocurrency-falls-below-1200/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-as-cryptocurrency-falls-below-1200/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum fell by 1.87% on Wednesday to relinquish $1,200 price level Ethereum price is ailing from the weak sentiment in the crypto sector The price faces further slump although it has some stability Looking to&#160;buy Ethereum (ETH/USD) in the new year? Probably waiting a little longer would help. Ethereum is yet to find a bullish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-as-cryptocurrency-falls-below-1200/">Ethereum price as cryptocurrency falls below $1,200</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum fell by 1.87% on Wednesday to relinquish $1,200 price level</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum price is ailing from the weak sentiment in the crypto sector</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The price faces further slump although it has some stability</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Looking to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/buy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy Ethereum</u></a> (ETH/USD) in the new year? Probably waiting a little longer would help. Ethereum is yet to find a bullish footing, and further downsides are possible. The recent price action shows it, but it is not outright.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Trading down 1.87% on Wednesday, Ethereum had slipped below the $1,200 price level. The loss is not unique to the second-largest cryptocurrency. All the cryptocurrencies in the top 10 by market cap were in the red. That probably tells that although crypto fans may wait for 2023 with enthusiasm, it may still be too early to jump into the ship.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum is a cryptocurrency with huge potential, considering that it trades at just four times lesser value than its 2021 highs. Then, the merge happened this year, and the blockchain transited to the proof of stake protocol. Yet again, the price has failed to take off. Perhaps, we should take the words of the co-founder Vitalik Buterin that we should focus on the technology rather than price. But to crypto speculators, price matters most. What crypto enthusiasts want is when is the next bull run. The answer is plain, not yet! The price action below shows.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ETH sliding below the support-turned resistance</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/28/1672242248365-e4bdf5dc-7e99-4e22-b047-16b087a31bba.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="298"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ETHUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ETH/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">On the technical outlook, Ethereum is sliding into a consolidating market. However, the cryptocurrency is in a bear market with weak momentum. ETH also trades below the $1,250 support zone. The $1,100 continues to support the price and prevent bears from crashing below $1,000.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What next for ETH?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The price outlook for ETH is slightly bearish. However, $1,100 is the level to watch should bear pressure mount. A break below the support would see ETH fall further lower.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the flip side, bulls must recover above $1,250 to consider the further upside for&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/#:~:text=One%20Ethereum%20is%20currently%20worth,29%3A00%20GMT%2D8." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum price</u></a>. For buyers, it could be crucial to wait for a bullish momentum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy ETH</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5MjQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg5MjQ&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-as-cryptocurrency-falls-below-1200/">Ethereum price as cryptocurrency falls below $1,200</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-as-cryptocurrency-falls-below-1200/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin rallies from a support zone as trading volumes rise</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-rallies-from-a-support-zone-as-trading-volumes-rise/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-rallies-from-a-support-zone-as-trading-volumes-rise/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-rallies-from-a-support-zone-as-trading-volumes-rise/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin correction was contained at the $64 support Micha&#235;l van de Poppe expects LTC price to rally 22% LTC is a good buy on the current retracement for short-term investors Litecoin (LTC/USD) may be well on course to another bullish rally. Despite the cryptocurrency cooling off from its recent gains, bulls have defended the $64 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-rallies-from-a-support-zone-as-trading-volumes-rise/">Litecoin rallies from a support zone as trading volumes rise</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin correction was contained at the $64 support</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Micha&euml;l van de Poppe expects LTC price to rally 22%</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">LTC is a good buy on the current retracement for short-term investors</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/what-is-litecoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Litecoin</u></a> (LTC/USD) may be well on course to another bullish rally. Despite the cryptocurrency cooling off from its recent gains, bulls have defended the $64 support as the price retraced. LTC has now initiated a short-term recovery above the support.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While technicals depict a potential rally in LTC, crypto analyst Micha&euml;l van de Poppe says the uptick will continue. Poppe says LTC price could rise by at least 22% from the current price level. To emphasise his point, the analyst notes Litecoin is demonstrating strengths. He says he will be interested in some scalp trades at the $69 level, with options to go long around $66.75, targeting $78 and $84. LTC traded at $67.48 as of press time and was on a slight bear correction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, development activity on Litecoin is on the rise. Santiment data indicates that activity grew strongly in September before peaking in October. As of December 27, Litecoin was the second most active chain. It recorded $2.88 billion in transaction volumes after Bitcoin&rsquo;s $3.98 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>LTC recovers at the 38.2% fib level but above $64 support</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/28/1672241358701-8fcbb04f-1b03-422e-8445-e36b9fa16acd.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="298"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/LTCUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>LTC/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Incorporating the Fibonacci retracement levels on LTC daily chart, the token&rsquo;s price initiated a recovery at the 38.2% fib level. Momentum increased as the cryptocurrency recovered the 50% fib level. LTC is also maintaining a short-term bullish trendline. The bulls have now successfully defended the $64 support.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>LTC concluding thoughts</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Technicals and fundamentals align for&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/#:~:text=What%20is%20LTC%20price%20today,in%20the%20last%2024%20hours." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>LTC price.</u></a> There is a clear uptrend, with price recovering key levels that spell a bullish surge for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">LTC is a good buy, with a price potential of up to $84, the previous resistance level. However, buyers would still target areas around $70, the 61.8% fib level, and $76, the 78.6% fib level. A further uptick in LTC will depend on the ongoing fundamentals and developments. Investors can buy on the short-term retracement.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy LTC</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5MjM&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg5MjM&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-rallies-from-a-support-zone-as-trading-volumes-rise/">Litecoin rallies from a support zone as trading volumes rise</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-rallies-from-a-support-zone-as-trading-volumes-rise/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP attempts recovery, but how is the SEC case shaping price?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-attempts-recovery-but-how-is-the-sec-case-shaping-price/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-attempts-recovery-but-how-is-the-sec-case-shaping-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 15:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-attempts-recovery-but-how-is-the-sec-case-shaping-price/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP price has remained tied to the ongoing Ripple case with SEC SEC recently filed a motion to restrict the Hinman documents $0.40 is the level to watch on the bull side or $0.30 on the bear side Ripple (XRP/USD) has been on a short recovery since falling below $0.34. Despite losing an intraday of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-attempts-recovery-but-how-is-the-sec-case-shaping-price/">XRP attempts recovery, but how is the SEC case shaping price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">XRP price has remained tied to the ongoing Ripple case with SEC</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">SEC recently filed a motion to restrict the Hinman documents</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$0.40 is the level to watch on the bull side or $0.30 on the bear side</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/what-is-ripple/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ripple</u></a> (XRP/USD) has been on a short recovery since falling below $0.34. Despite losing an intraday of 3.20% as of press time, it looked stable even as Ripple&rsquo;s case with SEC drags on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For a long time, the SEC&rsquo;s case has been a price driver for XRP. However, recently, investors have adopted a wait-and-see attitude amid speculations that the case was nearing an end. Up to this point, nothing is confirmed yet, but the ongoing legal tussles shape XRP trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The latest development in the longstanding case involved the SEC filing a motion to restrict the Hinman documents. SEC lawyers allege that the documents should be protected from the public since they carry sensitive matters. It should be remembered that Ripple has often called for the documents to be made public. If the SEC&rsquo;s wish is granted, that could be a blow to Ripple.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With XRP continuing to reflect the case, it is obvious that any win for the SEC will hurt the token&rsquo;s price. Consequently, Ripple will come under bear pressure. Similarly, a win for Ripple would increase speculations of SEC getting defeated at the end and boost XRP. That could see the cryptocurrency resume the uptrend.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>XRP trapped by $0.40 resistance but holds strongly above $0.30 support</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/28/1672240671311-a01d9cdc-b897-4e16-8497-f4592f76f30d.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="297"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>XRP/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">From the technical outlook, XRP is trading within a range. $0.40 is the resistance at $0.30 is the support. Any break above or below these levels will spell a win for bulls and bears, respectively. Momentum is, however, improving, with the MACD indicator shifting above the signal line. The indicator still shows XRP is bearish.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What next for XRP?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20XRP%20today,in%20the%20last%2024%20hours." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>XRP price</u></a> will be determined by the developments around Ripple&rsquo;s case with SEC. To a technical reader, it is important to buy the cryptocurrency on a confirmed breakout.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy XRP</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTg5MjE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTg5MjE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy XRP with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-attempts-recovery-but-how-is-the-sec-case-shaping-price/">XRP attempts recovery, but how is the SEC case shaping price?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xrp-attempts-recovery-but-how-is-the-sec-case-shaping-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
