<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Maintains $30K Price as Investors Await Data on Inflation and Jobless Claims</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262359</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/">Bitcoin Maintains $30K Price as Investors Await Data on Inflation and Jobless Claims</a></p>
<p>Although Bitcoin is holding strong in the $30K region, predictions are bullish, with one putting the coin at $50k this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/">Bitcoin Maintains $30K Price as Investors Await Data on Inflation and Jobless Claims</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/">Bitcoin Maintains $30K Price as Investors Await Data on Inflation and Jobless Claims</a></p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has maintained its level above $30K for a while now, even as it has been swinging. However, market forces heavily threaten the king coin as inflation and unemployment in the US seem unfavorable.</p>
<p>Several conditions may affect the price of Bitcoin in the near future. For instance, the US Federal Reserve recently published hawkish minutes that point to potential rate hikes. As it struggles to fight inflation. The release caused BTC to fall below $31,000 on Thursday, along with a declining global stock market.</p>
<p>According to Nexo co-founder Antoni Trenchev, not much may happen to Bitcoin, especially in relation to the Federal Reserve’s decision. Trenchev said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With headline inflation continuing to drift lower while core inflation remains sticky, don’t expect the narrative to change too much when it comes to this month’s Fed meeting.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Currently, these macroeconomic factors may not augur well for Bitcoin. However, a general anticipation of the inflation and unemployment data may keep BTC hovering around $30,000 until Thursday when these data become available.</p>
<p>According to CoinMarketCap data, Bitcoin is trading at $30,163, after falling 1.57% in the past 7 days.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s $30K Is Mild Considering Other Predictions</h2>
<p>Although Bitcoin has lost nearly 3% in the last few days, its 2023 has been commendable. In the last month, BTC has climbed almost 17%, and more than 48% in the last year. Since January, investors have seen an 82.15% increase in the value of their portfolios. Considering its steady rise, there is still a general bullishness in the Bitcoin sentiment.</p>
<p>Multinational banking and treasury services giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a> released a report on July 10 with a bullish outlook for Bitcoin. According to the report, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC could hit $50,000</a> this year and $120,000 in 2024.</p>
<p>One of the reasons for Standard Chartered’s bullishness, especially for next year, is the upcoming Bitcoin halving. The halving event sees Bitcoin block rewards cut in half &#8211; 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC for next year’s event. The reduction in supply creates scarcity which usually drives Bitcoin’s price.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Standard Chartered initially had a $100,000 prediction for Bitcoin for 2024 December. The bank believed that the crypto winter was over and that Bitcoin would continue its increase and eventually hit $100,000 next month. However, Standard Chartered analyst Geoff Kendrick has increased this projection. Kendrick believes that each miner’s “profitability per BTC mined” suggests that a miner can maintain cash inflows and sell less. This reduces Bitcoin’s net supply and increases its price.</p>
<p>Another enthusiastic Bitcoin <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitmex-arthur-hayes-bitcoin-ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">prediction</a> has come from BitMex co-founder Arthur Hayes who believes the AI boom would benefit Bitcoin. In a recent <a href="https://cryptohayes.substack.com/p/massa" target="_blank" rel="noopener">publication</a>, Hayes said Bitcoin could become an artificial intelligence (AI) currency.</p>
<p>Hayes argues that future AI tools may require blockchain-based payment as it would need more than the “analogue banking system [that is] balkanised between geographies and banks themselves”. He then argues that Bitcoin would be the best bet as it is available on a blockchain, censorship-resistant, provably scarce, and has provable longevity.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/">Bitcoin Maintains $30K Price as Investors Await Data on Inflation and Jobless Claims</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-30k-price-investors/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Announces Arkham (ARKM) Token Sale on Its Launchpad</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arkham]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arkm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/">Binance Announces Arkham (ARKM) Token Sale on Its Launchpad</a></p>
<p>The Arkham project is focused on deanonymizing blockchain technology through a decentralized token financial system to enable a safe adoption of the crypto market among other reasons.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/">Binance Announces Arkham (ARKM) Token Sale on Its Launchpad</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/">Binance Announces Arkham (ARKM) Token Sale on Its Launchpad</a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> cryptocurrency exchange has announced the 32nd token sale on its Launchpad involving the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ieo/arkham/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Arkham</a> (ARKM) project. According to the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/introducing-the-arkham-arkm-token-sale-on-binance-launchpad-6ad1921b56fb4b369f9cf3e4449e62e2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, 5 percent of the total ARKM supply, amounting to about 50 million units, has been allocated to Binance Launchpad. As a result, each user on the Binance Launchpad is capped at 300k ARKM units or about $15k at a price of around $0.05, as the project aims at raising about $2.5 million from the crypto traders.</p>
<h2>Further Notes on Arkham Binance Token Sale</h2>
<p>Notably, the Arkham (ARKM) token sale on Binance Launchpad is expected to be subscription-based to minimize the chances of insider trading. Additionally, the ARKM token sale on Binance Launchpad will only be in BNB coins. However, the leading centralized exchange has restricted users from several jurisdictions from participating in the ARKM token sale on its Launchpad.</p>
<p>Among the countries mentioned by Binance include: Belarus, Cuba, the Crimea Region, the Democratic Republic of Congo, Iran, New Zealand, North Korea, South Sudan, Syria, the United States of America and its territories, and Zimbabwe.</p>
<p>Anyone else from the remaining countries can begin the quest to invest in an early project from July 11 to July 17, when the preparation period will begin. During the ARKM token sale preparation period on Binance Launchpad, the user’s BNB balances will be calculated in hourly snapshots for each day over the past six days. The final average daily BNB balance over the past six days will determine the maximum amount of BNB that a single user can commit in the ARKM token sale.</p>
<p>After the preparation period, users will be required to enter the subscription phase which will be open for 24 hours to eligible users. The ARKM early adopters via Binance Launchpad will have their BNB assets locked until the final distribution period.</p>
<h2>Project Activities</h2>
<p>The Arkham project is focused on deanonymizing blockchain technology through a decentralized token financial system to enable a safe adoption of the crypto market among other reasons. The Binance Launchpad ARKM token sale coincided with the launch of its on-chain intelligence exchange to allow users to trade information regarding blockchain Wallet addresses anonymously, via a smart contract.</p>
<p>Notably, traders on the Arkham Intel Exchange request blockchain intelligence information from the community by placing bounties.</p>
<p>The Arkham bounty hunters can then claim rewards by submitting the requested intel. In a bid to prevent spamming accounts, Arkham has set that all bounty hunters must stake a small amount of ARKM tokens, which will be slashed in the event their submissions are not approved.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/">Binance Announces Arkham (ARKM) Token Sale on Its Launchpad</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-arkham-arkm-launchpad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase (COIN) Stock Soars over 50% amidst SEC Lawsuit Turmoil</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/">Coinbase (COIN) Stock Soars over 50% amidst SEC Lawsuit Turmoil</a></p>
<p>While Coinbase executives have engaged in pre-planned and periodic stock sales, other major COIN holders have chosen a different approach.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/">Coinbase (COIN) Stock Soars over 50% amidst SEC Lawsuit Turmoil</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/">Coinbase (COIN) Stock Soars over 50% amidst SEC Lawsuit Turmoil</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), the publicly listed American crypto exchange has witnessed an astounding surge in its stock price despite facing a lawsuit from the US <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) for allegedly offering unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Over the past month, Coinbase shares have soared by a remarkable 51%, highlighting the resilience and investor confidence in the company amidst a challenging legal battle. In early June, Coinbase was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">served with a lawsuit</a> by the SEC. The lawsuit accuses Coinbase of operating as an unregistered national securities exchange and broker, conducting business in violation of regulatory requirements since at least 2019.</p>
<p>The lawsuit claims that Coinbase failed to comply with regulatory obligations and obtain necessary operations licenses, as Federal Securities Laws mandated. Despite this bad legal outlook, Coinbase has defied expectations, demonstrating resilience and attracting investor confidence.</p>
<p>According to TradingView statistics, Coinbase shares have increased by 51% in a little more than a month. From approximately $52 per share on June 6, the stock climbed to $78.7 on July 7. This significant stock increase underscores the market&#8217;s optimism regarding Coinbase&#8217;s ability to navigate the SEC lawsuit and maintain its position as a leading player in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Amidst this surge, notable Coinbase stakeholders, including senior Coinbase executives, have been selling a portion of their stock holdings. On July 6, a combined total of 88,058 COIN stocks, valued at approximately $6.9 million, were sold by the executives, including CEO Brian Armstrong.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://investor.coinbase.com/financials/sec-filings/default.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">recent</a> SEC filing, Gokul Rajaram, a board member, sold 4,580 COIN shares, while Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal sold 1,818 COIN shares. Chief Accounting Officer Jennifer Jones also participated in the stock sales, selling 7,335 COIN shares.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Jennifer Jones had previously sold 74,375 Coinbase shares on June 29, which resulted in a net gain of $5.2 million.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Stock: Other Major Holders Continue to HODL</h2>
<p>While Coinbase executives have engaged in pre-planned and periodic stock sales, other major COIN holders have chosen a different approach. These “HODLers,” a term derived from a popular crypto meme encouraging long-term holding, have maintained their positions in COIN despite market fluctuations and executive sales.</p>
<p>For example, ARK Invest, known for its active involvement in innovative and disruptive technologies, including cryptocurrencies, made a substantial investment in Coinbase by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-coinbase-shares-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">purchasing</a> an additional 400,000 shares in early June.</p>
<p>This investment signaled ARK Invest’s confidence in the future prospects of Coinbase and its potential as a leading player in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Cathie Wood, the founder and CEO of Ark Invest has confirmed her unshakeable optimism in Bitcoin&#8217;s future potential, predicting that the digital currency will eventually reach an astounding price of $1 million per coin. Wood&#8217;s upbeat forecast reflects her long-term view of Bitcoin and its transformational power.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/">Coinbase (COIN) Stock Soars over 50% amidst SEC Lawsuit Turmoil</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-stock-soars-50-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan’s Nikkei 225 Enters Fifth Straight Losing Plunge as Global Economy Fluctuates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cac 40]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cac 404]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftse 100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq 100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq composite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nikkei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262347</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Enters Fifth Straight Losing Plunge as Global Economy Fluctuates</a></p>
<p>The Nikkei is reflecting a general plunge in the global financial economy as it saw a plunge today despite hitting a high last week.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Enters Fifth Straight Losing Plunge as Global Economy Fluctuates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Enters Fifth Straight Losing Plunge as Global Economy Fluctuates</a></p>
<p>Japan’s Nikkei stock average fell on Monday, cementing a fifth consecutive losing plunge. The fall is the longest straight session this year and points to a general economic fluctuation as Wall Street was frail last week despite a strong Yen.</p>
<p>The Nikkei had climbed 0.53% in the morning and fell 1% in the afternoon in an unstable trading session. Comprising 225 components, the Nikkei eventually closed at 32,189.73 after falling 0.61%.73 of these components climbed while 150 plunged. Only 2 of these remained flat.</p>
<p>Since March, the Nikkei has climbed 27% and hit a high last week. However, the Average fell below the 25-day moving average for the first time in three months last Thursday. According to Nomura Securities Strategist Maki Sawada, “Whether or not the Nikkei can recover above the 25-day moving average in a short time is a focal point for the market.”</p>
<p>Performance was low among car makers as Nissan fell 2.55%, while Honda lost 1.72%. The biggest loss was Yaskawa Electric Corporation, which fell 3.44%. The company had released lower-than-expected financial results.</p>
<h2>Earlier Projections for the Japanese Stock Market Before Nikkei Plunge</h2>
<p>In May, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GE) analysts were <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japanese-stock-market-projections/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">relatively bullish</a> about the stock market in Japan. Talks of corporate restructuring is a factor the analysts hope will make Japan a desired spot for investors. According to them, a large inflow into the country’s equity market is likely, if structural reforms restore or at least strengthen the desire for investments among long-term players. At the time, the analysts’ bullish outlook may have also come from anticipating the possible ripple effects of the then-proposed increase in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/senate-bill-31t-us-debt-ceiling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US debt ceiling</a>.</p>
<p>Goldman analysts had predicted that the Topix index would rise 3% to 2,200 points. Interestingly, strategists at the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of America</a> were more bullish, putting the rise at 7% to 2,300 points. The strategists hoped there would be a considerable amount of share buybacks this year, which would generally spur the stock market. As of press time, Goldman Sachs’ analysts seem more spot-on as the Topix is at 2,243.33 after falling 0.51%.</p>
<h2>Similar Plunges Across Global Markets</h2>
<p>Generally, markets around the world are having a hard time as the global economy is struggling. On Wednesday, the European markets opened lower, with the Stoxx 600, CAC 40 Index, and the FTSE 100 recording similar plunges. The DAX fell the most at 0.53%.</p>
<p>On the same day, there were also recorded plunges in the Asia-Pacific region, with the Shanghai Composite, Hang Seng index, and Hang Seng Tech indexes plunging between 0.69% and 1.6%. In the US, the Nasdaq 100, S&amp;P 500, and Dow Jones Industrial Average futures all plunged as well.</p>
<p>According to MarketWatch <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/index/comp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> as of press time, the Nasdaq Composite fell 0.13% to 13,660.72 from its previous close of 13,679.72. The S&amp;P 500 index also fell, losing 0.29% from its previous close at 4,411.59 to 4,398.95.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/">Japan’s Nikkei 225 Enters Fifth Straight Losing Plunge as Global Economy Fluctuates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/japans-nikkei-225-plunge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered Expects Bitcoin (BTC) Price to Surge to $120,000 by End of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262336</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/">Standard Chartered Expects Bitcoin (BTC) Price to Surge to $120,000 by End of 2024</a></p>
<p>Banking giant Standard Chartered expects the Bitcoin bull run to continue further with the BTC price to rally to $50,000 by the end of the year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/">Standard Chartered Expects Bitcoin (BTC) Price to Surge to $120,000 by End of 2024</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/">Standard Chartered Expects Bitcoin (BTC) Price to Surge to $120,000 by End of 2024</a></p>
<p>After hitting its 2023 high at $31,000 last week, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has been facing some selling pressure over the last week and is currently trading close to $30,000 levels. However, going ahead, market players continue to remain bullish on Bitcoin. Banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a> published a report on Monday, July 10, that notes that the BTC price could touch $50,000 by the end of the year and $120,000 by the end of 2024.</p>
<h2>Standard Chartered&#8217;s Predictions on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The report also notes that the predicted jump in the Bitcoin price could also encourage miners to hoard more cash. Bitcoin miners have been on a strong footing this year after a brutal crypto winter of 2022. As the Bitcoin hash rate continues to climb, the Bitcoin miner revenue has also grown accordingly. Also, with the launch of Bitcoin ordinals, the miners filled their kitty in 2023.</p>
<p>Also, the Bitcoin blockchain shall be undergoing the most-awaited halving event in mid-2024 which will cut the miner rewards from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC. This creates supply shock thereby driving prices higher. On the other hand, Bitcoin miners will also continue to accumulate more and more BTC going ahead.</p>
<p>In April, Standard Chartered predicted a $100,000 forecast for Bitcoin by the end of 2024, indicating the end of the &#8220;crypto winter&#8221;, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/standard-chartered-bumps-up-bitcoin-forecast-120000-2023-07-10/?rpc=401&amp;" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> Reuters. However, Geoff Kendrick, one of the bank&#8217;s leading FX analysts, now believes there is a potential 20% upside to that prediction.</p>
<p>&#8220;Increased miner profitability per BTC (Bitcoin) mined means they can sell less while maintaining cash inflows, reducing net BTC supply and pushing BTC prices higher,&#8221; Kendrick said in a report.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whales Are Buying</h2>
<p>On-chain data shows that Bitcoin whales along with the sharks have been accumulating at every stage. Over the last three weeks, Bitcoin shark and whale addresses have accumulated a total of 71,000 Bitcoins. Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1677805758216556544" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Bitcoin&#8217;s sharks and whales aren&#8217;t showing any signs of slowing down, even with prices beginning to get &#8220;boring&#8221; in this $30k to $31k range. Since June 17th, 10 to 10k $BTC addresses have accumulated 71k more coins, equating to $2.15 billion.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>On the downside, Bitcoin has strong support. If the price continues to decline, it is expected to find strong support levels around $29,300 and $28,800. A significant support level is also anticipated at $25,000, which aligns with the 200 MA and the upward trendline that began earlier this year.</p>
<p>Also, macro factors will play a key role in going ahead. The economic outlook remains highly uncertain. In the US, there are signs that the period of lower inflation may come to an end, while inflation remains persistent globally, especially in European countries and particularly in the UK.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/">Standard Chartered Expects Bitcoin (BTC) Price to Surge to $120,000 by End of 2024</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BIS Survey Reveals 24 Central Banks Planning to Introduce CBDCs by 2030</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/">BIS Survey Reveals 24 Central Banks Planning to Introduce CBDCs by 2030</a></p>
<p>According to the survey, progress in the global development of CBDCs has continued since last year, with a particular emphasis on emerging economies where CBDCs are viewed as a means of providing financial access to unbanked individuals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/">BIS Survey Reveals 24 Central Banks Planning to Introduce CBDCs by 2030</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/">BIS Survey Reveals 24 Central Banks Planning to Introduce CBDCs by 2030</a></p>
<p>The Bank for International Settlements (BIS) has <a href="https://www.bis.org/publ/bppdf/bispap136.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">released</a> its 2022 survey on central bank digital currencies, revealing that approximately 24 central banks from developed and underdeveloped economies plan to introduce their own Central Bank Digital Currencies (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a>) in the coming years. The survey gathered responses from 86 central banks from around the world, highlighting the growing interest in digital currencies and their potential impact on global financial systems.</p>
<p>The BIS has been conducting the CBDC survey for six years to understand the motivation and intentions behind central banks&#8217; involvement in CBDCs, focusing on enhancing cross-border payments.</p>
<p>So far, only four central banks worldwide have officially launched their own digital currencies. However, the latest BIS survey shows a significant increase in interest among central banks, with 93% of respondents actively engaged in CBDC-related work.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the survey reveals that 60% of central banks stated that the emergence of stablecoins and other crypto assets had accelerated their efforts in developing CBDCs.</p>
<h2>Central Banks Could Introduce Nine Wholesale CBDCs</h2>
<p>While interest in retail CBDCs was higher than in the wholesale version, the survey indicates that two dozen central banks plan to have their digital currencies in circulation by the end of the decade. Within the retail space, 11 central banks are planning to join countries like the Bahamas, the Eastern Caribbean, Jamaica, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nigerians-adopt-cbdc-physical-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nigeria</a>, which already have live digital retail currencies. On the wholesale side, nine central banks intend to introduce wholesale CBDCs, which could provide financial institutions with access to new functionalities through tokenization.</p>
<p>&#8220;Based on the number of central banks that indicated that they would be very likely to issue a CBDC over the next few years, it may be that there will be 15 retail and nine wholesale CBDCs publicly circulating towards the end of this decade,&#8221; the survey states.</p>
<h2>Central Bank Progress in the Development and Testing of CBDC</h2>
<p>According to the survey, progress in the global development of CBDCs has continued since last year, with a particular emphasis on emerging economies where CBDCs are viewed as a means of providing financial access to unbanked individuals. The BIS also suggests that if retail CBDCs are introduced, they will likely complement and coexist alongside existing domestic payment methods.</p>
<p>For instance, the Swiss National Bank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-national-bank-wholesale-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plans</a> to issue a wholesale CBDC on Switzerland&#8217;s digital exchange as part of a pilot program, while the European Central Bank is moving forward with its digital euro-pilot, aiming for a potential launch in 2028. Other countries such as China, India, and Brazil have also announced plans to introduce their separate digital currencies soon.</p>
<p>However, the survey raises concerns regarding stablecoins and crypto assets, noting that if widely used for payments, they could threaten financial stability. Recent events in the crypto market, including the fall of TerraUSD and FTX and the bankruptcy of banks servicing crypto providers, have heightened these concerns and triggered sell-offs among investors.</p>
<p>Approximately 40% of the central banks surveyed have conducted studies on the usage of stablecoins and other crypto assets among consumers or businesses, indicating a growing recognition of the need to understand the implications of these digital assets on the stability of financial systems.</p>
<p>The BIS survey underscores the increasing momentum behind CBDCs, with many central banks actively exploring their potential implementation. As these digital currencies continue to evolve, they have the potential to reshape the future of global economies, enhancing financial stability and revolutionizing cross-border payments.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/">BIS Survey Reveals 24 Central Banks Planning to Introduce CBDCs by 2030</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bis-24-central-banks-cbdcs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Analyst Believes BTC Is Future of Money, BlackRock ETF Spurs Increased Demand</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin brice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/">Bitcoin Analyst Believes BTC Is Future of Money, BlackRock ETF Spurs Increased Demand</a></p>
<p>According to the analyst, Bitcoin has a better chance of being valuable and stable as it has a fixed and constant supply compared to other forms of money.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/">Bitcoin Analyst Believes BTC Is Future of Money, BlackRock ETF Spurs Increased Demand</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/">Bitcoin Analyst Believes BTC Is Future of Money, BlackRock ETF Spurs Increased Demand</a></p>
<p>Luke Broyles, a Bitcoin analyst, has made a series of bold statements about the future of Bitcoin. In some recent <a href="https://twitter.com/luke_broyles/status/1677439291562106880" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweets</a>, he mentioned how the implementation of AI will promote the use of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. The recent introduction of a Bitcoin payment <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lightning-labs-tools-bitcoin-ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">solution</a> for AI by Lightning Labs has also strengthened Luke&#8217;s claim. The solution aims to address the issue of restrictive and costly payments for AI by providing them with their own built-in method of paying over the Internet facilitated by Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The analyst believes that Bitcoin has a strong chance against political and government currencies. He thinks that people will increasingly use it as their primary form of payment, as it will absorb the wealth and prosperity of other sources, leaving behind those who have no prior exposure to it. This prediction is based on the idea that Bitcoin has a better chance of being valuable and stable due to its unique feature of having a fixed and constant supply compared to other forms of money.</p>
<p>According to his analysis, in order to compete with changing prices, innovations like AI will attempt to drive prices down. However, governments will continue to print more money to raise prices and keep credit markets open. In this scenario, the supply of Bitcoin will remain unchanged, making it a desirable asset. Consequently, those who have exposure to Bitcoin will benefit from it, as future prosperity will flow from it.</p>
<h2>Significant BTC Price Increase after BlackRock&#8217;s Spot Bitcoin ETF Announcement</h2>
<p>The Bitcoin analyst has also expressed surprise at BlackRock CEO Larry Fink&#8217;s positive statements about BTC. This is significant because Larry has been against Bitcoin in the past. Taking all these factors into account, Luke <a href="https://twitter.com/luke_broyles/status/1677439294691000320" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">believes</a> that:</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="text-align: center;">&#8220;The ACTUAL big deal is that all prosperity gains from all future innovations will flow into society&#8217;s base money &#8211; #BTC.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>Recently, BlackRock applied to issue a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">spot Bitcoin Trust ETF</a>, and since then, Bitcoin has continued to rise, moving from $24,000 to over $30,000  between June 15 and now. Following BlackRock&#8217;s announcement, there has been an increase in Bitcoin activities in the United States, indicating that the US is reevaluating its stance on Bitcoin exposure. It appears that there is a race to secure more Bitcoin supply. On July 8, Glassnode, a platform for blockchain and crypto data intelligence, also confirmed this in a <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1677637186559135745" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a>.</p>
<p>Many companies have applied for a spot Bitcoin ETF without receiving any positive replies yet from the SEC. These companies include Fidelity, Ark Invest, and Invesco. BlackRock&#8217;s first application was also rejected, with the SEC demanding a surveillance partner to spot issues like fraud.</p>
<p>Reports indicate that BlackRock naming Coinbase as the surveillance partner makes the application seem too good to reject. The significant aspect of BlackRock&#8217;s application is also the company&#8217;s track record of successfully obtaining ETF approvals. It has applied for 576 ETFs and had only one rejection.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/">Bitcoin Analyst Believes BTC Is Future of Money, BlackRock ETF Spurs Increased Demand</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-analyst-btc-money-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gucci Owner Kering Paid $3.8B to Acquire Fragrance Label Creed</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[creed fragrance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gucci]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hermes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lvmh]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LVMH Moët Hennessy Louis Vuitton]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/">Gucci Owner Kering Paid $3.8B to Acquire Fragrance Label Creed</a></p>
<p>Kering first signalled interest in the acquisition of Creed earlier this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/">Gucci Owner Kering Paid $3.8B to Acquire Fragrance Label Creed</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/">Gucci Owner Kering Paid $3.8B to Acquire Fragrance Label Creed</a></p>
<p>A Financial Times <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/79ca0a2d-4114-425c-8b35-74042838ae6f" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> has revealed how much Gucci owner Kering paid to acquire fragrance label Creed late last month. Per the report, which cited in-house sources, the deal saw Kering pay around 3.5 billion euros (approximately $3.83 billion).</p>
<p>Kering, the French luxury group, first signaled interest in the acquisition of Creed earlier this year. At the time, Kering said the acquisition is in line with its efforts to expand its beauty unit. The group also projected that the acquisition will improve its chances to compete against the likes of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/lvmh/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LVMH</a> and Hermès.</p>
<p>According to the FT&#8217;s Monday report, however, the all-cash deal for the Paris-based luxury group to buy 100% of Creed from funds controlled by BlackRock Inc. and current chairman Javier Ferran, will close sometime in the second half of the year.</p>
<p>Although the payment was reportedly made last month, FT suggests that the firm may have intentionally left out the details of the transaction initially. This was so as not to publish Creed&#8217;s robust profit margins.</p>
<h2>Kering Keen on Beauty Unit Success</h2>
<p>As earlier mentioned, the recent move by Kering is aimed at strengthening its beauty segment. And to that end, the group named Raffaella Cornaggia to head the unit in February.</p>
<p>However, it is noteworthy that its focus on the so-called beauty unit may have been influenced by some of its rivals in the luxury business. For example, it is worth noting that Hermès International and LVMH Moët Hennessy Louis Vuitton SE have been relatively successful in the beauty segment recently.</p>
<p>More so, Kering&#8217;s interest in acquisitions goes beyond just Creed. And to achieve its aim, the firm has been raising funds from all sides. It, however, saw the most significant fund to help its cause from the sale of its Puma SE stake.</p>
<p>By acquiring Creed, Kering will be looking to tap into the growing demand for luxury cosmetics. But more importantly, it would also be hoping to leverage its reputable brands like Gucci, to scale its cosmetics business.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/">Gucci Owner Kering Paid $3.8B to Acquire Fragrance Label Creed</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gucci-kering-acquire-creed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Carl Icahn and Banks Finalize Amended Loan Agreements</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[carl icahn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hindenburg research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Icahn Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/">Carl Icahn and Banks Finalize Amended Loan Agreements</a></p>
<p>Following the publication of the Hindenburg Research study, Icahn Enterprises’ stock fell to a low of $31.78, the company’s lowest value in more than ten years.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/">Carl Icahn and Banks Finalize Amended Loan Agreements</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/">Carl Icahn and Banks Finalize Amended Loan Agreements</a></p>
<p>Billionaire investor Carl Icahn and several banks have reached an agreement to amend loan terms that previously tied Icahn&#8217;s personal loans to the trading price of Icahn Enterprises  (NASDAQ: IEP).</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/carl-icahn-gets-breathing-room-from-lenders-following-short-seller-attack-7f44133c" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> from the Wall Street Journal, Carl Icahn and lender banks have now finalized amended loan agreements that untie Icahn&#8217;s personal loans from the trading price of Icahn Enterprises. This significant move aims to address the concerns raised by the short-seller, Hindenburg Research report and create a more stable borrowing arrangement for Icahn.</p>
<p>By untying Icahn’s personal loans from the trading performance of Icahn Enterprises, the amended agreement ensures that his borrowing terms are no longer at the mercy of the stock’s volatility. This separation offers Icahn the freedom to make financial decisions based on his personal objectives and market analysis, without the added pressure of his company’s stock price fluctuations.</p>
<p>According to people familiar with the matter, Carl Icahn has reached an agreement to increase the collateral provided for his loans and has outlined a plan to fully repay the loans within three years. This move not only mitigates potential risks associated with the loans but also provides greater assurance to stakeholders and investors.</p>
<p>Carl Icahn, a well-known investor, and businessman, has a long history in the financial world. Icahn Enterprises, his investment firm, has been active in a variety of industries, including energy, automobile, and real estate.</p>
<p>Icahn has become well-known for his activist investing method, which entails taking major holdings in firms and advocating for changes to increase shareholder value. Last year, the billionaire investor <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-250m-risky-bet-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">made</a> a significant profit after investing up to $500 million in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter Inc</a>.</p>
<h2>Hindenburg Research&#8217;s Allegations on Carl Icahn and Ventures</h2>
<p>In May, Hindenburg Research <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/carl-icahns-investment-firm-tumbles-18-after-hindenburg-attack-2023-05-03/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">published</a> a report on Icahn Enterprises, arguing that the corporation overvalued its holdings and paid dividends through a “Ponzi-like” structure. The investigation called into doubt the authenticity and transparency of Icahn Enterprises’ financial statements, focusing on the valuation of its holdings.</p>
<p>Hindenburg Research had highlighted concerns about Icahn’s IEP holding being heavily collateralized for unidentified margin loans. The research raised concerns regarding the use of more than 65% of IEP shares as collateral, expressing concerns about the potential risks involved.</p>
<p>At the time, Carl Icahn dismissed the report as “self-serving.” He stood firmly behind Icahn Enterprises’ financial statements, defending the accuracy and reliability of the company&#8217;s valuation practices and dividend distribution methods. Icahn emphasized that the report was an attempt to manipulate the market and benefit Hindenburg Research’s own interests.</p>
<p>Following the publication of the Hindenburg Research study, Icahn Enterprises’ stock fell to a low of $31.78, the company’s lowest value in more than ten years. This fall represents a lack of investor confidence and indicates the market&#8217;s reaction to Hindenburg Research’s concerns.</p>
<p>However, the recent agreement serves to reassure investors and stakeholders in Icahn Enterprises. By demonstrating a commitment to transparency and risk mitigation, Icahn and his lenders instill confidence in the company’s stability and management.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/">Carl Icahn and Banks Finalize Amended Loan Agreements</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/carl-icahn-banks-loan-agreements/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs: India to Become World’s Second-Largest Economy Overtaking US by 2075</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=262263</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/">Goldman Sachs: India to Become World&#8217;s Second-Largest Economy Overtaking US by 2075</a></p>
<p>Goldman Sachs notes that India's lowering dependency rate, emphasis on infrastructure boost, and capital investment inflows will spearhead the country's economic output in the next few decades. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/">Goldman Sachs: India to Become World&#8217;s Second-Largest Economy Overtaking US by 2075</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/">Goldman Sachs: India to Become World&#8217;s Second-Largest Economy Overtaking US by 2075</a></p>
<p>As per the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> forecast, India is poised to become the world&#8217;s second-largest economy overtaking not just Japan and Germany, but also the US by 2075. As of date, India holds the fifth rank behind Germany, Japan, China, and the US.</p>
<p>In their recent report, Goldman Sachs noted that apart from its burgeoning population, India is seeing accelerated progress in innovation and technology. Furthermore, higher capital investment and rising worker productivity will aid India&#8217;s growth.</p>
<p>Goldman Sachs Research’s India economist, Santanu Sengupta, noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Over the next two decades, the dependency ratio of India will be one of the lowest among regional economies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>A country&#8217;s dependency ratio is a measure of the number of dependents compared to the total working-age population. A low dependency ratio means that there are relatively more working-age adults who can provide support to the younger and older population.</p>
<p>Sengupta emphasized that unlocking the potential of India&#8217;s fast-growing population relies on increasing the involvement of its workforce. According to Sengupta&#8217;s projections, India is expected to maintain one of the lowest dependency ratios compared to other major economies over the next two decades. He <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/how-india-could-rise-to-the-worlds-second-biggest-economy.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“So that really is the window for India to get it right in terms of setting up manufacturing capacity, continuing to grow services, continuing the growth of infrastructure.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The current Indian government had put greater priority and emphasis on infrastructure. They have been working at a fast pace to expand the country&#8217;s road and rail networks. In their recent budget, the central government has floated 50-year interest-free loan programs for state governments to spur investments in infrastructure.</p>
<h2>India&#8217;s Growing Tech Industry</h2>
<p>Goldman Sachs noted that India&#8217;s advancement in technology and innovation is playing a crucial role in driving its economic development. According to Nasscom, a non-governmental trade association in India, the revenue of the country&#8217;s technology industry is projected to surge by $245 billion by the end of 2023. This growth will be fueled by various sectors including IT, business process management, and software product streams, as highlighted in Nasscom&#8217;s report.</p>
<p>As per the investment bank, capital investment will also prove to be a significant driver in India&#8217;s growth story. It noted: “India’s savings rate is likely to increase with falling dependency ratios, rising incomes, and deeper financial sector development, which is likely to make the pool of capital available to drive further investment.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, Goldman Sachs has also mentioned a few downside risks that India could be facing. One gray area is the declining labor participation rate.</p>
<p>The report notes that the labor force participation rate in India has declined over the last 15 years. It also emphasizes that women&#8217;s participation rate in the labor force is significantly lower than men&#8217;s.</p>
<p>In a separate report in June, the investment bank writes that a mere 20% of all working-age women in India are employed. It further points out that the low figure could be due to women primarily engaging in piecework, which the economic measures of formal employment do not account for.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-sales-ai-tools-chips/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/">Goldman Sachs: India to Become World&#8217;s Second-Largest Economy Overtaking US by 2075</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4084 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1052631 metric#prefetches=155 metric#store-reads=48 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=203 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=97.45 metric#ms-cache=7.78 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1587 metric#ms-cache-ratio=8.0 -->