<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:55:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance on SEC’s lawsuit on Monday: ‘we will vigorously defend’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC sued Binance for violating securities laws on Monday. Here&#8217;s what Binance said in its response to the regulator. Coinbase Global ended 10% down on today&#8217;s development. Binance is in focus on Monday after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange. Here&#8217;s what Binance said in its response to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/">Binance on SEC’s lawsuit on Monday: ‘we will vigorously defend’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>SEC sued Binance for violating securities laws on Monday.</li>
<li>Here&rsquo;s what Binance said in its response to the regulator.</li>
<li>Coinbase Global ended 10% down on today&rsquo;s development.</li>
</ul>
<p>Binance is in focus on Monday after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued the world&rsquo;s leading crypto exchange.</p>
<h2>Here&rsquo;s what Binance said in its response to SEC</h2>
<p>In its lawsuit, the regulator <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-over-u-s-rule-violations-6918ed0f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">accused</a> Binance as well as its CEO Changpeng Zhao for failing to comply with the U.S. securities laws. The CFTC had previously filed such charges against the crypto company as well.</p>
<p>SEC also alleged that Binance commingled user funds worth billions of dollars with Merit Peak Limited &ndash; a CZ-controlled European company. Only hours later, though, Binance declined claims of wrongdoing and said in its <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/sec-complaint-aims-to-unilaterally-define-crypto-market-structure-8707489117122437402" target="_blank" rel="noopener">official response</a> to the regulator:</p>
<blockquote><p>Any allegations that user assets on the Binance.US platform have ever been at risk are simply wrong. We will vigorously defend against any allegations to the contrary.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto community stood with Binance on Twitter</h2>
<p>On Twitter, the crypto community demonstrated support for Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao. Many found the SEC unfair in the way it was dealing with crypto assets in the United States.</p>
<p>In its response, Binance also said that the regulator&rsquo;s overreach was hurting the U.S. reputation as a global hub for financial innovation. Still, it added:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;ll continue to cooperate with regulators and policymakers across the globe. We remain committed to productive engagement to ensure next-gen of crypto regulation fosters innovation.</p></blockquote>
<p>SEC&rsquo;s lawsuit against Binance saw shares of peer <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> lose about 10% today.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-response-to-sec-lawsuit/">Binance on SEC’s lawsuit on Monday: ‘we will vigorously defend’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan teams up with six Indian banks to build a blockchain-based platform</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The blockchain-based platform is aimed at settling interbank dollar transactions. The move is part of the Indian government&#8217;s strategy to elevate GIFT City to the League of Cities like Singapore. The parties will launch a pilot project over the next few months in order to analyze the banks&#8217; experience. American multinational financial behemoth JPMorgan Chase [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/">JPMorgan teams up with six Indian banks to build a blockchain-based platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The blockchain-based platform is aimed at settling interbank dollar transactions.</li>
<li>The move is part of the Indian government&rsquo;s strategy to elevate GIFT City to the League of Cities like Singapore.</li>
<li>The parties will launch a pilot project over the next few months in order to analyze the banks&rsquo; experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>American multinational financial behemoth JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. has partnered with Indian banks to build a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a>-based platform to settle interbank dollar transactions.</p>
<p>The Indian banks involved are based in the Gujarat International Finance Tec-City (GIFT) City and include HDFC Bank Ltd., ICICI Bank Ltd., Axis Bank Ltd., Yes Bank Ltd., and IndusInd Bank Ltd.</p>
<h2>Elevating GIFT City status</h2>
<p>Although it is a partnership within the private sector, the move is part of the Indian government&rsquo;s strategy of elevating GIFT City to a level where it can compete with the likes of Hong Kong, Singapore, the International Financial Centre (IFC) in Dubai, and the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM).</p>
<p>Kaustubh Kulkarni, a senior Indian officer, and vice chairman of Asia Pacific, at JPMorgan, have stated that the institution would be launching a pilot project in the coming months to examine banks&rsquo; experience.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan and blockchain technology</h2>
<p>JPMorgan also plans to use blockchain technology to restructure dollar transactions between financial institutions so that the transactions can be completed in a matter of seconds.</p>
<p>According to Kulkarni, GIFT City banks would be able to maintain their own time zone and business hours once JPMorgan creates the blockchain infrastructure enabling instant transactions around the clock.</p>
<p>JPMorgan&rsquo;s pilot project using the Onyx blockchain technology is already expected to start on Monday after receiving clearance from the International Financial Services Centre Authority. Onyx, which is a blockchain-based platform for wholesale payment transactions was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-launches-its-own-stablecoin/">launched by JPMorgan in 2020</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/">JPMorgan teams up with six Indian banks to build a blockchain-based platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/jpmorgan-teams-up-with-six-indian-banks-to-build-a-blockchain-based-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC sues Binance and CZ for breaking US Securities Rules</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The US SEC has sued Binance for breaking securities rules. The regulatory agency has also sued Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange. SEC sues Binance and CZ The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a lawsuit against Binance, the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, and Changpeng Zhao, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">SEC sues Binance and CZ for breaking US Securities Rules</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The US SEC has sued Binance for breaking securities rules.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency has also sued Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC sues Binance and CZ</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a lawsuit against Binance, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency exchange, and Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of the company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is according to a <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-binance-over-u-s-rule-violations-6918ed0f" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>report by The Wall Street Journal</u></a> a few minutes ago. According to the Wall Street Journal, the regulatory agency has sued Binance and its CEO for breaking US securities rules.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> doesn&rsquo;t come as a surprise to some experts in the industry, as the regulatory agency has been going after cryptocurrency exchanges in recent months.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance faces 13 charges from the SEC</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency alleges that Binance secretly allow[ed] high-value U.S. customers&rdquo; to trade on the platform in violation of U.S. securities laws which prohibits unregistered exchanges from servicing U.S. customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The lawsuit also alleges that CZ exercised control over customer assets, adding that he commingled them with personal and company holdings. SEC Chairman Gary Gensler stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Through thirteen charges, we allege that Zhao and Binance entities engaged in an extensive web of deception, conflicts of interest, lack of disclosure, and calculated evasion of the law. As alleged, Zhao and Binance misled investors about their risk controls and corrupted trading volumes while actively concealing who was operating the platform, the manipulative trading of its affiliated market maker, and even where and with whom investor funds and crypto assets were custodied.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes two weeks after the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-crypto-exchange-bittrex-and-its-ex-ceo/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>SEC sued Bittrex</u></a>, one of the world&rsquo;s largest and oldest cryptocurrency exchanges, and co-founder and ex-CEO William Shihara for violating securities laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency had also come after several other crypto exchanges in recent months, including Kraken and Coinbase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has lost more than 2% of its value so far today and could fall below the $26k level soon following this latest development. At press time, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">price of Bitcoin</a> stands at $26,682 per coin.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">SEC sues Binance and CZ for breaking US Securities Rules</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Than Cute Memes &#8211; The Top 12 Utility Tokens Give Investors More For Their Money</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/more-than-cute-memes-the-top-12-utility-tokens-give-investors-more-for-their-money/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basic Attention Token News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/more-than-cute-memes-the-top-12-utility-tokens-give-investors-more-for-their-money/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins might be fun, but holding them rarely has any additional benefits. This is in stark contrast to utility tokens, which provide unprecedented access to some of blockchain&#8217;s most innovative projects. To find out which utility tokens are the best, here are the 12 hottest options on the market right now: Chancer (CHANCER) AltSignals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/more-than-cute-memes-the-top-12-utility-tokens-give-investors-more-for-their-money/">More Than Cute Memes &#8211; The Top 12 Utility Tokens Give Investors More For Their Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Meme coins might be fun, but holding them rarely has any additional benefits. This is in stark contrast to utility tokens, which provide unprecedented access to some of blockchain&rsquo;s most innovative projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To find out which utility tokens are the best, here are the 12 hottest options on the market right now:</p>
<ul>
<li>Chancer (CHANCER)</li>
<li dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Metacade (MCADE)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chainlink (LINK)</li>
<li dir="ltr">1Inch Network (1INCH)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Basic Attention Token (BAT)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Binance Coin (BNB)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Ripple (XRP)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chiliz (CHZ)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Ethereum (ETH)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Yearn.Finance (YFI)</li>
<li dir="ltr">Enjin Coin (ENJ)</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">1. Chancer (CHANCER)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> (CHANCER) is the world&rsquo;s first decentralized predictive markets app which aims to revolutionize the betting industry. Chancer is simply a betting facilitator, so there&rsquo;s no house or bookmaker to lose to, which will appeal to betting enthusiasts. The power is firmly in the hands of the users. Moreover, any sort of bet can be made on the platform, big or small, from casual bets between friends, to viral bets on huge events like the Superbowl or the Oscars. Bets are not restricted to just sports, thus the potential user base is much bigger than that of traditional betting houses. All bets and winnings are made in CHANCER, Chancer&rsquo;s native token. Users are rewarded simply from using the app, earning them a passive income whilst engaging in something they would usually use anyway.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Uniquely, Chancer uses Google&rsquo;s WebRTC to live stream events to Chancer&rsquo;s market-making community. Additionally, the platform has impartial market moderators, ensuring all outcomes are correct and fair for all parties involved. To enhance transparency, the platform has been built on blockchain.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy CHANCER?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">There is plenty of opportunity to make great returns with CHANCER. The token is currently in its first presale stage and seems undervalued at a mere $0.01. Experts predict that, due to its disruptive nature, CHANCER is set to soar in price and could even potentially reach $1 by the end of the year. Given the size of the betting industry &mdash; worth over $60 billion &mdash; CHANCER could soar as a real challenger in the space, making it an excellent investment for gamers and investors alike.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can participate in the Chancer presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">2. AltSignals (ASI)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> (ASI) has supported 50,000 crypto traders with profitable trading signals since it first launched in 2017, and is now expanding its blockchain offering with an artificial intelligence toolkit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform&rsquo;s proprietary trading indicator, AltAlgo, has helped traders who matched its calls to 10x their portfolio in 19 separate months. The new AI-powered toolkit, ActualizeAI, is designed to improve the frequency and accuracy of trading signals, which gives it massive value in the realm of crypto trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ActualizeAI uses natural language processing (NLP) and predictive modelling to achieve a higher accuracy rate than alternative trading tools. Its machine learning capabilities are expected to constantly evolve its utility, which is accessed through holding the project&rsquo;s new native token, ASI.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI also gives access to AI Members Club, which provides additional benefits to AltSignals users. By holding the ASI utility token, users gain access to lucrative investment opportunities for early-stage cryptocurrencies and can compete in online trading tournaments for the chance to win cryptocurrency prizes.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy ASI?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The ASI token is brand-new and powers an existing platform that has a proven track record for success. By combining artificial intelligence with algorithmic indicators, AltSignals delivers profitable trading signals with an unprecedented level of accuracy. ASI token holders gain exclusive access to this new suite of tools and can gain a real edge while trading as a result.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ASI crypto presale is still ongoing. Early participants are expected to see major returns on their initial investment, and the ASI token is also designed to provide greater access to profitable investments in the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is certainly one of the top utility tokens around right now and the presale is a highly promising investment opportunity as a result. Crypto utility tokens rarely provide users with additional avenues for making a profit, which makes ASI stand out in the world of Web3.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can participate in the AltSignals presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">3. Metacade (MCADE)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en/?utm_source=media" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> (MCADE) is a GameFi platform that offers a vast selection of different arcade-style games in a single location. <strong>Each title has play-to-earn mechanics, allowing gamers to earn cryptocurrency rewards while they progress through levels and advance their skills</strong>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Gameplay in the metaverse arcade ranges from casual to competitive, as Metacade&rsquo;s Compete2Earn feature allows players to go head-to-head for the chance to win major prizes paid in MCADE tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE has vast utility within the Metacade ecosystem, with its primary use case being to provide rewards as users participate in the platform&rsquo;s various features. Metacade&rsquo;s features go beyond the arcade, as users can also earn MCADE while sharing knowledge, interacting with other users, and testing out new blockchain games before they are officially launched.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade aims to become a central hub for the Web3 community as it offers a central location to access some of the most valuable alpha in the blockchain gaming and cryptocurrency space. MCADE powers an advanced incentive system that is expected to attract a significant number of users over time.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy MCADE?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Not only is Metacade a comprehensive GameFi platform with a range of earning mechanics, but the platform also supports the development of new arcade games directly through the Metagrants program. MCADE token holders can vote to decide which new projects receive funding, as MCADE gains additional utility as one of the best governance tokens to be launched in recent times.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>&gt;&gt;&gt; You can find more information, including how to buy Metacade&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en/?utm_source=media" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>&nbsp;&lt;&lt;&lt;</strong></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">4. ChainLink (LINK)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is ChainLink?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ChainLink, or LINK as it is commonly known, is a type of decentralized network that connects blockchain platforms to external systems. ChainLink does this by collecting data from off-chain sources before recording it in blockchain-compatible APIs that can be used in smart contracts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The network is a tamper-proof and reliable way to securely transfer data between two incompatible systems. ChainLink provides data from real-world events that is stored in off-chain databases, which allows for a greater range of blockchain applications to be built using smart contracts and self-executing codes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ChainLink nodes are responsible for gathering and connecting the right data in order for these processes to occur automatically on the blockchain. The ChainLink solution makes it possible to build secure and reliable applications with improved complexity, making blockchain a viable alternative to centralized application networks.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy LINK?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ChainLink has become a top 20 cryptocurrency by market cap thanks to its unique blockchain solution. It&rsquo;s a decentralized storage network that serves an important function in Web3, and it has formed hundreds of major partnerships as a result.</p>
<p dir="ltr">LINK is naturally different from most utility tokens, as the network is used to grant access to data that would otherwise be unavailable on the blockchain. It is a highly sought-after crypto asset investment and one of the top utility tokens because it supports the wider crypto ecosystem directly.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">5. 1Inch Network (1INCH)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is 1Inch Network?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">1Inch Network, or 1INCH, is a decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregator that aims to provide the best possible trades for its users. Since the particular service offered by 1Inch Network is fully decentralized, it relies on complex smart contracts to find the ideal route for peer-to-peer cryptocurrency transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">1Inch is one of the largest crypto exchanges. 1Inch can also help to minimize costs as users pay transaction fees, as the smart contracts deployed by the platform consider the most cost-effective routes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">1INCH, the native token, offers a rebate of 1% &ndash; 7% of commissions on all transactions after connecting to the 1INCH swap protocol. The network ensures maximum efficiency for its users by harnessing external blockchain pools that contain token liquidity, allowing users access to global crypto markets and offering optimized rates.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy 1INCH?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The 1Inch token is one of the best examples of utility tokens powering a decentralized protocol, as the utility coin incentivizes external parties to contribute towards the protocol. 1INCH doubles as a governance token, allowing all holders of security tokens to vote in proposals made by the 1Inch Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The current price of 1INCH is $0.50. It is one of the best buy utility cryptocurrency investments as it has significant upside potential from the current price level. 1INCH has access to liquidity from 10 different blockchains, making it stand out from other utility tokens on this list.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">6. Basic Attention Token (BAT)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Basic Attention Token?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Basic Attention Token (BAT) is a blockchain-based, decentralised digital advertising system designed to offer higher efficiency and improved transparency in online advertising. BAT is the platform&rsquo;s native utility token which enables on-platform rewards for users who watch online advertisements.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Basic Attention Token platform is linked to Brave browser to enable privacy-preserving advertisements. Companies can purchase ad space directly on the network using BAT tokens, and a portion of all transactions is circulated back to both advertisers and users when adverts are watched.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform seeks to balance user privacy, publisher benefit and advertiser spend by making use of BAT tokens and Brave browser. In this anonymous system, users receive rewards for their attention to digital advertisements.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy BAT?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">BAT is an example of how utility tokens work to facilitate a broad number of blockchain use cases, as Basic Attention Token&rsquo;s unique blockchain infrastructure helps minimise ad fraud, improves user privacy and provides higher investment returns for advertisers due to improved targeting capabilities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The current price of BAT is $0.23. Not all utility tokens have a truly unique offering, but Basic Attention Token is a prime example of a coin that solves a specific problem using open-source distributed ledger technology. BAT is, without a doubt, one of the top utility tokens in Web3.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">7. Binance Coin (BNB)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Binance Coin?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin (BNB) is a cryptocurrency created by Binance, the company behind the largest of all centralized exchanges (CEX) in Web3 by daily trading volume. BNB is used to power the Binance Ecosystem, allowing traders and businesses to use BNB for various fees, such as token listings and trading fees on the centralized exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB is also used to pay gas fees for Binance Smart Chain (BSC), which is the most-used decentralized blockchain network in the world. It supports the development of custom tokens and applications, which has led to increasing utility for BNB as it is essential while using the network.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>By holding BNB tokens, users can also gain discounts on trading fees while using Binance exchange</strong>. Binance exchange also offers staking services to allow BNB holders to earn a passive income on the platform.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy BNB?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is one of the most influential crypto projects in the world and the platform&rsquo;s native token plays a crucial role. It powers the company&rsquo;s range of different blockchain assets and services, including the largest CEX and the most-used blockchain infrastructure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The current price of BNB is $307, down from an all-time high at $690. As one of the most comprehensive utility tokens in the crypto space, the current price level could be a great entry point for long-term investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">8. Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Ripple (XRP)?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">XRP, also known as Ripple, is a digital asset designed for use in secure and scalable payments. XRP was created by Ripple Labs Inc to provide banks and payment providers an instant and low-cost global settlement system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XRP has proven itself to be faster, safer and more efficient than traditional methods of transferring money internationally &ndash; allowing users to make transactions within seconds regardless of their geographic location.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XRP is one of the most popular utility tokens for financial institutions because it can provide instant liquidity for cross-border transactions. It is a cost-effective way of processing foreign exchange requests, as any fiat currency can be swapped for XRP before the transaction value is sent across the world in seconds.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy XRP?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">XRP continues to hold tremendous potential as a reliable, cost-effective way of transferring digital money across borders, despite its <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/roslynlayton/2021/12/29/sec-v-ripple-the-cryptocurrency-trial-of-the-century/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ongoing court case</u></a> with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC aims to prove that XRP is a security due to it being created by a centralized company, while Ripple argues that there was no initial coin offering (ICO) to raise funds and that the XRP security token is primarily used to secure a decentralized blockchain called XRP Ledger.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many different utility tokens fall under the same category as XRP, as a degree of centralization is necessary for an organization to achieve a goal. The industry is expected to gain regulatory clarity in the wake of the XRP trial, which could massively boost the total value price of XRP if it emerges victorious.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">9. Chiliz (CHZ)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Chiliz?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Chiliz (CHZ) is a digital fintech platform that specializes in blockchain technology and sports engagement. Its goal is to leverage an innovative platform to develop fan engagement and monetization opportunities for the world&rsquo;s leading sports brands, including teams, individual athletes, and federations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chiliz&rsquo;s technology also allows supporters to gain voting privileges for their favorite sports teams. CHZ tokens are used to purchase fan tokens that can be used to participate in governance. Not only does this make fans feel closer to the day-to-day action, but it also provides an additional revenue stream for sports franchises.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Through Chiliz, fans have the power to influence their favorite sports in ways that were never before possible, while receiving financial rewards via Fan Tokens for participating. Chiliz has already reached tremendous success, securing partnership deals with major sporting organizations such as LaLiga Santander, AC Milan and more.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy CHZ?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">CHZ holders access voting rights and can influence preceedings at major sporting organizations in brand-new ways. In exchange for having their voices heard, fans receive rewards with monetary value. CHZ underlies this entire process and is therefore one of the top utility tokens in Web3.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The current price of CHZ is $0.12. The native crypto coin for the Chiliz ecosystem has vast potential for the future thanks to its useful solution for major sporting enterprises, making it one of the best utilities to buy for the long-term.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">10. Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Ethereum?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum (ETH) is a blockchain-based, open-source platform that allows developers to build and deploy decentralized applications. Ethereum supports self-executing smart contracts, where contractual agreements are written in code and executed automatically when certain conditions are met.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum decentralizes data storage and enables peer-to-peer interactions without the need for third parties such as banks. Ethereum uses its own native cryptocurrency, Ether, which is used to pay gas fees every time they interact with the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Transaction fees are the primary use case for Ethereum. Since Ethereum supports almost 2000 independent decentralized applications (dApps), ENS domains, and the majority of non fungible tokens (NFTs), this gives ETH tremendous value within the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy ETH?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">ETH has seen widespread use as both an investment vehicle and a digital currency, owing to it being a medium of exchange within Web3. <strong>Its utility as a medium of exchange is a primary source of demand for the token</strong>, which is the second largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since Ethereum completed <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/08/26/technology/what-is-the-merge.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>The Merge</u></a> in 2022, the Ethereum blockchain has switched to a proof-of-stake protocol. This makes the network more efficient, which could help it support an increasing number of applications and users over time. ETH is certainly one of the top utility tokens to buy now for future returns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">11. Yearn.Finance (YFI)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Yearn.Finance?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Yearn.Finance (YFI) is a decentralized finance platform that enables users to maximize their earning potential. Through Yearn.Finance, users can optimize their cryptocurrency yield using a selection of automated strategies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">YFI provides all the services that a traditional financial advisor or bank would offer without the fees associated. It is similar to a traditional hedge fund, except the platform analyzes the most profitable strategies for yield farming across many leading DeFi projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Yearn.Finance is user-friendly and requires little effort to use, as anyone can access a full suite of DeFi services simply by depositing funds on the platform. Its intuitive design and integrated tools allow users to increase their income while saving both time and money.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy YFI?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">YFI utility token holders gain governance privileges in the Yearn.Finance DAO. Tokens can also be earned as a reward for staking on the platform, which helps to facilitate transactions and sustain liquidity levels and secure the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a leading DeFi aggregator that offers a comprehensive suite of tools, YFI is one of the best utility tokens on the crypto market. YFI has extremely scarce tokenomics, with just 36,666 tokens in circulation. Its deflationary design made it the first crypto to be worth more than Bitcoin and gives it major potential for future investment returns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">12. Enjin Coin (ENJ)</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What is Enjin Coin?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Enjin Coin (ENJ) is a popular cryptocurrency that was developed for use within the Enjin Network. It is an Ethereum-based token that was specially designed to enable the easy creation of digital assets for <a href="https://blog.quillhash.com/2019/06/10/blockchain-gaming-revolution/#:~:text=Focusing%20on%20the%20problems%20with%20the%20current%20traditional,ownership%20and%20trustless%20circulation%20of%20in-game%20virtual%20assets." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blockchain gaming</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Enjin enables developers and gamers to create virtual goods with custom functions. This can include in-game trading capabilities, variable scarcity levels and more. ENJ utility tokens represent a method of locking liquidity in in-game digital assets, which provides near-instant, low-slippage trading for blockchain gaming marketplaces.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ENJ utility tokens generally serve the creation of in-game digital assets, but they can also be used to pay transaction fees on Enjin Network and to help developers create NFT-based games. Marketplaces that are compatible with ENJ can be ported into custom-built dApps, helping make a smooth user experience for blockchain-based gamers.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Why buy ENJ?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Enjin Coin has vast utility within the Enjin ecosystem, which is a comprehensive suite of tools that helps to boost the overall level of development in GameFi. By easing the process of creating gaming applications on the blockchain, ENJ plays an important role in the blockchain gaming revolution.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ENJ tokens are currently valued at $0.40 and have major upside potential. As blockchain gaming grows in popularity, unique crypto assets that use ENJ facilities are likely to become more prevalent. As a result, ENJ is one of the best utility tokens to buy right now.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Related Crypto FAQs</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">What makes a token utility?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">A cryptocurrency typically offers utility within a specific platform when it is classified as a medium of exchange to facilitate peer-to-peer transactions. This sets utility tokens apart as digital currencies, as they are used to transfer value from one independent party to another in exchange for a digital good, service or asset.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Which crypto has real utility?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Most top cryptocurrencies have real utility. In fact, few cryptocurrencies have no utility. Prominent exceptions are meme coins and scam tokens; however, meme coins can still be used as a medium of exchange as long as there is token liquidity on the blockchain.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Which altcoins have the most utility?</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Major projects such as Binance, Chancer and AltSignals have extensive utility for their native token. Each project offers something unique to blockchain users, and the utility token helps to power each ecosystem in different ways.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/more-than-cute-memes-the-top-12-utility-tokens-give-investors-more-for-their-money/">More Than Cute Memes &#8211; The Top 12 Utility Tokens Give Investors More For Their Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s why the MANA, SAND, Enjin, AXS token prices are soaring</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-mana-sand-enjin-axs-token-prices-are-soaring/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-mana-sand-enjin-axs-token-prices-are-soaring/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ENJ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enjin Coin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-mana-sand-enjin-axs-token-prices-are-soaring/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most metaverse tokens rose sharply on Monday as cryptocurrencies retreated. The jump happened ahead of Apple&#8217;s WWDC event on Monday. Metaverse tokens like Decentraland MANA, Sandbox&#8217;s SAND, and Axie Infinity&#8217;s AXS were among the best-performing coins on Monday. Other metaverse tokens like Enjin Coin and ApeCoin were also in the green. Most of these coins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-mana-sand-enjin-axs-token-prices-are-soaring/">Here’s why the MANA, SAND, Enjin, AXS token prices are soaring</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Most metaverse tokens rose sharply on Monday as cryptocurrencies retreated.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The jump happened ahead of Apple&rsquo;s WWDC event on Monday.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Metaverse tokens like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/decentraland/"><u>Decentraland</u></a> MANA, Sandbox&rsquo;s SAND, and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/axie-infinity/"><u>Axie Infinity</u></a>&rsquo;s AXS were among the best-performing coins on Monday. Other metaverse tokens like Enjin Coin and ApeCoin were also in the green. Most of these coins rose by more than 1.5%, which is a better performer than other coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/05/1685969373384-17a6efcc-a12f-4685-a75a-67db9f919ef0.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.471px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.471"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Apple WWDC event</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The main reason why metaverse tokens jumped on Monday is the upcoming WWDC event by Apple. Historically, this has been the biggest event in the tech calendar since the company usually unveils its key upgrades.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apple is seen as the benchmark for key products. It made key products like iPhones, Apple Watch, and iPads cool. Today, other companies in the technology industry have come up with similar products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts believe that the WWDC event will see the company unveil its virtual reality set, which is its first major product in a decade. The company has been working on this product in the past seven years. In this period, the company has long believed that its product was not ready yet. According to the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-vr-headset-ios-17-new-mac-wwdc-21178480"><u>WSJ</u></a>, the device will retail at $3,000, making it one of the company&rsquo;s most premium products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Experts believe that Apple&rsquo;s entry in the industry will take the virtual reality industry mainstream. In the past, attempts by companies like Facebook and Microsoft to take them mainstream have failed. Today, only a handful of people use these products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-the-metaverse/"><u>metaverse</u></a> tokens like MANA, SAND, Enjin Coin, and AXS token have risen because of the ongoing hype. There is a belief that this hype could rival that of artificial intelligence.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will the metaverse tokens rally continue?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Decentraland MANA price jumped by more than 6% while Sandbox and Axie Infinity price soared by more than 5%. Similarly, Enjin and ApeCoin rose by over 4%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, I believe that these gains will not hold because of a concept known as buying the rumor and selling the news. This is a situation where an asset price jumps ahead of a major news release and then declines when the news happens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In this case, these tokens will retreat possibly because Apple&rsquo;s device will not have anything to do with these tokens and their ecosystem.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Decentraland</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQyMDM4&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy MANA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQyMDM4&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy MANA with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-mana-sand-enjin-axs-token-prices-are-soaring/">Here’s why the MANA, SAND, Enjin, AXS token prices are soaring</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-mana-sand-enjin-axs-token-prices-are-soaring/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Binance&#8217;s dominance falling?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/is-binances-dominance-falling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/is-binances-dominance-falling/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Binance&#8217;s share of trading volume is at 48%, despite being 66% at the start of the year Exchange has landed in hot water over a multitude of regulatory issues, while lack of transparency has caused concern in market A round of layoffs is planned at the company, following in the footsteps of many [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-binances-dominance-falling/">Is Binance&#8217;s dominance falling?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s share of trading volume is at 48%, despite being 66% at the start of the year</li>
<li dir="ltr">Exchange has landed in hot water over a multitude of regulatory issues, while lack of transparency has caused concern in market</li>
<li dir="ltr">A round of layoffs is planned at the company, following in the footsteps of many companies around the industry</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">The world&rsquo;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange dominates the landscape. At the end of last year, CCData reported that Binance&rsquo;s share of trading volume on centralised exchanges was a staggering 66%. Binance began 2022, when all was well in the crypto world and the phrase &ldquo;bear market&rdquo; had not entered the lexicon yet, with a 48% market share.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The surge in market share came despite overall trading volume falling 45% during the year 2022, spot trading coming in at $5.29 trillion on Binance. Nearly every other major exchange lost market share last year (with the exception of ByBit), showing that despite capital fleeing from the industry at large, Binance was eating up all before it. Second place went to Coinbase, toiling with far behind with an 8.2% share.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13992509">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Market share falling in 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Fast forward to today, however, and Binance&rsquo;s market share seems to be falling. According to <a href="https://www.cryptocompare.com/media/43977033/centralised-exchange-retrospective.pdf"><u>CC Data</u></a>, in February 2023, three months after Binance came in at a 66% share of volume, it was down to 57.5%. Today, it is down further again, to 43%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The dropoff follows what has been a turbulent few months for Binance, to say the least. The exchange has found itself in hot water with regulators, right at the heart of an industry-wide crackdown in the US. In February, the SEC shut down the Binance-branded stablecoin, BUSD, over securities laws violations (deep dive on put together on that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-busd-shutting-down-mean-for-the-crypto-industry-a-deep-dive/"><u>here</u></a>). BUSD was issued by Paxos, a firm domiciled in New York. BUSD accounted for over a third of the company&rsquo;s trading volume, the coin a vital part of the liquidity on the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13992872">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory trouble has not stopped there. Shortly after, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8680-23"><u>charged</u></a> Binance and high level executives, including CEO Changpeng Zhao, for leading an &ldquo;intentionally opaque common enterprise&rdquo;. The complaint alleges that &ldquo;even after Binance purported to restrict U.S. customers from trading on its platform, Binance instructed its customers &ndash; in particular its commercially valuable U.S.-based VIP customers &ndash; on the best methods for evading Binance&rsquo;s compliance controls&rdquo;. The charges are hefty, including alleging Binance &ldquo;failed to implement basic compliance procedures designed to prevent and detect terrorist financing and money laundering&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CEO Zhao also was forced to dispel concern around the company&rsquo;s lack of transparency in the wake of the FTX collapse last November. Despite publicly pushing for proof of reserves declarations, Binance&rsquo;s attempt to present finances to the world was lacking, omitting liabilities entirely. In truth, there is not much point proving reserves when the amount of liabilities are unknown, and the market did not react well to the omission. Zhao&rsquo;s response to why liabilites were not publicised was that &ldquo;liabilities are harder&rdquo;, and simply said to &ldquo;ask around&rdquo; for proof that &ldquo;we don&rsquo;t owe loans to anyone&rdquo;. Auditor Mazars, who oversaw the proof of reserves report, suspended work with Binance after this, citing a misunderstanding by the public on how they work. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What does this mean for crypto?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For the crypto industry, collapsing prices of 2022 have subsided thus far in 2023, with Bitcoin up 63% year-to-date. Nonetheless, liquidity across the space has been decimated (deep dive on that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/45-of-stablecoin-balance-has-left-crypto-exchanges-in-4-months-but-where-has-all-the-money-gone-a-deep-dive/"><u>here</u></a>), with prices volume still a magnitude below the pandemic peaks.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13825154">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">While prices are currently stable, the space is fighting a growing battle for legitimacy in the US. SEC chair Gary Gensler slammed the industry for &ldquo;mass non-compliance&rdquo;, while Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has admitted his exchange may be forced offshore if the regulatory climate continues to worsen (Coinbase was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-down-25-as-regulators-move-in-and-crypto-environment-worsens-again/"><u>issued</u></a> with a Wells notice in March over potential violations of securities laws).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One silver lining to all this is that the sheer dominance of Binance cannot be good for the crypto industry, which was built upon the pillar of decentralisation. Binance, like it or loathe it, represents an enormous central point of risk for the space, given its importance to overall liquidity. Were anything to happen the exchange, it would have seismic consequences &ndash; this is part of the reason that there was so much concern towards the tail end of last year when Binance was under fire for its lack of transparency,&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Binance&rsquo;s struggles are predominantly for regulatory reasons, which are affecting the overall industry. Sure, the exchange is getting hit harder than most with a plethora of complaints and allegations, but the floor seems to be falling from beneath all crypto companies domiciled in the US.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps the biggest signal of Binance&rsquo;s struggles this past few months is the round of layoffs that is coming. Many crypto companies pared down their workforces significantly over the past year, however Binance maintained that it was hiring through the downturn. That seems to have changed, although the company has not confirmed how many employees will be cut, with reports claiming up to 20% will go. Chief strategy officer Patrick Hillman <a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1663925648182607872?s=20"><u>insisted</u></a> on Twitter that it was a resource reallocation rather than a downsizing, however he also hinted at the role that regulation has played.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Regulators in almost every major market are also working overtime to provide greater clarity for their expectations of the industry and the asset class more broadly, which is putting even more pressure on orgs to adapt or fall by the wayside&rdquo;, he said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In conclusion, Binance&rsquo;s grip on the number one spot may have loosened, but it remains incredibly dominant and clear of all competitors, at least for now. The dropoff in dominance is not a bad thing for crypto in itself, but the reasons that have led to it &ndash; regulators turning the screw and volume dipping across the space &ndash; certainly are issues. Prices may be trading flat over the last while, but the challenges facing the space remain plenty.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/is-binances-dominance-falling/">Is Binance&#8217;s dominance falling?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spheroid Universe Coin to be Listed on MEXC Exchange</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/spheroid-universe-coin-to-be-listed-on-mexc-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/spheroid-universe-coin-to-be-listed-on-mexc-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142016</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 5th, 2023, Chainwire Spheroid Universe, a futuristic Metaverse that augments the real world in every part of the Earth, is announcing that their token, SPH, will officially be listed on MEXC today, on June 5th. Founded in 2018, MEXC (also known as MEXC Global) is a rapidly-growing cryptocurrency exchange with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/spheroid-universe-coin-to-be-listed-on-mexc-exchange/">Spheroid Universe Coin to be Listed on MEXC Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 5th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://spheroiduniverse.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Spheroid Universe</a>, a futuristic Metaverse that augments the real world in every part of the Earth, is announcing that their token, SPH, will officially be <a href="https://twitter.com/spheroid_io/status/1665619534705836032?s=46&amp;t=mZzHTDThl-MVAjY3Cjjqtw" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">listed</a> on <a href="https://www.mexc.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">MEXC</a> today, on June 5th.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2018, MEXC (also known as MEXC Global) is a rapidly-growing cryptocurrency exchange with more than 6 million users in over 200 countries, including the USA, UAE, Canada and Australia. MEXC is regularly featured as one the top exchanges globally for trading volume. The exchange offers one of the widest ranges of cryptocurrencies with over 1,500+ coins listed on the platform. It brings a wealth of experience listing top-performing tokens, with a reach that only a handful of exchanges in Crypto have, helping Spheroid Universe go global.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The move follows the company&rsquo;s recent launch of ChatGPT-powered artificial intelligence (AI) Avatars that will inhabit the world around us via augmented reality (AR). This ground-breaking development will deliver breakthrough opportunities across numerous business platforms &ndash; from e-commerce and retail to advertising, sales, general customer, and consumer interactions and more.</p>
<blockquote><p>Commenting on the announcement, Andrey Almiashev, CEO, of Spheroid Universe said: &ldquo;Launching our token on MEXC will place SPH firmly on its trajectory towards growth as well as will bring the bandwidth that aligns with our aspirations for Spheroid Universe &ndash; putting Spheroid Universe as a leader in the metaverse projects, and the entire Extended and Augmented Reality industry.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Spheroid Universe aims to be the battle-tested AR/XR platform across the entire landscape of web3, XR/VR and metaverse industries, ultimately helping to define the internet experience of the future.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Brands and organizations that are looking to create an immersive digital experience will make Spheroid Universe the place where they can truly demonstrate innovative experiences.</p>
<h3>&nbsp;<strong>About Spheroid</strong></h3>
<p><a href="https://spheroiduniverse.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Spheroid Universe</a> (Spheroid), an Extended Reality Metaverse company. It&rsquo;s a platform for developing Extended Reality projects. The technological basis of the platform is the Spheroid XR Cloud and the Spheroid Script programming language designed for AR/XR creation.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/spheroid-universe/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">SPH</a> is the native token of the Spheroid ecosystem that fuels the activities of the platform. It can be exchanged for Spaces (virtual lands of the Spheroid Universe), used for advertising in AR/XR, placing content, and for various platform services. Among the products powered by SPH there is Spheroid Earth &ndash; an open global project for creating Earth 3D Digital Twin.</p>
<p>For further details, please visit Spheroid Universe&rsquo;s <a href="https://spheroiduniverse.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Official website</a> or follow them on <a href="https://twitter.com/Spheroid_io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/spheroiduniverse/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Head of PR, Yousef Batter, White Label Strategy, yousef.batter@whitelabelstrategy.io, +971559356531</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/spheroid-universe-coin-to-be-listed-on-mexc-exchange/">Spheroid Universe Coin to be Listed on MEXC Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/spheroid-universe-coin-to-be-listed-on-mexc-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin network hash rate hit a record high in May</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-network-hash-rate-record-high-may/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 20:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin network activity climbed for the fifth month straight. Mining difficulty and transaction fee also climbed in May. The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency lost about 8.0% last month. Bitcoin may have lost about 8.0% last month on macro uncertainty but the network activity remained incredibly strong. JPMorgan analyst expects a slowdown in hash rate In May, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-network-hash-rate-record-high-may/">Bitcoin network hash rate hit a record high in May</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin network activity climbed for the fifth month straight.</li>
<li>Mining difficulty and transaction fee also climbed in May.</li>
<li>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency lost about 8.0% last month.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> may have lost about 8.0% last month on macro uncertainty but the network activity remained incredibly strong.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan analyst expects a slowdown in hash rate</h2>
<p>In May, the daily network <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/hash-rate-6746261" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hash rate</a> &ndash; a closely followed metric that indicates network&rsquo;s health climbed to a record high. It was the fifth consecutive month of increase for the said indicator.</p>
<p>Simply put, larger the hash rate, the more secure is the network. Nonetheless, Reginald Smith &ndash; a JPMorgan analyst said in a note on Friday:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our sense is that network hash rate growth could slow over the coming months (possibly lagging BTC price appreciation) as funding available rack space is hard to come by.</p></blockquote>
<p>In terms of market cap, the 13 U.S. listed miners that JPMorgan tracks noted an aggregate increase of 5.0% last month to $6.7 billion.</p>
<h2>Mining difficulty and transaction fee also increased</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-does-mining-difficulty-mean/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mining difficulty</a> &ndash; another metric that typically moves in tandem with the Bitcoin hash rate &ndash; also climbed to a record high in May.</p>
<p>Recent data confirmed the crypto transaction fee to have increased last month as well. JPMorgan&rsquo;s Smith also said in his research note:</p>
<blockquote><p>Transaction fees spiked to over 5 Bitcoin per block mined in early May, which should drive modest C2Q23 earnings upside for the industry at large.</p></blockquote>
<p>In recent weeks, though, Bitcoin transaction fees have returned close to its historic average of about 0.5 BTC per block mined. Last week, JPMorgan <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/31/jpmorgan-reveals-900-billion-gold-based-implied-bitcoin-price-alongside-an-ethereum-upgrade-prediction-warning/?sh=62cd1f1d2010" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> Bitcoin should be trading at $45,000.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-network-hash-rate-record-high-may/">Bitcoin network hash rate hit a record high in May</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CRUX Unveils a Thrilling Journey: Game Development, CEX Listing, and a Marketing Evolution</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>$CRUX, the new blockchain-powered gaming and financial platform, is proud to announce aims to revolutionize the crypto gaming industry and pave the way for exciting new milestones. They started to establish themselfs as a driving force in the gaming and blockchain space, building through bear market and with massive potential. At its core, CRUX offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/">CRUX Unveils a Thrilling Journey: Game Development, CEX Listing, and a Marketing Evolution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">$CRUX, the new blockchain-powered gaming and financial platform, is proud to announce aims to revolutionize the crypto gaming industry and pave the way for exciting new milestones. They started to establish themselfs as a driving force in the gaming and blockchain space, building through bear market and with massive potential.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685719079363-d9a6aeb2-0df4-4b03-b8be-154f1d0855ee.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="331"></p>
<p dir="ltr">At its core, CRUX offers a captivating gaming ecosystem that seamlessly integrates with its native token, CRUX (CRUX). They provide a play-to-earn (P2E) experience where players can unleash their skills, navigate challenges, and unlock real-world value. The immersive survival MMORPG game allows players to venture into a post-apocalyptic world, where they fight against relentless undead enemies and compete for survival in a resource-scarce environment all worth $CRUX that is tradeable for real value and money.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the game, CRUX offers a comprehensive financial platform that harnesses the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning technologies. Traders and investors can access real-time market analysis, social sentiment analysis, and on-chain data, enabling them to make well-informed decisions and capitalize on opportunities in the crypto market.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685719030295-1a29c3c5-f31f-44ce-b44c-327a0d22db18.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="340"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Exciting new milestones lie ahead for CRUX, with a key focus on expanding its reach and creating more value for its community. One of the most highly anticipated milestones is the upcoming listing on a major centralized exchange (CEX), which will significantly enhance accessibility and liquidity for the CRUX token. The CEX listing will empower users to seamlessly trade CRUX on a trusted and established platform, further fueling the growth and adoption of the ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another critical area of development for CRUX is the continuous enhancement of its game. The team is dedicated to delivering engaging gameplay experiences, expanding the world, introducing new features, and fostering a vibrant community of players. By incorporating player feedback and leveraging cutting-edge technologies, CRUX aims to establish its game as a benchmark for immersive and rewarding gaming experiences in the crypto space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CRUX recognizes the importance of strategic marketing initiatives to bolster its presence and drive user adoption. As the volume of CRUX transactions and the ecosystem&rsquo;s growth continue to surge, their smart contract allows them to gather even more funds for marketing due to a 4% fee on every transaction. On the tokenomics side, $CRUX has an 8% fee on every transaction, where 4% goes to marketing, 2% to liquidity, and 2% back to holders. These initiatives further strengthen the CRUX brand, attract new users, and expand its global community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Our upcoming CEX listing, coupled with ongoing game development and targeted marketing initiatives, will solidify CRUX&rsquo;s position as a leader in the crypto gaming industry,&rdquo; says Rodrigo, CEO of CRUX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CRUX remains steadfast in its long-term vision of building a dynamic and interconnected metaverse powered by blockchain technology. By creating a seamless and immersive gaming experience while providing real-world value through the CRUX token, the platform aims to revolutionize the gaming and financial industries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Their demo version of the game is out already and available on CRUX website.<br>Here&rsquo;s also a short gameplay of the alpha version:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yKlM2DZaG1I" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yKlM2DZaG1I</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">To stay updated on CRUX&rsquo;s latest news, milestones, and developments, visit the official website at<a href="http://www.cruxcryptos.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>www.cruxcryptos.com</u></a>. Join the vibrant CRUX community on Telegram at<a href="https://t.me/CRUX_CRYPTOS" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>https://t.me/CRUX_CRYPTOS</u></a> for engaging discussions and insights.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">About CRUX</h2>
<p>CRUX is a community-driven blockchain platform that combines gaming and finance to deliver a unique and rewarding experience. With its survival MMORPG game and advanced financial platform powered by AI and machine learning, CRUX is reshaping the crypto gaming industry. The CRUX token (CRUX) serves as the utility token within the ecosystem, facilitating in-game transactions, empowering the financial platform, and rewarding users. For more information, visit<a href="http://www.cruxcryptos.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>www.cruxcryptos.com</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/">CRUX Unveils a Thrilling Journey: Game Development, CEX Listing, and a Marketing Evolution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
