<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:24:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US SEC Indicts Coinbase over Unregistered Exchange and Broker Platform</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">US SEC Indicts Coinbase over Unregistered Exchange and Broker Platform</a></p>
<p>The new lawsuit against Coinbase is coming only a few hours after the SEC sued Binance for violation of the same US securities rules.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">US SEC Indicts Coinbase over Unregistered Exchange and Broker Platform</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">US SEC Indicts Coinbase over Unregistered Exchange and Broker Platform</a></p>
<p>American publicly listed crypto trading platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) has come under the radar of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) once again.</p>
<p>This time around, Coinbase was <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov/status/1666059252442746881?t=5do-w4_qrH_9nB4UYGLx1Q&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener">indicted</a> in a New York Federal Court earlier today for operating as an unregistered national securities exchange and broker according to the regulator. The lawsuit stated that Coinbase has been operating in this manner since at least 2019 when it started conducting crypto transactions.</p>
<p>Coinbase Prime and Coinbase Wallets were named as two products that the firm leveraged to attract investors.</p>
<p>The self-custody Coinbase Wallet is recognized to help investors access liquidity outside of the Coinbase platform and according to a Twitter post made by SEC Chair Gary Gensler, this &#8220;deprive investors of critical protections, including rulebooks that prevent fraud and manipulation, proper disclosure, safeguards against conflicts of interest, and routine inspection&#8221;.</p>
<p>Also, the regulator identified Coinbase staking service as an investment contract and unregistered securities, similar to the offense and charges levied against the Kraken cryptocurrency exchange earlier in the year. Precisely, the staking service was described as a means for investors to make a profit via Coinbase&#8217;s managerial efforts.</p>
<p>Therefore, the SEC is requesting that the company be permanently restrained and enjoined from doing so in the future.</p>
<h2>Coinbase and SEC Remains at Loggerheads</h2>
<p>Noteworthy, Coinbase and the SEC have been at each other&#8217;s throats for some time, especially as it concerns regulation for the nascent industry.</p>
<p>About two months ago, the American exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-enforcement-action-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">received</a> a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-sec-wells-notice/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wells Notice</a> from the regulator. Per the notice, SEC claimed to have identified potential violations of U.S. securities law, therefore, it planned to enforce action on the exchange. During that time, Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-sec-wells-notice-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">clarified</a> that none of its listed assets were securities.</p>
<p>Consequently, Coinbase chief legal officer Paul Grewal said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“If needed, we welcome a legal process to provide the clarity we have been advocating for and to demonstrate that the Commission simply has not been fair or reasonable when it comes to its engagement on digital assets. Until then, it is business as usual.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The new lawsuit against Coinbase is coming only a few hours after the same regulator <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> leading digital asset service provider Binance for violation of the same US securities rules. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> was accused of mishandling customers&#8217; funds and misleading investors and regulators alike. This is in addition to flouting Know-Your-Customer (KYC) rules by letting Americans trade on the platform after stating that they were not allowed.</p>
<p>Just like Coinbase had previously done, Binance called out the SEC for failing to provide clarity on crypto regulation. In response to the lawsuit, the leading trading platform announced that it was ready to defend its stance in court. However, the lawsuit had already done some damage to the crypto market, causing several digital assets to plunge.</p>
<p>Coinbase shares <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-tumble-sec-binance-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dipped</a> by 9% following the announcement of the Binance-SEC lawsuit and now the newly filed lawsuit against Coinbase has brought the stock down by 13%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">US SEC Indicts Coinbase over Unregistered Exchange and Broker Platform</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agoria Empowers Fans with NFT Ownership in Upcoming Album Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agoria]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bolero]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258016</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/">Agoria Empowers Fans with NFT Ownership in Upcoming Album Launch</a></p>
<p>Agoria is revolutionizing the music industry by granting fans ownership rights to his upcoming album through NFTs, creating a unique and immersive experience for his audience.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/">Agoria Empowers Fans with NFT Ownership in Upcoming Album Launch</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/">Agoria Empowers Fans with NFT Ownership in Upcoming Album Launch</a></p>
<p>Renowned French DJ, producer, and NFT artist Agoria is spearheading a groundbreaking initiative that challenges the traditional norms of the music industry. In an exciting <a href="https://decrypt.co/143542/nft-artist-agoria-give-fans-ownership-over-upcoming-album-launch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">move</a>, Agoria is giving fans the chance to own his upcoming album through non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>s). This innovative approach not only bridges the gap between the artist and their fans but also transforms the concept of ownership in the digital age.</p>
<p>By leveraging the power of blockchain technology, Agoria aims to provide a unique and immersive experience for his fans. NFTs, which are digital assets that represent ownership or proof of authenticity of a unique item, are at the core of this transformative endeavor. Each NFT will grant the owner exclusive rights to the album, allowing them to access special features, and unreleased content, and even participate in interactive experiences related to the music.</p>
<h2>Agoria Seeks to Democratize Music Ownership among Fans</h2>
<p>Agoria&#8217;s decision to explore NFTs is reflective of the wider trend within the music industry. Artists are increasingly turning to blockchain technology to create new revenue streams, foster closer connections with their fans, and combat issues such as piracy.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, one of the key advantages of Agoria&#8217;s NFT-based album launch is the democratization of music ownership. Historically, music ownership has been limited to physical copies or digital downloads, with fans having little control or involvement beyond the act of purchase. NFTs change this paradigm by granting fans true ownership of digital content, providing an opportunity to engage with the artist&#8217;s work on a deeper level.</p>
<p>Agoria&#8217;s upcoming song has already received an enthusiastic response, particularly during its debut in Ibiza. The artist expressed his satisfaction, revealing that the composition originated from an arpeggio he had discovered some time ago. The official release party for the song is scheduled for June 7 at the NFC Lisbon event in Lisbon, adding to the anticipation surrounding this groundbreaking project.</p>
<h2>Agoria Incorporates Blockchain-based Music Platform Bolero</h2>
<p>To bring this initiative to life, Agoria partnered with Bolero, a blockchain-based music platform. Bolero&#8217;s recently launched &#8220;Song Shares&#8221; feature will facilitate the distribution of rewards to fans holding NFT-based songs in their wallets. Bolero&#8217;s CEO, William Bailey, highlighted the platform&#8217;s significant growth since the introduction of Song Shares, surpassing their figures for 2022. The Agorians Song Shares will be primarily allocated to Agoria&#8217;s top NFT collectors on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tezos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tezos</a>, with the remaining 10% available for purchase by Bolero users.</p>
<p>Notably, by leveraging traceability and redistribution, Agoria&#8217;s collaboration with Bolero embodies a shift towards a fairer compensation structure for artists and creators. This approach has the potential to transform the traditional dynamics of the music industry and empower artists with direct compensation. Bolero users seeking entitled royalties must create an account on the platform and connect their wallets, enhancing the transparency and accessibility of the process.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/">Agoria Empowers Fans with NFT Ownership in Upcoming Album Launch</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/agoria-nft-ownership-album/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Louis Vuitton Launches Treasure Trunk Digital Collectible Priced at €39,000</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[consensys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[louis vuitton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lvmh]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mercedes benz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prada]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258012</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/">Louis Vuitton Launches Treasure Trunk Digital Collectible Priced at €39,000</a></p>
<p>Each Treasure Trunk from Louis Vuitton is a soulbound token that opens owners to exclusive experiences and designs.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/">Louis Vuitton Launches Treasure Trunk Digital Collectible Priced at €39,000</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/">Louis Vuitton Launches Treasure Trunk Digital Collectible Priced at €39,000</a></p>
<p>French luxury fashion house Louis Vuitton has launched its iconic travel trunk as a digital collectible in a collection called the VIA Treasure Trunk. The launch is part of Louis Vuitton’s affinity for digital adoption and Web3.</p>
<p>The Treasure Trunks are part of Louis Vuitton’s broader “Via” project. Translated from Latin as “road”, Via is the fashion house’s project that offers several products and experiences to a select few.</p>
<p>Each Treasure Trunk will cost a pricey €39,000. Although there is no specific number yet, Louis Vuitton has said it will mint “only a few hundred”. Interested persons would have to join a waiting list by completing a registration process using a crypto wallet. Registration will begin on June 8.</p>
<p>After the registrations, the company will select qualified persons and send them invitations to view a private VIA page on June 14. However, these persons will not be able to buy a Treasure Trunk until June 16.</p>
<p>Each Louis Vuitton Treasure Trunk is a soulbound token (SBT). An SBT is a non-fungible token (NFT) that is unique and non-transferable. SBTs help to track the token’s reputation, and instead of being sellable, they are permanently bound to specific accounts or wallets. This supports Louis Vuitton’s plan for each Treasure Trunk owner to enjoy exclusive access to a special experience that includes designs never seen before.</p>
<p>Louis Vuitton’s travel trunk was initially launched in 1858.</p>
<h2>Treasure Trunks Continue Louis Vuitton’s Blockchain Involvement</h2>
<p>The launch of Treasure Trunk SBTs is not Louis Vuitton’s first dalliance with blockchain technology. In 2021, Louis Vuitton’s parent company LVMH <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuittons-aura-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> the Aura Blockchain Consortium with a few other luxury brands. The Aura Blockchain is a blockchain solution available to any luxury brand interested in extra product traceability and transparency.</p>
<p>Founding members include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mercedes-benz/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mercedes-Benz</a>, Prada Group, Richemont, OTB Group, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/lvmh/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LVMH</a>. Other members include Maison Margiela, Cartier, Bvlgari, Hennessy, Givenchy, and Hublot, among others. The consortium says it is open to any luxury brand.</p>
<p>The Aura Blockchain is secured using technology from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/consensys/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ConsenSys</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corp</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT). The infrastructure helps customers of these luxury brands easily authenticate their products. For example, Swiss luxury watchmaker Hublot has an e-warranty feature on the Aura Blockchain that allows customers to confirm product genuineness.</p>
<h2>LVMH Metaverse</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.lvmh.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LVMH</a> may also have its eyes set on Web3 goals, including gaming and the metaverse. During an earnings call last year, LVMH chief financial officer Jacques Guiony mentioned that the company is considering blockchain gaming and metaverse endeavors.</p>
<p>Regardless, Guiony said LVMH is doing its consideration “carefully”. He said at the time that the metaverse was promising although still nascent. Nonetheless, the CFO assured that LVMH will be a part of the metaverse boom. However, he said he was unsure of specific plans, while CEO Bernard Arnault warned that LVMH must be “wary of bubbles”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/">Louis Vuitton Launches Treasure Trunk Digital Collectible Priced at €39,000</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/louis-vuitton-treasure-trunk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SushiSwap Launches Sushi DEX Aggregator for Liquidity Support</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sei Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sushi DEX Aggregator]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushiswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257994</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/">SushiSwap Launches Sushi DEX Aggregator for Liquidity Support</a></p>
<p>Sushi noted that its team had been working secretly on building an aggregation router for a while now as it is part of the platform's bigger vision for 2023. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/">SushiSwap Launches Sushi DEX Aggregator for Liquidity Support</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/">SushiSwap Launches Sushi DEX Aggregator for Liquidity Support</a></p>
<p>Open-source Decentralized Exchange (DEX) SushiSwap has <a href="https://www.sushi.com/blog/dex-aggregator-live" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduced</a> a new aggregator as it makes its first foray into the aggregation business.</p>
<p>With this DEX aggregator, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/sushiswap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SushiSwap</a> customers are allowed to obtain the best prices when trading on the platform without further or additional procedures. In order words, customers will be offered optimum pricing while also exposed to a large range of assets available for trading.</p>
<p>It would also serve to manage the range of liquidity that liquidity providers (LPs) can provide, thereby, increasing the transaction fees they can earn.</p>
<p>Noteworthy, liquidity has been the problem of many DEX seeing that it is most times unstable. For this reason, it is projected that there will be an increased demand for the DEX aggregator. These DEX aggregators often act as liquidity aggregators from various sources like traditional Automated Market Makers (AMMs) or Centralized Exchanges (CEXs).</p>
<p>DEX aggregators are financial protocols that help unify liquidity across different exchanges on a given chain. It then employs a complex algorithm to establish the cheapest route based on several factors for a user&#8217;s swap in the available platforms. Notably, aggregators are very popular in the Decentralized Finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) sector due to this single, unified interface that it offers for communication amongst crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>In addition, the DEX aggregator aims to optimize the price slippage and the transaction fee via a mechanism. At the end of the day, it makes it more convenient for users to trade. The fact that it provides users with a wide range of assets, there is every possibility that it would attract more users to the platform.</p>
<p>Consequently, this would lead to increased swap fees for liquidity providers and attract more liquidity overall in a positive feedback cycle.</p>
<h2>Sushi DEX Aggregator Holds Numerous Benefits for LPs</h2>
<p>Sushi noted that its team had been working secretly on building an aggregation router for a while now as it is part of the platform&#8217;s bigger vision for 2023.</p>
<p>&#8220;The goal is to deliver optimal pricing to our users while also opening up the sheer amount of assets our users can trade with and can provide liquidity for LPs, increasing the number of swap fees they can accrue,&#8221; the blog post explained.</p>
<p>The Sushi protocol is focused on becoming the hub of swaps in DeFi. Sushi mentioned that the most significant and essential benefit of its aggregator is the fact that it is “biased”, hence routing many of the trades through Sushi and allowing for exposure to a plethora of tokens that were not available in the Sushi UI before.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, the DEX platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-exchange-sei-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> a new Perpetual contract futures exchange on the Sei Network. For Sei Network, the partnership is another strategy to generate a new revenue stream for the protocol as well as grow its influence.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/">SushiSwap Launches Sushi DEX Aggregator for Liquidity Support</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sushiswap-dex-aggregator-liquidity-support/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Will Compete with Meta Quest 3, Here’s Difference</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple vision pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta quest 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257981</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/">Apple Vision Pro Will Compete with Meta Quest 3, Here&#8217;s Difference</a></p>
<p>Apple and Meta will be taking the battle on the frontier of mixed-reality headsets. Here's a look into how each of the devices - Apple Vision Pro and Meta Quest 3 - compare with each other. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/">Apple Vision Pro Will Compete with Meta Quest 3, Here&#8217;s Difference</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/">Apple Vision Pro Will Compete with Meta Quest 3, Here&#8217;s Difference</a></p>
<p>Mixed Reality, AR, and VR is the new battleground for tech giants to compete with each other. While Facebook parent Meta has been in the game for a while, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> just made a big bang entry into the space by unveiling its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-mixed-reality-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Vision Pro</a> during the WWDC 2023 event&#8217;s opening day on Monday, June 5.</p>
<p>Apple&#8217;s first mixed-reality headset will be available in early 2024. However, it will set the competition straight up with the Meta Quest 3 headset planned for launch later this year. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta</a> made the announcement for Quest 3, just two days before Apple did it.</p>
<p>The Meta Quest 3 will be a successor to Quest 2 and will operate without a PC, smartphone, or console. It will have a 40% slimmer body with high-end display resolution, powerful graphics, and much more. The Meta Quest 3 will directly <a href="https://decrypt.co/143522/apple-vision-pro-vs-meta-quest-3/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">compete</a> with the Apple Vision Pro. Let&#8217;s take a look into how these two headsets pitch against each other on different verticals.</p>
<h2>Design and Hardware</h2>
<p>The Apple Vision Pro is very much in line with Apple&#8217;s existing design language with curved edges snugly strapping to your face. It certainly looks like a premium product from the range of Apple&#8217;s offerings.</p>
<p>The Apple Vision Pro is a special device that has many cameras and sensors. It can do more than just show virtual reality things in front of you. It also has a screen on the outside that lets other people see your eyes and facial expressions while you wear it. This is different from other virtual reality and augmented reality headsets that exist in the market.</p>
<p>With the Apple Vision Pro, you can control everything using your fingers, hands, and voice commands. Apple won&#8217;t give you a separate controller or wand to use with it. But if you want to play games from Apple Arcade, you can connect a Bluetooth controller. And if you need to get work done, you can use the Magic Keyboard and Magic Trackpad with the headset.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Meta Quest 3 will be Meta&#8217;s first take on mixed-reality headsets. Thus, unlike Quest 2, it will offer a full-color pass-through. The Quest 3 will be 40% slimmer than its predecessor and will have external cameras and a depth sensor to enable full-color augmented reality passthrough.</p>
<p>The Quest 3 comes with improved motion controllers designed specifically for games and immersive apps, in addition to supporting finger and hand gestures. This feature could be a significant advantage in terms of content, as explained in more detail below.</p>
<h2>Display</h2>
<p>The screens inside the Apple Vision Pro are super clear, with a resolution that&#8217;s even better than 4K for each eye. Apple hasn&#8217;t given us the exact details, but they claim the screens have over 23 million pixels, giving you a really sharp image.</p>
<p>As for Quest 3, we don&#8217;t have specific information about how clear its screen is yet. Meta, the company behind Quest, says it&#8217;s sharper than the Quest 2, which had a resolution of 1,832 x 1,920. However, a hands-on review by Bloomberg suggests that the Quest 3 doesn&#8217;t look much sharper than the Quest 2 in real-world use. We&#8217;ll have to wait and see for a direct comparison between the two.</p>
<h2>Power and Battery</h2>
<p>The Apple Vision Pro uses a powerful M2 processor, which is the same kind used in recent Mac computers. It also has a special R1 chip that handles the data from the cameras and sensors. On the other hand, the Meta Quest 3 is expected to use the Snapdragon Qualcomm XR2 chip, which is made specifically for devices like this, but it&#8217;s based on smartphone chips. Meta says the Quest 3 will have double the graphics performance compared to the Quest 2, but it might not be as powerful as the Vision Pro.</p>
<p>The Vision Pro doesn&#8217;t have its own built-in battery. Instead, it has a separate pack that you can plug in, and it gives you around two hours of use. You can easily carry the pack in your pocket or keep it nearby while you&#8217;re sitting. Alternatively, you can use a wall plug for unlimited use.</p>
<p>Also, there&#8217;s no info currently on the battery life of Quest 3. But the Quest 2 can be used for up to three hours on a full charge. Additionally, there&#8217;s a special Elite Strap available for the Quest 2 that includes an extra battery pack, doubling the usage time. Meta has yet to reveal how the Quest 3 compares in terms of battery life.</p>
<h2>Software and Content</h2>
<p>Software and content will be a major differentiator between the Apple Vision Pro and the Meta Quest 3. Apple has projected its Vision Pro as a spatial computer for entertainment and productivity, but not a gaming destination. It will run the Apple Arcade games on the Visison Pro&#8217;s floating, flat screen and could have new VR and AR games running for it. However, Apple hasn&#8217;t talked on this much, so far.</p>
<p>With the Apple Vision Pro, you can use popular apps like FaceTime and Zoom. It has a special 3D camera that can create a digital version of yourself called a &#8220;Persona.&#8221; This digital persona reacts in real time based on your actions, making the experience more immersive and connecting your physical and digital worlds. The 3D camera can also take photos and videos that have depth, which is a really cool feature.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Meta Quest platform already has many exciting VR games like Beat Saber, Resident Evil 4, Pistol Whip, and Superhot VR. These games will likely perform even better on Quest 3. Additionally, Meta has shown plans to create AR games specifically for the new headset.</p>
<p>Both the Apple Vision Pro and Meta Quest 3 can be used for various purposes. They can be used for work to access apps and websites, and also for watching movies and TV shows in virtual environments. However, there are some differences. The Apple Vision Pro can connect with iOS apps and a Mac, giving it access to a wide range of content. In contrast, Meta&#8217;s platform doesn&#8217;t have as many features and options available.</p>
<h2>Pricing and Availability</h2>
<p>The Apple Vision Pro will be priced at $3,499, which is higher than the expected range of $2,000 to $3,000. This high price means that it will mainly attract tech-savvy early adopters, which is typical for Apple.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Meta is targeting consumers with the main Quest line. The Quest 3 will start at $500, which is only one-seventh of the Vision Pro&#8217;s price. Currently, the Quest 2 is priced at $300. The Quest Pro, a more powerful version, is currently sold for $1,000 after originally being priced at $1,500.</p>
<p>Apple plans to release the Vision Pro early next year, while Meta intends to launch the Quest 3 later this year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/">Apple Vision Pro Will Compete with Meta Quest 3, Here&#8217;s Difference</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-vision-pro-meta-quest-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase, CFTC, and Others Testify in Congress Over Proposed Crypto Bill</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257986</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/">Coinbase, CFTC, and Others Testify in Congress Over Proposed Crypto Bill</a></p>
<p>Representatives from Coinbase, Robinhood, and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, among others, will speak at a House Agriculture Committee hearing on digital asset regulation about the recently released draft crypto bill.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/">Coinbase, CFTC, and Others Testify in Congress Over Proposed Crypto Bill</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/">Coinbase, CFTC, and Others Testify in Congress Over Proposed Crypto Bill</a></p>
<p>United States legislators put forth a crypto bill to provide clear regulations for cryptocurrency, its users, and companies. The 162-page bill attempts to establish regulatory jurisdiction and definitions. However, it was also acknowledged that the bill would require extensive reviews. One is the House Agriculture Committee hearing on digital asset regulation today.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> and the CFTC are among those expected to testify in Congress. The event is titled &#8220;The Future of Digital Assets: Providing Clarity for Digital Asset Spot Markets&#8221;. The purpose of the meeting, as the title reveals, is to talk about the proposed crypto classification and each organization&#8217;s position on the proposed bill that tries to classify specific cryptos.</p>
<p>&#8220;I will be testifying tomorrow in front of the House Committee on Agriculture on the issues related to #digitalcommodityassets. Watch the hearing here,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/CFTCbehnam/status/1665781056606289920" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> Rostin Behnam, CFTC chairman, on Twitter.</p>
<p>Coinbase&#8217;s Chief Legal Officer, Paul Grewal, revealed some of his thoughts on cryptocurrency regulation and what he will testify about. He stated that the US is missing out and that ignoring crypto will continue to cause the US market to fall behind as other markets capitalize on the opportunities that crypto provides. The rules that should be enacted should be those that will allow the industry to thrive and even offer solutions to international markets. He also mentioned that he will support the proposed cryptocurrency bill, which he sees as an important step toward the long-awaited regulatory solution.</p>
<p>Sharing his thoughts on his Twitter page, Grewal <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1665859395358474240%7Ctwgr%5Ed7ce3deb3e32743527d4f8d34c6ec24cb40764be%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fcoinbase-robinhood-cftc-testify-congress-draft-crypto-bill" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We need a clear rulebook in the US to achieve the full promise of crypto. Until rules and laws are developed that reflect the realities of this new economic system, we cannot realize the full potential of making our financial system faster, fairer, and more affordable.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Major Move towards Clear Crypto Regulatory Guidelines</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is riddled with inconsistencies, owing primarily to ambiguous regulations. Several legal disputes between regulators and cryptocurrency exchanges have occurred. The three-year-old <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> and SEC lawsuit, which is anticipated to be resolved this year, is a well-known example. The lawsuit against Binance that was filed this week is one recent example. The SEC claimed that the crypto company used BNB and BUSD as securities without registering them as such. The situation reveals Binance&#8217;s violations of security regulations and the general irregularities in classifying crypto assets according to the law and their intended use.</p>
<p>Providing clear regulatory guidelines for the crypto industry is an important step. With so many people owning and using cryptocurrency, such clear guidelines will be required to protect crypto users, guide crypto use, and help the industry grow healthily. Obviously, this move aligns with the desire of many major cryptocurrency exchanges, which have been the target of several lawsuits due to unclear regulatory stances.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/">Coinbase, CFTC, and Others Testify in Congress Over Proposed Crypto Bill</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-cftc-congress-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Deletes Former Director Hinman’s Biography amidst Ripple vs SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[william hinman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257982</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/">SEC Deletes Former Director Hinman&#8217;s Biography amidst Ripple vs SEC Case</a></p>
<p>The US SEC has mysteriously deleted Hinman's biography from its website ahead of the court's imminent order to disclose unredacted emails from Hinman's communications. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/">SEC Deletes Former Director Hinman&#8217;s Biography amidst Ripple vs SEC Case</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/">SEC Deletes Former Director Hinman&#8217;s Biography amidst Ripple vs SEC Case</a></p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) erased the biography of former commissioner William Hinman from its website eight days before the court demanded the financial watchdog to provide unedited copies of all of Hinman&#8217;s emails in its case against Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>Before now, the SEC&#8217;s website contained important information about Hinman&#8217;s employment history, roles, and advisory contributions to the Commission. However, the updated biography now presents only his name, photograph, and his former position as the Director of the Division of Corporation Finance unit from May 2017 to December 2020.</p>
<p>According to a Twitter user, Mr. Huber, who called out Hinman&#8217;s revised biography on the social media platform, the SEC might be planning to throw him under the bus.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SECGov</a> has now removed Bill Hinman&#8217;s biography from its website. Getting ready to throw him under the bus. <a href="https://t.co/O7HCUGWSgt">pic.twitter.com/O7HCUGWSgt</a></p>
<p>— Mr. Huber🔥🦅🔥 (@Leerzeit) <a href="https://twitter.com/Leerzeit/status/1665662937376145408?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Hinman&#8217;s Speech Could Be a Decisive Factor in the Ripple vs SEC Case</h2>
<p>Hinman&#8217;s departure from the SEC in 2020 coincided with the Commission&#8217;s lawsuit against Ripple Labs. The former SEC director left the agency the same month it sued Ripple for violating federal security rules by selling an unregistered token <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP. </a></p>
<p>Hinman gained attention for delivering a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/speech/speech-hinman-061418" target="_blank" rel="noopener">speech</a> in 2018 stating that Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) are non-securities and should not be classified as such. However, he failed to address the legal status of XRP, which is distributed similarly to Ether.</p>
<p>Due to the lack of legal classification of XRP, Ripple and other critics of the SEC have long sought internal transcripts and discussions regarding the speech to ascertain whether ETH received favorable treatment over XRP.</p>
<p>Last year, the financial company succeeded in obtaining Hinman&#8217;s speech documents, although their contents remained confidential at the time.</p>
<p>Recently, the court has mandated SEC to produce all of Hinman&#8217;s email communications and drafts of his 2018 speech. Judge Analisa Torres <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-judge-motion-amici-ripple-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ruled</a> in May that the SEC and Ripple should unseal Hinman&#8217;s emails and other summary judgment materials on June 13, 2023.</p>
<p>Crypto enthusiasts believe the email could be a smoking gun for the ongoing court battle between the regulator and Ripple.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-vs-ripple/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple vs SEC</a> case has significantly impacted the US crypto industry, which seeks clarity and legal precedent regarding categorizing virtual assets as securities in the United States.</p>
<p>The two parties filed for a summary judgment in December 2022, raising hopes that a conclusion might be near.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/">SEC Deletes Former Director Hinman&#8217;s Biography amidst Ripple vs SEC Case</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-director-hinman-ripple/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cboe Digital Bags CFTC Approval to Trade Bitcoin and Ether Futures</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cboe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257970</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/">Cboe Digital Bags CFTC Approval to Trade Bitcoin and Ether Futures</a></p>
<p>The CFTC has officially given Cboe Digital the approval it needs to offer margined futures contracts trading to clients.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/">Cboe Digital Bags CFTC Approval to Trade Bitcoin and Ether Futures</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/">Cboe Digital Bags CFTC Approval to Trade Bitcoin and Ether Futures</a></p>
<p>Cboe Global Markets’ digital asset exchange has received <a href="https://twitter.com/CFTC/status/1665849007464144899?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1665849007464144899%7Ctwgr%5Eb435556b7ed7550f618603e897cbfd4ca1ebedaf%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fcboe-digital-approved-margin-trades-crypto-futures-exchange" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">approval</a> to allow users to trade crypto futures contracts. Customers of the Cboe Digital platform will now trade Ether (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/">ETH</a>) and Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/">BTC</a>) futures contracts later this year following the CFTC’s approval for an amended order of registration.</p>
<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) gave Cboe Digital approval to financially and physically settle margin contracts from the second half of the year. The futures trading approval is pivotal for Cboe even though the company has allowed crypto futures contracts trading for more than five years. However, although this has been available for a while, users could not conduct margined trades.</p>
<p>In an official <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8712-23" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a> yesterday, the CFTC said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The amended order permits Cboe [Digital] to provide clearing services for digital asset futures on a margined basis for futures commission merchants, in addition to the fully collateralized futures and fully collateralized swaps previously authorized.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Before the approval, Cboe offered fully collateralized crypto futures that require the full value of a contract before the trade. Margined trading differs as users can begin trading without 100% of the funds. In addition, the new approval will allow Cboe support traditional firms physically settling their assets without requiring custody services from intermediaries.</p>
<p>Cboe will settle the assets and support margin trading as it is the only exchange registered in the US that offers spot and derivatives trading. Supported assets include Bitcoin, Ether, Bitcoin Cash, USDC, and Litecoin.</p>
<p>Speaking to Bloomberg on traditional firms’ direct access without intermediary custody, Cboe Digital President John Palmer noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“That’s where the concept of us also having a spot market has advantages. We didn’t want to have to force participants to custody or touch the physical asset.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Cboe Still In Race for Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval</h2>
<p>Last month, Cboe submitted an application to the Securities Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-an-exchange-traded-fund-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETF</a>). The submission is the Cboe’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-third-attempt-spot-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">third attempt</a> at getting the SEC to approve the ETF, with the previous two rejected. In January, the SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-cboe-ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">denied</a> the Cboe’s second attempt stating that the ETF had inadequate measures to protect investors from fraud and manipulation.</p>
<p>The SEC has rejected all applications for spot BTC ETFs, including submissions from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/fidelity-investments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fidelity</a>, the New York Digital Investment Group (NYDIG), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale</a>. In October, the SEC also rejected a proposal from WisdomTree. Again, the commission said there wasn’t enough investor protection.</p>
<p>The SEC’s stubborn stance against spot Bitcoin ETFs is unjustified to many. Hopefuls believe that the commission is being deliberately difficult about its refusal to approve these ETFs. Last year, Grayscale instituted legal action against the SEC and gathered support from Coinbase. In October, the exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-joins-grayscale-in-fighting-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-from-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> an amicus brief to support Grayscale’s lawsuit against the SEC after the rejection. The SEC had raised the same concerns, citing problems with market manipulation. Nevertheless, Grayscale said the disapproval was “arbitrary, capricious, and discriminatory”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/">Cboe Digital Bags CFTC Approval to Trade Bitcoin and Ether Futures</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cboe-cftc-approval-btc-eth-futures/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) and Broader Crypto Market Come Crashing Down Following SEC Lawsuit on Binance</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257902</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/">Bitcoin (BTC) and Broader Crypto Market Come Crashing Down Following SEC Lawsuit on Binance</a></p>
<p>After SEC's action on Binance, Bitcoin and the broader crypto market tanked instantly. Altcoins face heavy correction to the tune of 7-8% with Binance BNB suffering the most. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/">Bitcoin (BTC) and Broader Crypto Market Come Crashing Down Following SEC Lawsuit on Binance</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/">Bitcoin (BTC) and Broader Crypto Market Come Crashing Down Following SEC Lawsuit on Binance</a></p>
<p>The filing of the lawsuit by the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">US SEC</a> against crypto giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> sent shockwaves across the entire cryptocurrency market on Monday, June 5. Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and the broader cryptocurrency market have corrected by over 4%.</p>
<p>As of press time, the Bitcoin (BTC) price is down by 4% and is currently trading at $25,778 with its market cap dropping under $500 billion. With the recent move, Bitcoin has lost its most important support of $26,300, and this could further drag the BTC price all the way to $23,000.</p>
<p>On-chain data provider Glassnode further <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1665805368163721218" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The recent Bitcoin move downwards from $27.3K to $25.8K (-5.8%) has caused the percent supply in profit to decline from 69% to 62.5% (-6.5%), plunging a further 1.26M coins into loss.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<div>
<dl id="attachment_257907">
<dt>
<p><div style="width: 4062px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-Profit-Supply.png" alt="Bitcoin (BTC) and Broader Crypto Market Come Crashing Down Following SEC Lawsuit on Binance" width="4052" height="2334" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Photo: Glassnode</p></div></dt>
<dd>After a strong start to the year 2023, the world&#8217;s largest crypto cryptocurrency has come under selling pressure over the last few weeks. It has already corrected by more than 15% from its 2023 high of over $30,000.</dd>
</dl>
</div>
<p>Also, the US boosting its debt ceiling hasn&#8217;t helped Bitcoin investors much as they wait on the sidelines for the next FOMC meeting next week on June 14. In its recent report, on-chain data provider Glassnode <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1665706100161761280" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As an increasingly hostile regulatory environment is established in the US, capital appears to be flowing out, and eastward in the digital asset sector. Much of this hints to a generally risk-off environment, with the remaining capital concentrating in the more liquid majors, and a growing preference for Stablecoin capital.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Altcoins Face Greater Correction</h2>
<p>Along with Bitcoin, the altcoins have entered a deeper correction. In its lawsuit, the SEC has named altcoins like Binance BNB, Cardano’s ADA, Solana’s SOL, Polygon’s MATIC, Filecoin’s FIL and Algorand’s ALGO, for violating the securities laws by trading on the Binance crypto exchange.</p>
<p>The Binance BNB coin has faced the most correction and is down by 9% in the last 24 hours. All the above-mentioned altcoins have also corrected in the range between 5-9% each.</p>
<p>On-chain <a href="https://dune.com/queries/1582039/2633662" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a> from Dune analytics shows that crypto exchange Binance witnessed net outflows of a massive $635 million following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit. It will be interesting to see how strong can Binance continues to stay against the regulatory headwinds.</p>
<p>Binance and its chief CZ have received massive support from industry leaders. Cardano chief Charles Hoskinson has asked industry players to unite against the authoritarianism of the SEC and other regulatory bodies.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The total market capitalization for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> is still sustaining on the 200-Week MA and 200-Week EMA.</p>
<p>As long as that holds, and given that the final party, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a>, is receiving an attack, we could also be reaching the low of this correction. <a href="https://t.co/gAY7fig2ns">pic.twitter.com/gAY7fig2ns</a></p>
<p>— Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1665990139149971458?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>However, investors need not panic immediately. Popular crypto trader and analyst Michael Van de Poppe noted that the crypto market is still sustaining above the 200-week moving average (WMA).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/">Bitcoin (BTC) and Broader Crypto Market Come Crashing Down Following SEC Lawsuit on Binance</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Hedge Fund Arca to Lay Off 30% of Its Staff</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arca]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arca fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arca hedge fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arca lay off]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arca layoffs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto hedge fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto hedge fund arca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/">Crypto Hedge Fund Arca to Lay Off 30% of Its Staff</a></p>
<p>The company cited the challenging environment as a reason behind its headcount cut.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/">Crypto Hedge Fund Arca to Lay Off 30% of Its Staff</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/">Crypto Hedge Fund Arca to Lay Off 30% of Its Staff</a></p>
<p>Amid crypto winter and uncertain market conditions, companies continue to employ cost-cutting measures that often include layoffs. Digital asset management firm Arca is one the latest on the list of those currently in the middle of staff downsizing. Arca has reduced its headcount by as much as 30% (currently, it has only 66 employees in total), explaining the decision to lay off a third of its staff in a challenging environment.</p>
<p>Arca representative <a href="https://news.coincu.com/192382-arca-lays-off-30-of-employees/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Growth has been hard to predict in this extended bear market and uncertain regulatory environment. Our headcount adjustment will allow us to preserve capital and resources giving us a greater chance of success until this sector experiences a shift in sentiment and a clear regulatory picture.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Last year, Arca shut down its Digital Yield Fund within its cost-cutting strategy. Digital Yield Fund was claimed to be the first actively managed income fund in the digital-assets sector. Its goal was to offer a digital-asset investment with minimal volatility, targeting effective yields in the low double digits. However, the fund functioned for less than a year because of the market downturn. Exposure to TerraUSD (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/terrausd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UST</a>) stablecoin that collapsed has also affected Digital Yield Fund&#8217;s operation.</p>
<p>Following the closure of the Arca Digital Yield Fund, Arca&#8217;s vice president of portfolio management Hassan Bassiri left the company. Bassiri co-managed the Arca Digital Yield Fund with Arca Chief Investment Officer Jeff Dorman. Notably, Hassan Bassiri played a crucial role in managing the fund, and his departure had an impact on Arca’s portfolio management and investment strategies. Bassiri’s expertise in mergers and acquisitions and decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) made him a valuable asset to the firm.</p>
<h2>About Arca Fund</h2>
<p>Founded in 2018, Arca provides investment products and solutions to guide professionals and institutions into a digital economy powered by blockchain. The company consists of Arca Investments, which is an asset management arm, and Arca Labs, an innovation division. Arca&#8217;s flagship hedge fund strategy, the Arca Digital Assets Fund, invests in securities via tokens, equities, bonds and other instruments issued by companies in the digital asset ecosystem. Meanwhile, Arca Labs pioneers innovative products in a digital structure that aim to revolutionize the way how people think about investments.</p>
<p>Back in 2021, Arca raised $10 million in a Series A funding round led by RRE Ventures with additional participation from Alex Tisch, President of Loews Hotels &amp; Co and a coalition of top financiers led by Littlebanc Advisors. In 2022, Arca reached a $50 million cap in a raising round run by its Arca NFT Fund.</p>
<p>Arca has raised a total of $80M so far. Its leading investors are Alex Tisch and  RRE Ventures.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-series-products-wwdc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/">Crypto Hedge Fund Arca to Lay Off 30% of Its Staff</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arca-lay-off-30-staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4163 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1019238 metric#prefetches=201 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=207 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=106.82 metric#ms-cache=5.49 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2745 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.1 -->