<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
<p>The injection of $5 million from Binance Labs transcends a simple financial transaction; it represents a collaborative effort focused on strengthening Curve's security infrastructure and aiding the protocol in recovering its stability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
<p>Binance Labs, the investment arm of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, has committed a substantial $5 million investment in Curve DAO Token (CRV). The strategic move comes as a response to a recent security breach that rattled the Curve ecosystem. Binance Labs said in its <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-labs-invests-$5m-in-curve-dao-token-crv-and-supports-curve-deployment-to-bnb-chain-4372009526169554266" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> on August 10 that the investment demonstrates its commitment to shaping the future of the decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) sector.</p>
<p>The funds will be used to support Curve&#8217;s native token, CRV, which serves as a utility token that regulates all the activities in the Curve protocol. The DeFi platform is renowned as the largest stableswap and the industry&#8217;s second-largest decentralized exchange (DEX). With this infusion of funds from Binance Labs, the protocol can further strengthen its foothold and ensure that the platform is tightly packed with security features that make it impenetrable to hackers.</p>
<p>Curve faced a setback due to a vulnerability in its underlying programming language, Vyper. Cybercriminals exploited this vulnerability on July 30, losing $73.5 million from its stable pools. However, the DeFi platform has since recovered around 73% of the stolen funds worth around $52.3 million. The platform recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/curve-finance-bounty-exploiter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">issued</a> a $1.85 million bounty hunter seeking to expose the hacker who claimed he was smarter than the protocol in an on-chain message on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum.</a></p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m refunding you, not because you can find me. It&#8217;s because I don&#8217;t want to ruin your project. I&#8217;m smarter than all of you, f**k!!,&#8221; reads the message.</p>
<h2>Curve Finance Receives Support from Binance Labs after Hack</h2>
<p>The DeFi platform has now received financial support from Binance Labs to help recover from the attack. The injection of $5 million from Binance Labs transcends a simple financial transaction, it represents a collaborative effort focused on strengthening Curve&#8217;s security infrastructure and aiding the protocol in recovering its stability. This investment is not solely aimed at addressing vulnerabilities but is geared toward amplifying the platform&#8217;s functionalities.</p>
<p>Yi He, Co-Founder of Binance and Head of Binance Labs, referenced the attack while noting that the platform had significantly impacted the adoption of the DeFi apps in 2023.</p>
<p>&#8220;Curve is the largest stableswap, and as a key protocol in DeFi, it has contributed to the steady growth of the space in 2023. Given the recent events that have impacted the protocol, Binance Labs has offered our full support to Curve through our investment and strategic collaboration. We view this cooperation as a starting point and look forward to working together to propel the growth of the DeFi ecosystem further.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Curve to Deploy on BNB Chain</h2>
<p>As part of the collaboration with Binance Labs, Curve plans to explore BNB Chain. According to the announcement, the DeFi protocol, which currently operates across several chains, will expand its protocol to the BNB ecosystem. The move will further propel the growth of the BNB Chain DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>&#8220;BNB Chain has earned a significant presence in DeFi and is well positioned to deploy Curve&#8217;s current and future products on its chain. We look forward to collaboratively fostering innovation and growth across the DeFi ecosystem,&#8221; said Michael Egorov, founder of Curve.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/">Binance Labs Supports Curve Finance with $5M Investment to Aid Recovery from Recent Hack</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-curve-5m-recovery-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrpl]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
<p>Gemini highlighted that XRP will be available for trading under several currency pairs including USD, GBP, EUR, CAD, SGD, HKD, and AUD.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
<p>Following the court&#8217;s ruling earlier last month on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a> vs Ripple case, cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> announced on Thursday that it has now added the support of XRPL and its native digital asset <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>. According to the announcement, XRP is now available for trading on the company’s API/FIX and ActiveTrader applications for USD pairs. Additionally, the company announced that the Gemini Mobile App and website users can trade XRP pairs in USD, GBP, EUR, CAD, SGD, HKD, and AUD. The announcement was welcomed by the XRP and Ripple community as it means enhanced liquidity for the digital asset.</p>
<p>“Adding XRP Ledger to our list of supported crypto networks is an important step on our mission to unlock the next era of financial, creative, and personal freedom,” Gemini noted in the <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-adds-support-for-xrp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange, however, noted that XRP can only be stored in its exchange wallet before it is made available for the Gemini Custody. The company additionally advised its users that they must upgrade to the latest version of its mobile app to deposit XRP.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Be sure to update your Gemini mobile app to version 23.808.0 to deposit XRP</p>
<p>Read more here ⤵️<a href="https://t.co/ib7lvQkz1r">https://t.co/ib7lvQkz1r</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1689634983609057280?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Market Implications for Gemini Listing Ripple-backed XRP</h2>
<p>The support of XRPL and XRP on the Gemini cryptocurrency exchange is a mutual benefit that extends the interaction of both communities. Notably, XRP is globally traded and adopted by a wide range of institutional investors tapping Ripple&#8217;s cross-border payment infrastructure like On-Demand Liquidity (ODL), and RippleNet. According to the latest crypto market data, the XRP digital asset has a market capitalization of approximately $33.4 billion and a 24-hour trading volume of about $1.147 billion.</p>
<p>Gemini exchange, on the other hand, is available to over 70 countries through regulated means and has facilitated over $200 billion in traded volume. The company has several products in the market including staking, credit card, eOTC, and custody for institutional investors. The company has made strategic partnerships along the way to help accelerate the mainstream adoption of digital assets. Among the companies in Gemini’s portfolio as partners, there are Samsung, Nifty Gateway, and Brave, among others.</p>
<p>As a New York-based crypto company, Gemini is regulated by the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYSDFS) to provide its services. With millions of crypto traders already using Gemini exchange and XRP offering deep liquidity, experts believe the integration is strategic for their future growth prospects.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the announcement did not have a major positive effect on the XRP price in the past day. According to market data provided by Coingecko, XRP price trades around 63 cents, down approximately 5.1 percent in the last week. Nevertheless, XRP price has gained approximately 83 percent YTD fueled by regulatory clarity and several listings.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/">Gemini Opens XRP Deposits after Announcing Support for XRPL</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-xrp-deposits-xrpl/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fdic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[occ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
<p>The US SEC filed a complaint against Bittrex on April 17 with the US District Court for the Western District of Washington alleging the exchange listed unregistered securities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) counted another win against the cryptocurrency market on Thursday after digital asset exchange Bittrex agreed on a $24 million settlement for allegedly listing unregistered securities in the name of crypto assets trading. However, the SEC noted that the defendants agreed on the settlement under the condition that the former neither admits nor denies the allegations. Nonetheless, the SEC counted it as a win after a recent blow in the Ripple case, which the agency intends to appeal.</p>
<h2>SEC vs Bittrex Litigation</h2>
<p>Earlier this year, the United States SEC filed a complaint against the Bittrex crypto exchange and its former CEO William Shihara for allegedly operating an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency. The SEC highlighted that Bittrex has earned at least $1.3 billion from 2017 through 2022 by charging transaction fees from investors.</p>
<p>The SEC further complained that Bittrex and Shihara, who was the company’s CEO from 2014 to 2019, coordinated with crypto issuers to first delete from public channels certain problematic statements that the exchange believed would lead to regulatory scrutiny. As a result, the SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-78" target="_blank" rel="noopener">argued</a> that the exchange chose profits over investor protection.</p>
<p>Having been cornered without further argument based on existing laws, Bittrex and Bittrex Global agreed to pay a joint disgorgement fee of about $14.4 million, prejudgment interest of $4 million, and a civil penalty of $5.6 million, thereby bringing the total penalty to about $24 million. Notably, the settlement is subject to the court’s approval</p>
<p>“Today’s settlement makes clear that you cannot escape liability by simply changing labels or altering descriptions because what matters is the economic realities of those offerings. I am grateful to the SEC staff for aggressively pursuing non-compliance in the crypto industry, resolving this matter, and bringing additional relief to harmed investors,” Gurbir S. Grewal, Director of the SEC’s Division of Enforcement, <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-150" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The US SEC has already filed similar complaints against several crypto exchanges including Binance US and also Coinbase Global, Inc. (NASDAQ: COIN). However, the SEC has been accused of overstepping its mandate as some argue that the crypto market is not under its jurisdiction.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today we announced that crypto asset trading platform Bittrex Inc. and its co-founder and former CEO, William Shihara, agreed to settle charges that they operated an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency.</p>
<p>&mdash; U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (@SECGov) <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov/status/1689741781481504768?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency market in the United States is expected to experience heavy regulatory onslaught from several agencies including the Fed, SEC, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>, FDIC, and OCC. Notably, Congress too has made swift progress in regulating the crypto industry more so the stablecoins market in a bid to ensure a safe adoption of the digital dollar, which in turn helps the greenback retain its status as the global reserve currency.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/">Bittrex Agrees to Pay $24M to Settle with SEC for Failing to Register as National Securities Exchange</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bittrex-24m-sec-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital rupee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iwbdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rbi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266523</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
<p>The competition, which has a submission deadline in July next, will allow tech enthusiasts add to crypto innovation in India.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
<p>India is looking to launch a new web browser that allows people to digitally sign documents using crypto tokens. According to an official <a href="https://pib.gov.in/PressReleaseIframePage.aspx?PRID=1947243" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a>, the Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology (MeitY) launched the Indian Web Browser Development Challenge (IWBDC) to build the app.</p>
<p>The press release explains that the IWBDC is an open competition to inspire tech enthusiasts, developers, and innovators looking to build the browser. The announcement also expects that the browser would come equipped with tight security and data privacy protection.</p>
<p>“Proposed browser would also focus on accessibility and user-friendliness, ensuring built-in support for individuals with diverse abilities. Moreover, the browser envisions the ability to digitally sign documents using a crypto token, bolstering secure transactions and digital interactions,” reads the announcement.</p>
<p>The browser is expected to fully support Web3 and similar functionalities. The MeitY has also announced a $400,000 prize for the winner and has set the submission deadline for July 1, 2024.</p>
<h2>Crypto in India</h2>
<p>India has tried repeatedly to ban cryptocurrency in the country but has not had much success. While there is no direct ban on cryptocurrencies in India, the unregulated nature suggests that authorities oppose the widespread adoption of digital assets in the Southeast Asian country. There are also no official guidelines for using crypto and no government-backed recourse for problems arising from crypto investment and related issues.</p>
<p>Last year, India launched the Digital Rupee, a crypto version of its national currency, after initially proposing the asset in 2017. Now, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is hoping that the Digital Rupee would help significantly with cross-border transactions.</p>
<p>The RBI has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-rbi-central-banks-digital-rupee/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">engaged nearly 20 central banks</a> all over the world, seeking ways through which the central bank digital currency (CBDC) will support cross-border payments. According to RBI Governor Shaktikanta Das, India is a vibrant market for trade and receives a large number of cross-border payments from citizens working in other countries. However, there have been setbacks.</p>
<p>Das explains that access to the United States dollar is an increasingly difficult problem for traders in most countries looking to import goods. He states that while India has no shortage of dollars, many other countries have these problems and are affected by the scarcity.</p>
<p>The RBI Governor explains there is a market for the Digital Rupee as a tool for cross-border payments since many popular options have seen reduced patronage because of the increased adoption of Bitcoin and many other cryptocurrencies. Using the Digital Rupee, the RBI Governor assures that cross-border transactions and payments will be cheaper, easier, and much faster. India hopes to counter the dependence on USD and make the Digital Rupee the preferred cross-border payment option instead of Bitcoin and other digital assets.</p>
<h2>India’s Economy</h2>
<p>Last month, Goldman Sachs <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-india-2075/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> India would become the world’s second-largest economy by 2075. The firm states India will overtake large economies like Germany, China, and Japan.</p>
<p>Goldman’s India economist Santanu Sengupta also added that India’s dependency ratio would become one of the lowest sometime in the next 20 years. A dependency ratio compares the number of a country’s working population with its dependent sector.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/">India Launches Open Competition to Build Web Browser Using Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/india-sign-documents-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eu mica]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[france]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266476</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
<p>The "enhanced" registration requirements will be effective from January 1, 2024.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
<p>In a bid to conform to the recently finalized Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation, France has just revised its requirements for crypto firms. The country&#8217;s financial regulator AMF <a href="https://www.amf-france.org/en/news-publications/news/digital-assets-amf-amends-it-general-regulation-and-its-policy-dasp-light-enhanced-registration-and#xts=607212&amp;xtor=RSS-3&amp;type=RSS" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed</a> this on Thursday, as countries in the European Union (EU) stand in line to implement the new rule which will take effect in about one and a half years.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, France already has a seemingly robust licensing regime for crypto firms. Therefore, it has been a place of high interest to many firms looking to register ahead of implementing MiCA. That is considering that firms that have duly registered under the current licensing regime may not have any need to be MiCA-compliant when the rule takes effect.</p>
<h2>MiCA Regulation: How&#8217;s the AMF Preparing?</h2>
<p>According to AMF, the &#8220;enhanced&#8221; registration requirements will be effective from Jan. 1, 2024. And, it will be mandatory for &#8220;new players&#8221; that may want to offer any digital assets services. About the old players, however, the regulator said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As a reminder, DASPs that obtained a simple registration before Jan. 1, 2024 benefit from a &#8220;grandfather&#8221; clause and continue to be subject to the framework applicable before this date.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Per the AMF, the amendment to its rule covers diverse areas that seek to ensure that digital asset service providers conduct their businesses in good faith. Its revised rule, for instance,  bans crypto firms from using client assets without their express permission. Also, it requires that digital asset service providers issue clear and non-misleading information about their operations. That is as it pertains to their pricing policies, custody provisions ( proper differentiation between client assets and own assets), and security and control systems. And, lastly, the amended rule also seeks for these firms to establish systems for managing conflicts of interest.</p>
<p>Although <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-approval-france/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and Hex Trust are registered with the AMF, they were recently joined by Societe Generale&#8217;s crypto division which recently bagged the license as well.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/">France Modifies Regulatory Requirements for Crypto Firms to Align with MiCA Regulation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/france-crypto-firms-mica-regulation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Records Impressive Fiscal Q1 2024 Revenue Growth of 14%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266531</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/">Alibaba Records Impressive Fiscal Q1 2024 Revenue Growth of 14%</a></p>
<p>The company’s expansion into new business verticals has played a significant role in bolstering its fiscal Q1 2024 results.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/">Alibaba Records Impressive Fiscal Q1 2024 Revenue Growth of 14%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/">Alibaba Records Impressive Fiscal Q1 2024 Revenue Growth of 14%</a></p>
<p>Chinese e-commerce giant, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holding Ltd</a> (HKG: 9988) has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/10/alibaba-baba-earnings-report-q1-2024.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> remarkable revenue and financial results for its fiscal Q1 2024 ending June 30.</p>
<p>With a 14% year-on-year increase in revenue and a surge of more than 2.5% in pre-market trading for its US-traded shares, Alibaba continues to demonstrate its resilience and strength in the ever-evolving online marketplace.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Revenue Outperforms Expectations in Q1 2024</h2>
<p>Alibaba’s strong second-quarter performance was highlighted by its healthy revenue results of 234.16 billion Chinese Yuan ($32.29 billion). This is significantly above Refinitiv’s consensus estimate of 224.92 billion Yuan, representing a 14% year-on-year increase.</p>
<p>Not only did Alibaba outperform in terms of revenue growth, but its net income also increased significantly. The net income attributable to common shareholders was 34.33 billion Chinese Yuan, exceeding the expected 28.66 billion Yuan. This translates to an impressive 51% year-on-year increase in net income.</p>
<p>Such remarkable growth in net income reflects the effectiveness of Alibaba’s strategic decisions, operational excellence, and ability to capitalize on emerging trends in the e-commerce sector.</p>
<p>Alibaba&#8217;s impressive Q2 performance is not merely a stroke of luck but a result of the company&#8217;s unwavering commitment to innovation, strategic expansion, and relentless pursuit of excellence.</p>
<p>One of the pivotal factors behind Alibaba’s remarkable Q1 2024 performance lies in its strategic integration of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Artificial Intelligence</a> (AI). The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-ai-image-generation-model/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduction</a> of a new AI image generation model dubbed Tongyi Wanxiang has not only elevated productivity but also fostered an environment of creativity for businesses across the spectrum.</p>
<p>Additionally, the company’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/freshippo-presence-china-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expansion</a> into new business verticals has played a significant role in bolstering its Q1 2024 results. Alibaba&#8217;s dedication to long-term growth and its emphasis on innovation-driven solutions have instilled confidence in investors, propelling the company to unprecedented heights.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Navigates through Stormy Waters</h2>
<p>Alibaba has long been a prominent player in the world of online commerce, but recent times have presented the corporation with unusual problems.</p>
<p>Since December, when China relaxed its rigorous pandemic controls, the country&#8217;s economic trajectory has been a mixed bag, leaving Alibaba to navigate through an environment that has both surprised and confounded investors. The anticipation of a robust economic rebound clashed with the reality of sluggish domestic consumer demand, presenting Alibaba with a complex set of circumstances to navigate.</p>
<p>To address the shifting landscape, Alibaba announced significant organizational changes in March. The company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-split-6-groups-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> it would split into six distinct business groups as a strategic move to enhance flexibility and potentially raise outside funding.</p>
<p>This restructuring also grants select business groups the opportunity to go public, a move that could inject fresh capital into specific segments of the conglomerate. Notably, Alibaba has already disclosed its intention to publicly list its cloud computing division, a pivotal step in capitalizing on the growing demand for cloud services.</p>
<p>In the midst of these changes, Alibaba is also undergoing a shift in leadership. The impending <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">departure</a> of current CEO and Chairman Daniel Zhang in September marks the end of an era.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/">Alibaba Records Impressive Fiscal Q1 2024 Revenue Growth of 14%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-q1-2024-revenue-growth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fireblocks Uncovers BitForge: Series of Security Vulnerabilities Affecting Crypto Wallets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitforge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fireblocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zengo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/">Fireblocks Uncovers BitForge: Series of Security Vulnerabilities Affecting Crypto Wallets</a></p>
<p>Coinbase, Zengo, and Binance expressed gratitude to Fireblocks for identifying and responsibly disclosing the security issues before any losses occurred. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/">Fireblocks Uncovers BitForge: Series of Security Vulnerabilities Affecting Crypto Wallets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/">Fireblocks Uncovers BitForge: Series of Security Vulnerabilities Affecting Crypto Wallets</a></p>
<p>It was discovered through a recent study carried out by Fireblocks that many crypto wallets are at risk of being drained due to a security flaw that exchanges do not know about. Fireblocks dubbed the security flaw BitForge. It is a series of vulnerabilities affecting wallets using multi-party computation (MPC) technology that allows multiple parties to control and manage cryptocurrency holdings. These security threats have never been identified, and have impacted several major <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-a-crypto-wallet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto wallet</a> providers, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>, WaaS, Zengo, and Binance.</p>
<p>BitForge can enable attackers to drain wallets without the knowledge of users or vendors. The potential draining of numerous retail and institutional investors&#8217; wallets, with no immediate solution available, could lead to increased apprehension within the crypto industry. Thus, it becomes imperative for crypto exchanges to swiftly address the issue.</p>
<p>Addressing the problem proactively is essential, as attempting to resolve it once it starts happening might prove challenging because the whole draining process could be completed within seconds.</p>
<p>Pavel Berengoltz, co-founder of Fireblocks, emphasized the significance of web3 technologies collaborating with security experts with extensive knowledge to stay ahead of vulnerabilities. He <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/fireblocks-researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-impacting-dozens-of-major-wallet-providers-301897357.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As decentralized finance and Web3 continue to gain popularity, the need for secure wallet and key management providers is evident. While we are encouraged to see that MPC is now ubiquitous within the digital asset industry, it is evident from our findings &#8211; and our subsequent disclosure process &#8211; that not all MPC developers and teams are created equal. Companies leveraging Web3 technology should work closely with security experts with the know-how and resources to stay ahead of and mitigate vulnerabilities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Numerous other crypto wallet providers have also been affected by this series of vulnerabilities. As a result, Fireblocks has introduced a BitForge checker to help exchanges and other wallet providers know if they are exposed.</p>
<h2>Coinbase, Zengo, and Binance Have Addressed the BitForge Security Issue</h2>
<p>Coinbase, Zengo, and Binance expressed gratitude to Fireblocks for identifying and responsibly disclosing the security issues before any losses occurred. Jeff Lunglhofer, Chief Information Security Officer for Coinbase, shared his thoughts on the matter:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We would like to thank Fireblocks for identifying and responsibly disclosing this issue. While Coinbase customers and funds were never at risk, maintaining a fully trustless cryptographic model is an important aspect of any MPC implementation. Setting a high industry bar for safety protects the ecosystem and is critical to the broader adoption of this technology.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The three exchanges mentioned that they have fixed the issues, assuring their customers about the safety of their services. They also emphasized the importance of partnering with security experts so as to stay ahead of potential security issues.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/">Fireblocks Uncovers BitForge: Series of Security Vulnerabilities Affecting Crypto Wallets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fireblocks-bitforge-security-vulnerabilities/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Announces Open Beta for eSignature Feature in Google Docs and Drive</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/">Google Announces Open Beta for eSignature Feature in Google Docs and Drive</a></p>
<p>Users will now be able to request for and place an eSignature on contracts within Google Docs and Google Drive.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/">Google Announces Open Beta for eSignature Feature in Google Docs and Drive</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/">Google Announces Open Beta for eSignature Feature in Google Docs and Drive</a></p>
<p>Google has unveiled an open beta of its eSignature feature for the Google Workspace. The feature is available for Google Docs and Google Drive users.</p>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2023/08/esignature-google-docs-google-drive.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>, Google has been alpha testing eSignatures in Google Docs since June last year. The testing involved dragging and dropping signatures and dates, as well as requesting signatures after resolving all comments and suggestions. Google was also experimenting with monitoring contract progress and also tracking the status of pending signatures and contracts. All of these features are now available to users.</p>
<p>The blog post also announces a few more features that would be available a little later this year. Users would see an automatic audit trail report for all completed contracts, and a multi-signer feature that allows people to request signatures from multiple users. Furthermore, requesting an eSignature from a non-Gmail user will also be possible, in addition to initiating an eSignature on a PDF file in Google Drive. According to the blog post, some Google Workspace editions will be able to test the eSignature sometime in the next few weeks.</p>
<p>The new Google eSignature feature comes long after other platforms have introduced similar options for users. For instance, Dropbox <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/01/28/dropbox-snares-hellosign-for-230m-gets-workflow-and-esignature/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquired</a> workflow and eSignature company HelloSign for $230 million in 2019 and integrated the feature. Now called Dropbox Sign, the feature allows users to exchange and sign documents within Dropbox. Adobe Acrobat also has a similar feature.</p>
<p>There’s also DocuSign, the California-based eSignature company that offers basic integrations with several platforms, including Google Drive, Evernote, Microsoft 365, and Dropbox. On specific plans, integrating Microsoft Dynamics, NetSuite, Salesforce, Sugar CRM, and Microsoft SharePoint is also possible. In June, DocuSign <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/docu-shares-docusign-q1-2024/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> strong earnings of $661 million for fiscal Q1 2024, beating the expected $642 million.</p>
<h2>Google eSignature Follows Other Product Announcements</h2>
<p>Last week, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-upgrade-assistant-ai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that Google plans to upgrade its Google Assistant feature using artificial intelligence. According to reports, the company is working on a “supercharged” assistant powered by large language model (LLM) technology.</p>
<p>The new Google Assistant would support enhanced conversations and make user interactions a lot more engaging. By using LLM similar to generative AI chatbots like Bard and ChatGPT, users will experience a more advanced assistant with more solutions and tools to solve problems and perform the assistant’s role.</p>
<p>Google is also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-ai-tool-journalists/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">developing</a> an AI-powered tool for journalists. Also using LLM technology, Google is creating a tool to help journalists and media personnel write news articles. Reportedly, Google has already pitched the tool to a few news organizations, including the New York Times, Washington Post, and News Corp.</p>
<p>Called Genesis, the new tool can create a news copy using details provided by the journalists. The tool is also expected to create these articles by relying on current affairs. However, reactions to Genesis have been broadly polar. While some believe it should be applauded, others say that Google is treating news writing with levity. Some journalists also believe employers will begin to cut journalist roles in favor of Genesis.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/">Google Announces Open Beta for eSignature Feature in Google Docs and Drive</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-beta-signature-docs-drive/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain’s August Upgrades Expected to Improve Security and Sync with EVM Chains</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb chain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bsc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eip]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[evm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266494</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/">BNB Chain&#8217;s August Upgrades Expected to Improve Security and Sync with EVM Chains</a></p>
<p>A fast finality mechanism on the BNB Chain would mean a safer environment for decentralized applications (dApps).</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/">BNB Chain&#8217;s August Upgrades Expected to Improve Security and Sync with EVM Chains</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/">BNB Chain&#8217;s August Upgrades Expected to Improve Security and Sync with EVM Chains</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>’s BNB Chain is scheduled for two upgrades this month to improve the chain’s finality and its compatibility with other Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) blockchains. The hard forks are expected to reduce the likelihood of malicious blockchain reorganization and are scheduled for August 10 and 30.</p>
<p>The first upgrade, called the Plato upgrade has already occurred and introduces BEP-126. <a href="https://forum.bnbchain.org/t/bep-126-draft-introduce-fast-finality-mechanism/123" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BEP-126</a> is an improvement proposal that introduces a fast finality mechanism to the BNB Smart Chain. Arno Bauer, a senior solution architect at BNB Chain <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bnb-chain-hard-forks-improve-finality-security" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a> that the fast finality mechanism is expected to reduce the possibility of chain reorganization and stabilize block production, allowing users immediate access to accurate data from the latest finalized block in the chain.</p>
<p>“Overall, BEP-126 aims to enhance blockchain security and efficiency on the BNB Smart Chain by introducing a fast finality mechanism,” Bauer stated.</p>
<p>Finality refers to a point at which a blockchain transaction or block can no longer be changed or reversed. It is one of the most important features of blockchain technology as it is key to maintaining trust and preventing double-spending. A fast finality mechanism on the BNB Chain would mean a safer environment for decentralized applications (dApps). Improved transaction finality speed is also expected to improve the responsiveness and efficiency of dApps run on the network.</p>
<p>The fast finality introduced by BEP-126 occurs via a series of steps. First, a validator proposes a block, which is propagated to other validators. The validators use their private key to sign for the block as a vote message. Validator votes are then gathered into a pool and aggregated if the direct parent block has enough votes.</p>
<p>Validators are expected to strictly adhere to guidelines when voting for blocks. For example, validators can not publish contrasting votes for the same height. The guidelines also state that a block is “justified” if its child block header contains an attestation and it is “finalized” if it and its direct child are justified.</p>
<p>The second upgrade is the Hertz hard fork which is expected to catch the BNB Chain up to the latest developments of EVM blockchains. According to Bauer, the chain’s block and transaction structures and its base EVM need to stay updated to match Ethereum’s latest Berlin and London forks.</p>
<p>“Therefore, for compatibility reasons it is important that those EIPs are also enabled on BSC to ensure a smooth development and ecosystem growth,” explained Bauer.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/">BNB Chain&#8217;s August Upgrades Expected to Improve Security and Sync with EVM Chains</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-evm-chains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virgin Galactic to Launch First Private Tourists Space Travel</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[richard branson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[space tourism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virgin galactic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266468</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Launch First Private Tourists Space Travel</a></p>
<p>Virgin Galactic has highlighted that its narrative doesn't end with the launch of the VSS Unity, but extends to the development of an even more sophisticated fleet, aptly named the Delta class.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Launch First Private Tourists Space Travel</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Launch First Private Tourists Space Travel</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/virgin-galactic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Virgin Galactic Holdings</a> (NYSE: SPCE) is on the verge of making history once again with the launch of its second commercial spaceflight that will carry its first cohort of private tourists into space.</p>
<p>Recent <a href="https://gulfnews.com/business/tourism/virgin-galactic-is-set-to-fly-first-private-tourists-to-space-1.97454160" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> reveal that this momentous journey is scheduled to unfold later today. To share this remarkable experience with the world, Virgin Galactic plans to broadcast the flight through a live webcast. Starting at 11am New York time (Thursday, 8:30 pm IST), enthusiasts and curious onlookers alike will be able to witness this historic event unfold in real-time on the company’s official website.</p>
<p>The upcoming flight marks a pivotal transition for Virgin Galactic as it embarks on its maiden voyage into the realm of hosting paying customers. Preceding this groundbreaking event was the notable Galactic 01 research mission, which paved the way for the company’s innovative approach to private space travel.</p>
<p>However, this imminent launch is set to be the company’s inaugural foray into commercial space tourism, solidifying its position as a key player in the rapidly expanding field. The launch will take place from a cutting-edge spaceport in New Mexico, a testimony to the relentless efforts that have spanned over two decades of development.</p>
<p>This project underscores the profound commitment of Virgin Galactic’s founder, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/richard-branson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sir Richard Branson</a>, to create a platform that offers citizens the awe-inspiring experience of space travel, competing directly with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeff-bezos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeff Bezos</a>’ Blue Origin.</p>
<p>This event is not merely a singular achievement but also symbolizes the beginning of addressing the backlog of approximately 800 eager ticket holders. Virgin Galactic&#8217;s dedication to fulfilling these dreams aligns with its mission to democratize access to space and make the cosmos a tangible reality for the masses.</p>
<h2>Genesis of Virgin Galactic’s Historic Space Flight</h2>
<p>The genesis of Virgin Galactic dates back to its establishment in 2004, with the company originally promising to commence passenger flights as early as 2007. Tickets were initially available at a price of $200,000 but were later increased to $250,000 trailing unforeseen delays in the development process.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the firm experienced a big setback in 2014 when a Virgin Galactic spaceplane crashed during a test flight, killing one test pilot and severely injuring another. This terrible occurrence led Virgin Galactic to temporarily suspend ticket sales while the firm undertook extensive introspection and restructuring.</p>
<p>In 2018, a significant breakthrough was achieved as the company successfully reached space for the first time. Another notable milestone arrived in 2021 when Branson himself <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/branson-space-virgin-galactic-flight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">embarked</a> on a voyage to space aboard a Virgin Galactic spacecraft.</p>
<p>Currently, Virgin Galactic anticipates a span of time before seeing substantial revenue streams. According to the company&#8217;s predictions, revenue will be about $1 million in each of the last two quarters of the year. However, if research flights are included in the calculation, these figures may rise slightly.</p>
<p>Virgin Galactic has highlighted that its narrative doesn&#8217;t end with the launch of the VSS Unity, but extends to the development of an even more sophisticated fleet, aptly named the Delta class. Expected to be operational around 2026, these advanced spacecraft represent a quantum leap in technology and capability.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-ceo-threat-usd/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Launch First Private Tourists Space Travel</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-tourists-space-travel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4112 metric#misses=47 metric#hit-ratio=98.9 metric#bytes=1064180 metric#prefetches=201 metric#store-reads=25 metric#store-writes=4 metric#store-hits=208 metric#store-misses=8 metric#sql-queries=36 metric#ms-total=110.35 metric#ms-cache=5.55 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1982 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.0 -->