<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:44:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Sandbox Stalls. Could Metacade’s MCADE Price Overtake The Sandbox’s SAND in 2023 and Beyond?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-stalls-could-metacades-mcade-price-overtake-the-sandboxs-sand-in-2023-and-beyond/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-stalls-could-metacades-mcade-price-overtake-the-sandboxs-sand-in-2023-and-beyond/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-stalls-could-metacades-mcade-price-overtake-the-sandboxs-sand-in-2023-and-beyond/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sandbox price failed to recover from a year-long slump during the bullish price action of early 2023. 3D games in the metaverse have been a source of great excitement among blockchain investors, but a new kind of play-to-earn (P2E) platform may be the next big thing in the GameFi sector. Metacade&#8217;s hugely successful token [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-stalls-could-metacades-mcade-price-overtake-the-sandboxs-sand-in-2023-and-beyond/">The Sandbox Stalls. Could Metacade’s MCADE Price Overtake The Sandbox’s SAND in 2023 and Beyond?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox price failed to recover from a year-long slump during the bullish price action of early 2023. 3D games in the metaverse have been a source of great excitement among blockchain investors, but a new kind of play-to-earn (P2E) platform may be the next big thing in the GameFi sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=68" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>&rsquo;s hugely successful token presale is a testament to an exciting roadmap that has appealed to Web3 users. While The Sandbox price continues to struggle, Metacade&rsquo;s continues to gain momentum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade is a very interesting niche investment opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While the majority of cryptocurrencies in Web3 enjoyed significant gains at the beginning of 2023, The Sandbox price underperformed. 3D games in the metaverse posted impressive returns during the 2021 bull market, yet a prolonged slump for The Sandbox price has concerned some long-term investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox price remains more than 90% down from its all-time high. Meanwhile, <strong>Metacade rose more than 2x in the space of a week</strong> as it continues to generate excitement among the blockchain gaming community. The token is fresh from two primary exchange listings and looks ready to continue its rapid development.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=68" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> raised $16.4 million during the MCADE token presale, with most fundraising stages sold out. Since then, the MCADE token has launched on Uniswap and BitMart and skyrocketed to a $0.03 price level towards the end of April.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While 3D games based in the metaverse are still in their infancy, Metacade&rsquo;s comprehensive <a href="https://sensoriumxr.com/articles/what-is-play-to-earn-gaming" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>play to earn</u></a> environment intends to include 3D games as it grows. It awaits to be seen whether The Sandbox price will reclaim its previous highs over time.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is The Sandbox</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox is a blockchain-based virtual gaming world where players can create, share, and monetize their gaming experiences. Utilizing the Ethereum blockchain, The Sandbox aims to revolutionize the gaming industry by providing a decentralized platform for gamers and game developers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With its unique combination of user-generated content and P2E mechanics, The Sandbox offers a new frontier for gamers to explore and connect. Players can also purchase LAND, virtual real estate that can be used to build and monetize custom gaming experiences.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Could SAND reach $5 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Sandbox remains one of the top 3D games in Web3. Despite its reduced price of $0.60, which is 92% down from the all-time high of $8.50, The Sandbox price could target higher price levels above $1 and $2.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Price analysts have highlighted a key resistance area for The Sandbox price at the $3.50 level. As the broader crypto market enters long-awaited bull market conditions over the coming years, a leading 3D game such as The Sandbox certainly has the potential to reach its previous resistance levels.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=68" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> will be the first community-driven blockchain arcade and the most extensive platform found in Web3. It plans to offer many different play-to-earn arcade games in a single location, which gives players an extensive opportunity to earn cryptocurrency rewards while enjoying some addictive gameplay experiences.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project also aims to become a central hub for the blockchain community by introducing several unique earning mechanisms. Metacade will serve investors, entrepreneurs, and gamers through a range of on-chain services. The platform is genuinely planning on taking P2E mechanics to the next level.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does MCADE work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token is used to pay rewards in the metaverse arcade. Players can play solo, earn MCADE tokens while trying to beat their highest score, or join paid entry tournaments to win major crypto prizes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is also developing a suite of DeFi services for its community. MCADE token holders can use on-platform staking to earn a passive yield and use their tokens to vote in governance proposals released by the project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Metacade community hub is introducing a novel variation of the play-to-earn mechanism called Create2Earn. <strong>This will reward content creators with MCADE tokens for their contributions to the community</strong>. Contributions can include posting game reviews, sharing alpha, and interacting with other users&rsquo; posts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As well as all this, Metacade will advertise paid job opportunities at leading companies in <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/web3/"><u>Web3</u></a>. Crypto enthusiasts can apply for full-time and part-time roles directly through the Metacade jobs board, which will also include a Work2Earn feature that connects users to unique beta testing opportunities for brand-new P2E titles.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Could MCADE reach $2 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token has enjoyed a fruitful start to 2023. The presale was successfully closed with $16.4 million raised as funding for the metaverse arcade, which displays the widespread popularity of the project and its projected future demand.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE has extensive utility on the Metacade platform and deflationary tokenomics. Price analysts are forecasting significant returns from the current price of $0.027 as long-term investors continue to buy the token ahead of a future crypto bull market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade vs. The Sandbox price predictions: Which token is worth buying?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain can support 3D games with integrated earning potential for players. This is a crucial reason why metaverse projects such as The Sandbox and Metacade have high price forecasts for the future. Metacade and The Sandbox prices are expected to rise significantly from the current levels.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade, as a brand new platform in the GameFi sector, could be preparing for massive action over the coming years. Further information about this exciting project is available on Metacade&rsquo;s <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=68" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>.</p>
<p><strong>You can find more information, including how to buy MCADE,&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=68" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-stalls-could-metacades-mcade-price-overtake-the-sandboxs-sand-in-2023-and-beyond/">The Sandbox Stalls. Could Metacade’s MCADE Price Overtake The Sandbox’s SAND in 2023 and Beyond?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sandbox-stalls-could-metacades-mcade-price-overtake-the-sandboxs-sand-in-2023-and-beyond/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Has institutional money left crypto?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Crypto prices have rebounded strongly this year, but the space remains barren compared to the pandemic hysteria Institutional money has fled at an alarming pace, and there is no guarantee it will return Scandals of 2022 were on such a large scale that capital is reluctant to return Mention &#8220;2022&#8221; to anyone remotely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/">Has institutional money left crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto prices have rebounded strongly this year, but the space remains barren compared to the pandemic hysteria</li>
<li dir="ltr">Institutional money has fled at an alarming pace, and there is no guarantee it will return</li>
<li dir="ltr">Scandals of 2022 were on such a large scale that capital is reluctant to return</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Mention &ldquo;2022&rdquo; to anyone remotely involved in the cryptocurrency industry and you&rsquo;ll likely send a shudder down their spine. The year was fraught with scandals, embarrassments and, more than anything else, thundering price collapses.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> is a good gauge for the action of the industry. The world&rsquo;s biggest crypto peaked at close to $69,000 in November 2021. One year later, it was $15,500.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13653672">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Since the nadir in November, prices have bounced strongly. Bitcoin is currently trading around $29,000, as softer inflation data and optimism around the future path of interest rates picked up since the winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, things are different. And despite these rising prices, there has to be a fear that the cryptocurrency industry has suffered an indelible blow to its reputation. For institutions, have the events of last year put a sour taste in the mouth?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Justin Chapman, Northern Trust&rsquo;s head of digital assets and financial markets, summed up these concerns in an <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/04/crypto-has-lost-its-shine-for-institutional-investors-says-northern-trust-executive.html"><u>interview</u></a> with CNBC this week, saying that &ldquo;client interest has definitely gone off (a) cliff in terms of institutional interest in cryptocurrencies&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s definitely quiet now, since 2022, from the institutional side,&rdquo; he continued. &ldquo;Before that, we were seeing traditional fund managers looking to launch crypto funds, ETPs in Europe, which is the equivalent of ETFs in the U.S. &mdash; that&rsquo;s really gone quiet. Even the hedge funds, who are pretty active in the markets, have certainly reduced their exposure within that particular space.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The evidence for this goes beyond anecdotes. I&rsquo;ve put together a few reports on the immense capital flight out of crypto markets recently. One of my favourite charts to demonstrate the extent of this is by looking at the balance of stablecoins on exchanges. Since FTX collapsed in November, over half the total stablecoin balance has evaporated from exchanges. That translates to an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/"><u>outflow of $22 billion</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13612192">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Market depth on exchanges is similar: capital has just <em>fled</em>.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto messed up when the cameras were on</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto&rsquo;s surge during the pandemic undoubtedly put it on the main stage, with money flowing into the sector like never had before. Such were the scale of the scandals, most notably the FTX and LUNA collapses, there is concern that institutional money will never return at the same pace.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">When Tesla purchased Bitcoin and put it on its balance sheet, it felt like the start of a movement for the cryptocurrency industry as a whole. Everybody was talking about crypto, and funds from previously non-crypto domiciles like Wall Street were flowing like a tidal wave into the space.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But then came the crashes. Not only that, but the total lack of regulation in the space, and the absence of any sort of risk management, sent the whole industry into a very public and ignominious tailspin, with bankruptcy after bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Today, regulators are moving in harshly and the environment in the US is becoming increasingly hostile. February saw the Binance-branded BUSD stablecoin shut down. Disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried is awaiting trial. Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao has been charged by the CFTC for operating an &ldquo;intentionally opaque common enterprise&rdquo;, including accusations it &ldquo;failed to implement basic compliance procedures designed to prevent and detect terrorist financing and money laundering&rdquo;. Coinbase has been issued with a Wells notice by the SEC, warned of impending charges around securities violations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">How many blows can one industry take?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is somewhat separate, and its unique place as the first cryptocurrency, and aims of becoming a store-of-value, at least mean it has a goal. But for the rest of crypto, the point of everything is not as clear, nor are the future prospects.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto was given the perfect set-up: an explosive bull run stemming all the way back to 2009, fuelled by historically low (sometimes negative) interest rates and, to top it all off, a pandemic where everybody was stuck at home with stimulus cheques arriving while DIY investing took off.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Public companies moved in, countries declared it legal tender (El Salvador, Central African Republic), clients called fund managers asking how they could buy these mystical virtual coins.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A couple of years on, the reputation of the space is in tatters. Retail money may come and go, but the big institutional cash may be tougher to goad back in, and the lofty dreams of decentralised altcoins revolutionising how the world lives are certainly more quixotic. Most fund managers want nothing to do with crypto right now, nor should they.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even after the price rises this year, most coins are still trading far below their peaks. Even Bitcoin is still down 58% from its high. Not only that, but the liquidity for most coins is still low, volatility extremely elevated, legal trouble for crypto companies mounting, and the regulatory picture murkier than ever.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto prices may be rising. But the space is still barren compared to the hysteria of the bull market. And there is not much evidence suggesting institutional funds will pour back in anytime soon.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/">Has institutional money left crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/has-institutional-money-left-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price predictions: Tron, Optimism, Stacks (STX)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-tron-optimism-stacks-stx/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-tron-optimism-stacks-stx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-tron-optimism-stacks-stx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency prices were mixed, with key coins like Bitcoin moving sideways. Meme coins like Pepe and Floki Inu surged after their Binance listing. Cryptocurrencies were relatively mixed this week as Bitcoin remained stubbornly below $30,000 and Ethereum below $2,000. Meme coins like Pepe and Floki Inu soared after being listed in Binance while Sui jumped [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-tron-optimism-stacks-stx/">Crypto price predictions: Tron, Optimism, Stacks (STX)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency prices were mixed, with key coins like Bitcoin moving sideways.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Meme coins like Pepe and Floki Inu surged after their Binance listing.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies were relatively mixed this week as Bitcoin remained stubbornly below $30,000 and Ethereum below $2,000. Meme coins like Pepe and Floki Inu soared after being listed in Binance while Sui jumped and then dumped. This crypto price prediction will look at Tron, Optimism, and Stacks.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tron price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/tron/"><u>Tron</u></a> price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. It jumped to a high of $0.070, the highest point since February. On the four-hour chart, the coin has jumped above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. It also moved above the important resistance point on $0.069, the highest point in March.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, it seems like the coin will continue rising in the coming days as buyers target the next key resistance point at $0.073, the highest level on February 20. This price is about 3.50% above the current level. A drop below the key support at $0.7070 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/05/1683297407616-b194f4e9-2353-427e-a9af-3fb86e70e089.png" style="width: 683px;height: 332.393px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="683" height="332.393"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Tron</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM4NzQz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy TRX with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTM4NzQz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy TRX with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Optimism price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Optimism is one of the biggest layer-2 networks in the blockchain industry. It competes with other well-known blockchains like Arbitrum and Polygon. OP price has been in a steep sell-off this week as it dropped below the key support at $2.07, which was the lower side of the descending triangle pattern. It has also formed a head and shoulders pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Optimism also remains below the 25-day and 50-day exponential moving averages and the support at $2, the lowest point on March 27. Therefore, it seems like bears have the momentum, which could see it crash to the next support at $1.80. The stop-loss of this trade is at $2.20.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/05/1683297407447-1a3ea903-4d4d-4562-b1e5-d648759c1284.png" style="width: 673px;height: 327.527px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="673" height="327.527"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stacks price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/"><u>Stacks</u></a> is a leading blockchain project that seeks to create a Bitcoin layer for smart contracts. It solves an important challenge in that Bitcoin does not have smart contract capabilities. As such, developers can build applications that take advantage of Bitcoin to handle transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks surged earlier this year after the launch of Bitcoin Ordinals. It jumped to a high of $1.314 and has now erased most of those gains to trade at $0.72. The coin remains below the 50-day moving average and the key support point at $0.78.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin is slightly above the key support point at $0.6720. Therefore, the path of the least resistance for STX price is downwards, with the next key level to watch being at $0.60.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/05/1683297407593-cbfb7366-0a49-4446-8fe9-da980dc7282f.png" style="width: 639px;height: 310.98px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="639" height="310.98"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Stacks</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Okcoin</h3>

    <p>Okcoin is a globally licensed exchange with offices in San Francisco, Miami, Malta, Hong Kong, Singapore and Japan. Okcoin's mission is to help decentralize finance and level the economic playing field for everyone around the world. Serves 190+ countries with over 100K+ active traders and investors.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/okcoin-crypto?guid=MTM4NzQz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy STX with Okcoin today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=MTM4NzQz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy STX with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-tron-optimism-stacks-stx/">Crypto price predictions: Tron, Optimism, Stacks (STX)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-tron-optimism-stacks-stx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase stock jumps 15% on strong Q1 results: sell into the strength?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-jumps-on-q1-results/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase reports market-beating results for its fiscal Q1. Analysts are still keeping bearish on the Coinbase stock. Coinbase shares are now up roughly 70% year-to-date. Coinbase Global Inc are up nearly 15% on Friday after reporting its financial results for the first quarter that handily topped Street estimates. Coinbase stock up on narrowed loss Lost [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-jumps-on-q1-results/">Coinbase stock jumps 15% on strong Q1 results: sell into the strength?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Coinbase reports market-beating results for its fiscal Q1.</li>
<li>Analysts are still keeping bearish on the Coinbase stock.</li>
<li>Coinbase shares are now up roughly 70% year-to-date.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> are up nearly 15% on Friday after reporting its financial results for the first quarter that handily topped Street estimates.</p>
<h2>Coinbase stock up on narrowed loss</h2>
<ul>
<li>Lost $78.9 million versus the year-ago $429.7 million</li>
<li>Per-share loss also narrowed sharply from $1.98 to 34 cents</li>
<li>Revenue tanked 34% year-on-year to $772.5 million</li>
<li>Consensus was $1.45 a share loss on $655 million in revenue</li>
<li>Total operating expenses were down 24% versus last year</li>
</ul>
<p>The crypto company attributed strength in its quarterly performance partially to the surge this year in the price of bitcoin. Still, Wells Fargo analyst Jeff Cantwell remains bearish on the Coinbase stock due to the <a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/sec-reluctant-define-digital-assets-crypto-regulatory-uncertainty/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">regulatory uncertainty</a>.</p>
<p>His $43 price objective suggests more than a 20% downside from here.</p>
<h2>BofA is also dovish on Coinbase shares</h2>
<p>Remember that Coinbase Global Inc had received a &ldquo;<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/03/22/coinbase-stock-drops-after-sec-wells-notice-a-possible-prelude-to-enforcement-action/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wells notice</a>&rdquo; from the U.S. SEC in late March. It is also noteworthy that trading volume in the recently concluded quarter came in at $145 billion and missed the consensus estimate by $2.7 billion.</p>
<p>To that end, Bank of America analyst Jason Kupferberg also reiterated his &ldquo;underperform&rdquo; rating on the Coinbase stock today and said:</p>
<blockquote><p>We maintain our cautious view on Coinbase shares as we continue to think retail crypto volumes will remain weak and regulatory overhang will linger for some time.</p></blockquote>
<p>In its current quarter, Coinbase Global Inc expects its subscription and services revenue to sequentially decline to around $300 million, as per its <a href="https://s27.q4cdn.com/397450999/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter-Q1-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">letter to shareholders.</a></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-stock-jumps-on-q1-results/">Coinbase stock jumps 15% on strong Q1 results: sell into the strength?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here is why Floki Inu’s price surged by over 50% today</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/here-is-why-floki-inus-price-surged-by-over-50-today/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/here-is-why-floki-inus-price-surged-by-over-50-today/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/here-is-why-floki-inus-price-surged-by-over-50-today/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways FLOKI is the best performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. The token has added more than 50% to its value today and could rally higher in the near term. Binance is set to list Floki Inu in its Innovation Zone while the token is now live on Bitfinex Floki [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/here-is-why-floki-inus-price-surged-by-over-50-today/">Here is why Floki Inu’s price surged by over 50% today</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">FLOKI is the best performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token has added more than 50% to its value today and could rally higher in the near term.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance is set to list Floki Inu in its Innovation Zone while the token is now live on Bitfinex</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Floki Inu price rally by more than 50% today</h2>
<p dir="ltr">FLOKI, the native token of the Floki Inu ecosystem, has been the best performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/floki/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Floki Inu</u></a> stands at $0.00005282, up by 56% over the past few hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The rally comes thanks to two massive listings of the Floki Inu token. Earlier today, Bitfinex, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges in the world, listed FLOKI on its trading platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We&rsquo;re live now for trading &ndash; <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FLOKI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FLOKI</a> can now be traded with USD and Tether <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDt&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$USDt</a>!</p>
<p>You&rsquo;ll also enjoy our trading fee promotion:<br>&#9989; ZERO fees for market makers<br>&#9989; 4 bps for market takers</p>
<p>Start trading on Bitfinex:<a href="https://t.co/RXJ1Kg0JQ4">https://t.co/RXJ1Kg0JQ4</a> <a href="https://t.co/2xHWKTmBgQ">pic.twitter.com/2xHWKTmBgQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bitfinex (@bitfinex) <a href="https://twitter.com/bitfinex/status/1654444168742072322?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> means that FLOKI can be traded against USDT on the Bitfinex crypto exchange.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance lists FLOKI in its innovation zone</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Following the announcement by Bitfinex, Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, also announced earlier today that it would be listing Floki Inu and PEPE coins in the Binance Innovation Zone.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> will list <a href="https://twitter.com/pepecoineth?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@pepecoineth</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PEPE</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RealFlokiInu</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24FLOKI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$FLOKI</a> in the innovation zone.</p>
<p>&#10145;&#65039; <a href="https://t.co/yxcINj0whc">https://t.co/yxcINj0whc</a> <a href="https://t.co/o4UTvWZkHj">pic.twitter.com/o4UTvWZkHj</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1654448067255361537?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Binance Innovation Zone was introduced to users of the cryptocurrency exchange a safe place to trade new and innovative projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">These latest developments were behind FLOKI rallying by more than 50% over the last 24 hours. The positive performance comes despite the broader crypto market currently stagnating.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is down by less than 1% in the last 24 hours and continues to trade above the $29k level. Ether, the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, is up by less than 1% so far today and is trading just above $1,900.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the total cryptocurrency market cap stands at $1.2 trillion.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/here-is-why-floki-inus-price-surged-by-over-50-today/">Here is why Floki Inu’s price surged by over 50% today</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/here-is-why-floki-inus-price-surged-by-over-50-today/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kenya eyes 3% tax on cryptocurrency transfers</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-eyes-3-tax-on-cryptocurrency-transfers/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-eyes-3-tax-on-cryptocurrency-transfers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 11:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Africa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-eyes-3-tax-on-cryptocurrency-transfers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kenya&#8217;s Treasury Secretary outlined the tax proposals in a document sent to parliament on 4 May, 2023. The 3% crypto tax will target cryptocurrencies and NFT transfers on exchanges and by individuals. Kenya is one of the countries with the fastest growing adoption of cryptocurrencies in the world. Kenya is seeking a 3% tax on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-eyes-3-tax-on-cryptocurrency-transfers/">Kenya eyes 3% tax on cryptocurrency transfers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Kenya&rsquo;s Treasury Secretary outlined the tax proposals in a document sent to parliament on 4 May, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The 3% crypto tax will target cryptocurrencies and NFT transfers on exchanges and by individuals.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Kenya is one of the countries with the fastest growing adoption of cryptocurrencies in the world.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Kenya is seeking a 3% tax on the transfer of digital assets, budget proposals from the Treasury ministry outline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tax proposals were part of the Finance Bill 2023 that Njuguna Ndung&rsquo;u, Cabinet Secretary for National Treasury and Economic Planning, sent to the National Assembly on Thursday, 4 May 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Treasury CS is expected to present the budget statement to Parliament on 8 June, and could see the East African nation have the new taxation measures in place for the 2023/2024 budget year, the <a href="http://www.parliament.go.ke/sites/default/files/2023-05/THE%20FINANCE%20BILL%20%2C%202023_compressed.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>details</u></a> of the proposal showed.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Authorities eye tax for crypto and NFTs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Apart from <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrencies</a>, the tax proposals also target non-fungible token (NFT) transfers. These will relate to transactions made by exchanges as well as individuals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Digital assets are classified as property in Kenya, and any gains from the sale, exchange, or disposal of such assets would be subject to capital gains tax. Other than crypto, Kenya also targets monetized online content, with the sector set to be subject to a 15% tax.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Around 8.5% of Kenya&rsquo;s adult population own or hold cryptocurrencies. While countries in Africa such as Nigeria and South Africa have more people owning crypto, Kenya places higher in terms of percentage of the population.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recent statistics on global crypto ownership and usage by the UN <a href="https://unctad.org/news/unctad-spells-out-actions-curb-cryptocurrencies-developing-countries" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ranked</u></a> Kenya fifth worldwide and fourth among emerging economies &ndash; behind Ukraine, Russia and Venezuela.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the latest <a href="https://triple-a.io/crypto-ownership-data/#" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ownership figures</u></a> from Singapore-based crypto research company Triple A, over 2.7 million Kenyans own digital assets. Globally, cryptocurrency ownership has risen to an average of 4.2%, with numbers jumping from 320 million in early 2022 to over 420 million in May 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kenya&rsquo;s plans for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/crypto-tax/">crypto taxation</a> rules come as the trend around the world sees increased regulatory scrutiny of cryptocurrencies. The UK, EU and other jurisdictions are looking to offer clear regulatory guidelines for the industry, particularly around overall protection of investors amid likely risks from unregulated crypto exchanges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-eyes-3-tax-on-cryptocurrency-transfers/">Kenya eyes 3% tax on cryptocurrency transfers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kenya-eyes-3-tax-on-cryptocurrency-transfers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 reasons to invest in Metacade after the 275% rally</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-to-invest-in-metacade-after-the-275-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-to-invest-in-metacade-after-the-275-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-to-invest-in-metacade-after-the-275-rally/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metacade price has jumped by 275% from its all-time low. The token will benefit from a Fed pivot as US banks collapse. Technicals are supportive of the cryptocurrency. Metacade (MCADE) price has done well since going public in April this year. In all, data compiled by&#160;Uniswap shows that the token has jumped by more than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-to-invest-in-metacade-after-the-275-rally/">3 reasons to invest in Metacade after the 275% rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Metacade price has jumped by 275% from its all-time low.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token will benefit from a Fed pivot as US banks collapse.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Technicals are supportive of the cryptocurrency.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/metacade/"><u>Metacade</u></a> (MCADE) price has done well since going public in April this year. In all, data compiled by&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/uniswap/"><u>Uniswap</u></a> shows that the token has jumped by more than 275% from its all-time low, making it one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the world. Here are three reasons why Metacade price will likely continue soaring in the near term.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Macro events favor cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The first main reason to invest in Metacade is that macro events seem to favor cryptocurrencies and other assets. On Wednesday, the Federal Reserve decided to hike interest rates by 0.25%, bringing them to about 5.25%. Analysts believe that the Fed has now ended its hiking cycle since there are signs that the American economy is slowing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, GDP data published last week showed that the economy slowed down in A1. Further data showed that the manufacturing sector continued contracting in April this year. Retail sales have slowed as inflation remains stubbornly high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, the banking sector is at its biggest risk in years. On Monday, the FDIC seized First Republic Bank and sold it to JP Morgan, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-tops-0-027-as-analysts-turn-bullish-on-first-republic-sage/"><u>here</u></a>. Other banks are at a significant risk. For example, PacWest shares tumbled by over 50% on Thursday while Comerica and Western Alliance fell by double-digits.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, it is hard to fathom the Fed continuing hiking rates in a period when banks are collapsing. As such, there is a likelihood that Metacade will and other altcoins will do well because of Bitcoin&rsquo;s role as a safe haven. &nbsp;In fact, Bitcoin and other major tokens have outperformed stocks this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade important news</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The other main reason to invest in&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/en"><u>Metacade</u></a> is that there are some important news that could push the token higher. First, the number of MCADE holders has continued rising in the past few weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data compiled by Etherscan shows that the&nbsp;<a href="https://etherscan.io/token/0xed328e9c1179a30ddc1e7595e036aed8760c22af"><u>number</u></a> has jumped to 9,239, which is much higher than where it was last month. This is a sign that the token is gaining traction and that the number will get to 10k soon. The number of MCADE transfers has jumped to over 27,289.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, according to the Metacade&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the developers are working to get the token listed in more centralized exchanges. Already, the token has been listed in platforms like MEXC and BitMart. Other potential exchanges where the developers plan to list it are Binance and OKX. In most cases, cryptocurrencies tend to do well after a major exchange listing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, the developers are working on the Metacade game, which is expected to be launched in the next few months. We expect that the game will do well, which will help the token gain traction in the next few months. Historically, crypto tokens tend to do well ahead of a major event.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade technicals are supportive</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/05/1683261734716-36a2d1f5-1cdc-4137-bd90-62456824eded.png" style="width: 691px;height: 336.287px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="691" height="336.287"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The other main reason to invest in MCADE is that technicals are supportive. On the four-hour chart, we see that the Metacade price has been in a bullish trend in the past few weeks. As it rose, the token moved above the important resistance point at $0.034, the highest point on April 20th. It has now retested that price in what is known as a break and retest pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is being supported by the 50-period moving average. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the token will bounce back as buyers target the all-time high of $0.045. A break above that level will see it jump to the next psychological level at $0.05.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-to-invest-in-metacade-after-the-275-rally/">3 reasons to invest in Metacade after the 275% rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/3-reasons-to-invest-in-metacade-after-the-275-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should you buy Block stock on a boost to bitcoin revenue in Q1?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-block-stock-bitcoin-revenue-q1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 23:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stock markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Block didn&#8217;t see an impairment loss on its bitcoin holdings in Q1. Analysts at KeyBanc continue to see upside in its shares to $85. Block stock is currently down about 5.0% versus the start of 2023. Block Inc says it did not see an impairment loss related to its bitcoin hoard in the first financial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-block-stock-bitcoin-revenue-q1/">Should you buy Block stock on a boost to bitcoin revenue in Q1?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Block didn&rsquo;t see an impairment loss on its bitcoin holdings in Q1.</li>
<li>Analysts at KeyBanc continue to see upside in its shares to $85.</li>
<li>Block stock is currently down about 5.0% versus the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Block Inc says it did not see an impairment loss related to its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> hoard in the first financial quarter. Shares are trading up in extended hours.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin price recovery helped</h2>
<p>The surge in BTC this year pushed the fintech company&rsquo;s bitcoin revenue in Q1 to $2.16 billion &ndash; up 18% sequentially and a whopping 25% versus the same quarter last year.</p>
<p>Gross profit from bitcoin holdings also increased 43% versus the previous quarter, as per its <a href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter_Block_1Q23.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">letter to shareholders</a>. Block generated $770 million of total gross profit in its recently concluded quarter &ndash; up 16% on a year-over-year basis.</p>
<p>The fair value of its position in bitcoin was $229 million as of March 31<sup>st</sup> versus the original purchase price of $220 million.</p>
<p>Year-to-date, Block stock is down about 5.0% at writing.</p>
<h2>Should you buy Block stock now?</h2>
<p>Block ended the quarter with 20 million monthly active users on &ldquo;Cash Card&rdquo; &ndash; up 34%. Earlier this week, K33 analyst Vetle Lunde <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/amp/story/bitcoin-could-soon-reach-45-000-if-this-pattern-repeats-analyst-says-has-the-crypto-started-a-new-bull-market-8dc1701a?mod=mw_quote_news" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noted</a> the similarity in how bitcoin is performing this year and how it recovered after the bear market of 2018-2019.</p>
<p>If it continued on the same trajectory, he added, bitcoin could be worth as much as $45,000 in the coming weeks which could be a significant benefit to Block Inc both in terms of its financial performance as well as the share price.</p>
<p>Those interested in buying Block stock today should also know that analysts at KeyBanc continue to see upside in it to $85 &ndash; up roughly 40% from here.</p>
<p>Other notable bulls of the financial technology company include <a href="https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/stock-market-news-today-03-24-2023/card/cathie-wood-s-ark-buys-dip-in-block-coinbase-WCR1JILbLudmIm2K6p5G" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cathie Wood</a> &ndash; the Founder and Chief Executive of Ark Invest.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-block-stock-bitcoin-revenue-q1/">Should you buy Block stock on a boost to bitcoin revenue in Q1?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Stacks price go back up? Here’s the short-term outlook for STX</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stacks price has declined 4% in the past 24 hours and is -15% this past 30 days. STX currently trades near $0.78, and has a key supply zone near the psychological $1.00 level. The price of STX rose sharply in February and March as the Ordinals hype hit the market. The price of Stacks (STX) [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/">Will Stacks price go back up? Here’s the short-term outlook for STX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Stacks price has declined 4% in the past 24 hours and is -15% this past 30 days.</p>
</div>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">STX currently trades near $0.78, and has a key supply zone near the psychological $1.00 level.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of STX rose sharply in February and March as the Ordinals hype hit the market.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/">Stacks (STX)</a> made another higher low move on Wednesday, trading to highs of $0.82 after surging double digits alongside Bitcoin (BTC). The upside followed the crypto market&rsquo;s upward reaction to the US Federal Reserve&rsquo;s interest rate hike.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But as the FOMC tide cools, STX is down 4% in the past 24 hours, cutting weekly gains to just 5% and wiping out gains from key price bursts in April.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will Stacks go back up after the recent dump?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks (STX) is a digital asset that has shown considerable fluctuations in price in the past few weeks. As CoinJournal highlighted in<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-price-relentless-bull-run-gains-steam-is-it-still-a-buy/">&nbsp;<u>this article</u></a>, the main driver of Stacks price in February was the strong interest in Ordinals, a platform for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> inscriptions (crypto assets similar to NFTs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Stacks, which brings the power of smart contracts to Bitcoin, also surged in March as<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stacks-stx-is-a-whale-aggressively-loading-up/">&nbsp;<u>whales loaded up on the native STX</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As seen on the weekly chart below, STX/USD has been constrained between robust support at $0.64 and new resistance near $1.33 since 20 February. The coin is up 5% this week but is in the red on the monthly chart after today&rsquo;s declines helped erase gains made earlier in the year. STXUSD is down nearly 15% over the past 30 days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Incidentally, STX rose 122% in one week in February and another 51% over seven days in mid-March. So the question is: will Stacks go back up after retreating from year-to-date highs above $1.32?&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The surge in Bitcoin ordinals, which on-chain data <a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shows</a> reached over 3.5 million this week, suggests interest in the inscriptions is still high. The activity on the Ordinals Protocol and other layer 2s on the Bitcoin blockchain and the potential uptick in BTC price are likely to be major catalysts of upside momentum for the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/altcoin/">altcoin</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Below is the outlook for Stacks price from a technical perspective.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stacks price: short term outlook for STX</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For a short-term technical outlook for STX, we can look at its weekly chart focusing on the Relative Strength Index (RSI), Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD), and Fibonacci retracement levels.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/04/1683223211828-21871ca3-eb5d-4127-8513-f6230a61b33e.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="259"><span class="fr-inner">Chart showing the price movement of Stacks (STX) with key technical indicators. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/fnsqMrDa/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></span></span>As shown above, the RSI indicator for STX on is currently at 57. This suggests that STX is largely neutral, indicating its neither oversold nor overbought.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the MACD indicator is suggesting a potential bearish crossover. We can see the MACD line is above the signal line but could cross below to give the advantage to the bears.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the main barrier to the upside is likely to be at the Fibonacci retracement level at 23.6% that marks the retracement of the last swing from the highs of $3.37 to lows of $0.20. That level is currently around $0.95. Stacks also highlight the 50% and 61.8% retracement levels as main resistance areas.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In case the Stacks (STX) price continues its downward trend, the first support level could be at a long-term horizontal line near $0.45. The 50-week moving average line is currently leveling up around this area, while the $0.20 demand reload line provides a key buffer zone.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/will-stacks-price-go-back-up-heres-the-short-term-outlook-for-stx/">Will Stacks price go back up? Here’s the short-term outlook for STX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
