<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:13:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chancer presale nets more investors with the addition of ETH and USDT buying options</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer is revolutionizing the betting industry by leveraging the power of blockchain technology. Chancer presale now allows investors to use ETH, USDT, BUSD, and BNB. Currently, CHANCER is selling for $0.01. Stage one of the Chancer presale has hit $823,011 days after it added Ethereum (ETH) and Tether (USDT) buying options to complement the current [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/">Chancer presale nets more investors with the addition of ETH and USDT buying options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Chancer is revolutionizing the betting industry by leveraging the power of blockchain technology.</li>
<li>Chancer presale now allows investors to use ETH, USDT, BUSD, and BNB.</li>
<li>Currently, CHANCER is selling for $0.01.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stage one of the Chancer presale has hit $823,011 days after it added <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a> buying options to complement the current BNB and BUSD options. The addition of the two crypto options makes the project appeal to millions more blockchain aficionados and is likely to accelerate their presale.</p>
<p>In just four weeks, Chancer, which was initially hailed as one of the most interesting cryptocurrency ventures of 2023, has raised nearly $1 million. Chancer is a new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> initiative that is upending the online gambling industry.</p>
<h2>Opening the door for Ethereum and Tether ecosystem</h2>
<p>Ethereum is valued at an astounding $240 billion, making it the second-largest coin in the world by market valuation after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>. The addition of ETH was a very wise business move on the part of the project team given that there are over 238 million ETH holders worldwide.</p>
<p>ETH token holders will now have the opportunity of purchasing the new CHANCER token</p>
<p>Most blockchain presales use USDT and ETH for their presales and Chancer has just joined the list.</p>
<h2>Why investors are flocking to the new betting platform</h2>
<p>Chancer is developing the world&rsquo;s first decentralized social predictive markets platform. The new betting platform will allow Chancer token holders to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets based on their interests, expertise and social opportunities. Interested parties can purchase the CHANCER tokens <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>
<p>By &ldquo;removing the house&rdquo; and capturing a portion of the market, the project seeks to disrupt the worldwide gaming and betting industry while attracting attention by upending the established bookmaking and betting business model.</p>
<p>Chancer is attracting thousands of investors from both the cryptocurrency and betting sectors thanks to its innovative use of Google&rsquo;s WebRTC technology, which enables users to create their own odds and bets and then broadcast these to a global audience who can participate in live bets. Many anticipate that the project holds great potential given its rapid progress through its early stages including the currently rapidly selling presale.</p>
<p>It is obvious why Chancer is attracting thousands of investors from the cryptocurrency and betting sectors with its innovative approach to online betting that allows users to create their own odds and their own bets and then broadcast these to a global audience who can participate in live bets. Many anticipate that this token will sell out quickly at its current price of $0.01 and given how quickly the project is moving through its early stage.</p>
<p>Adam and Paul Kelbie, the company&rsquo;s founders, are actively interacting with their audience as well as a number of prominent influencers in the blockchain, gambling, sports, and online gaming areas. They are supported by a devoted group of &lsquo;Chancers&rsquo; who are spreading the word about their original concept. This might quickly take on the role of P2P social betting.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/">Chancer presale nets more investors with the addition of ETH and USDT buying options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin since the Merge?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Ever since the Merge went live in September, Ether has underperformed Bitcoin significantly&#160; This is despite the supply of Ethereum falling post-Merge More Ether is also being staked since the Shapella upgrade in April&#160; Demand has fallen with regard to Bitcoin, however, overriding the lower supply Regulatory crackdown and greater institutional interest in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/">Why is Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin since the Merge?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ever since the Merge went live in September, Ether has underperformed Bitcoin significantly&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">This is despite the supply of Ethereum falling post-Merge</li>
<li dir="ltr">More Ether is also being staked since the Shapella upgrade in April&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Demand has fallen with regard to Bitcoin, however, overriding the lower supply</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory crackdown and greater institutional interest in Bitcoin appears to be driving the divergence, writes our Head of Research</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the more interesting trends to follow within crypto is that of the ETH / BTC chart. In other words, how the world&rsquo;s two largest cryptocurrencies move in relation to one another. Now ten months on from the Ethereum Merge, it feels like a good time to re-analyse the relationship.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Merge completely transformed Ethereum, switching the network to a proof-of-stake mechanism rather than the proof-of-work mechanism it was on previously. On the other hand, Bitcoin remains (and always will be) a proof-of-work blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This means that the fundamentals underlying the Ethereum network have flipped. Perhaps this is most noticeable when plotting the total circulating supply of ETH. The Merge going live in September 2022 sticks out like a sore thumb, with the supply (slightly) contracting from that date.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14475145">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Zooming in on the post-Merge period in the next chart shows the contraction. The supply has reduced at an average rate of 0.15% per month. Prior to the Merge, the supply grew by 0.41% per month. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14475270">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, the supply of liquid Ether has contracted even further than the above charts show. Looking at the total value of staked Ether, the pattern was relatively steady from when the staking contract opened in November 2020. This trend more or less continued as the Merge went live in September 2022. However, as seen on the next chart, the amount of staked Ether spiked notably in April of this year, as the Shapella upgrade went live.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689688360391-8e5b27c9-08a2-4c45-87a3-0c4a800817f3.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="377"></p>
<p dir="ltr">This Shapella upgrade, also known as Shanghai, allowed staked Ether to finally be sold, with some of the early stakers having locked up their tokens since Q4 of 2020. Despite concern that this would lead to a vast amount of Ether flooding the market and denting the price, the opposite has happened. With the indefinite lock-up restriction no longer a factor, the Ether staked has spiked noticeably, with the trend far steeper in the three months since.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But how has this structural break on the supply side affected Ether&rsquo;s performance against Bitcoin? Less supply equals a higher price, right? Well, no actually. Almost on a dime from when the Merge went live, ETH has fallen relative to Bitcoin, as I have plotted on the below chart (the black line denotes the Merge in September).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14475531">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The reason, of course, is that price is governed by supply and demand, rather than just supply. And while supply has contracted, the demand side of the equation has not held up &ndash; at least relative to Bitcoin.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ether underperforms Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Two months after the Merge, FTX collapsed, sending the entire crypto sector for a spin. As is customary in times of price decline, Bitcoin fell less than the rest of the market. Thus, Ether falling against Bitcoin in the aftermath of the crash is not surprising.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, thus far in 2023, the crypto market has been on fire, with token prices accelerating across the board as the macro climate has softened amid falling inflation. The Nasdaq jumped 32% in the first six months of the year, its best half-year return since 1983. And yet, despite the crypto market riding this wave, Ether fell further still against Bitcoin, something which seemingly bucks the trend.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The reason is most likely regulation. The great regulatory crackdown in the US has been brutal on crypto, but Bitcoin has not been as squarely in the crosshairs as a lot of the market. This has led to Bitcoin dominance rising to its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/"><u>highest level in two years</u></a>, now comprising over 50% of the entire cryptocurrency market cap. It opened the year at 42% (it was also roughly at this level at the time of the Ethereum Merge in September).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689688360114-9b756a88-6af6-47f6-bece-045bc86a408f.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="256"></p>
<p dir="ltr">This comes amid sentiment that Bitcoin could be carving out its own niche in the space. This is the view that many in the space have long held (and a Bitcoin maximalist&rsquo;s sworn mantra), but the difference now is that the law appears to be coming around to the same point of view. I&rsquo;ll let Coinbase CEO Brian Armstong put it more succinctly than I:&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We go back to 2021, we wanted to become a public company, we described everything about our business, the assets that we list on our platform, how we do staking. The SEC at that point allowed us to become a public company&rdquo;.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;A totally different tone started to happen (about a year ago),&rdquo;</em> Armstrong continued. <em>&ldquo;We kind of got this information from the SEC that, well actually everything other than Bitcoin is a security.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Although Ether was not present on the list of tokens announced by the SEC that comprised securities, a list which included some other popular cryptos such as MATIC, SOL and ATOM, it has not been immune. Viewed more or less in a grey area, Ether nonetheless has suffered as the regulatory blows kept coming. While last week&rsquo;s XRP ruling is positive for the space, and there will be many more twists and turns to come, it still feels like Bitcoin has separated itself from the crowd.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further reinforcing this view is the slew of Bitcoin ETFs submitted for approval from some of the world&rsquo;s biggest asset managers, including Blackrock. Denied repeatedly to date, the presence of big names backing Bitcoin amid this suffocating US legal environment is another boon for the orange coin. And while one could (rightly) hypothesise that a Bitcoin ETF would make an Ether ETF more likely, there is no denying that Bitcoin has pulled further ahead in the race.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This has led to a situation in 2023 where Bitcoin has outperformed Ether, which seems surprising when the latter has tended to outperform the former during prior periods of price expansion. But it is always important to remember how brief the trading history for both Ether and Bitcoin is. Ether was only launched in 2015, and it was another couple of years before it traded with any genuine liquidity. So, leaning on past performance must always be done with a pinch of salt. Additionally, the crypto market has <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-bitcoin-has-never-seen-a-bear-market-before-this-time-its-different/"><u>never experienced</u></a> a macro environment like this.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, any hopes that the Merge would accelerate Ether into the stratosphere perhaps overlooked how much of the upgrade was priced in. This was in the works for a long time, repeatedly delayed before it finally came and went.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">All in all, this has led to Ether lagging Bitcoin, with the latter increasing its dominance over not only Ether, but the crypto market as a whole. Things are changing quickly in crypto, and Bitcoin has been weathering the turbulent waters better than altcoins in recent months, primarily due to the legal climate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then again, the way prices have been going, Ether investors can&rsquo;t be too unhappy &ndash; despite Ether&rsquo;s second-place medal, it is still up 57% thus far this year. It could be worse, even if they did back the wrong horse.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/">Why is Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin since the Merge?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brian Armstrong to meet House Democrats about crypto legislation</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Coinbase CEO will meet with House Democrats to discuss crypto regulation. Armstrong wants clearer rules on crypto from Washington. Coinbase CEO wants clearer crypto regulation in the US Coinbase Inc. Chief Executive Officer Brian Armstrong is set to meet with House Democrats behind closed doors Wednesday morning. This is according to a&#160;Bloomberg report [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/">Brian Armstrong to meet House Democrats about crypto legislation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase CEO will meet with House Democrats to discuss crypto regulation.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Armstrong wants clearer rules on crypto from Washington.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coinbase CEO wants clearer crypto regulation in the US</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase Inc. Chief Executive Officer Brian Armstrong is set to meet with House Democrats behind closed doors Wednesday morning. This is according to a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-17/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-set-to-meet-with-house-democrats?sref=3REHEaVI" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bloomberg report</u></a> on Monday, citing sources familiar with the plans.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the report, Armstrong will speak privately with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition about cryptocurrency legislation and related issues, including tax, national security, privacy and climate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes as Coinbase faces a lawsuit by the Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recently, lawmakers from the House and Senate have introduced bills that would bring clarity to the cryptocurrency industry in the United States. However, the divided nature of Congress makes it unclear whether the bills would be adopted soon.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Coinbase continues to battle SEC in court</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On June 6, the US&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>SEC charged Coinbase</u></a> with violating federal securities law, adding that the cryptocurrency exchange was operating as an unlicenced broker, national securities exchange and clearing agency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange responded, saying that the SEC&rsquo;s action violates due process and constitutes an abuse of discretion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On June 29th,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/coinbase-files-to-have-the-lawsuit-by-the-sec-dismissed-for-lack-of-merits/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Coinbase submitted a motion</u></a> to the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York, asking that the SEC complaint charges be dismissed for lack of merit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Coinbase&rsquo;s stock price has grown by nearly 200% since the start of the year, thanks to Bitcoin&rsquo;s price rallying by nearly 50% during that period. At the start of the year, COIN was trading at $40 per share but currently stands at $105.55.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/">Brian Armstrong to meet House Democrats about crypto legislation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/brian-armstrong-to-meet-house-democrats-about-crypto-legislation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink price prediction: LINK just formed a double top pattern</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink announced a new plan to expand in the traditional finance industry. It unveiled the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP). The coin has formed a double-top pattern on the 4H chart. Chainlink price rose to a high of $7.32, the highest level since April 26th. At its peak on Tuesday, the LINK token was up by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/">Chainlink price prediction: LINK just formed a double top pattern</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink announced a new plan to expand in the traditional finance industry.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It unveiled the Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP).</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The coin has formed a double-top pattern on the 4H chart.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/chainlink"><u>Chainlink</u></a> price rose to a high of $7.32, the highest level since April 26th. At its peak on Tuesday, the LINK token was up by more than 53% from the lowest level in June. It has outperformed other coins like Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink expands its offerings</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink is the biggest oracle network in the blockchain industry. An oracle is a network that links off-chain data to the on-chain. It is widely used to provide price feeds in decentralized and centralized exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chainlink has been growing its ecosystem in the past few years. In June, the developers announced that they had begun testing connecting banks to the blockchain by partnering with Swift.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a statement on Tuesday, the company unveiled Chainlink&rsquo;s Cross-chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP). CCIP is designed to connect traditional financial institutions to the blockchain. The initial blockchains will be&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche"><u>Avalanche</u></a>, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon. Early adopters in this testing were Synthetix and Aave.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, LINK price jumped as investors hope that the network will see more action in the coming months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data compiled by DeFi Llama shows that the network has a total value secured (TVS) of over&nbsp;<a href="https://defillama.com/oracles"><u>$21.85 billion</u></a>. This makes it the biggest oracle provider in the world. The other big oracles are Chronicle, WINKLink, Pyth, TWAP, and RedStone.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chainlink price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689681924119-12a04c41-8cdb-4cce-84c6-16d3ffdec0ce.jpg" style="width: 642px;height: 291.503px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="642" height="291.503"></p>
<p dir="ltr">LINK price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. On the 4H chart, the coin has moved above the 25-period and 50-period moving averages. It has also formed an ascending channel shown in black. The price is a few points below the upper side of the channel.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most importantly, Chainlink has formed a double-top pattern at $7.30. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually a bearish sign. The neckline of this pattern is at $6.50. Therefore, despite the new product launch, there is a likelihood that LINK price will have a bearish breakout.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $6.50, which is ~6.50% below the current level. On the flip side, a move above the double-top level of $7.30 will invalidate the bearish view.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Chainlink</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ2NjE1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ2NjE1&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy LINK with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/">Chainlink price prediction: LINK just formed a double top pattern</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chainlink-price-prediction-link-just-formed-a-double-top-pattern/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CROWN Token Project launches limited-edition NFTs on ADOT marketplace</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The NFT collection will unlock opportunities for lovers of animated films, starting with Legend of Two Heroes. CROWN Token&#8217;s NFTs will be available on the platform&#8217;s ADOT NFT marketplace. The Legend of the Two Heroes NFT series features 590 NFT mints from 39 NFTs. CROWN Token Project, a Web3 platform that bridges the traditional IPs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/">CROWN Token Project launches limited-edition NFTs on ADOT marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The NFT collection will unlock opportunities for lovers of animated films, starting with <em>Legend of Two Heroes</em>.</li>
<li dir="ltr">CROWN Token&rsquo;s NFTs will be available on the platform&rsquo;s ADOT NFT marketplace.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Legend of the Two Heroes NFT series features 590 NFT mints from 39 NFTs.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://crowntoken.io/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>CROWN Token Project</u></a>, a Web3 platform that bridges the traditional IPs market with blockchain, has launched its first non-fungible token (NFT) collection.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/nfts/">NFTs</a> debut is on<a href="https://www.adotmarketplace.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>ADOT</u></a>, the CROWN Token&rsquo;s own NFT marketplace, and will roll out with a limited-edition of the animated film <em>Legend of the Two Heroes</em>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a press release shared with CoinJournal on Tuesday, July 18, the NFT series will showcase characters from the $15 million budget film from Hong Kong director Hernan Yau and renowned screenwriter Robert Lence.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Toy Story, Beauty and the Beast and Shrek are some of the feature masterpieces to incorporate Lence&rsquo;s scripts.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">590 mints across 39 NFTs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While <em>Legend of the Two Heroes</em> is in post-production and is scheduled for global release early next year, CROWN Token says its NFT series on the feature film will be open for minting beginning July 19, 2023. The timing of the mint will see NFT holders included in the film&rsquo;s creation, right from ideation to release on the big screen.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Pan Lorattawut, CEO of VUCA Digital which manages the CROWN Token Project, said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It&rsquo;s exciting to see this project with our ADOT marketplace come to life. We want NFT holders to be involved in the animated action film&rsquo;s creation in every possible way. This is one of the ways we not only reward our ecosystem, but continue to expand the benefits of IPs</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The limited NFT series will allow for 590 mints spread across 39 NFTs, with each NFT having 15 mints. Meanwhile, there will also be 5 rare NFTs each of which will have only 1 mint. Collectors can only buy the rare NFTs with CROWN Token, the platform said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The top three main characters in the film to feature in the NFTs will later be added to an upcoming MMO role-playing game.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689679663574-fadd2df1-b4b9-4b7b-879f-6dab0543f5eb.jpg" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="598"><span class="fr-inner">A character from Legend of the Two Heroes. Source: CROWN Token Project</span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">Although the global NFTs market size shrank alongside the broader crypto industry during the crypto winter, projections are that the market size will expand at a CAGR of 27.6% to $342 billion by 2032.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">According to a<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/en/news-release/2023/05/18/2671911/0/en/NFT-Market-size-to-Cross-USD-342-54-Billion-By-2032-With-an-27-60-CAGR-by-2032-Report-by-Market-Research-Future-MRFR.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>report</u></a> by Market Research Future (MRFR), key drivers of this growth will include cryptocurrency use and rising global demand for digital art.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">CROWN Token Project expects its ADOT Marketplace to experience growth in coming years, with the utility of its token expanding as a result. CROWN Token is a crypto project by VUCA Digital, a blockchain consulting firm affiliated to IP management firm T&amp;B Media Global.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crown-token-project-launches-limited-edition-nfts-on-adot-marketplace/">CROWN Token Project launches limited-edition NFTs on ADOT marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget added 9,033 new elite traders in Q2</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-q2-transparency-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=146566</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitget says it made a bunch of notable achievements in the second quarter of this year &#8211; a few of which it underscored in a Transparency Report on Tuesday. Bitget continued to increase market share in Q2 According to the quarterly update, its market share climbed further in the three-month period to 8.7%. That translates [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-q2-transparency-report/">Bitget added 9,033 new elite traders in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitget says it made a bunch of notable achievements in the second quarter of this year &ndash; a few of which it underscored in a <a href="https://www.bitget.com/blog/articles/bitget-sees-second-highest-increase-in-market-shares" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Transparency Report</a> on Tuesday.</p>
<h2>Bitget continued to increase market share in Q2</h2>
<p>According to the quarterly update, its market share climbed further in the three-month period to 8.7%.</p>
<p>That translates to a 1.81% increase &ndash; second highest among the top five centralised exchanges. Spot trading exceeded $60 billion in terms of volume while futures trading surpassed $600 billion.</p>
<p>Bitget is the only CEX that saw an increase in futures trading volume this year following the FTX fiasco, as per Nansen &ndash; a blockchain analytics platform.</p>
<p>These disclosures arrive just days after the Seychelles-based company launched &ldquo;Crypto Loans&rdquo; to debut in lending (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-launches-crypto-loans/">find out more</a>).</p>
<h2>Copy trading helped add new elite traders</h2>
<p>Bitget increased its followers by more than 85,000 in the second quarter. Copy trading, it added, helped grow the number of elite traders on the platform by 9,033 as well.</p>
<p>&ldquo;BGB&rdquo; &ndash; its native token outperformed peers unlocking a whopping 23% as trading volume hit $1.3 million &ndash; an 80% increase. The Transparency Report also reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>Demand for BGB has been on the rise, with the number of BGB holders rising by 130% to 305,653 in three months.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitget remained committed to expansion in the second quarter and successfully registered as a VASP in <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/in/news-releases/bitget-registers-as-virtual-asset-service-provider-in-poland-301831988.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Poland</a> and <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-secures-regulatory-license-in-poland-reserve-funds-up-80m-in-q1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lithuania</a>. It also entered <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/">Turkey</a> in Q2 with a new website.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-q2-transparency-report/">Bitget added 9,033 new elite traders in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals’ stage two presale surpasses 50%: should you get in now?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways AltSignals&#8217; stage two presale event is already halfway over, with more investors pouring into the project. Bitcoin continues to struggle to defend its price above the $30k level. The cryptocurrency market has been bearish since the start of the week. Following last week&#8217;s rally, prices of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are currently underperforming. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/">AltSignals’ stage two presale surpasses 50%: should you get in now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; stage two presale event is already halfway over, with more investors pouring into the project.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin continues to struggle to defend its price above the $30k level.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been bearish since the start of the week. Following last week&rsquo;s rally, prices of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies are currently underperforming.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, AltSignals&rsquo; presale event continues to surge ahead, with the second presale event already 50% completed.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is an exciting Web3 project that specially targets traders. The development team seeks to solve some of the pain points of traders and make it easier for people to enter the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, AltSignals is a trading platform that provides trading signals for stocks, forex, indices, cryptocurrencies, and CFDs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the biggest concerns for traders is accurately carrying out technical analysis and determining when to enter and exit traders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals seeks to solve all that thanks to its use of blockchain technology and AI. The team has raised more than $1.1 million in the second presale stage and will use the funds to develop its trading platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI will be the native token that powers the AltSignals ecosystem. It is currently going for 0.01875 per token and could increase ahead of the next presale event.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In their whitepaper, AltSignals explained that they would use the funds generated from the funding rounds to develop ActualizeAI, a solution that could make it easier for more people to enter the cryptocurrency trading scene.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With ActualizeAI, users would have access to a fully automated solution that makes it easier for people to trade cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the official&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals website</u></a> to learn more about their presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals continues to generate more buzz</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has been retracing following last week&rsquo;s rally. Bitcoin has lost more than 1% of its value over the past few days and is currently struggling to maintain its price above the $30k threshold. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,960 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other leading cryptocurrencies, including Ether, and BNB, are also underperforming. Despite the recent market retracement, AltSignals&rsquo; presale event continues to attain new milestones.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; stage two presale event has generated nearly $1.2 million, 52% of the total amount required. The project is still in its early days and could serve as an excellent investment for investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the market currently retracing, more investors could be looking to purchase more cryptocurrencies. Furthermore, other investors could be looking to invest in new projects, and&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> could be one of the projects to consider.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in AltSignals now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the poor performance this week, the cryptocurrency market has outperformed the other financial markets since the start of the year. Bitcoin is up by nearly 50% year-to-date, making it one of the best-performing global assets so far this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Market experts predict that Bitcoin&rsquo;s price could surpass the $100,000 mark over the next few months or years. If that happens, other cryptocurrencies could benefit.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals could be one of the biggest beneficiaries due to its niche-specific product. As a product that targets traders,&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> could become an important project in a multi-billion dollar industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI is currently in its presale stage, and its price could soar higher once the token gets listed on cryptocurrency exchanges. Furthermore, if the crypto market embarks on a Bull Run, ASI&rsquo;s price could also appreciate in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/">AltSignals’ stage two presale surpasses 50%: should you get in now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-stage-two-presale-surpasses-50-should-you-get-in-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu nears $1M presale as trailblazing AI integration sparks investor gold rush</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu sparks gold rush for crypto investors with trailblazing AI protocol SHMU presale, uniquely tailored to investor interests, is close to hitting $1 million with over $954k raised so far. The Shiba Memu platform targets becoming the superpower of meme coin marketing. Shiba Memu is the latest meme coin craze in the vast cryptocurrency [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/">Shiba Memu nears $1M presale as trailblazing AI integration sparks investor gold rush</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu sparks gold rush for crypto investors with trailblazing AI protocol</li>
<li dir="ltr">SHMU presale, uniquely tailored to investor interests, is close to hitting $1 million with over $954k raised so far.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu platform targets becoming the superpower of meme coin marketing.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> is the latest meme coin craze in the vast cryptocurrency sphere. But unlike the rival coins that play on the original meme dog theme over and over again, Shiba Memu is looking to ride an innovative strategy powered by artificial intelligence (AI) to change the game.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token is currently in presale and is more of a gold rush for investors as the raised token sale amount edges closer to a $1 million just days into the 8-week offering. As seen on their <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">presale page</a>, investors have so far allocated over $954k to the project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Here we look at what Shiba Memu brings to the meme coin battleground and why investors think it could be a winning bet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A first in crypto meme and AI</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The question of what happens to crypto next is no longer a vague one, thanks to a global recognition that the industry is here to stay. While meme coins like Shiba Inu and Pepe have exploded and helped create the next crypto millionaires, none commands as much hype and positivity as does Shiba Memu (SHMU).</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a> is at the center of this outlook for the new token, and as we shall shortly see, could be the differentiator that sends SHMU to the top of the meme list.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a meme coin project that integrates the revolutionary technology behind AI. By leveraging the best of machine learning and NLP, the project seeks to evolve into a marketing powerhouse that will focus on bringing value to the SHMU ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project will learn and constantly re-imagine itself with the help of AI capabilities, incorporating all possible marketing strategies that put it ahead of competition and beneficial to SHMU token holders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, AI will make Shiba Memu a genius marketer, capable of extracting juices from a 24/7 presence across social media and other online platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Compared to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>, Pepe, and the other so-called Doge killers, Shiba Memu stands out for one thing: the ability to self-market and not rely on human-driven hype to gain traction. It is being designed as the robot meme dog that crypto investors are showing a lot of confidence in.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SHMU presale is live <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What else is unique about Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The presale offers a unique approach to SHMU pricing. A built-in system allows the price of the token to increase automatically each day at 6 pm GMT. Like an excited Shiba Inu pup, SHMU will spike at this set interval for 8 weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project will provide access to all the key data on an AI dashboard, with SHMU holders having an opportunity not just to see how AI is growing their visibility but also participate in this growth by sharing feedback and proposals. One earning opportunity will be in getting rewarded with SHMU if the system adopts your proposal.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is this a good time to buy Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is still under development and will have to deliver a working product for its AI dashboard to gain traction. This is the bare minimum if the project has to follow up the success of the presale stage with even more penetration in what could be a crowded AI-powered crypto field. As an investment, it would pay to know that market risks abound.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, with the industry in upbeat mood amid growth across altcoins and AI a big bet even in mainstream tech companies, there could be no other best opportunity to buy SHMU low.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently at $0.01405, the next price jump will see it hit $0.014275 and continue on this trajectory until the token&rsquo;s presale value eventually hits $0.0244. This is when Shiba Memu will look to explode as those who miss out on the presale get to buy it across exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Adding SHMU to an altcoin portfolio today might therefore be both an exposure to what&rsquo;s shaping up to be a huge prospect.</p>
<p>Do you want to know more about this AI-powered crypto protocol? Visit <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ShibaMemu.com</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/">Shiba Memu nears $1M presale as trailblazing AI integration sparks investor gold rush</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-1m-presale-as-trailblazing-ai-integration-sparks-investor-gold-rush/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge orders Ripple, SEC to agree to possible settlement dates</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>US Judge Analisa Torres referred Ripple vs. SEC case to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn. Last week&#8217;s ruling was that XRP was not a security. The Ripple vs. SEC case continues but Judge Netburn has suggested both Ripple and SEC can agree to possible settlement conference dates if they believe it to be &#8220;productive&#8221; at this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/">Judge orders Ripple, SEC to agree to possible settlement dates</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">US Judge Analisa Torres referred Ripple vs. SEC case to Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Last week&rsquo;s ruling was that XRP was not a security.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Ripple vs. SEC case continues but Judge Netburn has suggested both Ripple and SEC can agree to possible settlement conference dates if they believe it to be &ldquo;productive&rdquo; at this stage.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple news</a> is that US Magistrate Judge Sarah Netburn has ordered both Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to agree on possible dates for a settlement conference.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The order came not long after Judge Analisa Torres of the US District Court for the Southern District of New York referred the next phase of the Ripple vs. SEC court battle to Judge Netburn.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a court document filed on July 17, Judge Netburn, who will now preside over the General Pretrial, has recommended that the parties come to this agreement 6-8 weeks beforehand, referencing the court&rsquo;s busy schedule. &nbsp;As noted in the judge&rsquo;s order, the parties should agree to three mutually convenient dates.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will SEC and Ripple want to settle?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The pretrial phase includes aspects of the case around &ldquo;<em>scheduling, discovery and non-dispositive pretrial motions</em>.&rdquo; It is also likely the stage where the parties would want to settle. While the anticipation is that the SEC might want Ripple to settle, the coming days could make it clear whether any of the two sides view this as a route to take.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Fox Business journalist Eleanor Terrett shared the outlook on Twitter:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128680;To be clear: Judge Netburn is suggesting that both sides agree on some possible dates for a settlement meeting, *IF* "they believe it to be productive at this time." </p>
<p>This doesn't mean we'll see a settlement in 6-8 weeks. It means that if they do decide on a date, it will have&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/3bxqCGLyPr">https://t.co/3bxqCGLyPr</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eleanor Terrett (@EleanorTerrett) <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1681038538316423168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Last week, Judge Torres effectively declared XRP not a security and sparked a massive rally for the token and the broader crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Even though the outcome of the rest of the case is anybody&rsquo;s guess, the crypto industry believes Ripple&rsquo;s partial victory provided a watershed moment that could translate into the much needed regulatory clarity.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/">Judge orders Ripple, SEC to agree to possible settlement dates</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/judge-orders-ripple-sec-to-agree-to-possible-settlement-dates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
