<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:44:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase one]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
<p>By launching the subscription service, Coinbase is seeking to expand its global reach.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
<p>American crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> is bracing up to roll out its subscription service &#8211; Coinbase One. According to a Thursday <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/new-updates-to-coinbase-one-zero-trading-fees-boosted-staking-rewards-and" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the zero trading fee subscription service will start out in Germany, Ireland, and the United Kingdom. However, there are plans to extend the rollout to at least 32 other countries within the shortest time possible. A company statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Coinbase One is rolling out to full availability in the coming months, and we plan to expand to additional markets internationally.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase One, which has been in testing in the US since 2021, allows subscribers to pay a monthly fee of $29.99. With the subscription, users may trade for free throughout the month and also get amplified staking rewards.</p>
<p>Furthermore, subscribers will have exclusive access to industry insights and analytics from Messari and CoinTracker. And in addition to that, the subscription will also offer US members pre-filled tax return documents &#8211; Form 8949. That is, users do not have to go through the hassle of filing crypto taxes. Instead, they&#8217;ll enjoy the benefit of having their transactions organized automatically.</p>
<p>Coinbase also confirms that its new subscription service will give members round-the-clock access to its support team. That is, at any time of any day, members who need any form of assistance will get prompt help.</p>
<p>It might also be worth noting that Coinbase still has other plans to make the lives of subscribers much easier. Per its announcement, the exchange is also eyeing potential partnerships with the likes of Alto IRA (Individual Retirement Account) and Blockworks’ Permissionless and Lemonade.</p>
<h2>Coinbase One to Boost Exchange&#8217;s Global Reach</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the launch of the subscription service is part of Coinbase’s efforts to expand its global reach.  And with plans to offer the service in at least 35 countries, the exchange is looking to further deepen its roots across the globe.</p>
<p>It might be interesting to note that this launch comes after CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-uk-europe-market-us-regulatory/">suggested</a> that Coinbase might be moving out of the United States. At the time, Armstrong cited regulatory uncertainty in the country as the reason behind the company’s consideration. However, the CEO has since changed his earlier position, confirming that the exchange will no longer exit the US.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/">Coinbase One: American Crypto Exchange to Roll Out Subscription Service in 35 Countries</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-one-subscription/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dtwap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[orbs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quickswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255555</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
<p>QuickSwap has become the latest DEX to integrate dTWAP for traders to cut down on the price impact of their orders. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
<p>Leading Polygon decentralized exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/quickswap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">QuickSwap</a> recently integrated dTWAP for DEXs. Powered by <a href="https://www.orbs.com/dtwap/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Orbs</a>, dTWAP, the fully permissionless and composable DeFi protocol, will grant QuickSwap dragons access to its algorithmic trading strategy. This means that traders can lower the price impact of their orders without incurring additional costs. Meanwhile, besides dTWAP, QuickSwap dragons will also deploy Orbs &#8211; infrastructure for Limit Swap orders.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at QuickSwap &#8211; dTWAP Development</h2>
<p>The QuickSwap-dTWAP development follows similar integrations by the Orbs-powered protocol with SpookySwap, Spirit, and Pangolin. Furthermore, the latest dTWAP integration underpins the technical working relationship between QuickSwaps and the separate decentralized execution layer Orbs. Both projects leveraged dTWAP&#8217;s smart contract audits and comprehensive developer documentation to integrate the protocol with QuickSwap.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://defillama.com/dexs/quickswap" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DeFiLlama</a>, QuickSwap&#8217;s transaction volume for the past week exceeds $209 million. Furthermore, the decentralized layer-2 digital trading platform&#8217;s transaction volume in the last 24 hours exceeds $30 million. As a DEX automated market maker, QuickSwap&#8217;s offerings comprise multi-chain swaps, limit, order, and &#8216;best price trades&#8217;. However, the dTWAP integration will expand current offerings and increase transaction volumes from cost-conscious traders.</p>
<p>As an algorithmic trading strategy, TWAP also sees a lot of use cases in centralized finance (CeFi). The tool helps the protocol cut down the impact of large orders by reducing them into smaller portions.</p>
<p>Setting up a dTWAP order is relatively seamless and requires the specification of three parameters. These include the number of intervals, max duration, and the trade interval.</p>
<p>Users are also required to switch to the dTWAP UI to make the execution of trades easier and better manageable. The trade user interface features a customizable dashboard that updates changes in order in real time.</p>
<p>For instance, the &#8216;number of intervals&#8217; parameter lets the user choose the exact number of individual trades, after which the estimated trading interval is calculated. &#8216;Max duration&#8217; is the optimum time to execute the total amount of individual trades on the full dTWAP order. Lastly, &#8216;trade interval&#8217; establishes the time gap between each trade. However, users can edit this parameter to reflect the order sheet&#8217;s corresponding trade sizes and number changes.</p>
<h2>dTWAP</h2>
<p>The dTWAP protocol is the go-to tool in the decentralized finance space for algorithmic orders. Backed by the Orbs network L3 technology, the protocol is expected to experience substantial growth in usage as it adds support for additional DEXs. dTWAP is currently integrated with 4 DEXs across 3 different chains, accounting for its $200 million+ transaction volume in the past week.</p>
<h2>Orbs</h2>
<p>The Orbs Network is executed by secure permissionless validators that use the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus. Founded in 2017, Orbs launched its mainnet and token in March 2019 and has a development team of more than 30 people. The backend staff of the open, decentralized, public blockchain infrastructure is based in offices in the Middle East (Tel Aviv), Europe (London), North America (New York), and Asia (Tokyo and Seoul).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/">QuickSwap Integrates Orb-Powered dTWAP for Cheaper Price Impact on DEX Orders</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/quickswap-orb-dtwap-dex-orders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
<p>The new Meta Training and Inference Accelerator (MTIA) chip shall specifically handle "inference", an already-trained AI model that makes a prediction or takes action. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
<p>For the very first time, Facebook parent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) publicly announced that it is working on custom computer chips which will help the company with its artificial intelligence and video processing tasks.</p>
<p>Ahead of the virtual event on Thursday, May 18, Meta disclosed its internal silicon chip projects for the very first time while discussing the company&#8217;s AI technical infrastructure investments. Investors have been keen on knowing about Meta&#8217;s investments in AI along with the related data center hardware.</p>
<p>Over the last year, Meta has announced multiple layoffs as the company works on streamlining its operations while embarking on &#8220;a year of efficiency&#8221;. However, designing and building indigenous chips is always an expensive path for companies to undertake.</p>
<p>But Meta&#8217;s vice president of infrastructure Alexis Bjorlin believes that the improved performance will justify the investment. Recently, Meta has been overhauling its data center designs to focus on other energy-efficient techniques for reducing excess heat and liquid cooling.</p>
<p>For e.g. the company&#8217;s new computer chips, the Meta Scalable Video Processor, or MSVP, will process and transmit video to users while cutting down on energy requirements. Bjorlin said that there were no options available commercially to handle the task of processing and delivering 4 billion videos a day, as effectively as Meta wants.</p>
<p>Also, another processor Meta Training and Inference Accelerator, or MTIA, is the first in Meta&#8217;s family of chips that will help with various AI-specific tasks. The new MTIA chip shall specifically handle &#8220;inference&#8221;, an already-trained AI model that makes a prediction or takes action.</p>
<p>This AI-powered &#8220;inference&#8221; chip will power Meta&#8217;s recommendation algorithm used to show content and ads in people&#8217;s news feeds. However, Bjorlin didn&#8217;t speak about who the manufacturer is, but the blog post shows a “fabricated in TSMC 7nm process”.</p>
<h2>Meta&#8217;s Multi-Generational Roadmap</h2>
<p>Bjorlin said that Meta has a &#8220;multi-generational roadmap&#8221; for its family of AI chips which will include processors used for training AI models. As per the Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/inside-metas-scramble-catch-up-ai-2023-04-25/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> earlier, Meta canceled its AI inference chip project and started another one scheduled to roll out by 2025.</p>
<p>Bjorlin said that since Meta isn&#8217;t in the business of cloud computing, the company didn&#8217;t feel compelled to talk about the internal data center chip projects. She <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/18/meta-pulls-the-curtain-back-on-its-ai-chips-for-the-first-time.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“If you look at what we’re sharing &#8211; our first two chips that we developed &#8211; it’s definitely giving a little bit of a view into what are we doing internally. We haven’t had to advertise this, and we don’t need to advertise this, but you know, the world is interested.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meta&#8217;s new hardware works effectively with the company&#8217;s PyTorch software. This has become one of the most popular tools used by third-party developers in creating AI apps. The new hardware will eventually power several metaverse-related tasks, including augmented reality and virtual reality.</p>
<p>Additionally, Meta has also created a generative AI-powered coding assistant which will help the company&#8217;s developers to easily create and develop software. Meta said that it will continue to contribute to open-source technologies and AI research driving technological innovation ahead.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/">Meta Shares Details of Its AI Chips for First Time</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-details-ai-chips/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google’s YouTube Generated About $40B in Revenue in Past Year, CEO Neal Mohan Says</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 07:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neal mohan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[youtube]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255577</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/">Google’s YouTube Generated About $40B in Revenue in Past Year, CEO Neal Mohan Says</a></p>
<p>YouTube ads generated a revenue of about $6.69 billion during the first quarter of 2023 compared to $6.869 billion reported during the first quarter of 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/">Google’s YouTube Generated About $40B in Revenue in Past Year, CEO Neal Mohan Says</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/">Google’s YouTube Generated About $40B in Revenue in Past Year, CEO Neal Mohan Says</a></p>
<p>YouTube LLC, a product of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google LLC</a>, which is under <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL), reported a revenue of nearly $40 billion in the past 12 months according to its Chief Executive Officer Neal Mohan. The American online video-sharing and social media platform, however, recorded a decline in revenue for the third consecutive time. According to Mohan, the increased competition in the social media industry has reduced the volume of advertising. Furthermore, the company noted that there was an overall decline in digital advertising compared to previous years.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, GOOGL shares edged 1.65 percent higher on Thursday to close the day trading around $122.83. The $1.5 trillion valued tech behemoth has seen its stock rise about 40 percent YTD to trade around $123.24 during the after-hours session.</p>
<p>YouTube remains heavily reliant on the advertisement sector to collect revenue for its shareholders.</p>
<p>“Monetization for us, first and foremost, is driven by advertising,” <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-18/youtube-generated-40-billion-in-sales-in-past-year-ceo-says" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Mohan.</p>
<p>Speaking at the MoffettNathanson technology conference on Thursday, Mohan, noted that YouTube will continue to take emerging opportunities in advertising including YouTube Shorts.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the company offers a premium subscription platform for users who do not want to have ads in their videos. Dubbed YouTube Premium and formerly referred to as YouTube Red, has millions of subscribers but the company has not recently released its detailed financial results. The company has other revenue collection avenues including YouTube TV which is available in the United States for a subscription of about $65.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at YouTube Parent Company</h2>
<p>Earlier last month, Alphabet announced the financial results for the first quarter of 2023. During the first quarter, the company announced an expenditure of about $2.6 billion related to reductions in its workforce. As the company narrowed down to the artificial intelligence (AI) industry through its cloud sector. In total, Alphabet reported a revenue of about $69.78 billion during the first quarter.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, YouTube ads generated a revenue of about $6.69 billion during the first quarter of 2023 compared to $6.869 billion reported during the first quarter of 2022.</p>
<p>The company announced huge progress in deep computer science and artificial intelligence (AI) in its bid to revolutionize internet searches.</p>
<p>Ruth Porat, CFO of Alphabet and Google, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Resilience in Search and momentum in Cloud resulted in Q1 consolidated revenues of $69.8 billion, up 3% year over year, or up 6% in constant currency. We remain committed to delivering long-term growth and creating capacity to invest in our most compelling growth areas by re-engineering our cost base.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/">Google’s YouTube Generated About $40B in Revenue in Past Year, CEO Neal Mohan Says</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/youtube-40b-revenue-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Group Announces Mixed Q4 and Full Year 2023 Financial Results, BABA Shares Drop 5.41%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 07:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baba stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/">Alibaba Group Announces Mixed Q4 and Full Year 2023 Financial Results, BABA Shares Drop 5.41%</a></p>
<p>Alibaba announced a full spin-off of its Cloud Intelligence Group through a stock dividend distribution to existing shareholders to ensure its independence as a publicly traded company.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/">Alibaba Group Announces Mixed Q4 and Full Year 2023 Financial Results, BABA Shares Drop 5.41%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/">Alibaba Group Announces Mixed Q4 and Full Year 2023 Financial Results, BABA Shares Drop 5.41%</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holding Ltd</a> (NYSE: BABA) announced the financial results for the quarter that ended on March 31 ( fiscal Q4) and the full fiscal year 2023 on Thursday, May 18. The Chinese multinational technology company with a huge presence in the e-commerce industry announced revenue of RMB 208.200 billion, about $30.316 billion, during the quarter that ended on March 31.  While the revenue in the quarter increased by about 2 percent year-over-year, analysts surveyed by REFINITIV expected the company to report revenue of about 210.2 billion yuan in the quarter.</p>
<h2>Alibaba in Its Fiscal Q4 2023</h2>
<p>As for the Non-GAAP diluted earnings per share, Alibaba posted about RMB1.34, which is around $0.20. Although the company’s Non-GAAP EPS increased by approximately 35 percent year-over-year, analysts surveyed by REFINITIV expected the tech giant to post 2.08 yuan. The company’s Non-GAAP net income was RMB 27.375 billion, about $3.986 billion, thus representing an increase of about 38 percent year-over-year during the quarter.</p>
<p>Valued at around $231.13 billion, the Chinese tech giant continued to separate its businesses to ensure independence and greater service output.</p>
<p>“In an increasingly complex world, we have proactively transformed our organization to strengthen the competitiveness of our businesses through greater independence to address the evolving needs of different customers and capture new opportunities,” said Daniel Zhang, Chairman, and Chief Executive Officer of Alibaba Group.</p>
<p>For instance, Alibaba announced a full spin-off of its Cloud Intelligence Group through a stock dividend distribution to existing shareholders to ensure its independence as a publicly traded company.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Full-Year Results</h2>
<p>For the full fiscal year 2023, Alibaba reported a revenue of about RMB 868.687 billion, around $126.491 billion, representing an increase of approximately 2 percent YoY. As a result, the company posted non-GAAP diluted earnings per share of RMB 6.82, or about $0.99, thereby representing an increase of approximately 4 percent YoY basis.</p>
<p>“We have established a capital management committee at the Alibaba board level to undertake a comprehensive capital management plan to enhance shareholder value. Alibaba is committed to improving shareholders’ return through the implementation of a robust capital allocation framework,” <a href="https://data.alibabagroup.com/ecms-files/1532295521/e6f712b2-580c-4adf-ae1b-77c15c1ac262/Alibaba%20Group%20Announces%20March%20Quarter%20and%20Full%20Fiscal%20Year%202023%20Results.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Toby Xu, Chief Financial Officer of Alibaba Group.</p>
<p>For instance, the company announced its board approved the process to start exploring an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a> for the Cainiao Smart Logistics Group and Freshippo. Furthermore, the company announced a restructuring plan to ensure all its major business groups are headed by a different Chief Executive Officer.</p>
<p>As the Chinese market slowly recovers from the Covid-19 restrictions that affected businesses&#8217; supply chains, Alibaba is optimistic about posting better financial results amid the automation of its operations through AI.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/">Alibaba Group Announces Mixed Q4 and Full Year 2023 Financial Results, BABA Shares Drop 5.41%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-mixed-q4-full-year-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Integrates Its Spot Trading Platform with TradingView</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradingview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255554</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/">Binance Integrates Its Spot Trading Platform with TradingView</a></p>
<p>The integration of TradingView will give Binance users access to a wide range of tools while exposing Binance products to traditional investors.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/">Binance Integrates Its Spot Trading Platform with TradingView</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/">Binance Integrates Its Spot Trading Platform with TradingView</a></p>
<p>The Binance Spot market trading platform has been <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/binance-integrates-with-tradingview-to-enhance-trading-capabilities-301828343.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">integrated</a> with TradingView, a leading charting platform that offers traders a greater insight into the markets. The news broke via a press release seen on Thursday, May 18.</p>
<h2>Providing Greater Insight into the Market via Tools and Data</h2>
<p>With the integration, users of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> will have access to a wide range of tools featured on TradingView, enabling them to approach their trades with greater insight into the market and deploy a wider range of strategies in their trades. They’ll also be able to access TradingView tools via the Binance interface without a secondary log-in.</p>
<p>Binance had earlier integrated its derivatives offering with the charting platform, and the latest initiative is a reflection of an ongoing effort to give users of the platform more analytical trading tools, a press release from the company said.</p>
<h2>Conferring Legitimacy on Tokens among Traditional Investors</h2>
<p>The latest integration will give more exposure to Binance’s high liquidity products to existing TradingView users, who mostly invest in traditional financial instruments such as stocks, bonds, and commodities. The press release said that the TradingView integration will attract traditional investors who rely on technical tools provided by TradingView to access opportunities in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>It added that the availability of advanced charting tools will further confer legitimacy on digital asset tokens as investable instruments, despite the traditional skepticism of conservative investors.</p>
<h2>Creating Exposure to Traditional Investors</h2>
<p>Catherine Chen, who heads Binance’s VIP and Institutional divisions, said that the availability of level 1 and level 2 market data and advanced charting in Tradingview will act as a boost that will help in driving development in the growing cryptocurrency market. She added that these tools will engender the confidence of mainstream investors in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Chen said that institutional investors that have shown interest in cryptocurrency investment have made demands for these data and analytical tools and that with the integration with TradingView, this class of investors will be able to navigate the market with a higher sense of confidence and assurance.</p>
<p>&#8220;Users now have the convenience of a single sign-on to utilize TradingView&#8217;s interface to trade directly on Binance, the largest and most liquid digital asset exchange,&#8221; Chen said.</p>
<h2>Binance Futures Already Supports TradingView</h2>
<p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges and has listed more than 350 tokens. There are currently 1400 pairs available for trading on its spot market listing and 260 pairs available on its futures trading platform. The exchange boasts high liquidity, depth, and low fees.</p>
<p>Last December, Binance announced the integration of its Binance Futures with Tradingview. It gave users of its futures platform access to technical analysis tools. The latest spot market integration is a result of the success of the futures platform integration.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/">Binance Integrates Its Spot Trading Platform with TradingView</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-spot-trading-tradingview/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Labs Debuts CBDC Platform for Central Banks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaco]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255532</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/">Ripple Labs Debuts CBDC Platform for Central Banks</a></p>
<p>The CBDC Private Ledger, according to Ripple, will handle tens of thousands of transactions per second.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/">Ripple Labs Debuts CBDC Platform for Central Banks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/">Ripple Labs Debuts CBDC Platform for Central Banks</a></p>
<p>Popular blockchain payments firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Labs Inc</a> is set to launch its own Central Bank Digital Currency <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">(CBDC)</a> platform, which will allow central banks, governments, and financial institutions to issue digital currencies.</p>
<p>The news comes shortly after Ripple and the Central Bank of Montenegro <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/montenegro-ripple-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">agreed</a> to collaborate on the development of a pilot project for a national digital currency.</p>
<p>This platform&#8217;s goal is to equip Central Banks with the technology and infrastructure required to issue and operate their own CBDCs. Through Ripple’s CBDC platform, government agencies will be permitted to manage and customize the entire CBDC lifecycle including minting, distribution, redemption, and token burning.</p>
<p>Additionally, the platform will enable financial institutions to administer and engage in CBDC-related inter-institutional settlement and distribution functions. This could involve facilitating the secure and efficient transfer of CBDCs between financial institutions, enabling interoperability and settlement finality.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Central banks can issue both wholesale and retail CBDCs, which can also be used to conduct offline transactions. This would enable users to perform transactions with their CBDCs even if they did not have an active internet connection.</p>
<p>However, it is worth noting that the specific features and capabilities of CBDCs, including offline transaction support, would be determined by each central bank&#8217;s design choices and requirements.</p>
<p>Ripple said it would demonstrate use cases for the platform as part of the e-HKD pilot, a program of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, the de facto Central bank. Additionally, it is also <a href="https://www.hkma.gov.hk/media/eng/doc/key-information/press-release/2023/20230518e4a1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">working with Taiwan&#8217;s Fubon Bank</a> to tokenize real estate assets and develop stock trading products as part of the e-HKD trial.</p>
<h2>CBDC Platform Enhanced by Ripple’s Private Ledger</h2>
<p>Notably, the CBDC platform is an improved version of Ripple&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdcs-private-ledger/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">private ledger</a>, launched in 2021 to issue CBDCs. It is built on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripples-xrp-8-price-pump-court-twist/">XRP</a> Ledger but on a new private ledger.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Ripple has been leveraging the XRP Ledger, an open-source blockchain protocol, in its existing technology solutions. The firm has utilized the XRP Ledger for various applications, including facilitating fast and efficient transaction settlement.</p>
<p>The CBDC Private Ledger would leverage Ripple&#8217;s existing blockchain technology, specifically the XRP Ledger, to enable Central banks to create and distribute their digital currencies securely and efficiently. The goal is to deliver a holistic solution that meets the unique needs of Central banks, such as scalability, security, and regulatory compliance.</p>
<p>The CBDC Private Ledger, according to Ripple, will handle tens of thousands of transactions per second. This compares to the previous hundreds of thousands of transactions per second. By collaborating with central banks to develop CBDCs, Ripple aimed to support the modernization of the global financial system and promote the adoption of digital currencies.</p>
<p>In a bid to advance its business reach, Ripple has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-acquires-metaco-250m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">paid</a> $250 million to Switzerland-based firm, Metaco in order to expand its remittance network into institutional Bitcoin custody.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/">Ripple Labs Debuts CBDC Platform for Central Banks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-cbdc-central-banks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BT Shares Drop 8% after BT Group Announced Move to Cut Up to 55K Jobs by 2030</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bt group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bt shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bt stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255524</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/">BT Shares Drop 8% after BT Group Announced Move to Cut Up to 55K Jobs by 2030</a></p>
<p>The job cuts will happen despite an increase in its network connection, whereby BT Group reported a total of 8.6 million 5G connections, up 62% last year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/">BT Shares Drop 8% after BT Group Announced Move to Cut Up to 55K Jobs by 2030</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/">BT Shares Drop 8% after BT Group Announced Move to Cut Up to 55K Jobs by 2030</a></p>
<p>Shares of BT Group PLC (LSE: BT.A) dropped as much as 8 percent on Thursday to trade around £136.85. The sudden drop in the £14.91 billion valued British multinational telecommunications holding company was attributed to the announcement that between 40,000 to 55,000 of its workforce will be reduced by 2030. According to the company, the workforce reduction is set to begin in five years, which will represent between 31-42 percent of its total staff members. Notably, the company intends to cut down both third-party workers and its direct employees.</p>
<p>The company intends to digitize most of its services, which in return will help cut down huge operating costs. As the largest provider of fixed-line, broadband, and mobile services in the United Kingdom, BT Group will significantly streamline its services through the automation of some redundant tasks. Moreover, the information technology sector has significantly been automated throughout the world with the help of artificial intelligence (AI).</p>
<p>“By continuing to build and connect like fury, digitize the way we work, and simplify our structure, by the end of the 2020s BT Group will rely on a much smaller workforce and a significantly reduced cost base. New BT Group will be a leaner business with a brighter future,” BT Chief Executive Philip Jansen <a href="https://newsroom.bt.com/results-for-the-full-year-to-31-march-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<h2>BT Group Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The announcement came as the company highlighted its financial results for the fourth quarter and the fiscal year that ended on March 31. According to the announcement, the company grew both its pro forma revenue and its EBITDA for the first time in six years. Moreover, the company focused on delivering a quality 5G network across several markets in the past few years.</p>
<p>According to the financial earnings results, BT Group has a total of 8.6 million 5G connections, whereby 62 percent materialized last year. Nevertheless, the company noted that its revenue for the full year came in at £20.7 billion, down 1 percent. As a result, the company reported profit before tax of about £1.7 billion, down about 12 percent from the prior year. BT Group attributed the decline in profit for the financial year that ended March 31 to increased depreciation from network build.</p>
<p>Notably, the company reported a net debt of about £18.9 billion, up approximately £850 million primarily due to pension scheme contributions of £1 billion. Nonetheless, 19 analysts surveyed by MarketWatch gave BT shares an average of Over despite issuing disappointing guidance for the financial year 2024.</p>
<p>Other business news can be found <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/">BT Shares Drop 8% after BT Group Announced Move to Cut Up to 55K Jobs by 2030</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bt-shares-cut-up-55k-jobs-2030/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walmart Q1 2023 Results Sees Retail Giant Beat Expectations on Earnings &amp; Revenue despite Prudent Consumer Spending</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[walmart]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[walmart stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255529</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/">Walmart Q1 2023 Results Sees Retail Giant Beat Expectations on Earnings &#038; Revenue despite Prudent Consumer Spending</a></p>
<p>Walmart “leveraged expenses and expanded operating margin” in Q1 2023 and now expects a 3.5% increase in consolidated net sales for the year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/">Walmart Q1 2023 Results Sees Retail Giant Beat Expectations on Earnings &#038; Revenue despite Prudent Consumer Spending</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/">Walmart Q1 2023 Results Sees Retail Giant Beat Expectations on Earnings &#038; Revenue despite Prudent Consumer Spending</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/walmart/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Walmart Inc</a> (NYSE: WMT) has raised its 2023 full-year guidance following its stellar <a href="https://corporate.walmart.com/media-library/document/q1-fy24-earnings-release/_proxyDocument?id=00000188-2c80-dc3a-af89-bfecf9740000" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q1 earnings report.</a> On Thursday, the multinational retail corporation reported better-than-expected revenue, which was boosted by grocery and online businesses.</p>
<p>For the first quarter of the year, Walmart posted revenue of $152.30 billion compared to the $148.76 billion analysts expected. In addition, the Arkansas-based retail giant reported earnings per share of $1.47 adjusted versus $1.32 expected.</p>
<p>Walmart’s Q1 2023 sales grew 8%, with its substantial grocery business counterbalancing underwhelming clothing and electronic sales. Groceries amounted to approximately 60% of annual US sales, with revenue and operating income growing 7.6% and 17.3%, respectively.</p>
<p>The company’s stock rose in premarket trading amid increased guidance to reflect the positive earnings.</p>
<p>Walmart expects a 3.5% increase in consolidated net sales for the financial year. In addition, the retail corporation expects full-year adjusted earnings per share of between $6.10 and $6.20, which analysts also anticipate.</p>
<h2>Walmart CEO Expresses Contentment with Q1 2023</h2>
<p>Walmart President and Chief Executive Officer Doug McMillon spoke about the company’s latest outing in glowing terms, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We had a strong quarter. Comp sales were strong globally, with eCommerce up 26%. We leveraged expenses, expanded operating margin, and grew profit ahead of sales. And a big thank you to our associates, who continue to step up and deliver for customers and members whenever and however they want to be served.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, Walmart Chief Financial Officer John David Rainey drew attention to sustained consumer spending despite more prudent spending habits. According to Rainey, consumers bought smaller pack sizes and spent less on discretionary items while banking on promotions for pricier item purchases. However, despite these strains, consumer spending resilience remained unaffected. In a media session with CNBC, Rainey said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I think [the reason for the resilient consumer spending habits] is probably because balance sheets are much stronger than they were pre-pandemic, even at this point.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Popular American retail chains, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/home-depot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Depot</a> (NYSE: HD) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Target </a>(NYSE: TGT), previously reported more prudent consumer spending habits.</p>
<p>Walmart shares closed Wednesday at $149.53, with a market value of $403.33 billion.</p>
<h2>Q4 2022</h2>
<p>Walmart’s <a href="https://s201.q4cdn.com/262069030/files/doc_financials/2023/q4/Earnings-Release-(FY23-Q4)-(final).pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">2022 fourth-quarter results</a>, released in February, also reflected <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-revenue-holiday-quarter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">substantial revenue</a> for the retail giant amid the holiday period. For Q4 2022, the largest retail chain in the US reported revenue of $164.0 billion, with international net sales coming in at $27.6 billion. However, at the time, Walmart said $900 million from currency valuation negatively impacted its international net sales figures.</p>
<p>The retail company maximized consumer spending at the height of inflation by positioning itself as a choice option for cheap deals.</p>
<p>Mcmillon described Walmart’s Q4 2022 results as a great way to finish the year 2022. At the time, the CEO said Q4 built on the momentum gained in the preceding quarter and put Walmart in a prime position for 2023.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/">Walmart Q1 2023 Results Sees Retail Giant Beat Expectations on Earnings &#038; Revenue despite Prudent Consumer Spending</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/walmart-q1-2023-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Expects AI Tech to Boost S&amp;P 500 Profits by 30% Over Next Decade</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us federal reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255459</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/">Goldman Sachs Expects AI Tech to Boost S&#038;P 500 Profits by 30% Over Next Decade</a></p>
<p>The investor community is brewing with optimism as it expects AI to drive profit growth at a time of rising borrowing costs and supply chain problems</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/">Goldman Sachs Expects AI Tech to Boost S&#038;P 500 Profits by 30% Over Next Decade</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/">Goldman Sachs Expects AI Tech to Boost S&#038;P 500 Profits by 30% Over Next Decade</a></p>
<p>Although the onslaught of artificial intelligence (AI) is creating a major disruption in the market date, banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> is bullish about the tech and expects it to boost the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a> profits over the next decade.</p>
<p>The emergence of ChatGPT from OpenAI and several AI platforms subsequently, has created a significant storm in the tech space. While on the one hand, AT raises concerns over job losses, it also brings excitement on the other hand.</p>
<p>Particularly, the investor community is brewing with optimism as it expects AI to drive profit growth at a time of rising borrowing costs and supply chain problems. Speaking to CNBC on Thursday, May 18, Goldman’s senior strategist Ben Snider <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/18/goldman-sachs-ai-driven-gains-could-lead-to-30percent-sp-500-profit-spike.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Over the next 10 years, AI could increase productivity by 1.5% per year. And that could increase S&amp;P500 profits by 30% or more over the next decade. A lot of the favorable factors that led to that expansion (of S&amp;P 500) earnings seem to be reversing. But the real source of optimism now is productivity enhancements through artificial intelligence. It’s clear to most investors that the immediate winners are in the technology sector. The real question for investors is who are going to be winners down the road.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Snider takes us down memory lane adding that during the tech bubble of 1999-2000, it would have been hard to think about companies like Facebook and Uber changing our lives. He sees the artificial intelligence space in a similar situation right now.</p>
<h2>Energy and Healthcare Attractive in Short Term</h2>
<p>Snider also recommended that investors should spread their investments in the cyclical and defensive sectors. Furthermore, he said that considering the current valuations, the energy and healthcare sectors look attractive.</p>
<p>In the short term, he also expects the US Federal Reserve to end its monetary tightening measures. Snider said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The question is: In which ways will that continue to affect the economy moving forward? One sign of concern in the recent earnings season is that S&amp;P 500 companies are starting to pull back a bit on corporate spending.”</p></blockquote>
<p>“If interest rates are high, as a company, you might be a little more averse to issuing debt and therefore you might pull back on your spending. And indeed if we look at S&amp;P 500 buybacks, they were down 20% year-over-year in the first quarter of this year &#8211; that is one sign perhaps we haven’t seen all the effects of this tightening cycle,&#8221; he added.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sony-finance-unit-listing/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/">Goldman Sachs Expects AI Tech to Boost S&#038;P 500 Profits by 30% Over Next Decade</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-ai-tech-sp-500/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4528 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1257164 metric#prefetches=196 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=15 metric#store-hits=203 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=100.85 metric#ms-cache=6.82 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1895 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.8 -->