<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 17:30:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>NYDFS: Banks must seek approval before engaging with crypto</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nydfs-banks-must-seek-approval-before-engaging-with-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/nydfs-banks-must-seek-approval-before-engaging-with-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[New York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nydfs-banks-must-seek-approval-before-engaging-with-crypto/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Department of Financial Services published the new guidelines on 15 December 2022. All banking organisations must apply for permission to undertake any crypto activities. The regulatory guidelines are effective immediately and come as the spotlight is firmly on crypto following FTX&#8217;s implosion. Amid all the scrutiny on cryptocurrency exchanges after FTX&#8217;s collapse, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nydfs-banks-must-seek-approval-before-engaging-with-crypto/">NYDFS: Banks must seek approval before engaging with crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>New York Department of Financial Services published the new guidelines on 15 December 2022.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>All banking organisations must apply for permission to undertake any crypto activities.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The regulatory guidelines are effective immediately and come as the spotlight is firmly on crypto following FTX&rsquo;s implosion.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Amid all the scrutiny on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> after FTX&rsquo;s collapse, the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) has announced new guidelines targeting banks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The NYDFS, the top financial regulator in the Empire State, said in an announcement that all banking institutions in the jurisdiction have to seek prior permission if they wish to get involved in the crypto space.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">NYDFS&rsquo; new guidelines to banks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The agency specified in its 15 December <a href="https://www.dfs.ny.gov/system/files/documents/2022/12/il20221215_prior_approval.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">letter</a> to players within the banking industry that any involvement in virtual currency-related activities must first be addressed to authorities. Only once approved can such an entity go on to engage in the permitted initiative.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The NYDFS said these demands apply to all New York-based banking organizations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also covered are all branches and agencies of foreign banks and other financial providers licensed to operate in the state. Combined, the regulator referred to the targeted entities as &ldquo;Covered Institutions.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>A Covered Institution should seek the Department&rsquo;s prior approval before commencing any new or significantly different virtual currency-related activity</em>,&rdquo; the NYDFS wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But even with approval to engage with crypto, banks will still need further permission to undertake new activities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Prior approval for a Covered Institution to engage in a virtual currency-related activity does not constitute general consent for that institution to engage in other types of virtual currency-related activity, nor does it authorize other Covered Institutions to undertake that same activity</em>,&rdquo; the letter reads in part.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto in the spotlight</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The NYDFS&rsquo; latest regulatory action comes amid the fallout of FTX&rsquo;s implosion, a much more devastating setback to crypto in a year dictated with multiple bankruptcies and massive losses for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But the agency sees the crypto market as one that continues to evolve and innovate &ndash; part of the growth trajectory that has seen several banks seek to offer various crypto products and services.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The guidance is thus part of the thorough assessment for banks before they engage in digital assets-related activity, with the goal of ensuring safety for consumers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The requirements are effective immediately, the agency pointed out, and only apply on top of already existing laws and regulations.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nydfs-banks-must-seek-approval-before-engaging-with-crypto/">NYDFS: Banks must seek approval before engaging with crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/nydfs-banks-must-seek-approval-before-engaging-with-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentraland Price Prediction: Metacade Seems to Be a Better Option</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/decentraland-price-prediction-metacade-seems-to-be-a-better-option/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/decentraland-price-prediction-metacade-seems-to-be-a-better-option/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 17:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/decentraland-price-prediction-metacade-seems-to-be-a-better-option/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The metaverse looks increasingly poised to become a major player in the tech world in the next few years. As more and more major companies are joining in, it looks like widespread adoption is just on the horizon. That means that now is the time to be looking at these projects that still have a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/decentraland-price-prediction-metacade-seems-to-be-a-better-option/">Decentraland Price Prediction: Metacade Seems to Be a Better Option</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The metaverse looks increasingly poised to become a major player in the tech world in the next few years. As more and more major companies are joining in, it looks like widespread adoption is just on the horizon. That means that now is the time to be looking at these projects that still have a lot of room to grow with some promising price predictions for the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Two projects in particular that could drive this progress are Decentraland (MANA) and Metacade (MCADE). In terms of price prediction, the big question is &ndash; which has the higher potential?</p>
<p dir="ltr">This article will cover the characteristics of each project and look over which has the bigger opportunity for returns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Decentraland (MANA)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Decentraland is a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DAO</u></a> (Decentralised Autonomous Organisation) that creates, maintains, and governs a virtual world. The platform&rsquo;s native token, MANA, is an ERC20 token that is used to purchase metaverse real estate and take part in governance voting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Through leveraging the power of decentralised communities, Decentraland is one piece of the foundation on which the future of the GameFi industry could be built. In Decentraland, anyone can freely build 3D worlds, while exploring, navigating, and sharing their creation, which is a key reason why some investors believe that the Decentraland price prediction could be promising.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Decentraland platform consists of two main elements. The Decentraland <a href="https://clevertap.com/blog/what-is-an-sdk/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>SDK</u></a> is used to build metaverse-based experiences and the Decentraland client is used to view and interact with these experiences.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Decentraland platform allows users to create, experience, and monetise content and applications. There are numerous ways to enjoy the Decentraland metaverse and a broad range of digital creations that can be made. Users can build their very own section of the virtual reality landscape and monetise artwork and other assets by minting them as NFTs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By making the game-building process more accessible, Decentraland is expanding the scope of play-to-earn gaming.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Decentraland: prime real estate but losing popularity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A key drawback to Decentraland&rsquo;s price prediction is its ongoing struggle to attract users in the past 12 months. The long-term price prediction for MANA could suffer as a result. A recent report indicated that there were fewer than 1000&nbsp;<a href="https://messari.io/asset/decentraland/chart/act-addr-cnt" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>active users</u></a> that were buying and selling MANA tokens. So although the platform offers unique functionality and does have high potential, the price prediction is currently less than others in the metaverse space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Experts see metaverse-based projects as prime long-term investments due to the utility being offered in these digital landscapes. Investors are predicting that the MANA price will rise from current levels alongside other metaverse tokens, but it may struggle to reclaim its previous highs. These projects use advanced technologies that bring people together from all over the world and long-term Decentraland price predictions are higher than the current prices but nothing to marvel at.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One metaverse project that is enjoying a different level of success is Metacade which has already shown major potential for the coming years. While Decentraland&rsquo;s MANA coin has been disappointing for a lot of crypto investors during 2022, Metacade&rsquo;s MCADE has become an attractive alternative.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is a comprehensive Play-to-Earn gaming platform that is building the biggest arcade on the blockchain. Metacade offers a range of arcade-style games on a platform that integrates gaming with earning opportunities.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On top of this, Metacade hosts Play-to-Earn tournaments, where gamers can add a competitive element to their experience. By connecting GameFi enthusiasts on the platform and providing MCADE token rewards, Metacade offers competitive gamers new ways to enjoy some of the best Play-to-Earn games around.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">A strong approach to community-building</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Aside from being the go-to arcade for P2E gaming, Metacade is also a user-focused platform. For example, MCADE tokens will be used to reward community members for their contributions to the Metacade space. Users can help other players to uncover the best methods for playing the latest GameFi titles and Metacade will provide financial rewards. Simply put, users can earn by taking part in the community. That includes sharing their knowledge about the latest games while building new relationships with other gamers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since the project is fully focused on its community, Metacade will become a DAO to allow players to vote on governance proposals using MCADE tokens. This hands more power back to gamers as they decide on the best course of action for several key features in a digital world that will be entirely controlled by MCADE token holders.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Supporting the future of GameFi</h3>
<p dir="ltr">A key feature that community members will be able to influence is the Metagrants program. Metagrants will be used to fund the next wave of GameFi innovators, as the community can vote on a number of investment pitches and decide which projects sound the best. In this sense, the Metacade community will have a direct influence over the future of Play-to-Earn gaming.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade will also include a Web3 jobs board from 2024 onwards. This section of the metaverse world will connect up-and-coming blockchain games with a dedicated community of gamers. The aim is to let the Metacade community test out these new titles and provide feedback to the development teams in exchange for MCADE token rewards.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Decentraland vs Metacade</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metaverse projects are certainly looking like a solid bet for the future, especially as the utility being offered in these roadmaps is extensive. With Metacade still at an earlier stage in its development, it naturally has much higher than any Decentraland price prediction.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at Decentraland, the MANA coin has already experienced major growth in its token value. Between 2020 and 2021, MANA&rsquo;s price rose by almost 10,000%. Since then, however, the project has experienced a major pullback and investors are predicting that the price may never reach the same heights as in 2021. For now, the Decentraland price prediction is $2.22. If MANA manages to break this key level of resistance, then new all-time highs can be reached.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In contrast, Metacade has just started its token <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> and has nowhere to go but up. With so much value on the horizon, investors have been jumping into MCADE and have made some major gains already. The long-term price prediction looks significantly higher than current prices after the token was initially launched at just $0.008. At such an early stage, Metacade could even rise by a similar level to Decentraland&rsquo;s 10,000% before the next bull run begins. By 2025, MCADE price prediction is expected to reach the $5 mark.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at everything with clear eyes, the choice between MCADE and MANA is clear. Metacade&rsquo;s token looks like it has a much brighter future ahead of it.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Buy MANA on eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.etoro.com/markets/mana" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/decentraland-price-prediction-metacade-seems-to-be-a-better-option/">Decentraland Price Prediction: Metacade Seems to Be a Better Option</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/decentraland-price-prediction-metacade-seems-to-be-a-better-option/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This week in crypto: SBF arrested in The Bahamas</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-arrested-in-the-bahamas/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-arrested-in-the-bahamas/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 15:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-arrested-in-the-bahamas/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Authorities have arrested Sam Bankman-Fried in the Bahamas. Binance reserves are accounted for, says CryptoQuant. Ark Invest continues to invest in Coinbase. Sam Bankman-Fried has been arrested Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX cryptocurrency,&#160;was arrested in The Bahamas earlier this week. The former billionaire now faces extradition to the United States, where he would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-arrested-in-the-bahamas/">This week in crypto: SBF arrested in The Bahamas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Authorities have arrested Sam Bankman-Fried in the Bahamas.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance reserves are accounted for, says CryptoQuant.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ark Invest continues to invest in Coinbase.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Sam Bankman-Fried has been arrested</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX cryptocurrency,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bankman-fried-arrested-what-happens-now-and-where-are-caroline-ellison-and-sam-trabucco/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>was arrested</u></a> in The Bahamas earlier this week. The former billionaire now faces extradition to the United States, where he would face numerous charges by both the Securities and Exchange Commission and the U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office for the Southern District of New York.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A Bahamian judge denied SBF bail as he is deemed a flight risk. The U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office for the Southern District of New York charged SBF with eight criminal counts. Meanwhile, the SEC also charged Sam Bankman-Fried with allegedly orchestrating a scheme to defraud equity investors in FTX Trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to John J Ray III,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bankman-fried-arrested-what-happens-now-and-where-are-caroline-ellison-and-sam-trabucco/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>FTX had no record-keeping</u></a> whatsoever and accused the cryptocurrency exchange of committing old-fashioned embezzlement.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance reserves are accounted for</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain analytics provider CryptoQuant revealed earlier this week that it had&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptoquant-confirms-binance-reserves-are-accounted-for/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>verified Binance&rsquo;s proof of reserve</u></a> in its recently released audit report. The report analysed the recently released proof-of-reserves by Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There has been a lot of FUD around Binance over the past few days, with a surge in withdrawals on the platform. Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, told CNBC that the cryptocurrency exchange could meet 100% of withdrawals on its platform. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;People can withdraw 100% of the assets they have on Binance; we will not have an issue on any given day. Binance doesn&rsquo;t operate on a fractional banking system.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Cathie Wood&rsquo;s Ark Invest mops up more Coinbase stocks</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ark Invest acquired Coinbase stocks on two separate occasions last week. At the start of the week, Ark Invest acquired over 78,000 Coinbase stocks, despite the declining price of the company&rsquo;s shares.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Before the end of the week, Ark Invest spent $3.2 million on Coinbase shares, bringing its total to 58 million. The investment came despite the fact that Coinbase&rsquo;s CEO revealed the company expects its 2022 revenue to decline by 50% or more from what it generated in 2021.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Microsoft drops the hammer on cryptocurrency mining on its online services</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cloud computing giant Microsoft announced earlier this week that it had placed new restrictions on activities like cryptocurrency mining. As a result of this latest development, users will now require written pre-approval from the company before they can be allowed to use Microsoft Azure for mining cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Brazil is next to launch a CBDC</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The president of the Brazil Central Bank, Roberto Campos Neto, announced earlier this week that they are preparing to launch a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) in 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The central bank is also planning to carry out a pilot program alongside other financial institutions before the implementation of the CBDC.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-arrested-in-the-bahamas/">This week in crypto: SBF arrested in The Bahamas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-arrested-in-the-bahamas/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance&#8217;s proof of reserves auditor pulls report, what does it mean?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-proof-of-reserves-auditor-pulls-report-what-does-it-mean/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-proof-of-reserves-auditor-pulls-report-what-does-it-mean/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 15:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-proof-of-reserves-auditor-pulls-report-what-does-it-mean/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways&#160; Mazar&#8217;s, the accounting firm who worked with Binance on the proof of reserves report, has pulled the link from its website It has also paused all crypto work indefinitely Controversy followed the report, with critics decrying its lack of information on the liability side&#160; Mazar&#8217;s had previously stated that this was a &#8220;report&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-proof-of-reserves-auditor-pulls-report-what-does-it-mean/">Binance&#8217;s proof of reserves auditor pulls report, what does it mean?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Key Takeaways&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>Mazar&rsquo;s, the accounting firm who worked with Binance on the proof of reserves report, has pulled the link from its website</li>
<li>It has also paused all crypto work indefinitely</li>
<li>Controversy followed the report, with critics decrying its lack of information on the liability side&nbsp;</li>
<li>Mazar&rsquo;s had previously stated that this was a &ldquo;report&rdquo; and not an &ldquo;audit&rdquo;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Woops.</p>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>&rsquo;s &ldquo;audit&rdquo;, with the inverted commas very much intended there, is no more. Mazar&rsquo;s the auditing firm that worked with Binance on the proof of reserves report &ndash; which was what it was referred to by Mazar&rsquo;s, rather than an audit &ndash; has removed the report from its website.</p>
<p>It also announced that it would be pausing its work with all crypto clients. As well as Binance, this includes Crypto.com and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/kucoin/">KuCoin</a>.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Unfortunately, this means that we will not be able to work with Mazar&rsquo;s for the moment&rdquo;, a Binance spokesperson said.</p>
<h2><strong>Why was Mazar&rsquo;s report controversial?&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p>I have <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-is-next-for-crypto-proof-of-reserves-is-not-helping-this-mess/">written extensively</a> about the failure that was the proof of reserves initiative. In short, it couldn&rsquo;t be less of an audit, with the report throwing up more questions than it answered.</p>
<p>Most prominently, there was a refusal to present liabilities, with CEO Changpeng Zhao stating on Twitter that this was &ldquo;harder&rdquo; and to merely &ldquo;ask around&rdquo; to verify that Binance don&rsquo;t owe anybody anything.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">yes, but liabilities are harder. We don't owe any loans to anyone. You can ask around.</p>
<p>&mdash; CZ &#128310; Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1600596763404079124?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 7, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Needless to say, this instruction to ask around didn&rsquo;t exactly appease the investing public, fresh from being told &ldquo;assets are fine&rdquo; by FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, before he promptly deleted the tweet, filed for bankruptcy and was arrested this week.</p>
<p>Now, Binance has nothing to do with FTX, but the PTSD that investors have over the collapse of the latter is fuelling a very sensitive market right now.</p>
<p>Then came the terribly timed news that US prosecutors were reportedly <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-ceo-zhao-could-face-criminal-charges-what-does-this-mean-for-crypto/">considering filing criminal charges</a> against Zhao and other Binance executives in relation to a money laundering case that has been ongoing for a number of years, and Binance were suddenly news story number one. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Withdrawals then <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/withdrawals-flood-out-of-binance-cz-warns-of-bumpy-road-ahead/">flooded out</a> of Binance.</p>
<pre data-stringify-type="pre">        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12168197">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    </pre>
<p>In addition to this, the BNB token peeled back, which had previously been holding up well throughout 2022 &ndash; compared to the rest of the crypto market, at least.</p>
<pre data-stringify-type="pre">        <div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/12195243">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    </pre>
<h2><strong>What happens next?</strong></h2>
<p>Mazar&rsquo;s revocation of the report doesn&rsquo;t really change much. It is widely acknowledged in the space now that more transparency is needed. Binance &ndash; and other exchanges &ndash; operate in an opaque manner compared to traditional finance firms.</p>
<p>It is an ironic truth in an industry that is meant to be built on the premise of trutlessness, investors are forced to rely upon the assurances of executives on Twitter. Hopefully, the furore this episode has caused will force Binance to come completely clean and present to the world a bona-fide audit.</p>
<p>There is certainly nothing to suggest that the firm has any reason not to, but for paranoid investors, the opposite is also true &ndash; there is currently no way to verify that Binance are making true on their word.</p>
<p>Mazar&rsquo;s had declared that Binance was 101% collaterised.</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;At the time of assessment, Mazars observed Binance controlled in-scope assets in excess of 100% of their total platform liabilities,&rdquo;&nbsp;</em>the report said.&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Audited proof of reserves. Transparency. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a> <a href="https://t.co/IClZxTYaWp">https://t.co/IClZxTYaWp</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CZ &#128310; Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1600567141887000580?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 7, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>But on closer look, the data wasn&rsquo;t as satisfying. Binance&rsquo;s assets amounted to 582,486 bitcoins and its liabilities numbered 597,602 bitcoins. This appeared to suggest an undercollaterization of 3%, but when including assets lent to customers through loan and margin accounts, came to a collaterization ratio of 101%. &nbsp;</p>
<p>While things seem to have subsided recently, with withdrawals from Binance returning to normal levels, the episode sums up that cryptocurrency has a transparency problem.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s great that Binance have survived this little &ldquo;stress test&rdquo;, but in reality, this never should have transpired in the first place. Until crypto companies bring their disclosures in line with what is presented in traditional finance, however, these episodes of trepidation will continue to pop up throughout time.</p>
<p>For its part, Binance has affirmed that it is moving towards more transparency. That is a great thing &ndash; and something the space desperately needs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-proof-of-reserves-auditor-pulls-report-what-does-it-mean/">Binance&#8217;s proof of reserves auditor pulls report, what does it mean?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-proof-of-reserves-auditor-pulls-report-what-does-it-mean/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australian regulator ASIC sues Finder Wallet</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-asic-sues-finder-wallet/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-asic-sues-finder-wallet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 14:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-asic-sues-finder-wallet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ASIC is suing Finder Wallet for providing unlicenced financial services. ASIC claims the Finder Earn product closely resembled a debenture. Finder Wallet stopped providing the service to its customers last month. ASIC sues Finder Wallet for providing unlicenced services The Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) announced on Thursday, December 15th, that it had sued [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-asic-sues-finder-wallet/">Australian regulator ASIC sues Finder Wallet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ASIC is suing Finder Wallet for providing unlicenced financial services.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">ASIC claims the Finder Earn product closely resembled a debenture.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Finder Wallet stopped providing the service to its customers last month.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ASIC sues Finder Wallet for providing unlicenced services</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) announced on Thursday, December 15th, that it had sued Finder Wallet, a subsidiary of comparison website Finder.com, over a crypto-linked yield product.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Australian financial watchdog revealed that it sued the platform for alleged unlicensed conduct and inadequate risk disclosure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASIC is suing Finder Wallet for providing Finder Earn, a product that was offered between February and Nov. 10, 2022. The product saw Finder Wallet convert user deposits in Australian dollars into an Australian dollar-linked stablecoin called TAUD. Finder proceeds to use the stablecoin as working capital.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finder Wallet offered Australian users interest rates on deposits of 4.01% and 6.01%. According to ASIC, Finder Earn resembles a debenture and Finder Wallet should have acquired appropriate licences before providing the product to Australians.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASIC deputy chair Sarah Court said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;This is ASIC&rsquo;s third recent action against a firm offering a crypto-asset-related product that we consider to be a financial product. Our message to the industry is clear &mdash; just because an offer involves a crypto-asset-related product does not guarantee it will fall outside the current regulatory regime.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>ASIC drops the hammer on FTX</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">ASIC is suing Finder Wallet despite the platform stop offering the product on November 24. Finder Wallet returned all funds to customers after ASIC informed the company of concerns about the product.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes a month after ASIC dropped the hammer on FTX. Last month, ASIC <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-australian-securities-and-investments-commission-suspends-ftx-australias-licence/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>suspended the licence</u></a> issued to FTX Australia, the Australian arm of the FTX exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The suspension came following the collapse of the parent FTX cryptocurrency exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The bear market continues to affect the operations of numerous cryptocurrency companies. Earlier this month, Australian crypto exchange Swyft, announced that it had <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-crypto-exchange-swyftx-to-cut-45-of-staff-amid-crypto-winter/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>cut 45% of its total workforce</u></a> as revenue dropped due to the bear market.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-asic-sues-finder-wallet/">Australian regulator ASIC sues Finder Wallet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/australian-regulator-asic-sues-finder-wallet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade Smashes Past $1 Million In Three Weeks &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-smashes-past-1-million-in-three-weeks-heres-why/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-smashes-past-1-million-in-three-weeks-heres-why/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 13:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-smashes-past-1-million-in-three-weeks-heres-why/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The GameFi market continues to prove popular with crypto investors, and MCADE, the native token for Metacade, is leading the charge. In the three weeks of its beta presale, the MCADE token has already smashed the $1 million barrier, making it one of the hottest new blockchain tokens on the market. Metacade is quickly gaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-smashes-past-1-million-in-three-weeks-heres-why/">Metacade Smashes Past $1 Million In Three Weeks &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The GameFi market continues to prove popular with crypto investors, and MCADE, the native token for <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>, is leading the charge. In the three weeks of its beta presale, the MCADE token has already smashed the $1 million barrier, making it one of the hottest new blockchain tokens on the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is quickly gaining momentum as gamers and investors recognize the potential to become a leader in the Web 3.0 gaming space. As a result, both are moving early to support the project to maximize their potential returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Almost 90% of the available MCADE tokens in the beta presale have been purchased at the introductory price of $0.008, leaving a small amount still available to intelligent investors. Once the beta presale is complete, MCADE tokens will remain open for purchase at the increased price of $0.10.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While this remains excellent value, the beta presale token price is 25% lower, promising an even better return to shrewd investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is the first play-to-earn (P2E) virtual arcade that harnesses the tremendous potential of Web 3.0 technology to build the metaverse&rsquo;s premier gaming space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Players can earn rewards in MCADE tokens as they interact with the platform. As well as earning while they play through success in tournaments and climbing leaderboards, players can earn rewards by sharing gaming knowledge, writing game reviews, and providing feedback to developers through the platform&rsquo;s backtesting capability.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What makes Metacade unique?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">GameFi-based apps are nothing new. Several gaming apps utilize blockchain but offer gamers fewer options or opportunities to earn than Metacade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s most significant selling point is the range of games available on the platform. Where many virtual gaming apps exist with either a single title or a minimal range to choose from, Metacade intends to host the most comprehensive library of titles of any metaverse gaming app.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, Metacade isn&rsquo;t simply a platform for gamers to hang out. Instead, there&rsquo;s a significant focus on developing new titles unique to Metacade. Indeed, the platform supports game developers on their journey by offering them the chance to apply for funding through Metagrants to turn their plans into reality.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform&rsquo;s greatest strength is that Metacade will put the power in the hands of users by granting them full autonomy on the direction the platform takes. For example, they will be able to stake MCADE tokens to vote on which games make the cut and go into development after assessing applications from developers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Gamers can approve games they want to see within the community and not see the library full of titles they have no interest in or want to play. Indeed, the entire ethos of Metacade is to hand power back to the gamers. Metacade will remove barriers currently existing between gamers and development studios.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s platform will undergo several iterations, each one bringing new features. For instance, there are plans for a career hub to link the finest new talent in metaverse gaming development with exciting Web3 companies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The ultimate goal is to build a fully self-sufficient community with a flow of MCADE tokens from investors and advertisers into the wallets of developers, Metagrants, and players through rewards. By this stage, the plan is for Metacade to transition into a DAO, allowing the community members to build the best possible platform for gamers of all experience levels.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Invest in MCADE?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain gaming is a rapidly evolving industry with more than 2,000 percent growth since January 2021. Furthermore, experts predict that this growth will continue throughout the rest of the decade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade&rsquo;s offering will position it at the vanguard of the metaverse gaming revolution, making the beta presale a wise investment. Moreover, with the price of an MCADE token at rock-bottom levels, there is substantial room for a significant and quick return on investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, what makes Metacade such an attractive investment opportunity is the diverse and multi-layered roadmap that will lead to an ever-evolving environment. Unlike many crypto-platforms, which are limited by offering a single-use, Metacade has a unique longevity that will keep the platform growing in the future.</p>
<p><strong>Here are some more details on&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>how to buy MCADE</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-smashes-past-1-million-in-three-weeks-heres-why/">Metacade Smashes Past $1 Million In Three Weeks &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-smashes-past-1-million-in-three-weeks-heres-why/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HOOK price defies gravity as Hooked Protocol activity rises</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hook-price-defies-gravity-as-hooked-protocol-activity-rises/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hook-price-defies-gravity-as-hooked-protocol-activity-rises/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hook-price-defies-gravity-as-hooked-protocol-activity-rises/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hooked Protocol is a small but fast-growing platform. Its activity has surged to position 1 in DappRadar rankings. Hooked Protocol price defied gravity as the developers started airdrop distributions. It also rose as the platform rose to the top of the DappRadar rankings of the top BSC chain networks. HOOK rose to $2, which was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hook-price-defies-gravity-as-hooked-protocol-activity-rises/">HOOK price defies gravity as Hooked Protocol activity rises</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Hooked Protocol is a small but fast-growing platform.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Its activity has surged to position 1 in DappRadar rankings.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Hooked Protocol price defied gravity as the developers started airdrop distributions. It also rose as the platform rose to the top of the DappRadar rankings of the top BSC chain networks. HOOK rose to $2, which was much higher than this month&rsquo;s low of $0.10.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Hooked Protocol and why is it rising?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Hooked Protocol is an on-ramp layer that hopes to guide the broad web3 adoption. Its main product is known as Wild Cash, which is a platform that provides quiz-to-earn and other gaming solutions with over 2 million users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It also makes it possible for users to earn rewards through their Proof of Work (PoW) mechanisms by contributing to its platform. Further, users can refer other people to earn rewards in the ecosystem. Wild Cash&rsquo;s Android app has over 1 million users and a 4.8 star rating.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are several reasons why the HOOK price has defied gravity in the past few days. First, the developer started distributing the first batch of airdrops on Thursday. According to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.bscscan.com/address/0x99c1c5b6771dd96291a18d96225cdf67d3b6489a#tokentxns"><u>BscScan</u></a>, there are now tokens worth $187 million in its airdrop wallet.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This airdrop was meant to reward early supporters of the&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/@HookedProtocolOfficial/hooked-airdrop-announcement-4e2223999d77"><u>network</u></a> on the Hooked Party Pass NFTs. It also supports the motivation of users to continue building on the network. There will be five more airdrop batches in the coming months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The last five airdrops will be for existing Hooked Party Pass NFT holder and long-term community contributors. They will happen on the first day of each month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">HOOK price also rose as it rose to the top ranking of the&nbsp;<a href="https://dappradar.com/binance-smart-chain/social/hooked"><u>social section</u></a> of DappRadar rankings of the most active apps.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/HookedProtocol/status/1603266717282889728"><u>https://twitter.com/HookedProtocol/status/1603266717282889728</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hook price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The hourly chart shows that the HOOK price has been in a consolidation phase in the past few days. It has been hovering at the important level of $2.0 This price is along the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has risen above the neutral point of 50.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, Hooked Protocol price will likely drop during the weekend as the enthusiasm of the airdrop fades. If this happens, the token will likely drop to about $1.50.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/16/1671195255080-da190cf3-64e4-47f3-bdfd-bba2298357e4.png" style="width: 591px;height: 292.964px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="591" height="292.964"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/HOOKUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>HOOK/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Hooked Protocol</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hook-price-defies-gravity-as-hooked-protocol-activity-rises/">HOOK price defies gravity as Hooked Protocol activity rises</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hook-price-defies-gravity-as-hooked-protocol-activity-rises/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price predictions: Bitcoin, Cardano, Binance Coin</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-bitcoin-cardano-binance-coin/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-bitcoin-cardano-binance-coin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-bitcoin-cardano-binance-coin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto prices remained in a consolidation phase this week as concerns about FTX contagion continued. They also reacted to the latest interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve and the arrest of Sam Bankman-Fried. Here are some of the top crypto price predictions for the weekend. Bitcoin price prediction Bitcoin pulled back sharply after the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-bitcoin-cardano-binance-coin/">Crypto price predictions: Bitcoin, Cardano, Binance Coin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Crypto prices remained in a consolidation phase this week as concerns about <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-collapse-hearing-kevin-oleary-says-binance-caused-the-ftx-implosion/"><u>FTX contagion</u></a> continued. They also reacted to the latest interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve and the arrest of Sam Bankman-Fried. Here are some of the top crypto price predictions for the weekend.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> pulled back sharply after the latest interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve. This decline correlated with the performance of American indices like the Dow Jones and the Nasdaq 100 indices.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price dropped to a low of $16,923, which was the lowest level since December 12. It also declined below the important level at $17,395, which was the neckline of the inverted head and shoulders pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has also pulled back below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved below the neutral level of 50. Therefore, Bitcoin price will likely continue falling as contagion fears continue.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If this happens, the next key level to watch will be at $16,000. In the near term, however, a bullish breakout to $18,000 cannot be ruled out as the shakeup eases.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/16/1671192616228-51d996a5-113c-4ef4-98fd-ed36c832029b.png" style="width: 595px;height: 295.517px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="595" height="295.517"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=BITSTAMP"><u>BTC/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTc2MzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTc2MzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance Coin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Coin price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few days. It collapsed to the lowest level since November this year. This decline accelerated this week as Bitcoin FUD trended in Twitter and other social media platforms like Reddit. FUD stands for Fear, Uncertainty, and Doubt.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Concerns about Binance continued after the arrest of Sam Bankman-Fried, which we wrote about in this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-a-mountain-of-red-flags/"><u>article</u></a><strong>.&nbsp;</strong>Investors are worried about the significant information that we still don&rsquo;t know about Binance. For one, it is unclear how much money Binance makes and how much debt it has.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, like Bitcoin, the BNB price will likely continue falling as sellers target the psychological level of $200.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/16/1671192616071-e50f15cf-74ac-462e-b414-5007bae2d1ee.png" style="width: 469px;height: 232.937px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="469" height="232.937"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BNBUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>BNB/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy BNB</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTc2MzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTc2MzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BNB with Binance today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Cardano price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Cardano price plunged on Friday as concerns about the hawkish Fed continued. It has also fallen because of the underperformance of its DeFi and NFT ecosystem. NFT volume crashed to just $8 million in November, its lowest level in months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano"><u>Cardano</u></a> remains below all moving averages. It also crashed below the important support level at $0.300, the lowest level on December 13. The Relative Strength Index has moved to the oversold level. Cardano price will likely continue falling as sellers target the next key support at $0.2500.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/16/1671192616243-1cd07e3e-efd8-4522-b854-576700dc4706.png" style="width: 583px;height: 289.557px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="583" height="289.557"></p>
<p dir="ltr" style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/ADAUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>ADA/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Cardano</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTc2MzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTc2MzI&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=IA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ADA with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-bitcoin-cardano-binance-coin/">Crypto price predictions: Bitcoin, Cardano, Binance Coin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-bitcoin-cardano-binance-coin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We can meet 100% of withdrawals, says Binance&#8217;s Changpeng Zhao</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/we-can-meet-100-of-withdrawals-says-binances-changpeng-zhao/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/we-can-meet-100-of-withdrawals-says-binances-changpeng-zhao/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 11:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/we-can-meet-100-of-withdrawals-says-binances-changpeng-zhao/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CZ dismisses concerns over whether Binance could handle a $2.1 billion withdrawal. The CEO confirmed that the crypto exchange could meet 100% of withdrawals on its platform. Binance has very solid revenue, CZ added. Binance can meet withdrawals on its platform Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO of Binance,&#160;told CNBC in a recent interview that the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/we-can-meet-100-of-withdrawals-says-binances-changpeng-zhao/">We can meet 100% of withdrawals, says Binance&#8217;s Changpeng Zhao</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">CZ dismisses concerns over whether Binance could handle a $2.1 billion withdrawal.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The CEO confirmed that the crypto exchange could meet 100% of withdrawals on its platform.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance has very solid revenue, CZ added.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance can meet withdrawals on its platform</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO of Binance,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/15/binance-ceo-changpeng-cz-zhao-brushes-off-2-billion-ftx-clawback-concerns-fraud.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>told CNBC</u></a> in a recent interview that the cryptocurrency exchange has what it takes to meet 100% of its withdrawals.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a> is the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency exchange and has been in the spotlight recently, following the collapse of FTX.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">When asked if Binance can withstand a $2.1 billion request on its platform, CZ said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;People can withdraw 100% of the assets they have on Binance; we will not have an issue on any given day. Binance doesn&rsquo;t operate on a fractional banking system.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">He added that cryptocurrency businesses should hold user assets 1-to-1, and that is what Binance does.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CNBC quoted the US bankruptcy code, which states that if bankruptcy proceedings can establish that a payment was carried out via proceedings of fraud or that an individual should have reasonably known that a payment was fraudulent, any beneficiary in a two-year lookback window can have their gains clawed back by the trustee.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">When asked if Binance is prepared to send that money to them, CZ replied that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;I think we&rsquo;ll leave that to the lawyers. I think our legal team is perfectly capable of handling it. &ldquo;We have very solid revenue.</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Kevin O&rsquo;Leary blames Binance for FTX&rsquo;s crash</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a recent hearing by the House Finance Committee, Kevin O&rsquo;Leary&nbsp;<a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/former-ftx-spokesman-kevin-oleary-believes-binance-put-ftx-out-business-intentionally" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>accused Binance</u></a> of intentionally crippling FTX. O&rsquo;Leary was a former spokesperson for the now-defunct FTX exchange. He said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Now, maybe there&rsquo;s nothing wrong with that &ndash; maybe there&rsquo;s nothing wrong with love and war. But Binance is a massive, unregulated global monopoly now. They put FTX out of business &ndash; now, lots of other reasons, I&rsquo;m sure. But that&rsquo;s my personal opinion.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this week, blockchain analytics provider CryptoQuant revealed that it had&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptoquant-confirms-binance-reserves-are-accounted-for/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>verified Binance&rsquo;s proof of reserve</u></a> in its recently released audit report after it analysed the recently released proof-of-reserves by Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The report put to bed the FUD storm that has been circulating following the recent surge in withdrawals.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/we-can-meet-100-of-withdrawals-says-binances-changpeng-zhao/">We can meet 100% of withdrawals, says Binance&#8217;s Changpeng Zhao</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/we-can-meet-100-of-withdrawals-says-binances-changpeng-zhao/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
