<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:29:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ducati announces NFT debut on XRP Ledger</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ducati will debut its digital collectibles on the XRP Ledger. The Bologna-based motorcycle company will work with NFT PRO on this project. XRP Ledger is a decentralised public blockchain that uses XRP as its native cryptocurrency. Ducati, a Bologna-based motorcycle manufacturer, is making a foray into Web3 with an upcoming launch of a digital collectible [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/">Ducati announces NFT debut on XRP Ledger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ducati will debut its digital collectibles on the XRP Ledger.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The Bologna-based motorcycle company will work with NFT PRO on this project.</li>
<li dir="ltr">XRP Ledger is a decentralised public blockchain that uses XRP as its native cryptocurrency.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Ducati, a Bologna-based motorcycle manufacturer, is making a foray into Web3 with an upcoming launch of a digital collectible project.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company said in an <a href="https://www.ducati.com/ww/en/news/ducati-announces-its-entry-into-the-world-of-web-3-0-in-partnership-with-nft-pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> on Tuesday that it will deploy its new NFT collection on the XRP Ledger, a decentralised public blockchain network. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ripple/">Ripple</a> is a contributor on the XRPL.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ducati makes entry into Web3</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ducati has partnered with NFT PRO, a corporate white-label NFT solution, to bring the project to life. According to the company, the digital collectibles project its digital strategy as it looks to add to the engagement and experiences of its fans. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Entering WEB 3.0 is another way to get closer to the Ducatisti community by further extending the number of services offered to them. It also represents an opportunity to meet and make ourselves known to a new community of NFT enthusiasts, giving them the opportunity to live unique Ducati-style experiences and collect the digital assets that we will develop exclusively for this new dimension of the brand</em>,&rdquo; Claudio Domenicali, Ducati CEO, said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bike company says it will release more details in coming months as it rolls out new digital services and goods.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple&rsquo;s <em>XRP Markets Report</em> <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q1-2023-xrp-markets-report/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> in April indicated that the XRP Ledger logged increased activity in the first quarter compared to the previous three month period. In terms of on-chain activity, the company noted a 9% increase in transactions from 106 million to 116 million between Q4, 2022 and Q1, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">NFTs are a key component of the XRPL activities, as it has seen users mint more than 1 million assets. DEX volumes, which jumped 34% in the period covered in the report, also demonstrated the increased usage of the blockchain network, Ripple said.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/">Ducati announces NFT debut on XRP Ledger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ducati-announces-nft-debut-on-xrp-ledger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venom blockchain surpasses one million registered wallets in three months</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The Venom blockchain has reached one million registered wallets within three months. The Venom Foundation is focused on making the adoption of blockchain technology mainstream. The Venom Foundation announced on Tuesday, July 25th, that its blockchain has surpassed one million registered wallets. This latest milestone was achieved within three months. The Venom testnet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/">Venom blockchain surpasses one million registered wallets in three months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Venom blockchain has reached one million registered wallets within three months.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation is focused on making the adoption of blockchain technology mainstream.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation announced on Tuesday, July 25th, that its blockchain has surpassed one million registered wallets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest milestone was achieved within three months. The Venom testnet took place on April 26th, and the team achieved the milestone on July 25th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, the Venom Foundation added that the substantial growth signifies the accelerating popularity and adoption of Venom&rsquo;s various blockchain solutions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The foundation further added that Venom&rsquo;s rapid growth can be attributed to its innovative technology, rigorous regulatory compliance, and secure, user-friendly environment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Smooth operations and regular updates on the&nbsp;<a href="https://venom.network/" rel="nofollow"><u>Venom testnet</u></a> also help to strengthen the blockchain&rsquo;s appeal, helping to attract and retain users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last month, Venom achieved some exciting milestones. Some of the blockchain&rsquo;s achievements last month include;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">277 million transactions, a significant increase of 46% from the previous month.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">A 65% increase in the number of accounts with smart contracts, which now stand at 28 million.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">A 93% surge in minted NFTs, with more than 5.8 million NFTs minted on the blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Venom wants to take blockchain adoption mainstream</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation said it is focused on making the adoption of blockchain technology mainstream while adhering to regulatory compliance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Christopher Louis Tsu, acting CTO and CEO of Venom Foundation, stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Frankly speaking, it took me completely by surprise. We had 250,000 users in the first six days. Can you imagine opening a new shop in town, drawing the curtains back and seeing a quarter of a million people lined up outside your door&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">In May, the Venom Foundation entered into a&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-strategic-partnership-with-the-government-of-kenya/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>strategic partnership</u></a> with the Kenyan government. The partnership will see the two entities work together to establish a &ldquo;blockchain hub&rdquo; in Africa, focusing on the development of Web3 and blockchain technology applications.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Venom Foundation provides scalable blockchain solutions for real-world applications, delivering performance and security.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/">Venom blockchain surpasses one million registered wallets in three months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-blockchain-surpasses-one-million-registered-wallets-in-three-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xandeum, the L1 with Scalable Storage Layer, Announces Grand Launch on July 30</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 13:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147508</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Las Vegas, Nevada, July 25th, 2023, Chainwire Xandeum, a trailblazing blockchain startup committed to accelerating humanity&#8217;s transition to decentralized control, announces its highly anticipated launch on July 30, 2023, at 11:00 am PT. Leveraging the power of blockchain technology, Xandeum&#8217;s mission is to empower collective self-determination by creating a scalable, blockchain-based storage layer for smart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/">Xandeum, the L1 with Scalable Storage Layer, Announces Grand Launch on July 30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Las Vegas, Nevada, July 25th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://xandeum.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xandeum</a>, a trailblazing blockchain startup committed to accelerating humanity&rsquo;s transition to decentralized control, announces its highly anticipated launch on July 30, 2023, at 11:00 am PT.</p>
<p>Leveraging the power of blockchain technology, Xandeum&rsquo;s mission is to empower collective self-determination by creating a scalable, blockchain-based storage layer for smart contracts, which adds a new dimension to the decentralized web. Named External Global Grouped Storage (EGGS), this solution pioneers a new era of storage-enabled Web3 apps (sedApps) on Xandeum.</p>
<p>In a departure from the traditional model of seeking venture capital, Xandeum prioritizes community control by selling node licenses directly to its users. The grand launch will introduce an incentivized purchase model, creating a buzz for this revolutionary blockchain project.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Xandeum is all about transforming the world of blockchain,&rdquo; said Bernie Blume, founder of Xandeum. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re not just creating another blockchain; we&rsquo;re creating a holistic platform that integrates advanced blockchain technology with a revolutionary storage solution, paving the way for fully-fledged, storage-enabled Web3 apps.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>The grand launch introduces an attractive purchase model: the first transaction to purchase a node will receive a generous 50% rebate, the second 49%, the third 48%, and so on until the 50th transaction, which will still secure a 1% rebate.</p>
<p>This follows Xandeum&rsquo;s track record of success, already having sold over 2,809 nodes for proceeds surpassing $1.9 million under the prior brand name Bitoku. By opening the market to its community, Xandeum aims to foster further expansion and innovation.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Our community just loves to embark on this journey so early, at least 4 to 5 months ahead of the ICO, in order to reap the maximum benefits.&rdquo; notes Blume.</p></blockquote>
<p>Post-launch, Xandeum will roll out an incentivized Devnet on August 15, followed by a Testnet in the fall, an ICO of the XAND token in November and a beta version of the mainnet scheduled for 2024.</p>
<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Join us in this exciting journey. Visit our website, explore the lightpaper and the RFC version of our technical whitepaper, check out the roadmap, and prepare to participate in our grand launch,&rdquo; urged Blume.</p></blockquote>
<p>Users are invited to join the blockchain revolution at xandeum.com and prepare for the Grand Launch. <a href="https://xandeum.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xandeum.com</a> is set to take blockchain technology to the next level.</p>
<h3>About Xandeum</h3>
<p><a href="https://xandeum.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Xandeum</a> is a blockchain startup aimed at advancing blockchain technology. With projects like the development of the Xandeum blockchain, the integration of the Move language, and building the EGGS storage layer for smart contracts, Xandeum is pushing the boundaries of decentralized control and collective self-determination.</p>
<p>For more information: <a href="https://xandeum.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Official Website</a> | <a href="https://discord.com/channels/943357342626496592/943357343578595391" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/XandeumLabs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>CEO, Bernie Blume, Xandeum Labs, bernieb@xandeum.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/">Xandeum, the L1 with Scalable Storage Layer, Announces Grand Launch on July 30</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xandeum-the-l1-with-scalable-storage-layer-announces-grand-launch-on-july-30/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top meme coin pumps on X speculation: Does this impact Shiba Memu?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin price rallied to above $0.076 on Tuesday, a day after Elon Musk&#8217;s Twitter rebranded to X. Shiba Memu (SHMU) presale on the other hand has seen $1.14 million raised so far amid huge interest in meme tokens. The launch of the Shiba Memu&#8217;s AI dashboard could have a significant impact on the token&#8217;s performance. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/">Top meme coin pumps on X speculation: Does this impact Shiba Memu?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Dogecoin price rallied to above $0.076 on Tuesday, a day after Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter rebranded to X.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHMU) presale on the other hand has seen $1.14 million raised so far amid huge interest in meme tokens.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The launch of the Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI dashboard could have a significant impact on the token&rsquo;s performance.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale is on fire with nearly 40 million SHMU sold and over $1.14 million raised within weeks of the revolutionary meme project&rsquo;s token sale launch.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, meme coins have added more than $730 million to their total market cap in the past 24 hours, with most of that down to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a>&rsquo;s latest pump.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Elon Musk&rsquo;s X Payments could add Dogecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">DOGE price rose to highs of $0.078 early Tuesday after a spike in positivity since Monday, primarily injected by Twitter&rsquo;s rebranding to X. More than that, the speculation that X could incorporate DOGE in its payment feature sees Dogecoin price on the verge of what could be a mega upside leg.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elon Musk hinted at the possibility of DOGE becoming a payment currency on the rebranded X platform when he put the meme coin&rsquo;s symbol next to the X logo in his bio on Monday. That action fuelled speculation that the cryptocurrency could soon be part of the &ldquo;everything app&rdquo; that Musk and team envision for X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision <a href="https://twitter.com/RaoulGMI/status/1683618358380429312" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">believes</a> this is a possibility even as he sees AI playing a big role in X&rsquo;s future developments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Two things I&rsquo;ve said when Elon bought &ldquo;X&rdquo;: &nbsp;Elon bought it for the AI, and the free speech angle is to give it an unbiased model. He needs the AI to train the Optimus robot. He will use crypto to be able to make global payments for creators etc. My guess is he uses Doge</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What makes Shiba Memu different from Dogecoin?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">What sets Shiba Memu apart from Dogecoin and other meme coins is that it integrates blockchain technology and artificial intelligence to create an autonomous marketing powerhouse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While most meme coin ecosystems, including Dogecoin, rely on market hype for traction, Shiba Memu is taking the game a notch higher by making this entirely AI-driven.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Its AI technology works via robotastic dashboard &ndash; the marketing genius behind this project and one that could catapult the project above rivals in terms of community traction and adoption. Two narratives likely to put Shiba Memu on top is the increased adoption of crypto and the emergence of AI as a strong narrative.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the Shiba Memu <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">presale page</a> to learn more.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dogecoin price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Musk could go for any other coin when he eventually integrates crypto into X Payments, much of the global speculation is that DOGE sits at the top of the list.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If this happens, we could see the price of Dogecoin could skyrocket. The same happens in 2021 when Tesla announced it would accept DOGE as payment method for car purchases. Dogecoin hit its ATH of $0.73 in May 2021, rallying from lows of $0.009 in January for a staggering 362x gain in four months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2023, Dogecoin has fluctuated between $0.10 and $0.06 and currently hovers below $0.08.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although the immediate target remains the elusive $0.1, bulls are likely to see the all-time high of $0.73 as the barrier that will need to be broken if DOGE has to hit $1. A move by Elon Musk&rsquo;s X could catalyse such a breakout.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Does Dogecoin price impact Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin is the top meme coin by market capitalization, and also the most popular one today thanks to its status as the original meme token. The native DOGE&rsquo;s rally in 2021 and on multiple occasions whenever Musk tweets about it has seen other meme coins pick up some upward momentum.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In fact, it is this scenario that has seen several dog-inspired tokens spawned, particularly in 2023. The likes of PEPE and FLOKI have as a result gained massive traction and are competing to take a chunk of the DOGE market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is no different and its trajectory could follow the popular meme tokens&rsquo; recent spectacular price gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHMU will be priced at $0.0244 at the end of its 8-week presale. Per the roadmap, the AI dashboard will go live in Q1, 2024 and SHMU will list on exchanges in Q3 that year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Shiba Memu price might not mirror DOGE&rsquo;s 2021 explosion, the meme project&rsquo;s unique model has the potential to fuel a enourmous price rally.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Do you want to join the presale? <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Click here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/">Top meme coin pumps on X speculation: Does this impact Shiba Memu?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/top-meme-coin-pumps-on-x-speculation-does-this-impact-shiba-memu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gnosis price outlook after the 7 days plunge: is Chancer a better option?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Gnosis (GNO) token has lost 22.5% in the past year. While some predict that GNO has hit the bottom, it has dropped by 2.5% in the past seven days. As Gnosis drops, a new decentralized prediction market token called CHANCER is gaining traction. The decentralized prediction markets have been an industry that has seen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/">Gnosis price outlook after the 7 days plunge: is Chancer a better option?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The Gnosis (GNO) token has lost 22.5% in the past year.</li>
<li>While some predict that GNO has hit the bottom, it has dropped by 2.5% in the past seven days.</li>
<li>As Gnosis drops, a new decentralized prediction market token called CHANCER is gaining traction.</li>
</ul>
<p>The decentralized prediction markets have been an industry that has seen some tremendous growth in the recent following the increasing decentralized betting platforms. Gnosis was among the first decentralized prediction market to be developed on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum blockchain</a> and it cleared the way for many more such platforms.</p>
<p>Despite the Gnosis platform being famous, its native token has witnessed a long bear market that has lasted for about a year now. On the contrary, the tokens of other decentralized market platforms like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/augur/what-is-augur/">Augur (REP)</a> and Stox (STX) have enjoyed rapid price surges in the past week.</p>
<h2>Gnosis (GNO) price prediction</h2>
<p>Gnosis (GNO) technical analysis shows that its continuous bearish trend has been accompanied by significant price volatility. However, it currently has a sideways trend signalling a possible short-term price rise in the near future.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/gnosis/">GNO price</a> has continuously traded within the range of $95 to $124 in the last three months.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/25/1690281709035-6f8003ff-dbb5-4b2d-a6f7-488da729dedf.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="295"><span class="fr-inner" style="background: transparent;position: relative"><em>Gnosis price chart. Source: </em><a href="https://www.geckoterminal.com/eth/pools/0xf56d08221b5942c428acc5de8f78489a97fc5599?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=coingecko&amp;utm_campaign=livechart-btn"><em>Coingecko terminal</em></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">It recently bounced back downwards after hitting the resistance at $124.19 and it is fast approaching the pivot point level at $113.11. If it goes below the pivot point, it could drop towards the next support level at $107 or further down to $96.</p>
</div>
<h2>Does Chancer offer a better investment opportunity?</h2>
<p>Chancer is a cutting-edge Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform that features live streaming. It emphasizes transparency among the many betting platforms available worldwide.</p>
<p>The goal of the Chancer platform is to give users the ability to create and customize P2P betting markets in real time based on their interests, knowledge, and social media connections.</p>
<p>Through a decentralized platform, Chancer enables users to create their own unique P2P betting markets without being restricted by what bookmakers offer and their odds.</p>
<p>Chancer is an intriguing project because it allows for wagering on events other than sports or popular ones. Users of Chancer can wager on virtually anything in addition to sporting events like football games, such as the day that a person will set foot on Mars, as well as make private bets with their friends to see if they can complete a task with predetermined requirements.</p>
<p>The CHANCER token will power the ecosystem and the success of the Chancer platform and the markets it supports may depend heavily on token holders. Holders can create markets with the tokens, which also gives them the chance to invest in markets established by other users. If interested, you can purchase the CHANCER token <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>
<p>Investors are flocking to the new Chancer decentralized prediction markets project, as Gnosis (GNO) token, which has long been a leader among the decentralized prediction markets tokens, struggles with a long bear market.</p>
<p>Just like Gnosis, Chancer offers a decentralized prediction market allowing users to create markets where they can speculate on any event or arbitrary outcome.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/">Gnosis price outlook after the 7 days plunge: is Chancer a better option?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/gnosis-price-outlook-after-the-7-days-plunge-is-chancer-a-better-option/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin up 4% as X payments speculations return</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways DOGE is outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies, up by 4% in the last 24 hours. The positive performance comes as speculations return that DOGE could become a payment option on X (Twitter). DOGE outperforms the broader market DOGE, the native coin of the Dogecoin ecosystem, is the best performer amongst the top 10 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/">Dogecoin up 4% as X payments speculations return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">DOGE is outperforming the other major cryptocurrencies, up by 4% in the last 24 hours.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The positive performance comes as speculations return that DOGE could become a payment option on X (Twitter).</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOGE outperforms the broader market</h2>
<p dir="ltr">DOGE, the native coin of the Dogecoin ecosystem, is the best performer amongst the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market cap today. The coin has added 4% to its value in the last 24 hours, outperforming Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Dogecoin</u></a> stands at $0.0771. The positive performance comes as speculations returned that DOGE could be used for payments on Twitter, which was rebranded to X by Elon Musk earlier this week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Market analysts believe that DOGE&rsquo;s price could soar higher thanks to this speculation. Kryptomon Chief Marketing Officer Tomer Nuni told CoinDesk that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;The speculation is that advertisers could be able to pay DOGE for ads and for other uses on Twitter. We saw the same happening when Tesla revealed the ability to pay for its goods with DOGE. So the speculation could be around Musk&rsquo;s businesses and stakeholdings starting to accept crypto, as Tesla does.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin is currently the seventh-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, behind Circle&rsquo;s USDC stablecoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Twitter is reportedly designing a system that would allow users to make payments via the social media platform. However, Elon Musk wants fiat currencies to be supported before Twitter will include cryptocurrencies as payment options.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin drops to the $29k level</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Dogecoin was rallying, Bitcoin was tanking. Bitcoin is down by more than 2% in the last 24 hours, briefly dropping below the $29k level late on Monday.</p>
<p>At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $29,255. The poor performance came following the Wall Street Journal&rsquo;s report on Monday, alleging possible wash trading activities by the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/">Dogecoin up 4% as X payments speculations return</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-up-4-as-x-payments-speculations-return/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity is bullish on Ethereum for the long term</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-is-bullish-on-ethereum-for-the-long-term/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity likes Ethereum as burn rate now exceeds issuance. ETH continues to be the largest holding in investors&#8217; portfolios. Ether is currently up more than 50% versus the start of the year. Ethereum is already up more than 50% for the year at writing but Fidelity Digital Assets still remains bullish on the premier altcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-is-bullish-on-ethereum-for-the-long-term/">Fidelity is bullish on Ethereum for the long term</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Fidelity likes Ethereum as burn rate now exceeds issuance.</li>
<li>ETH continues to be the largest holding in investors&rsquo; portfolios.</li>
<li>Ether is currently up more than 50% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> is already up more than 50% for the year at writing but Fidelity Digital Assets still remains bullish on the premier altcoin for the long term.</p>
<h2>Why does Fidelity like Ethereum?</h2>
<p>The crypto platform that caters to institutional investors is constructive on Ether primarily because its burn rate now exceeds issuance.</p>
<p>Since the &ldquo;Merge&rdquo;, the net supply has declined by more than 700,000 coins, as per the firm&rsquo;s recently published <a href="https://www.fidelitydigitalassets.com/sites/default/files/documents/1096171.1.0%20Fidelity%20Digital%20Assets%20-%20Q2%20Signals%20Report.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q2 2023 Signals Report</a>.</p>
<p>Fidelity also drives optimism from an increase in active Ethereum validators of 15% in the second quarter. The excitement around EIP-1153 update that promises lower costs and better efficiency will help unlock further upside in ETH, the firm added.</p>
<p>&ldquo;New Address Momentum&rdquo; was among other reasons cited for the positive long-term view on Ether.</p>
<h2>Could ETH ever be bigger than BTC?</h2>
<p>Separately, a recent CryptoVantage survey suggested about 46% of Americans expect Ether to eventually surpass Bitcoin in market capitalisation. The said study saw participation from 1,000 Americans who have had exposure to cryptocurrencies as an investment over the past five years.</p>
<p>Recent data from <a href="https://coinshares.com/research/digital-asset-quarterly-fund-manager-survey-jul-23" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinshares</a> was green as well. In a report over the weekend, the asset manager confirmed that Ethereum continues to be the largest holding in investors&rsquo; portfolios even though it has underperformed Bitcoin this year.</p>
<p>Note that ETH could benefit as the U.S. Federal Reserve signals a pivot as well. That&rsquo;s because a lenient monetary policy tends to boost interest in the risk-on assets. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-price-prediction-fed-and-options-expiry-in-focus/">Ethereum</a>, though, has been trending down in recent sessions, though, ahead of the central bank&rsquo;s announcement on Wednesday.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-is-bullish-on-ethereum-for-the-long-term/">Fidelity is bullish on Ethereum for the long term</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price outlook: BNB, Dogecoin</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 19:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies traded largely lower today, with Bitcoin dipping to below $29k. BNB moved above XRP although bulls need to keep prices above $330 to keep bears at bay, otherwise it could dump to $220 or lower. Dogecoin spiked as Twitter rebranded to X. Can DOGE go higher? Crypto news today has been dominated by headlines [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/">Crypto price outlook: BNB, Dogecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies traded largely lower today, with Bitcoin dipping to below $29k.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BNB moved above XRP although bulls need to keep prices above $330 to keep bears at bay, otherwise it could dump to $220 or lower.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Dogecoin spiked as Twitter rebranded to X. Can DOGE go higher?</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/">Crypto news</a> today has been dominated by headlines around the launch of Worldcoin (WLD) token and Elon Musk&rsquo;s Twitter rebrand to X. Meanwhile, the broader crypto market has continued to see a slump for major altcoins, with Bitcoin hovering just above $29k following further weakness on Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While analysts have outlined a potential upward flip after recent consolidation, regulatory uncertainty remains a big negative trigger. Also key this week could be the overall investor reaction to the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s policy decision after their two-day meeting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, with these factors in perspective, what&rsquo;s the price outlook for BNB and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB price outlook: $330 key support level</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/">BNB</a>, the native coin of the Binance ecosystem, has overtaken XRP as the fourth largest crypto asset by market cap after the Ripple token slumped 6% on Monday. However, BNB price is also down (currently 2%) and trades below its 20-day EMA.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/24/1690227074192-e128df51-81e8-4c51-a345-0710534d9dc7.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="320"><span class="fr-inner">BNB price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/UYrbhYPP/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">While support is likely at $230, a dip below this buffer could allow bears to target a retest of areas below the lower trendline of the symmetrical triangle.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">It&rsquo;s a scenario that could see BNB price such for fresh footing around $220, an area that provided a breather in June this year and in December 2022.</p>
</div>
<h2 dir="ltr">DOGE price outlook: Another push related to X?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dogecoin (DOGE) price was an outlier of sorts today in the crypto markets. While all major altcoins dipped, the OG meme coin spiked by 10% to break above $0.075.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As Elon Musk revealed Twitter&rsquo;s rebranding to X, he put the DOGE symbol next to the X logo.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$DOGE</a> up almost 10% as Elon Musk adds Doge logo to his profile location <a href="https://t.co/vDYn4KPzq3">pic.twitter.com/vDYn4KPzq3</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dan Gambardello (@cryptorecruitr) <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptorecruitr/status/1683476882518360066?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Bulls took cue to push the coin higher and have succeeded in keeping it above the 20-day and 50-day EMA.&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/24/1690227169352-5994b171-44aa-49ad-ba07-700f8fe8c4f0.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="287"><span class="fr-inner">Dogecoin price chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/PGjgAHuA/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">The moving averages could offer a key demand reload zone should DOGE flip lower. However, the daily RSI is trending upwards but not yet overextended into the overbought territory.</p>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">This suggests potential upside moves are still likely, particularly in relation to news around DOGE adoption on X.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If bulls push higher, the area around $0.08 will be a key barrier that would need a convincing retest. &nbsp;$0.09 and $0.11 could be the next bull targets. On the downside, a breakout below $0.07 could risk a dump to $0.057.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-outlook-bnb-dogecoin/">Crypto price outlook: BNB, Dogecoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Caldera brings decentralized sequencing to OP stack with Espresso</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Caldera developers can leverage Espresso Sequencer for greater scaling and decentralisation. The rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform recently partnered with Manta Network and SupraOracles. Caldera, a rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform, and blockchain infrastructure company Espresso Systems have announced a partnership that will see them work together towards enabling decentralized sequencing to the OP stack and Caldera chains. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/">Caldera brings decentralized sequencing to OP stack with Espresso</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Caldera developers can leverage Espresso Sequencer for greater scaling and decentralisation.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform recently partnered with Manta Network and SupraOracles.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Caldera, a rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform, and blockchain infrastructure company Espresso Systems have <a href="https://blog.caldera.xyz/caldera-partners-with-espresso-to-bring-decentralized-sequencing-to-the-op-stack/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> a partnership that will see them work together towards enabling decentralized sequencing to the OP stack and Caldera chains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The integration will also be key in allowing Caldera layer 2s to tap into the Espresso Sequencer to improve on scalability and interoperability.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Decentralized sequencing is coming to Caldera!</p>
<p>We're partnering with <a href="https://twitter.com/EspressoSys?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@EspressoSys</a> to make it easy for teams to use the Espresso Sequencer as a plug-in component of our modular rollup stack on their Caldera chains!</p>
<p>Let's dive into the details &#129525; <a href="https://t.co/Ib6qt3ubn1">pic.twitter.com/Ib6qt3ubn1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Caldera (@Calderaxyz) <a href="https://twitter.com/Calderaxyz/status/1683508651263410180?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Caldera eyes greater scaling and decentralization</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sequencers are the nodes tasked with aggregating and ordering transactions as well as executing these transactions on the virtual machine. They are like validators in an L1 network ecosystem and thus crucial to the transaction process of a rollup network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Layer 2 rollups that offer a scaling solution for <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> have one limitation &ndash; they rely on centralized sequencers that can be impacted by risks such as unreliability and censorship. The Espresso Sequencer offers the utility that not only allows for greater decentralization, but also high throughput, low latency transaction ordering and interoperability. This will help developers on Caldera, the team noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Through this partnership, developers building with Caldera will be able to deploy performant app-specific rollups that utilize the Espresso Sequencer for ordering and fast confirmations, bringing another layer of customizability to our modular stack that should enable teams to build their dream applications without compromises!</em>&rdquo; they wrote.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Developer teams will have the option of easily opting into the Espresso Sequencer, with this designed as a plug-in component of Caldera&rsquo;s modular rollup stack.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership with Espresso Systems comes a few days after Caldera partnered with Web3 privacy hub Manta Network. The platforms are collaborating on a project that targets an L2 EVM execution layer for zero-knowledge applications.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this month, Caldera integrated blockchain oracles service SupraOracles to bring price feeds and VRF to Caldera.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/">Caldera brings decentralized sequencing to OP stack with Espresso</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/caldera-brings-decentralized-sequencing-to-op-stack-with-espresso/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
