<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:49:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model y]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261793</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
<p>By reducing prices, Tesla aims to offer a compelling value proposition compared to other electric vehicle options in terms of features, performance, range, and affordability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
<p>American multinational Electric Vehicle (EV) giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has recently announced a price reduction for its Model 3 and Model Y cars in Japan. The company implemented a low single-digit percentage price cut, effective from the beginning of this month.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-cuts-prices-japan-model-100649805.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, Tesla reduced the prices of all variants of its lower-priced Model 3 by approximately 3%, as reflected on its official website. Additionally, the costs of all Model Y variants were reduced by around 4%.</p>
<p>The Tesla&#8217;s move has highlighted that the recent price reduction of the Model 3 in Japan has made it more affordable than ever before, especially when considering various subsidies that can be applied to the purchase. This move is in line with Tesla&#8217;s ongoing efforts to make EVs more accessible to a broader customer base.</p>
<p>Notably, the price cuts come approximately two months after Tesla had previously increased the prices of Model 3 and Model Y prices  Asian nation. With this adjustment, the Model 3 now has a price tag of 5,245,600 Yen ($36,362), while the Model Y is priced at 5,637,000 Yen.</p>
<p>In addition to the price reductions for the Model 3 and Model Y in Japan, it is worth noting that Tesla has maintained the prices of its higher-end electric vehicles, the Model S and Model X. These premium models have retained their existing price points, as Tesla continues to accept orders for them in the Japanese market.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> emphasized during <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-q1-2023-deliveries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla&#8217;s Q1 2023</a> earnings call, that the firm is focused on increasing sales volumes rather than increasing margins. This strategy suggests Tesla&#8217;s commitment to expanding its market presence and capturing a larger share of the electric vehicle market.</p>
<h2>Is Tesla Inc’s Price Cut Influenced by Heightened Competition?</h2>
<p>Tesla Inc&#8217;s unwavering commitment to innovation, technological advancement, global expansion, and customer satisfaction has positioned it as a formidable player in the electric vehicle market. According to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-auto-production-shanghai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reports</a>, Tesla automobiles accounted for over a quarter of total auto production in Shanghai last year.</p>
<p>However, as more traditional automakers and new entrants embrace electrification, the market has become more crowded, prompting Tesla to navigate this landscape strategically. One approach Tesla has considered to maintain its competitive edge is by implementing price reductions.</p>
<p>Notably, heightened competition puts pressure on Tesla to evaluate its pricing strategy. Lowering prices can help Tesla stay ahead of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/byd-tesla-denza-n7-electric-suv/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rivals</a> by making its electric vehicles more attractive to consumers.</p>
<p>By reducing prices, Tesla aims to offer a compelling value proposition compared to other electric vehicle options in terms of features, performance, range, and affordability.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s important to note that Tesla&#8217;s pricing decisions are multifaceted and take into account various factors. Some of these factors vary by region and it includes production efficiency, economies of scale, competition and profitability amongst others.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/">Tesla Slashes Price of Model 3 and Y Electric Vehicles in Japan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dbs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[development bank of singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e-cny]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261760</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
<p>The merchant program ensures automated settlement of e-CNY into businesses' DBS bank accounts.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
<p>Clients of the Development Bank of Singapore (DBS) can now get payments from their customers in e-CNY, electronic Chinese Yuan. The e-CNY is the digital currency of the Chinese central bank, issued by the People&#8217;s Bank of China. The announcement about this was made on Wednesday, July 5.</p>
<p>The merchant program launched by the bank helps businesses receive payments in digital currency while having automated settlement of e-CNY in their DBS bank deposit accounts.</p>
<p>Based on the information from the Development Bank of Singapore, at least one client has transacted using the platform. With this, when a client pays a business using e-CNY, the fund will automatically appear in the business&#8217;s DBS account.</p>
<p>Ginger Cheng, the Chief Executive Officer of DBS Bank (China), <a href="https://www.dbs.com/newsroom/DBS_launches_e_CNY_merchant_collection_solution_for_mainland_businesses_to_receive_CBDC_payments_completes_first_client_transaction" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;We received strong interest from several clients for the solution since its launch, and we are pleased to have completed the first e-CNY collection for a client &#8211; a catering company in Shenzhen. By seamlessly integrating a CBDC collection and settlement method into our clients&#8217; existing payment systems, this will help position their business for a digital future where consumers in China use e-CNY for their daily activities.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>DBS Committed to Making Digital Innovations to Facilitate Payments with e-CNY</h2>
<p>DBS is also engaging in other initiatives in the financial technology space. The bank is participating in Project Guardian, a program launched by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) to see how asset tokenization and decentralized finance (defi) will work with a bank like DBS. The project will explore the potential benefits and the likely challenges banks may face when incorporating these new technologies.</p>
<p>Project Guardian includes institutions like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JP Morgan</a>, Japan&#8217;s SBI Digital, Marketnode, and Temasek. It uses technologies like Aave, Uniswap, and Polygon as part of the infrastructure for testing the DeFi and asset tokenization programs.</p>
<p>In the first phase of Project Guardian testing, transactions were carried out with tokenized versions of the Singapore dollar (SGD), Japanese Yen (JPY), Singapore government securities, and Japanese government bonds.</p>
<p>The bank is also involved in projects surrounding the creation of infrastructure for issuing programmable digital Singapore dollars. The project seeks to determine how to create a digital version of the Singapore dollar that can carry out specific functions based on how it is programmed. This is no doubt related to the goal of creating a more efficient financial service.</p>
<p>Apart from the projects that have been described, DBS has been involved in several other projects. In 2021, it co-founded Partior, a solution for carrying out payments across borders and also easing the global movement of value for banks. It was also a part of Project Orchid, which aimed at creating a structure for issuing programmable digital Singapore dollars.</p>
<p>These developments show that the Development Bank of Singapore is committed to exploring digital innovations to make payments safer and more efficient. These are solid moves toward transforming the future of money.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/">Singapore Bank DBS Launches Merchant Platform Enabling e-CNY Collection</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/singapore-bank-dbs-launches-merchant-platform-enabling-e-cny-collection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
<p>Foxconn expressed optimism about the upcoming third quarter, anticipating a brighter outlook as they approach the peak shopping season at the end of the year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, July 5, Taiwan-based leading iPhone assembler Foxconn announced that its second-quarter (Q2) revenue dropped by 14% on the year-on-year timeline. Foxconn is one of the world&#8217;s largest contract electronics makers.</p>
<h2>Foxconn in Q2</h2>
<p>According to a statement by Foxconn, the company noted a decline in revenue for smart consumer electronics products, including smartphones, in the second quarter compared to the previous year. However, specific details were not provided.</p>
<p>The revenue for the April-June period stood at T$1.3 trillion ($41.76 billion), pretty much in line with the company&#8217;s expectations. For the last month of June 2023, the sales at Foxconn dropped by 19.7% year-on-year. However, the sales numbers stood at T$422.8 billion which makes it the second-highest figure by numbers for the month of June. In a statement recorded by Reuters, the company <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/foxconn-q2-sales-slip-14-q3-outlook-brighter-ahead-year-end-peak-2023-07-05/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the second half of the year peak season currently underway, operations will gradually ramp up. The outlook for the third quarter, which will be better than the second quarter, is expected to increase at an on quarter pace higher than seen in the previous two years. When compared to the pre-pandemic period, the growth rate is expected to be approximately on par.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Foxconn Predicts Robust Sales for Q3</h2>
<p>Traditionally, the first half of the year tends to be slower for tech manufacturers in Taiwan, as major electronics companies like Apple often release new products closer to the year-end holiday season. On August 14, Foxconn is set to report its second-quarter earnings.</p>
<p>In the first quarter, Foxconn experienced a significant decline in net profit, plunging by 56%, which was larger than anticipated. This marked their largest quarterly fall in three years. The decline was attributed to a $565 million write-off associated with their 34% stake in Japanese electronics maker Sharp Corp.</p>
<p>Foxconn expressed optimism about the upcoming third quarter, anticipating a brighter outlook as they approach the peak shopping season at the end of the year. Foxconn <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expects</a> substantial growth in its AI server business driven by strong demand. As people increasingly rely on AI applications like ChatGPT, the need for AI servers is expanding. Foxconn forecasts a three-digit percent increase in the growth of its AI servers in 2023.</p>
<p>While Foxconn shares have seen an 8.6% increase this year, they have not performed as well as the broader Taiwan market, which has risen by 20.1%. On Wednesday, Foxconn shares closed down 1.4%, compared to a 0.5% drop in the broader market.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/">Foxconn Sees 14% Drop in Q2 2023 Sales, Shares Robust Outlook for Q3</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-q2-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grammy awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grammys]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261703</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
<p>The role of AI in music has generated both excitement and debate among artists.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
<p>The Grammy Awards, known for honoring artistic brilliance, are breaking new ground by acknowledging the growing influence of AI-generated music. In a recent <a href="https://apnews.com/article/grammys-ceo-ai-rules-interview-dea135035893deab37719c354f31a889">interview</a> with the Associated Press, Harvey Mason Jr., CEO and President of the Recording Academy, shed light on the Grammy eligibility for AI-generated music.</p>
<p>According to him, if an AI voice model takes on the lead vocals of a track, it may be considered for the songwriting category but not for performance. Mason further explained that the performance aspect, which lacks human creation, does not align with the Academy&#8217;s vision of artistic expression and, therefore, will not be nominated or awarded.</p>
<p>The Academy&#8217;s CEO emphasized that human involvement and meaningful contributions are paramount in Grammy considerations. As long as humans play a crucial role in the creative process, their contributions will always be recognized and eligible for nomination, but not to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AI</a> part.</p>
<p>&#8220;As long as the human is contributing in a more than contributing in a more than a minimis amount, which to us means a meaningful way, they are and will always be considered for a nomination or a win. We don&#8217;t want to see technology replace human creativity. We want to ensure technology enhances, embellishes, or adds to human creativity. That&#8217;s why we took this particular stand in this award cycle,&#8221; Mason told AP in an interview.</p>
<h2>AI-Generated Songs Are Eligible for Nominations</h2>
<p>These clarifications come in response to the Academy&#8217;s revised rules and eligibility criteria announced on June 28. The guidelines were introduced after Paul McCartney revealed that an AI was used to extract John Lennon&#8217;s voice for the &#8220;last Beatles record&#8221;.</p>
<p>The newly updated rules explicitly stated that music without human authorship is ineligible in any Grammy category. However, Mason has clarified that the AI-infused compositions will be considered for nominations at the upcoming 2024 Grammy Awards.</p>
<p>&#8220;AI, or music that contains AI-created elements, is absolutely eligible for entry and for consideration for Grammy nomination. Period,&#8221; Mason said.</p>
<h2>Music Artists Express Concerns about AI-Generated Works</h2>
<p>The role of AI in music has generated both excitement and debate among artists. Grimes, a Canadian musician who has never received a Grammy award before, welcomed the use of AI technology and even offered to share royalties with creators who successfully incorporated her voice into their tracks.</p>
<p>The Canadian-born artist recently launched AI software that allows her fans and music creators around the world to integrate her voice into their music at will without facing any legal repercussions.</p>
<p>Unlike Grimes, Ice Cube has expressed concerns, referring to AI as &#8220;demonic&#8221; and expressing a willingness to take legal action against those imitating their voice on AI tracks and the platforms hosting such songs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/">Grammys Embraces AI-Generated Music, Considers It Eligible for Award Nominations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grammys-ai-generated-music/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[csrc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[didi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fourth paradigm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261728</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
<p>Following acceptance by the CSRC, Fourth Paradigm should proceed with launching its IPO in the Hong Kong market.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
<p>Chinese artificial intelligence (AI) company Fourth Paradigm Technology has completed the process required for an initial public offering (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IPO</a>) in Hong Kong. The company has now received a regulatory green light from the China Securities Regulatory Commission (CSRC).</p>
<p>Fourth Paradigm is one of only a few companies to receive the green light from the CSRC this year after the Commission instituted <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-new-rules-overseas-ipos-march/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">new rules</a> for offshore listings. Introduced in February, the rules became effective from March 31 and provided clarity for companies interested in overseas IPOs. As of June 15, the CSRC had received filings for offshore IPOs from 14 companies and was reportedly waiting for 38 others.</p>
<p>According to the new rules, Fourth Paradigm and other companies looking for foreign IPOs must file with the CSRC first. In addition, each of these companies must receive approval from other regulators. These regulators are now involved in the VIE (variable interest entity) process Chinese companies use to list overseas. Agencies that could potentially be involved in the process include the National Development and Reform Commission and the Cyberspace Administration of China (CAC).</p>
<p>Fourth Paradigm’s IPO nod dissolves some uncertainty surrounding adherence to the new rules and the difficulty of listing abroad. Upon announcing the new rules, the CSRC said that any firm in violation could pay a fine of up to 10 million yuan, about $1.5 million. This fine also applies to any persons or companies who share wrong information.</p>
<h2>China&#8217;s Crackdown on Foreign IPOs</h2>
<p>China has always been particular about offshore listings, although they were much easier. Even before adopting the rules, the CAC &#8211; China’s cybersecurity regulator &#8211; requires firms holding personal data of at least 1 million users to apply for a cybersecurity review before an offshore IPO.</p>
<p>This was why the CAC slammed transport company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/didi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Didi</a> with a $1.19 billion fine last year. Didi reportedly did not complete a cybersecurity review before listing on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE). The CAC also fined Didi founder Cheng Wei and president Jean Liu, 1 million yuan each.</p>
<h2>Fourth Paradigm Filed for the Hong Kong IPO in March</h2>
<p>The current attempt at an IPO is <a href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3218258/chinese-ai-firm-4paradigm-files-hong-kong-ipo-after-three-failed-attempts-citing-us-sanctions-risks" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Fourth Paradigm’s fourth</a> after previous ones failed. Founded in 2014, Fourth Paradigm filed for an IPO in August 2021 and in February 2022, with both attempts expiring for unidentified reasons. The startup filed the fourth attempt in March, only a few days before the third attempt &#8211; filed last September &#8211; was to expire.</p>
<p>Fourth Paradigm was sanctioned by the US and placed on the Commerce Department’s Entity List in March. Companies on this list need a license to buy or access specific goods, services, or technologies. Following its addition to the list, Fourth Paradigm allayed public fears. The company clarified that the inclusion “should not have a material impact on the business or operations of the group”. Fourth Paradigm company also said none of its suppliers, customers, or investors, have withdrawn their commitments to the company.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/">Fourth Paradigm Receives Hong Kong IPO Green Light from Chinese Regulator after Fourth Attempt at Public Listing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fourth-paradigm-hong-kong-ipo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[inflation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lira]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
<p>The Central Bank raised the country's key interest rate from 8.5% to 15% last month.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
<p>Despite the decline of the Turkish Lira following the re-election of President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, Turkey&#8217;s inflation rate is showing signs of recovery.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://data.tuik.gov.tr/Bulten/Index?p=Consumer-Price-Index-June-2023-49658" target="_blank" rel="noopener">data</a> released by the Turkish Statistical Institute, Turkey&#8217;s consumer price index (CPI) rose by 3.92% on a month-on-month basis in June. Additionally, On a year-on-year basis, Turkey&#8217;s inflation rate rose by 38.21%, slightly lower than Reuters&#8217; forecasts of 39.47%.</p>
<p>While still high by global standards, this reading came in lower than the forecasted 4.84% by Reuters and marked a significant tick compared to the 0.04% rise observed in May.</p>
<p>Among the various categories contributing to the CPI growth, tobacco, and alcoholic beverage prices experienced the largest gains, surging by 11.13%. This notable increase in prices for these goods likely influenced the overall CPI reading for the month.</p>
<p>Additionally, prices in the restaurant and hotel sector saw a modest increase of 4.31%, contributing to the overall inflation rate.</p>
<h2>Managing the Economic Crisis in Turkey</h2>
<p>In recent years, Turkey has been grappling with stubbornly high inflation rates, which have adversely affected the purchasing power of its citizens and strained the overall economy. In a previous <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkish-lira-slumps-erdogan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">report</a>, Wells Fargo’s Emerging Markets Economist and FX Strategist Brendan McKenna projected that the Lira could drop as low as 23 against the dollar.</p>
<p>However, the Turkish government has been implementing various measures to combat inflation.</p>
<p>In an effort to address the economic challenges, Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan appointed Mehmet Simsek as the new Treasury and Economy Minister. Simsek, known for his market-friendly policies, is expected to bring stability and implement measures to tackle the economic difficulties in the nation</p>
<p>Additionally, the Central Bank raised the country&#8217;s key interest rate from 8.5% to 15% last month. The apex bank affirmed its commitment to further gradual monetary tightening until the inflation situation improves.</p>
<h2>Turkey&#8217;s Inflation: Analysts Express Their Views</h2>
<p>This unexpected development has caught the attention of economists and analysts, sparking discussions about the factors influencing Turkey&#8217;s inflation dynamics and the implications for the country&#8217;s economic outlook.</p>
<p>Conotoxia&#8217;s Market Analyst Bartosz Sawicki expressed a pessimistic outlook, stating that there is “little reason for optimism.” Sawicki&#8217;s perspective reflects a cautious stance toward Turkey&#8217;s economic situation, despite the recent moderation in inflation rates.</p>
<p>Sawicki noted that the recent freefall of the Turkish Lira is starting to have adverse effects on the economy, reigniting cost pressures. This perspective aligns with the notion that a weakened currency can lead to inflationary pressures, as imported goods become more expensive and businesses face higher production costs.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Timothy Ash, Senior EM Sovereign Strategist at BlueBay Asset Management, acknowledged that the inflation numbers could have been higher given the significant depreciation of the Turkish Lira following the elections.</p>
<p>Additionally, Ash noted the importance of the role of the Central Bank in implementing appropriate policies in order to manage inflation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/">Turkey’s Inflation Recovers despite Decline in Turkish Lira</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/turkey-inflation-recovers-lira/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fsca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261014</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>
<p>Crypto exchanges will be classified as financial service providers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>

<p>With an <a href="https://triple-a.io/crypto-ownership-data/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">estimated</a> 6 million people in South Africa owning cryptocurrencies, South Africa&#8217;s financial regulator has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-04/south-africa-to-require-crypto-exchanges-licensing-by-year-end" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">updated</a> its crypto exchange licensing rules.</p>
<p>Currently, crypto exchanges operating in South Africa do so without any specific legislation guiding their operation. With no rules in place, these exchanges are not subject to any standards regarding customer protection, anti-money laundering, or taxation. </p>
<h2>New Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</h2>
<p>Per the new announcement, all crypto exchanges must obtain licenses from the Financial Sector Conduct Authority (FSCA) by the end of 2023.</p>
<p>To begin with, crypto exchanges will be classified as financial service providers. Consequently, they will be subject to various requirements and obligations under the Financial Advisory and Intermediary Services Act (FAIS Act). To obtain their license, exchanges must implement adequate governance, risk management, and compliance frameworks. They must also provide adequate disclosure and information to customers regarding the risks and benefits of using crypto assets.</p>
<p>Where crypto exchanges fail to comply with the licensing requirements, the new rule empowers the FSCA to impose sanctions and penalties on them. These could include fines, suspension, or revocation of licenses.</p>
<h2>Creating a Balanced and Effective Regulatory Framework</h2>
<p>The FSCA’s announcement is expected to bring more clarity, certainty, and stability to the regulatory environment for crypto exchanges. This could boost investor confidence and attract more capital and innovation to the sector. Likewise, it could improve customer protection and security while reducing illicit activities with crypto assets.</p>
<p>Contrarily, it could affect smaller and newer exchanges that may not be able to meet up with the licensing requirements. It may also limit the ability of exchanges to adapt to the dynamic and evolving nature of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-market-booming-with-bitcoin-solana-collateral-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a>.</p>
<p>Since the goal is to create a balanced and effective regulatory framework, the new rules are far from done. The crypto exchange licensing rule has been opened for public consultation and will also pass through parliamentary approval before they become law. This leaves room for various stakeholders, including crypto exchanges, users, experts, and regulators to add their input.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/">South Africa Updates Crypto Exchange Licensing Rules</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-africa-crypto-exchange-licensing-rules/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[browse with bing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt browse with bing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
<p>The feature was available in a beta version, and while observing it in work, OpenAI learned that Browse with Bing was violating the rights of content owners.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, American artificial intelligence (AI) research laboratory renowned for the invention of the AI chatbot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/#:~:text=ChatGPT%20is%20an%20artificial%20intelligence,advanced%20and%20capable%20language%20models." target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a>, has announced its decision to put a new ChatGPT feature called Browse with Bing on hold. The feature, introduced as beta earlier this year, was enabling ChatGPT users to search the internet to help answer questions that benefit from recent information.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We&#8217;ve learned that ChatGPT&#8217;s &#8220;Browse&#8221; beta can occasionally display content in ways we don&#8217;t want, e.g. if a user specifically asks for a URL&#8217;s full text, it may inadvertently fulfill this request. We are disabling Browse while we fix this—want to do right by content owners.</p>
<p>— OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1676072388436594688?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>How did Browse with Bing work? It was supposed to be an effective integration of ChatGPT with Bing, which would make the flow of information more dynamic and current, leading to a revolution in how humans employ artificial intelligence. Basically, Browse with Bing was an innovative plugin added to ChatGPT Plus that gave AI access to the Internet for real-time information. The feature helped ChatGPT to search using Bing’s search results to provide the most accurate and up-to-date answers to users&#8217; queries. Notably, only those subscribed to ChatGPT Plus membership were able to benefit from the feature.</p>
<p>The feature was available as a beta version, and while observing it in work, OpenAI learned that Browse with Bing was violating the rights of content owners. As OpenAI has explained, users discovered a way to bypass paywalls using the feature. In particular, users could instruct the chatbot to retrieve the full text of articles behind paywalls, getting access the restricted content without subscribing to the respective websites.</p>
<p>One of the hot-discussed cases was a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ChatGPT/comments/14j8q1u/it_looks_like_you_can_use_chatgpt_to_bypass/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">screenshot</a> of a Browse session made by a member of the r/ChatGPT subReddit. The user asked the chatbot to &#8220;print the text&#8221; of a link to a paywalled article from The Atlantic and received it in full without the paywall.</p>
<p>OpenAI did not wait for long to respond.</p>
<p>The company stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As of July 3, 2023, we’ve disabled the Browse with Bing beta feature out of an abundance of caution while we fix this in order to do right by content owners. We are working to bring the beta back as quickly as possible, and appreciate your understanding!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, OpenAI does not exclude resuming the Browse with Bing feature for ChatGPT. Currently, it is working on improving its service and adding other tools that might enhance ChatGPT users&#8217; experience.</p>
<h2 data-hook="post-title">ChatGPT and Copyright Issues</h2>
<p>Being able to create almost unlimited content, ChatGPT gathers publicly-available information from the internet, expanding its own databases and creating its own new answers. However, ownership of the content varies depending on the sources of the training database, the database’s owner, and the degree of similarity between the database and the output generated. Therefore, using ChatGPT-generated output may result in copyright infringement if it contains protected material such as text, images, or audio without proper authorization from the original creator. This is exactly what happened in June when ChatGPT faced a class-action lawsuit in California over allegedly using private user information from the internet. This is also the case with Browse with Bing feature.</p>
<p>The response of OpenAI has been a significant step in the AI industry. It is a prime example of AI companies that should not stay away from making difficult decisions if it has anything to do with content creators&#8217; rights.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/">OpenAI Suspends Bing Integration in ChatGPT to Protect Content Owner Rights</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-bing-integration-chatgpt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[asic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binnace cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261699</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
<p>Binance is facing regulatory challenges in multiple jurisdictions worldwide.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, faces intensified regulatory scrutiny as authorities search its offices in Australia. According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/binance-australia-offices-searched-by-regulator-as-part-of-derivatives-probe" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> on July 5 citing people familiar with the matter, the Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) invaded the company&#8217;s outlets in the country on Tuesday as part of an ongoing investigation into its derivative business.</p>
<p>Recall that Binance Australia <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/asic-binance-crypto-license/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decided</a> to wind down the derivatives exchange in April after ASIC rescinded its regulatory license to operate in the country as a derivative broker while keeping its spot platform operational.</p>
<p>The world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange planned to offer derivative financial instruments to customers in the region through a partnership with Oztures Trading Pty Ltd. However, the plan changed following the license cancellation. ASIC is now investigating the company&#8217;s Australian division, reviewing its classification of retail and wholesale clients, as some users&#8217; positions were closed due to incorrect classification as wholesale investors.</p>
<h2>Binance Cooperating with Local Authorities</h2>
<p>While ASIC neither confirmed nor denied the office searches, a Binance spokesperson disclosed that the company is cooperating with local authorities. Binance emphasized its commitment to meeting the country&#8217;s regulatory standards and serving its Australian users fully compliantly. The company aims to work closely with authorities to address any compliance requirements that may arise during the investigation.</p>
<p>&#8220;We are cooperating with local authorities, and Binance is focused on meeting local regulatory standards in order to serve our users in Australia in a fully compliant manner,&#8221; a spokesperson for Binance Australia told Cointelegraph.</p>
<p>Aside from the ongoing investigation into the Binance derivatives business in Australia, the company had earlier faced regulatory scrutiny from the security regulator. In February, ASIC launched a probe into the company after the exchange abruptly closed certain derivatives positions. Binance explained at the time that its decision was driven by the need to comply with investor classification requirements, resulting in restrictions imposed on users who did not meet the qualifications to be considered wholesale investors.</p>
<h2>Binance Faces Global Regulatory Challenges</h2>
<p>Apart from Australia, Binance is facing regulatory challenges in multiple jurisdictions worldwide. French authorities recently raided the exchange&#8217;s subsidiary in France to investigate the alleged illegal provision of digital-asset services and aggravated money laundering. The company&#8217;s CEO, Changpeng Zhao (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>), however, denied the rumors of money laundering, stating that the exchange is in compliance with all laws in France and other markets of operation.</p>
<p>In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) filed a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO, accusing them of mishandling customer funds, misleading investors and regulators, and violating securities rules. Responding to the civil charges, the company said it plans to defend its platform against the SEC&#8217;s claims vigorously. Binance and Zhao also face a Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) lawsuit.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange has recently been ordered to cease operations in Belgium. The country&#8217;s market regulator, the Financial Services and Markets Authority, asked the company to suspend all its exchange and custody offerings for violating local rules and regulations.</p>
<p>In Belgium, the company&#8217;s application to secure a legal operating license was reportedly rejected due to its inability to meet the country&#8217;s regulatory standards.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/">Binance Australia Offices Raided by Securities Regulator</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-australia-offices-raided/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cac 40]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftse 100]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=261705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
<p>There is a marked reduction in European stocks largely caused by the general apprehensiveness in the global economy.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
<p>Stocks in the European market opened lower on Wednesday as general uncertainty continues to permeate the financial market and global economy. The Stoxx 600 fell 0.44%, as tech and mining stocks plunged by 1%. The market also saw a 0.41% fall in the CAC 40 Index and a 0.42% reduction in the FTSE 100. The DAX recorded the largest plunge, losing 0.53%.</p>
<p>European stocks seem to be responding unfavorably to the situation of the economy across the board. Stocks in China, along with markets in the Asia-Pacific region also fell with the Shenzhen Component dropping 0.91% to 11,029.3. The Shanghai Composite also fell, closing at 3,222.95 after losing 0.69%. Larger plunges were seen in the Hang Seng and Hang Seng Tech indexes, losing 1.6% and 1.5%, respectively.</p>
<p>Across other Asian markets, the Kospi in South Korea closed at 2,579 after losing 0.55%, while Japan’s Nikkei 225 and Topix indexes fell, with the Nikkei 225 losing 0.25.</p>
<p>Markets in the US also reflected the losses elsewhere. Although US markets were closed for Independence Day, stock futures fell. While the Nasdaq 100 futures lost 0.15%, the Dow Jones Industrial Average futures and the S&amp;P 500 fell 0.13% and 0.09%, respectively.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the Nasdaq&#8217;s first half was its <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/04/stock-market-today-live-updates.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">best Q1 in 40 years</a>, since 1983, The S&amp;P also had its best Q1 since 2019, following increased interest in artificial intelligence (AI) stocks. For some, the rise points to more increase in Q2.</p>
<h2>European Stocks React to Global Economy</h2>
<p>The uncertainty in economies across the world is causing ripple effects in European stocks and financial markets. For instance, Oil prices have fallen due to uncertainty with demand. Prices had initially <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/oil-prices-soars-saudi-arabia-oil/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">soared</a> following Russia and Saudi Arabia’s decision to cut output. At the time, Saudi’s decision was criticized by some who feared the move would weaken the oil market. Nonetheless, Saudi Aramco CEO Amin Nasser described oil market fundamentals for 2023 as “generally sound”. Despite the economic downturn in China and India, Nasser believes both countries would drive oil demand growth of over 2 million barrels per day.</p>
<p>Anxiety over the economy in China is also causing some unease for European stocks. According to customs data for May, exports from China fell 7.5% year-on-year (YoY), much higher than the 0.4% predicted by analysts Reuters polled. The same May data further revealed that Chinese exports to the EU dropped 4.9%.</p>
<p>Adding to the bleak forecast on China’s economy is a reduced growth outlook. Investment banking and management giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) reduced its growth outlook for China following troubles with recovering from the COVID-19 pandemic. Goldman Sachs expects China’s 2023 gross domestic product (GDP) to fall from 6% to 5.4%. Furthermore, Goldman Sachs predicts the GDP in 2024 will fall from 4.6% to 4.5%.</p>
<p>In recent times, European stocks have swung noticeably in response to several market events. For instance, these stocks <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opened higher</a> in early June after the US Senate suspended the official debt ceiling. The Stoxx 600 had climbed only a few days after its lowest point in two months.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shares-k-pop-investigation-watchdog/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/">European Stocks Open Lower as Investors Worry about Downturn in Global Economy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-stocks-lower-economy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3976 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1054182 metric#prefetches=194 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=200 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=100.74 metric#ms-cache=4.69 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2346 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.7 -->