<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:28:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UK Neobank Monzo Attains First-Time Monthly Profitability Following Lending Surge</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monzo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monzo bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/">UK Neobank Monzo Attains First-Time Monthly Profitability Following Lending Surge</a></p>
<p>Monzo hit profitability after its lending volume for the period ending February 2023 ballooned to £759.7 million.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/">UK Neobank Monzo Attains First-Time Monthly Profitability Following Lending Surge</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/">UK Neobank Monzo Attains First-Time Monthly Profitability Following Lending Surge</a></p>
<p>British neobank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/monzo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Monzo Bank</a> has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/31/british-digital-bank-monzo-hits-profitability-for-first-time.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revealed</a> it attained monthly profitability for the first time in 2023 following a lending surge. In its annual report for the year ending February 2023, the online bank said it became profitable two months into the year. Monzo said it earned a 382% increase in net interest income which amounted to £164.2 million, driven by a surge in lending activity. Furthermore, the prominent London-based digital bank also realized a net operating income of £214.5 million ($266.1 million) for the year ending February 2023. The positive earnings outcome saw Monzo double its results year-over-year (YoY) from the previous net operating income of £114 million.</p>
<p>Discussing Monzo’s profitability in a media session, chief executive officer TS Anil pointed out:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Profitability was always a choice as we balance continuing to invest in growth with profitability. We could have chosen to be profitable a few quarters ago.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The British online bank’s Chief Financial Officer, James Davies, described it as “a business with diverse and stabilizing revenue”. Davies further said Monzo was primarily helped by its “large, growing, personal and business customer base”.</p>
<p>For the year ending February 2023, Monzo sustained a substantial loss of £116.3 million. However, this deficit was slightly lower than the £119 million net loss reported in the year-ago period.</p>
<h2>Monzo Profitable Run Came amid UK Cost-of-Living Crisis</h2>
<p>Monzo refrained from revealing how much profit it is currently making but said it is on track to attain full-year profitability in 2024. The digital bank benefited from growth in newer income streams during the last period. These include its lending and subscription businesses, which now see paid accounts totaling 350,000.</p>
<p>Monzo’s commendable revenue outing came amid rising inflation and expensive living costs for British consumers. The UK challenger bank’s lending volume for its last annual run tripled YoY to £759.7 million. However, Anil disputed suggestions that Monzo’s revenue performance was due to the UK’s cost-of-living crisis. Instead, the CEO explained the predicament reflected the importance of Monzo’s products, including savings pots and budgeting tools.</p>
<h2>Monzo Is Not the First British Challenger Bank to Attain Monthly Profitability</h2>
<p>Despite Monzo’s recent profitable run, the company is not the first British digital bank to achieve that feat. In 2021, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/starling-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Starling</a> hit profitability for the first time after the neobank’s revenue shot up 600% to £97.6 million from £14 million. At the time, the challenger bank’s CEO Anne Boden described the situation as “very much on track” to attain 2022 full-year profitability.</p>
<p>Last June, the UK’s Allica Bank also hit monthly profitability and saw a pre-tax profit of £3 million for H2 2022. Commenting on the digital bank’s glowing 2022 earlier this month, Allica CEO Richard Davies enthused:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Allica has entered 2023 with an excellent platform to continue to grow and expand its offer to SMEs.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition, Davies explained that the neo-bank had already experienced growth in profitability for the first quarter of the year. According to the chief executive, Allica’s Q1 2023 profitability was due to “very prudent capital and liquidity positions”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/">UK Neobank Monzo Attains First-Time Monthly Profitability Following Lending Surge</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-monzo-bank-profitability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former SEC Chief Warns Crypto Influencers against Price Manipulations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereummax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257269</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/">Former SEC Chief Warns Crypto Influencers against Price Manipulations</a></p>
<p>The former SEC chief hinted that influencers adopt various strategies to deceive and mislead their followers into making uncalculated investment decisions. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/">Former SEC Chief Warns Crypto Influencers against Price Manipulations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/">Former SEC Chief Warns Crypto Influencers against Price Manipulations</a></p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) is increasing its efforts to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-decision-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">regulate</a> and enforce compliance among crypto influencers, as former SEC Chief John Reed Stark issues a stern warning about potential prosecutions.</p>
<p>In a Twitter post on Wednesday, Stark, who headed the SEC&#8217;s Internet Enforcement unit for 11 years, cautioned those social media personalities in the crypto space who have endorsed dubious projects and engaged in price manipulation in the past, assuring them that their end is near.</p>
<p>According to Stark, the days of social media crypto influencers operating without accountability are coming to an end. He emphasized that the same anti-fraud regulations apply to all forms of price manipulation, whether it involves exchange-listed securities, penny stocks, or crypto assets.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Attention all crypto promoters who use social media to manipulate the price of crypto-securities: Fail not at your peril. Not only will you eventually get caught, but your prosecution will also be like shooting fish in a barrel.</p>
<p>Whether manipulating the price of exchange… <a href="https://t.co/AfKROIlR0N">pic.twitter.com/AfKROIlR0N</a></p>
<p>— John Reed Stark (@JohnReedStark) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1663642497581473794?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Social Media Aid Price Manipulation Schemes</h2>
<p>In his tweet, the former SEC chief hinted that influencers adopt various strategies to deceive and mislead their followers into making uncalculated investment decisions.</p>
<p>He further noted that these personalities use social media platforms such as Twitter, Discord, Instagram, and Reddit to perpetrate the scams, leveraging the popularity of the platforms to lure their victims.</p>
<p>Unlike other scams, Stark said that securities fraud could easily be detected and wrongdoers cannot hide their trails from authorities. According to him, law enforcement only needs to power their computers to unearth evidence trails that lead to the crimes.</p>
<p>&#8220;Regulators and law enforcement need only turn on their computers to discover an extraordinary and splendid evidentiary trail of compelling and vivid inculpatory evidence. Indeed, far from tying the government&#8217;s hands, social media has become the virtual rope that many crypto bros (and sisters) use to hang themselves,&#8221; <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-former-chief-warns-influencers-about-persecution-for-crypto-price-manipulation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Stark.</p>
<h2>US SEC Crackdowns on Crypto Influencers</h2>
<p>Stark cited the case of notorious crypto advocate Francis Sabo, who recently faced charges in a $100 million securities fraud case.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.sec.gov/litigation/litreleases/2023/lr25736.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">complaint</a>, Sabo, also known as Ricky Bobby, promoted himself as a &#8220;trustworthy stock-picking guru&#8221;, which helped him gain substantial followers on the Atlas Trading Discord forum, where users are educated about trading and the securities market.</p>
<p>Sabo purchased some stocks and convinced his followers to buy the same tokens. He posted price targets indicating he was buying, holding, or adding to his stock positions to prove that he had the asset.</p>
<p>The SEC had previously <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-jimmy-butler-1-billion-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">indicted</a> other crypto influencers and celebrities violating securities laws. Last year, the regulator fined billionaire celebrity <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kardashian-ethereum-max-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kim Kardashian</a> $1.26 million for endorsing a fraudulent crypto project called EthereumMax (EMAX). Other celebrities, such as Floyd Mayweather, were involved with the project.</p>
<p>Just recently, Bitboy Crypto, an influencer who has faced public criticism for promoting questionable crypto projects in the past, was named in a $1 billion lawsuit for endorsing unregistered securities.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/">Former SEC Chief Warns Crypto Influencers against Price Manipulations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-sec-chief-crypto-influencers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Telecom Invests 3B Yuan to Establish Quantum Technology Group in Anhui Province</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china telecom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xi jinping]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257265</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/">China Telecom Invests 3B Yuan to Establish Quantum Technology Group in Anhui Province</a></p>
<p>China Telecom has noted that the establishment of a quantum tech hub is in line with President Xi Jinping’s long-term tech adoption.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/">China Telecom Invests 3B Yuan to Establish Quantum Technology Group in Anhui Province</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/">China Telecom Invests 3B Yuan to Establish Quantum Technology Group in Anhui Province</a></p>
<p>China Telecom Corp Ltd (Hong Kong: 728), a Chinese telecommunications company, has announced plans to venture into the supercomputer quantum industry to streamline its services. According to the company’s announcement through WeChat, up to 3 billion Yuan, approximately $434 million, will be used to establish the China Telecom Quantum Information Technology Group. Reportedly, the company has chosen the eastern province of Anhui as the desired place to establish quantum technology.</p>
<p>The Chinese economy has experienced significant growth post Covid-19 fueled by the adoption of digital technology including artificial intelligence, blockchain, and distributed ledger, among others. The president of the People&#8217;s Republic of China <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/xi-jinping/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Xi Jinping</a> has laid a lot of emphasis on the adoption of technology to streamline the country’s economic activities.</p>
<p>“The establishment of China Telecom Quantum Information Technology Group is a practical action to thoroughly study and implement the spirit of General Secretary Xi Jinping&#8217;s important instructions on the development of quantum technology,” China Telecom said in its statement.</p>
<p>Following the announcement of a quantum technology hub by China Telecom, its stock market closed Wednesday trading around HK$ 3.89, down 1.39 percent from the day’s opening price. Nevertheless, China Telecom’s stock market has gained approximately 27 percent YTD, in addition to last year’s 40 percent spike.</p>
<p>The announcement of a quantum hub by China Telecom follows a similar move by China Mobile Ltd (Hong Kong: 941) earlier this year.</p>
<p>Notably, China Mobile, the leading wireless carrier in China with more than 900 million subscribers, signed a deal with Origin Quantum, a full-stack quantum computing company, to use its quantum computing to overhaul the challenges facing the 5G and 6G technologies.</p>
<h2>China Telecom and the Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Following a bullish outlook YTD, China Telecom has seen its market capitalization rise to about HK$ 570.64 billion. The company is the second largest wireless carrier in China with more than 362 million subscribers after China Mobile. The introduction of quantum technology is expected to significantly streamline its services amid the adoption of Web3 technology that emphasizes higher bandwidth data.</p>
<p>According to the company’s 2022 annual results recently released, China Telecom announced several developments including full implementation of Cloudification and Digital Transformation. As a result, the company saw its revenue hit a 10-year growth non-stop, whereby it grew at 8 percent YoY in 2022.</p>
<p>In 2022, China Telecom Cloud revenue <a href="https://www.chinatelecom-h.com/en/ir/transcripts/tra_ar2022.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recorded</a> a spike of 100 percent to RMB 57.9 billion. During the year, the company significantly increased its artificial intelligence (AI) outlook via the Xinghe Platform, which ostensibly has more than 100 use cases and over 10 million customers.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/">China Telecom Invests 3B Yuan to Establish Quantum Technology Group in Anhui Province</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-telecom-3b-yuan-quantum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts Workforce by 30%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nansen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257251</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/">Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts Workforce by 30%</a></p>
<p>Nansen has promised to work assiduously with its remaining team to ensure they provide the best services to their customers as well as build the best workplace in crypto.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/">Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts Workforce by 30%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/">Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts Workforce by 30%</a></p>
<p>Nansen, a leading startup in the blockchain technology industry, has recently announced a significant reduction in its workforce. The news of the 30% cut in blockchain data analytics firms has caused quite a stir in the industry, with many speculating on the reasons behind the decision.</p>
<p>According to the blockchain analytics platform’s Chief Executive Officer (CEO), Alex Svanevik in a <a href="https://twitter.com/ASvanevik/status/1663565127357177861?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1663565127357177861%7Ctwgr%5Efbdb4b1399f2801a2632872d184c21d6e8f1f4f3%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fnansen-lays-off-30-of-its-workforce" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a>, several factors beyond the firm’s control necessitated the reduction in its workforce. He also disclosed that it was an extremely difficult situation for the company to cut short the size of its team.</p>
<h2>Nansen to Now Concentrate on Core Services</h2>
<p>Alex cited two major reasons for the reduction in Nansen’s workforce. First, the company has recognized the need to streamline its operations and concentrate on its key strengths in order to remain competitive in an increasingly dynamic industry.</p>
<p>Likewise, the CEO mentioned that this past year has been brutal for the crypto markets, hence the need for layoffs. The company has done everything possible to diversify its revenue streams through its institutional customers, yet its cost base has remained high compared to the company’s current state. Also, Nansen has been experiencing a decrease in demand for its product and services, which has resulted in a decline in revenue.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the decision to reduce its workforce was not made lightly, with management acknowledging the impact this will have on affected employees. However, the company believes that this is the right decision to ensure its long-term sustainability and viability. Interestingly, Alex noted that the employees affected by the workforce reduction will be offered severance packages and career transition assistance to help them navigate this difficult period.</p>
<p>Going forward, the company has promised to work assiduously with its remaining team to ensure they provide the best services to their customers as well as build the best workplace in crypto.</p>
<h2>Beyond Nansen: Other Crypto Firms Forced to Reduce Workforce</h2>
<p>As the bear market continues to sweep the crypto industry, mass layoffs have continued to plague the firms operating in the space even though the rate has slowed significantly in recent months. In January, popular cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) announced a 20% <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-layoff-crypto-meltdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">staff layoff</a> to strengthen its financial position in the face of the crypto crunch. Although, this happens to be the second major round of staff downsizing for the exchange in the past year.</p>
<p>Also, Luno, a leading global cryptocurrency company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/luno-employees-layoff-tumult/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> that it would be shedding 35% of its global employees.</p>
<p>Outside of the blockchain and crypto industry, the American multinational tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META) also embarked on a series of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meta-mass-staff-layoff-costs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">layoffs</a> beginning in November last year, when the tech giant axed 11,000 of its workforce. All of these reductions were necessary to help the firm cut costs and focus on its restructuring.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/">Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts Workforce by 30%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nansen-cuts-workforce/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foxconn Expects Growing AI Demand to Boost Its Server Business This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aws]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257244</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/">Foxconn Expects Growing AI Demand to Boost Its Server Business This Year</a></p>
<p>Contract electronics manufacturing giant Foxconn banks on explosive AI popularity to drive its server business revenue in 2023. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/">Foxconn Expects Growing AI Demand to Boost Its Server Business This Year</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/">Foxconn Expects Growing AI Demand to Boost Its Server Business This Year</a></p>
<p>Foxconn has forecasted significant growth in its artificial intelligence (AI) server business due to robust demand. On Wednesday, the company&#8217;s Chairman, Young Liu, said revenue generated from its AI businesses would more than double this year. Liu credited the popularity of generative AI applications like ChatGPT for stoking interest in the sector.</p>
<p>At Foxconn&#8217;s annual shareholder meeting in New Taipei City, the leading Taiwanese contract electronics manufacturer&#8217;s Chairman <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/apple-s-iphone-maker-expects-to-more-than-double-ai-server-sales-1.1926814" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;People&#8217;s reliance on ChatGPT is growing. What we are seeing now is the demand for AI servers is expanding. The growth of Foxconn&#8217;s AI servers is forecast to be increasing by three-digit percent [in 2023].&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Liu pointed out that Foxconn, also known as Hon Hai in China and Taiwan, realized server revenue of 1.1 trillion Taiwan dollars ($36 billion) in 2022. According to the Chairman, this feat made the New Taipei-based company claim a 40 percent global market share. However, Liu believes last year&#8217;s achievements would pale compared to the sales prospects of Foxconn&#8217;s AI server business for 2023. He noted that AI servers remained bright amid fiscal policy tightening and rising inflationary pressure. Nonetheless, despite prevalent macroeconomic uncertainty, the Chairman doubled down on his upbeat predictions for 2023, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For the second half of this year, we may have a three-digit growth, not two digits&#8230; We will continue to boost our market share for servers.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Liu also said Foxconn remained cautious and suggested the firm would continue to operate efficiently but prudently.</p>
<h2>Foxconn to Deepen Market Dominance by Leveraging Diversified Services Alongside AI Interests</h2>
<p>Liu&#8217;s bold growth claims suggest that Foxconn seeks to increase its server market dominance by leveraging the AI boom. The company is currently the world&#8217;s largest contract electronics manufacturer, assembling devices for several renowned brands, most notably <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL). Additionally, Foxconn&#8217;s clientele includes <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT),<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Google</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/hp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hewlett-Packard</a> (NYSE: HPQ), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/dell-technologies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dell</a> (NYSE: DELL), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a>&#8216;s (NASDAQ: AMZN) Web Services.</p>
<p>Over time, Foxconn has diversified beyond its base electronics assemblage and now has businesses in servers, electric vehicles, and semiconductors. Liu said the company is number one in the global mobile phone and personal computer market share. Additionally, its AI server market is growing much quicker than anyone anticipated.</p>
<p>Liu also stated that Foxconn&#8217;s latest AI servers use<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Nvidia</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) chips.</p>
<h2>Foxconn Outlook on 2023 Full Year Restrained Despite AI Boon</h2>
<p>Foxconn&#8217;s positive outlook on generative AI follows the company&#8217;s underwhelming Q1 2023 net profit haul. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-supplier-foxconns-q1-profit-falls-56-yy-worse-than-forecasts-2023-05-11/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Earlier this month</a>, the leading contract electronics manufacturing firm reported a 56% plunge in first-quarter profits, its most significant setback in three years. The decline was due to a substantial multi-billion-dollar write-down from Foxconn&#8217;s 34% stake in Japanese electronics manufacturer Sharp Corp.</p>
<p>In early May, Foxconn also ascribed <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">a massive 12% sales drop</a> in April to a decline in smartphone shipments. Despite the projected growth in artificial intelligence demand, the Taiwanese company maintains a &#8220;flat&#8221; outlook for the 2023 full year. &#8220;We still think the performance for this year would be flattish from last year,&#8221; Liu explained. The Chairman also added that market visibility was still low.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/">Foxconn Expects Growing AI Demand to Boost Its Server Business This Year</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-ai-demand-server-business/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Requests Bahamas Consent to Continue FTX Bankman-Fried Post-extradition Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/">US Requests Bahamas Consent to Continue FTX Bankman-Fried Post-extradition Charges</a></p>
<p>The Bahamas government's response will determine whether to go on with or drop some of the cases.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/">US Requests Bahamas Consent to Continue FTX Bankman-Fried Post-extradition Charges</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/">US Requests Bahamas Consent to Continue FTX Bankman-Fried Post-extradition Charges</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> was apprehended last year in the Bahamas and subsequently transferred to the United States. The allegations against him involve multiple charges relating to financial fraud and the collapse of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. Bankman-Fried is charged with engaging in illegal activities, including allegedly working with former FTX executives to persuade American legislators to pass legislation that would benefit FTX. In carrying out these allegedly illegal actions, he managed to exceed the maximum contribution amounts the law permits. He was consequently accused of making illegal political contributions and bank fraud.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried was additionally accused of crimes related to paying off a foreign government to unfreeze brokerage accounts linked to his hedge fund, money laundering, and running an unlicensed money transfer operation, among others.</p>
<h2>Lawyer Argues for Dropping 10 out of 13 Charges for Bankman-Fried</h2>
<p>However, Bankman-Fried&#8217;s legal counsel took action by filing a motion in the United States Court to have the charges against him dismissed. According to his lawyer, many of the offenses were not sufficiently specified. Bankman-Fried is currently facing a total of 13 charges, all of which he has pleaded not guilty to. In addition, his lawyer is specifically seeking the dismissal of ten of those accusations.</p>
<p>The former CEO’s attorney also <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/some-sbf-charges-will-be-dropped-if-bahamas-objects-u-s-prosecutors-say" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">claims</a> that under the conditions surrounding the US-Bahamas treaty that governs his extradition, he can only be prosecuted on the specific grounds for which he was extradited. It is claimed that the US government added unrelated criminal charges and new elements without the Bahamas government&#8217;s consent. As a result, the defense argues that these new motions should be dismissed.</p>
<p>The US government went on to state that at this point in the case, there is no justification to drop any of the charges. The Department of Justice made it clear that there are no limitations on bringing new accusations against a defendant after extradition under the terms of the agreement between the United States and the Bahamas.</p>
<p>However, it is acknowledged that the Bahamas has the authority to waive some post-extradition requirements. In light of this, the US Justice Department is currently seeking a waiver from the Bahamas government in order to move forward with particular aspects of the cases. The course of action will ultimately depend on how the Bahamas government responds. The charges will move forward as planned if the Bahamas government approves the waiver. If the waiver is denied, on the other hand, the US Department of Justice will be forced to drop the new cases and concentrate only on the accusations that prompted Bankman-Fried&#8217;s extradition.</p>
<p>On June 15, a court hearing will be held to discuss the motion asking that 10 of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s 13 charges be dropped. The outcome of this proceeding will have a big impact on how the case might turn out.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/">US Requests Bahamas Consent to Continue FTX Bankman-Fried Post-extradition Charges</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-bahamas-ftx-bankman-fried-charges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Raises Concern about Crypto, Says It’s Matter of National Security</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/">Coinbase CEO Raises Concern about Crypto, Says It&#8217;s Matter of National Security</a></p>
<p>Coinbase CEO believes China might be looking to directly displace the US dollar from its role in global commerce.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/">Coinbase CEO Raises Concern about Crypto, Says It&#8217;s Matter of National Security</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/">Coinbase CEO Raises Concern about Crypto, Says It&#8217;s Matter of National Security</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a> has recently shared his thoughts on cryptocurrencies and the approach of the United States toward the special asset class. He admits that recent happenings around the world of cryptocurrency have made it necessary for policymakers to be more hostile toward crypto. However, he also says that America should not lose sight of the fact that crypto may be the only way for the country to maintain its position as a global financial leader and an innovation hub.</p>
<p>In a recent opinion <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/coinbase-ceo-americas-future-as-a-global-technology-leader-is-up-for-grabs-c3a9c6ae" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">article</a>, Armstrong once again raised the issue of regulatory clarity. He cited how Coinbase, himself, and many more in the industry have long been at loggerheads with regulators over the issue of more robust rules and regulations. However, rather than provide these, regulators are threatening <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-enforcement-action-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enforcement actions</a>, Coinbase CEO Armstrong claimed. And according to him, enforcement actions and strict measures such as this will only drive innovation far away from the US.</p>
<h2>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong: Present Situation Is a Threat to National Security</h2>
<p>Brian also shared the view that when innovations are taken offshore, America inadvertently loses its legacy of pioneering technological advancements in the world. This, he claims, will weaken the country’s national security in ways unimaginable.</p>
<p>In his explanation, he says currency has always been at the heart of innovations, while innovations are driven by technology. For example, the US dollar had been keeping the global economic system in order since around 1944. However, its position as a global reserve currency was not fully established until 1958. That was when the network technologies came about during the launch of the Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency. This status of the currency was what gave America so much power.</p>
<p>Today, however, while China is embracing digital systems, the US and other democratic nations appear to be up against them. China continues to push for the adoption of this new digital system both locally, and internationally via its Belt and Road Initiatives.</p>
<p>Furthermore, China has integrated its social credit system with its digital system and also recently launched its digital yuan. With the digital yuan, China might be looking to directly displace the US dollar from its role in global commerce. Especially since all its recent moves point to that fact.</p>
<p>But that&#8217;s not to say China is the only nation that has seen the endless possibilities of crypto. Other prominent traditional financial capitals are also in an unspoken competition to become the global crypto hub. Some of them include the UK, United Arab Emirates (UAE), Brazil, Australia, Brazil, Japan, the European Union, and Singapore.</p>
<p>Brian now calls on Congress to quickly make smart decisions as was done in the times before the Internet Age. And, ultimately, provide clear regulations for crypto that will not only protect consumers, but also foster innovation.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/">Coinbase CEO Raises Concern about Crypto, Says It&#8217;s Matter of National Security</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-ceo-armstrong-crypto-national-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Sees Software Stocks as Next Opportunity in AI</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ark invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/">Cathie Wood Sees Software Stocks as Next Opportunity in AI</a></p>
<p>Wood's Ark Innovation ETF has dropped more than 10% from its peak in early February, while the Nasdaq 100 Stock Index has climbed up by 12% in the same time frame.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/">Cathie Wood Sees Software Stocks as Next Opportunity in AI</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/">Cathie Wood Sees Software Stocks as Next Opportunity in AI</a></p>
<p>Cathie Wood, the renowned founder and CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ark-invest/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ARK Invest</a> is making headlines for stating that software stocks are the next big bet in the Artificial Intelligence (AI) world, following the success of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA). During an <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/cathie-wood-says-software-stocks-are-next-ai-bet-after-nvidia-1.1926782" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with Bloomberg TV, Wood noted that while Nvidia is likely to perform well in the long run, her focus has switched to identifying the next great market opportunity.</p>
<p>Wood&#8217;s focus on software stocks as potential giants in the AI sector has led her to identify key companies she believes have the potential to match the success of Nvidia. Among these companies, she specifically mentions UiPath Inc (NYSE: PATH), Twilio Inc (NYSE: TWLO), and Teladoc Health Inc (NYSE: TDOC) as notable examples.</p>
<p>Typically, Wood&#8217;s investment strategy frequently entails picking firms that have undergone large losses from past highs yet have tremendous long-term growth potential. In this regard, UiPath witnessed a rise in its share price after going public in 2021, hitting over $85 per share. However, since then, the stock has plunged nearly 80% from its peak.</p>
<p>Similarly, Twilio also saw a significant drop in its share price, declining around 85% from its peak in 2021. In addition, Teladoc Health also saw a more than 90% drop from its high in 2021.</p>
<p>Wood&#8217;s investment funds currently hold all three of these stocks, signaling her confidence in their growth prospects. She sees tremendous potential in software providers and Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) companies, emphasizing that for every dollar of hardware that NVIDIA sells, these software companies can generate eight dollars in revenue.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood Stays Positive Despite Decline in Ark Innovation ETF</h2>
<p>Notably, Wood&#8217;s Ark Innovation ETF has dropped more than 10% from its peak in early February, while the Nasdaq 100 Stock Index has climbed up by 12% in the same time frame.</p>
<p>Despite this recent underperformance, Wood remains optimistic about certain investments, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA), which she considers the “biggest artificial intelligence play”.</p>
<p>Wood reiterated her belief that Tesla&#8217;s stock price has the potential to reach $2,000 by 2027, emphasizing the importance of the company&#8217;s autonomous technology in driving this growth. She sees Tesla not merely as an automaker but as a company at the forefront of artificial intelligence and self-driving vehicles.</p>
<p>Wood&#8217;s positive attitude toward Tesla is predicated on her forecast that autonomous taxi systems will earn approximately $10 trillion in revenue globally by 2038, starting from a nearly non-existent revenue base. She sees Tesla as a vital participant in this field and anticipates the firm capitalizing on the future rise of autonomous technology.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Wood&#8217;s decision to reduce her holdings in Nvidia through her flagship ARK Innovation ETF in January proved to be a missed opportunity as the chipmaker experienced a significant rally, briefly reaching a market valuation of over $1 trillion. Wood, however, has defended her decision, explaining her concerns about the boom-bust cycle of the computer-chip industry and stating that NVIDIA was “priced ahead of the curve”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/">Cathie Wood Sees Software Stocks as Next Opportunity in AI</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cathie-wood-software-stocks-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Baidu Launches $145 Million VC Fund to Back AI Startups</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 11:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[baidu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[erbie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ernie bot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257194</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/">Baidu Launches $145 Million VC Fund to Back AI Startups</a></p>
<p>Chinese multinational tech company Baidu is launching a well-heeled fund to support AI development and growth. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/">Baidu Launches $145 Million VC Fund to Back AI Startups</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/">Baidu Launches $145 Million VC Fund to Back AI Startups</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/baidu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Baidu</a> (NASDAQ: BIDU) appears set to launch a 1-billion yuan ($145 million) venture capital artificial intelligence (AI) fund to support AI startups. Today, the Chinese tech giant announced its AI fund intentions alongside other related initiatives.</p>
<p>In addition to supporting platforms focused on artificial intelligence-generated content, Baidu also plans to launch a contest promoting its own AI product. The Beijing-based tech company explained that the competition would see developers creating applications using its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-chatgpt-ernie-bot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ernie</a> large language model (LLM). Alternatively, Baidu added that competitors could integrate the bot model into their existing products and services.</p>
<p>The Baidu AI fund initiative underscores the explosive popularity of artificial intelligence tech in everyday use cases. Since the release of OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT late last year, several tech platforms have raced to leverage AI popularity.</p>
<h2>Baidu AI Fund Part of Broader Chinese Interest in AI Development</h2>
<p>Although ChatGPT&#8217;s success spurred AI development and increased interest in the last six months, China has been familiar with the tech. For instance, a recent <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-organisations-launched-79-ai-large-language-models-since-2020-report-2023-05-30/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Reuters report</a>, citing Chinese government sources, said nearly 80 Chinese companies had launched their own LLMs since 2020. Furthermore, the report also stated that the number of China&#8217;s LLM releases for 2023 slightly edges out that of the US.</p>
<p>Yesterday, Reuters pointed out that in 2020, China released 2 LLMs compared to 11 in the US. However, by the succeeding year, the number of releases in both nations was even, with 30 LLMs apiece. In 2022, US companies again led with 37, compared to China&#8217;s 28. So far in 2023, the East Asian country leads the US with 19 LLMs released versus America&#8217;s 18. In conclusion, the report pointed out:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Judging from the distribution of large-language models released around the world, China and the United States lead by a big margin, accounting for more than 80% of the global total.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, despite the increasingly closer race between China and the US, findings concluded that the latter retains the edge, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The United States has always ranked first in the world in terms of the number of large-language models.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Baidu&#8217;s Ernie Bot</h2>
<p>Baidu,<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Alibaba</a> (NYSE: BABA), and SenseTime are some Chinese firms that have launched generative AI services in the last few months. For example, in late March, Baidu <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-chatgpt-ernie-bot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unveiled</a> its Ernie chatbot to rival ChatGPT&#8217;s functionality. The company launched the AI product to interested partners during a closed-door meeting. However, Baidu CEO Robin Li had earlier <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-shares-rival-openais-chatgpt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">teased</a> Ernie Bot at a pre-recorded demo session on March 16th. The chatbot was not fully ready at the time, likely contributing to Baidu&#8217;s stock drop.</p>
<p>Baidu developed Ernie on its ERNIE LLM and described the chatbot as having advanced promising features. According to the company, more than 650 companies signed up to use Ernie in a wide range of use cases. These use cases include AI cloud functionality, smart device services, autonomous driving applications, and searches.</p>
<p>Ernie is an abbreviation for Enhanced Representation through Knowledge Integration.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/">Baidu Launches $145 Million VC Fund to Back AI Startups</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/baidu-145m-vc-fund-ai-startups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Jesus Roger Ver: Ethereum, Not Bitcoin, Will Drive Global Crypto Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 11:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[roger ver]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/">Bitcoin Jesus Roger Ver: Ethereum, Not Bitcoin, Will Drive Global Crypto Adoption</a></p>
<p>Considering the kind of projects that the Ethereum blockchain hosts, and the kind of services it offers, Roger Ver believes that Ethereum will be able to drive major user adoption. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/">Bitcoin Jesus Roger Ver: Ethereum, Not Bitcoin, Will Drive Global Crypto Adoption</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/">Bitcoin Jesus Roger Ver: Ethereum, Not Bitcoin, Will Drive Global Crypto Adoption</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/roger-ver/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Roger Ver</a>, also popular as Bitcoin Jesus for being an early <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> advocate, recently gave a statement that it will be <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, and not Bitcoin, responsible for driving a bulk of new users towards cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>While speaking at the Show Me The Crypto podcast on Tuesday, May 31, Roger Ver said that despite the Ethereum blockchain facing scaling issues and other Layer-1 competitors arriving in the market, Ethereum has managed to stay at its dominating position. He <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TrdPHkiflaA&amp;t=2798s" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Even though Ethereum doesn’t have the biggest market cap compared to Bitcoin, I think Ethereum is the front-runner in terms of driving worldwide adoption.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The Ethereum development team, however, has been working hard for making the Ethereum blockchain more scalable and efficient. One pivotal moment for the Ethereum ecosystem was the Merge event in September 2022, following which, Ethereum moved to a more scalable Proof-of-Stake (PoS) blockchain network.</p>
<p>With future updates, Ethereum developers are likely to improve the network scalability to a great extent. In the podcast interview, Roger Ver also praised the rise of Ethereum Virtual Machine-compatible (EVM) blockchains as well as Layer-2 scaling solutions such as Polygon. He said that such solutions have helped to take the load away from the main chain.</p>
<h2>The Bitcoin vs Ethereum &#8216;Civil War&#8217;</h2>
<p>Roger Ver went down memory lane and spoke about the &#8220;civil war&#8221; that took place between Bitcoin developers and Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin, in the early days of crypto.</p>
<p>What drive Buterin to build Ethereum were the disagreements over the use of smart contracts as well as conflict over the idea that blockchains were purely for hosting currency or store of value. Ver said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“All of that would have been built on top of Bitcoin if not for the scaling civil war that happened. These Bitcoin core developers hate Vitalik, and they basically drove him from the project to go and create Ethereum, and more power to him for that.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Touching down on the recent Ldeger debate over the controversial Recover service, Ver called it &#8220;disappointing&#8221;. The Ledger Recover service proposed users store their encrypted seed phase along with external custodians to safeguard against any loss.</p>
<p>Ver emphasized that although custodial accounts and key recovery options are acceptable for individuals, the fundamental principle of cryptocurrency revolves around maintaining complete control over one&#8217;s assets at all times.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bybit-exit-canada-regulatory/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/">Bitcoin Jesus Roger Ver: Ethereum, Not Bitcoin, Will Drive Global Crypto Adoption</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/rover-ver-ethereum-crypto-adoption/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4039 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1029774 metric#prefetches=194 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=201 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=100.96 metric#ms-cache=5.14 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2449 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.1 -->