<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:44:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://news.coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186917-spartadex-first-gaming-dex-on-arbitrum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GameFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SPARTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SpartaDEX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX on the Arbitrum Network" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network 1">SpartaDEX combines the first decentralized cryptocurrency exchange and strategy game on the Arbitrum network.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX on the Arbitrum Network" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-17-1.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network 6">
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The arrival of SpartaDex broke this perception. It is no longer a mere reuse of DeFi logic, but the behavioral logic of the DEX is reflected in the game&#8217;s behavior, creating a product that is both DeFi and GameFi. Users can not only test it from a DeFi perspective but also experience it as a gamer. So what is SpartaDex? Let&#8217;s find out through the article below.</strong></h5>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is SpartaDEX?</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-502.png"><img decoding="async" width="1920" height="1080" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-502.png" alt="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX on the Arbitrum Network" class="wp-image-186929" title="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network 2"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>SpartaDEX combines a decentralized cryptocurrency exchange and a real-time strategy game set in ancient Greece. This is the first gamified<a href="https://news.coincu.com/184009-chronos-arbitrum-based-dex/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> DEX</a> on Arbitrum to increase user engagement by incorporating video game elements, helping foster loyalty and incentivize more liquidity.</p>



<p>In SpartaDEX, each user mints a free NFT of an ancient Greek city &#8211; Polis, and grows it to maximize their profit from the LP provided. To start upgrading their Polis, gathering resources, and building an army, users add a minimum of $100 in liquidity to one of the whitelisted pools.</p>



<p>The development of each Polis with all the achievements is being saved in the NFT, making the highly developed settlements more valuable and more desirable on the secondary market. Furthermore, the higher the Senate level of Polis, the higher the APR from staking LP that the user gets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What makes SpartaDEX unique?</h2>



<p>It is still in beta and is expected to launch on the mainnet in May of this year. SpartaDex will introduce the trading atmosphere and Devsifi character into Arbitrum, Various activities in the DEX have become games and you can earn income by building your own house. By combining full-featured decentralized exchange functions with ancient Spartan-themed games, users can experience the fun of the game while interacting with the DEX.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="569" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-1024x569.png" alt="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX on the Arbitrum Network" class="wp-image-186930" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-1024x569.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-300x167.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-768x426.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-1536x853.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-750x416.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503-1140x633.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-503.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network 3"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>DEX has 2 modes: gamified and normal. This duality allows users to make swaps through a simple and intuitive interface without entering the game layer.</p>



<p>Besides, it generates revenue from the DeFi exchange mechanism and the game itself (micropayments, NFT claims). Profits are then shared with the $SPARTA token staking.</p>



<p>All users, projects, and the DEX itself are protected from volatile liquidity with the Surrender Tax &#8211; an innovative concept that builds more profound and stable liquidity over time. The user is subject to a cooldown when withdrawing liquidity for the specified fees (as shown below). 100% of the fees are used to increase the liquidity of a particular project and will be locked forever.</p>



<ul>
<li>Instant LP withdrawal &#8211; 8% fee</li>



<li>Cooldown 7 days – 5% charge</li>



<li>Cooldown for 14 days – 2% cost</li>



<li>30 days cooldown &#8211; 0% charge</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">SpartaDex&#8217;s Ecosystem</h2>



<p>Currently, SpartaDex mainly consists of three parts: NFT+DEX+RTS Game.</p>



<p>The first is NFT: Before users can experience SpartaDex products, they need to pre-empt an NFT of the ancient Greek city of Polis. It&#8217;s worth noting that NFT minting itself is free, and it&#8217;s a specific manifestation of users adding LP, but for your NFT to work, users need to inject at least $100 of liquidity.</p>



<p>Next is DEX: According to the official introduction of SpartaDex, its DEX uses real income and Token commitment to participate in dividends (DEX fee, GameFi fee). Compared to the cold and boring storage of traditional DeFi, SpartaDex offers a new model for future DeFi growth: turning LPs into NFTs in GameFi (somewhat similar to Uniswap V3).</p>



<p>Finally, the Game section, SpartaDex, offers users an RTS strategy game similar to &#8220;Kingdom Awakening&#8221; and &#8220;Kingdom Era.&#8221;</p>



<p>In SpartaDex, every DEX-based user activity is displayed as a game. For example, the user&#8217;s LP is converted into an army to conquer the city. The form of LP income is called loot, or the user&#8217;s commit group is represented as a city in the game. The user&#8217;s mining behavior for the city-state is considered an acquisition of APY, the user&#8217;s upgrade and maintenance of the city-state is deemed to add liquidity, etc.</p>



<p>The results of each city-state&#8217;s development are stored in the NFT, making highly developed settlements more valuable and popular on the secondary market. More importantly, the higher the level of Senate Polis, the higher APR users can get by staking LP.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">SpartaDEX revenue stream</h2>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-1024x576.png" alt="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX on the Arbitrum Network" class="wp-image-186931" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-1024x576.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-1536x864.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-750x422.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504-1140x641.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-504.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network 4"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>As a gaming DeFi exchange, SpartaDEX monetizes both the dex and the game itself. The platform&#8217;s revenue sources include:</p>



<ul>
<li>Dex Fee</li>



<li>Reward claim fee (1 USDC/request)</li>



<li>Micropayments (buy premium in-game currency to speed up Polis development, build upgrade times, purchase premium accounts and resources, etc.)</li>



<li>Royalties from NFT (5% on Spartans NFT and 7.5% on Polis NFT)</li>



<li>Ecosystem fee (from the built-in bridge after we deploy the new EVM chain)</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">SPARTA token</h2>



<p>The native token of the SpartaDEX ecosystem is $SPARTA. The token technology and its mechanism are designed to provide widespread utility and low inflation.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="520" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505-1024x520.png" alt="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX on the Arbitrum Network" class="wp-image-186932" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505-1024x520.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505-300x152.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505-768x390.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505-750x381.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505-1140x578.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-505.png 1360w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SpartaDex Review: The First Gaming DEX On The Arbitrum Network 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Some utilities:</p>



<ul>
<li>It can be locked in one asset bet, get Real Profit from game revenue, and exchange</li>



<li>$SPARTA stakingers can participate in monthly voting for the new project&#8217;s liquidity pool to be eligible for ecosystem rewards in $SPARTA tokens (governance)</li>



<li>Users can use $SPARTA to purchase premium in-game currency &#8211; Gems &#8211; to grow their Polis faster and thus increase the APR on the liquidity provided.</li>
</ul>



<p>The $SPARTA token accumulates value through revenue from the DeFi exchange and the game itself. All revenue (other than NFT royalties) will be split into 3 equal pools dedicated to:</p>



<ul>
<li>Burn (or buy and burn)</li>



<li>Profits for single property bettors</li>



<li>further development</li>



<li>To prevent inflation, 75% of tokens from the ecosystem reward (the reward for staking LP, which constitutes the largest supply) will be automatically transferred to the single asset staking pool.</li>
</ul>



<p>Through staking unique assets, users can earn profits and participate in governance. However, withdrawals will involve a no-deposit fee or a no deposit period. Users can withdraw immediately, sacrifice 50% (of which 2/3 will be burned and 1/3 will be distributed among bettors), or choose a no-staking interval from 1 to 100 days, in which the fee is reduced by 0.5 % per day.</p>



<p>Finally, the $SPARTA token strengthens with each new partnership as more and more users use the token to extend their Polis.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How does it work?</h2>



<p>First, prepare before the game starts</p>



<p>The first thing you need to do before using the testnet is to add the Polygon Mumbai testnet to your Metamask.</p>



<ul>
<li>Visit: <a href="https://chainlist.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://chainlist.org/</a></li>



<li>Type &#8220;mumbai&#8221; and select &#8220;include testnet&#8221;</li>



<li>Select &#8220;Mumbai&#8221; and add it to the Metamask.</li>
</ul>



<p>Now it&#8217;s time to claim your test token. This activity includes two steps:</p>



<p>Get test $MATIC token on Polygon Mumbai network<br>You can do this with several types of faucets available. Our recommendation is:</p>



<ul>
<li>Link: <a href="https://mumbaifaucet.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://mumbaifaucet.com/</a></li>



<li>Gives you 0.5 $MATIC every 24 hours, and this amount is enough to try the testnet to the fullest.</li>
</ul>



<p>Get test tokens for swap and extra liquidity</p>



<p>For this, we have prepared a dedicated faucet with which you can claim tokens:</p>



<ul>
<li>Link: <a href="https://testnet.spartadex.io/faucet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://testnet.spartadex.io/faucet</a></li>



<li>You can access testnet from the following link: <a href="https://testnet.spartadex.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://testnet.spartadex.io/</a></li>
</ul>



<p>Second, after entering the game:</p>



<p>After entering the testnet site, you will see this beautiful scene. The SpartaDEX main screen shows your cities and a sub-menu with quick, alternate access to each building. On top of that, you can also see a button that toggles between the two modes: Game and DEX. The current connected network and wallet can be seen in the lower part of the menu.</p>



<p>If this is your first time interacting with SpartaDEX, clicking on any building will bring up a window saying that you have not created a city-state. You can start playing now or use the decentralized exchange feature.</p>



<p>If users want to experience the game part of SpartaDEX, they need an additional $100 of liquidity to mint the city state NFT.</p>



<p>After entering the city, the user needs to build buildings one by one and upgrade them. After the player builds the barracks, he can train troops to attack other targets or neutral players (multiplayer version is not online yet) and get rewards.</p>



<p>The rewards mainly consist of map NFT shards. Players can participate in the lottery by collecting NFT map pieces and eventually minting the map NFT. The specific awards still need to be made clear.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How to Airdrop $SPARTA Token?</h2>



<p>SpartaDEX will distribute a portion of SPARTA through blind mining and airdrop. Among them, blind mining accounts for 80% of token distribution, and users mine by locking up liquidity. The longer the liquidity lockup, the higher the mining profitability; The airdrop accounts for 20% of the token distribution and will be split into several release phases.</p>



<p>The best chance to get the $SPARTA token airdrop is (1) holding Spartan NFT and (2) interacting with the app:</p>



<p>The project team has confirmed that Spartan NFT holders are eligible for the future airdrop. All NFTs are prefabricated, but you can purchase an NFT in OpenSea.</p>



<p>The SpartaDex Test Network is now live on Polygon Mumbai. Currently, only whitelisted addresses (those that have completed the Galxe campaign) can interact with it. However, its mainnet will launch on Arbitrum later this year and is open to the public. Those who missed the whitelisted opportunity can then interact with the game for a chance to receive the airdrop.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Overall, SpartaDex is a unique concept of a decentralized exchange with a game layer implemented, built on Arbitrum. It allows users to develop their Spartan settlement, gather resources, recruit an army, and conquer barbarian territories. Yields and profits are directly related to the user&#8217;s progress through the game.</p>



<p>SpartaDex incentivizes whitelisted pool liquidity providers with their native $SPARTA token. Provide liquidity to selected partner project pairs that also reward with project tokens.</p>



<p>Importantly, SpartaDex confirmed the $SPARTA token airdrop for Spartan NFT holders and app users soon after the token launch so users can take advantage of the opportunity to get early investment in potential projects.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arbitrum DAO&#8217;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186913-arbitrum-daos-new-proposal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 06:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186913</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-501.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Arbitrum DAO&#039;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" title="Arbitrum DAO&#039;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue 7">The Arbitrum community has dispersed a percentage of the DAO's earnings to ARB token holders in accordance with the number of tokens each bearer has delegated.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-501.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Arbitrum DAO&#039;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" title="Arbitrum DAO&#039;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue 9">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Arbitrum is discussing giving 3,350 ETH to its DAO.</em></li>



<li><em>Once the protocol team fought with the community, Arbitrum established an incentive scheme.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Arbitrum community has <a href="https://forum.arbitrum.foundation/t/distribution-of-dao-revenue-to-arb-token-holders/14412" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">dispersed</a> a percentage of the DAO&#8217;s earnings to ARB token holders in accordance with the number of tokens each bearer has delegated.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-1024x576.png" alt="Arbitrum DAO&#039;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue" class="wp-image-186920" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-1024x576.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-1536x864.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-750x422.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500-1140x641.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-500.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Arbitrum DAO&#039;s New Proposal To Distribute 3,350 ETH In Fee Revenue 8"></a></figure></div>


<p>Arbitrum will give 3,352 ETH to its DAO, totaling more than $6 million, as part of the fees produced incentives.</p>



<p>The protocol further indicated that it would develop an income-sharing mechanism via the periodic activation of a smart contract. This will guarantee that the prizes are given on schedule. The project is anticipated to generate a more engaged and devoted user base, as well as distinguish Arbitrum from other institutions by its dedication to building a more profitable network for everybody.</p>



<p>The idea is still in the early stages of the debate, and the majority of the comments received so far indicate support for it.</p>



<p>Each Arbitrum One charge is broken into two parts: the L1 fee and the L2 fee. The DAO will get excess cash from the L1, base, and L2 fees, according to a revenue breakdown. The proposal would provide a revenue distribution system with delegated ARB tokens available for distribution.</p>



<p>According to Arbitrum, the move will offer ARB a purpose other than being a useless governance token, harmonizing community incentives. Several members, however, were concerned that the income distribution might define the ARB token as a security.</p>



<p>The daily active users on the popular layer-2 rollup ARB fell from a two-week peak in the recent 24 hours, prompting concerns about the spike&#8217;s long-term viability. Since its high in March, <a href="https://arbiscan.io/chart/tx" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">daily transactions</a> have decreased by more than half.</p>



<p>Arbitrum has declared that it will contribute any excess transaction fee earnings to DAO. The ARB token, on the other hand, is presently a pure governance token with no defined function, such as fee accrual or a burning mechanism.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186910-uniswap-overtakes-coinbase-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 06:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186910</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-499.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" title="Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row 10">Uniswap still looks to be slightly ahead of Coinbase, with trading volume surpassing the largest US exchange for the 4th time in a row.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-499.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" title="Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row 12">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Uniswap still looks to be slightly ahead of Coinbase, with trading volume surpassing the largest US exchange for the 4th time in a row.</em></li>



<li><em>The trading volume of both exchanges has fallen deeply since February.</em></li>



<li><em>The recent memecoin movement has also brought about active transactions on decentralized platforms.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Decentralized exchange (DEX) Uniswap beat centralized exchange Coinbase in terms of trading volume in April, marking the fourth consecutive month of this performance.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="512" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-1024x512.png" alt="Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row" class="wp-image-186915" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-1024x512.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-300x150.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-768x384.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-1536x768.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-360x180.png 360w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-750x375.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498-1140x570.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-498.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Uniswap Overtakes Coinbase For The 4th Time In A Row 11"></a></figure></div>


<p>According to <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/uniswap" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DeFiLlama</a> and <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/coinbase-exchange#statistics" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinGecko</a> statistics, both platforms had roughly $1.2 billion in volume on May 4, but Uniswap grew to $2.2 billion the following day, compared to Coinbase&#8217;s $1.3 billion.</p>



<p>Uniswap&#8217;s trading volume surpassed Coinbase&#8217;s in February, and although both exchanges&#8217; volumes have subsequently decreased, the DEX has stayed ahead of Coinbase.</p>



<p>In April, the DEX handled around $37 billion in transaction value, roughly half of its March number of $70 billion. However, Coinbase&#8217;s exchange recorded $34 billion in trade activity in April, down from $49 billion in March.</p>



<p>Uniswap is a decentralized trade mechanism with three variants available on six distinct blockchains, including Ethereum, Arbitrum, and Optimist. Coinbase, on the other hand, solely supports Ethereum and any EVM-compatible networks.</p>



<p>Although the current surge in activity might be linked to the meme coin craze, both platforms have been vying for second place in terms of trading volume since last year. In terms of volume, Uniswap centralized has already eclipsed Coinbase many times in 2022, notably following the bankruptcy of FTX last November, which drove traders away from platforms.</p>



<p>The DEX is the largest decentralized trading platform for users, having quadrupled the number of users in the last seven days compared to its nearest rival, PancakeSwap. According to Dune dashboard statistics, Uniswap represented 61% of all DeFi trade over the previous seven days in March.</p>



<p>Nonetheless, according to Coingecko, <a href="https://news.coincu.com/186546-binance-unveils-exclusive-capital-connect/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a> continues to be the clear leader, with trading volume over seven times that of the platforms.</p>



<p>The increase in Uniswap volume reflects the rising interest in decentralized exchanges. Although the current increase may be ascribed to the buzz surrounding meme currencies, the DEX&#8217;s protocol continues to gain market share due to its many variants on several blockchains, as well as its position as the industry leader in the decentralized trading sector.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186899-twitter-will-have-new-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 04:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[memecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position 13">Elon Musk announced on Thursday that he has selected a new CEO for Twitter.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-496.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position 16">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Elon Musk announced on Thursday that he has selected a new CEO for Twitter.</em></li>



<li><em>Twitter has recently selected a CEO, who will take over in six weeks, according to the technology billionaire.</em></li>



<li><em>Since taking charge, Musk has made modifications to content filtering and the blue-check verification mechanism.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Elon Musk has announced his intention to stand down as CEO of Twitter.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="614" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495-1024x614.png" alt="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position" class="wp-image-186906" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495-1024x614.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495-300x180.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495-768x461.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495-750x450.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495-1140x684.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-495.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position 14"></a></figure></div>


<p>Musk, who purchased Twitter last autumn and has been operating it since then, has often said that he is not the company&#8217;s permanent CEO. In a tweet on Thursday, the Tesla billionaire announced that he would become Twitter&#8217;s executive chairman and chief technical officer.</p>



<p>He said that he had selected a new CEO for X Corp., Twitter&#8217;s parent firm, who would likely take over in late June or early July. The unknown lady will succeed Musk, who purchased the social media network for $44 billion in October 2022.</p>



<p>He will be in charge of product, software, and system operations, according to the soon-to-be-former CEO. When Musk took over, he ousted prior CEO Parag Agrawal. Agrawal replaced Jack Dorsey, the platform&#8217;s co-founder, who started it in 2006.</p>



<p>Musk is a fervent proponent of cryptocurrencies, and he has voiced special fondness for the DOGE token meme. DOGE prices rose in many cases after Musk&#8217;s remarks, which were largely made on Twitter.</p>



<p>Nonetheless, DOGE, like the rest of the crypto market, is down over 30% from its top in April 2023 and is expected to fall further as a result of this revelation.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-497.png"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="800" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-497.png" alt="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position" class="wp-image-186908" title="Twitter Will Have New CEO As Elon Musk Resigns From His Position 15"></a></figure></div>


<p>The new CEO, who has yet to be chosen, will begin work in around six weeks. According to the <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/linda-yaccarino-in-talks-new-twitter-ceo-elon-musk-7a006bb5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Wall Street Journal</a></em>, this individual might be Linda Yaccarino, NBC Universal&#8217;s advertising business director. She was once the CEO of a Silicon Valley startup and a Hollywood executive. Linda interviewed Musk at a Miami event this month.</p>



<p>Tesla shares rose more than 2% immediately after the news, indicating investor satisfaction with the move.</p>



<p>While Twitter is still primarily a Web2 platform, it has made significant inroads into the crypto world. Musk&#8217;s and the media guy&#8217;s activities significantly impact the crypto community. Among the changes is replacing the famous bird emblem with a Shiba dog, the symbol of Musk&#8217;s favorite meme.</p>



<p>The day before, American business entrepreneur Elon Musk posted a parody including Milady NFT graphics, sending the collection&#8217;s average ETH selling price skyrocketing.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186897-irs-supports-ukraine-in-crypto-war/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 04:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IRS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ukraine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia 17">In pursuing sanctions evaders, the IRS criminal investigative division is increasing engagement with peers abroad.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-493.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia 20">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>In pursuing sanctions evaders, the IRS criminal investigative division is increasing engagement with peers abroad.</em></li>



<li><em>The agency collaborates with Chainalysis, a blockchain analytics company, and Ukrainian investigators.</em></li>



<li><em>Virtual training was attended by around 50 Ukrainian law enforcement professionals.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to a Thursday release, the US Internal Revenue Service (IRS) and crypto investigations firm Chainalysis is <a href="https://www.irs.gov/compliance/criminal-investigation/irs-ci-delivers-cyber-training-blockchain-analysis-tools-to-ukrainian-investigators-training-is-part-of-global-sanctions-related-enforcement-efforts" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">collaborating</a> with Ukraine to pursue Russian billionaires who may be utilizing cryptocurrency to avoid sanctions.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-492.png"><img decoding="async" width="2048" height="1365" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-492.png" alt="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia" class="wp-image-186901" title="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia 18"></a></figure></div>


<p>In the midst of Russia&#8217;s continuing invasion of Ukraine, the US and its private sector allies seek to assist Ukrainian authorities in preventing Russian actors from utilizing cryptocurrency to avoid sanctions, something European authorities have previously attempted to address.</p>



<p>The IRS Criminal Investigation (IRS-CI) section provides blockchain analysis tools to Ukrainian investigators. The IRS gave Ukraine licenses from the crypto investigative firm Chainalysis. Virtual training was attended by around 50 Ukrainian law enforcement professionals, with in-person training yet to follow. </p>



<p>According to the IRS, the measures are aimed at promoting information exchange and case development between the United States and Ukraine. IRS Criminal Investigation Head Jim Lee said in a statement:</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p class="has-small-font-size">“Sharing tools not only safeguards the US financial system, but the global economy.”</p>
</blockquote>



<p>Regulators, central bankers, and policymakers have warned that nations such as Russia and Iran may use cryptocurrency to circumvent international sanctions. Binance, the world&#8217;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange, is under investigation in the United States for allowing Russians to unlawfully use its website.</p>



<p>Crypto is currently too illiquid to facilitate large-scale Russian sanctions evasion, but it does occur on a smaller scale, according to Michael Gronager, co-founder and CEO of Chainalysis, during a conference call with reporters on Thursday. According to him, it is impossible to assess how much Russian oligarch money is coming through Ukraine since the effort to detect such transactions is ongoing.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-494.png"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="575" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-494.png" alt="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia" class="wp-image-186903" title="IRS Supports Ukraine In Crypto War Against Russia 19"></a></figure></div>


<p>Following Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine, the nations have utilized cryptocurrency to fund military operations, avoid sanctions, and aid humanitarian missions. Data suggests that cryptocurrency is not playing a significant part in Russia&#8217;s military effort. Yet, US politicians are worried that Russian billionaires may be exploiting crypto to avoid US and European economic sanctions.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186878-sec-vs-coinbase-the-agency-is-criticized/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Chamber of Commerce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully 21">While Coinbase attempts to get the SEC to respond to digital asset legislation, crypto groups step in.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-490.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully 24">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>While Coinbase attempts to get the SEC to respond to digital asset legislation, crypto groups step in.</em></li>



<li><em>The Chamber of Commerce has criticized the SEC&#8217;s attitude toward crypto exchanges.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) seems to be facing <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/5PWsXaPsqQ61gA9wlFWKEX/d1d3a27d35687082565770589ef9a3ac/Coinbase_-_Mandamus_Petition__TO_FILE_.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">strong opposition</a> from the parties because of the agency&#8217;s imposition in the Coinbase legal battle.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-489.png"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="675" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-489.png" alt="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully" class="wp-image-186892" title="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully 22"></a></figure></div>


<p>Many crypto organizations have joined the U.S.-based exchange in a series of &#8220;amicus&#8221; filings filed this week, claiming that the SEC is purposely ruining the new sector by insisting that there is nothing unusual or exceptional about crypto that deserves alternative treatment under securities rules.</p>



<p>On Thursday, the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit allowed the numerous organizations&#8217; motion to join the lawsuit.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p class="has-small-font-size">“It is no surprise that the SEC’s actions have crippled a nascent industry and sown confusion among countless firms unable to conform to the SEC’s view of the law or challenge that view in court,&#8221; said a brief from <a href="https://policy.paradigm.xyz/assets/writing/Coinbase-Amicus-File-Marked.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Paradigm</a>.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>The papers add to Coinbase&#8217;s request, made more than two weeks ago, to compel the SEC to reply to an earlier 2022 petition requesting that the agency issue guidelines defining cryptocurrency&#8217;s status in securities regulation. Although SEC Chair Gary Gensler has said that the agency has no intention of crafting unique regulations for cryptocurrency, the regulator is required to reply in the legal battle by May 13.</p>



<p>The US Chamber of Commerce also <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/assets/documents/U.S.-Chamber-Amicus-Brief-In-re-Coinbase-Third-Circuit.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">backed</a> Coinbase in an amicus brief submitted to the US Court of Appeals on May 9, accusing the SEC of intentionally creating a risky and unpredictable atmosphere for crypto firms operating in the nation.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-491.png"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="600" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-491.png" alt="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully" class="wp-image-186894" title="SEC vs. Coinbase: The Agency Is Criticized As A Bully 23"></a></figure></div>


<p>Coinbase now has the backing of one of the world&#8217;s top commercial groups. According to its website, the US Chamber of Commerce serves the interests of more than 3 million companies and organizations throughout the nation, ranging from local firms to worldwide corporations.</p>



<p>Notwithstanding the scale of the cryptocurrency markets and their prospective price, the SEC has failed to provide guidance to corporations. Instead, it continues to issue enforcement actions as well as ambiguous and conflicting public comments.</p>



<p>According to the Chamber, the SEC&#8217;s failure to participate in rulemaking or adopt a systematic approach jeopardizes due process, administrative law, and good governance.</p>



<p>The Crypto Council for Innovation, an industry advocacy group, also <a href="https://cryptoforinnovation.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CCI_Amicus-Brief-May-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">claims</a> that the SEC&#8217;s harsh posture against companies wanting to comply hampers investors&#8217; ability to distinguish between good and bad firms since the SEC paints them all with the same brush.</p>



<p>The crypto community believes that the Chamber&#8217;s engagement demonstrates the importance of the Coinbase vs. SEC lawsuit. The conclusion might have far-reaching repercussions for the digital asset industry and the US regulatory system.</p>



<p>The CEO of Ripple, a payment blockchain-based startup, Brad Garlinghouse, has repeatedly indicated that the lack of legislative certainty on crypto in the United States drives money overseas and stifles innovation.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186884-nyse-suspends-silvergate-230-jobs-cut/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cut staff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NYSE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silvergate bank]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silvergate Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut 25">Key points: Silvergate Capital shares are suspended from trading on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) on Wednesday, a large number of staffing will be cut today. On Thursday, the New York Stock Exchange announced delisting proceedings for Silvergate stock, citing delayed financial reports. The failed bank said in March that it would be shutting [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-16-1.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut 28">
<p><strong>Key points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Silvergate Capital shares are suspended from trading on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE).</em></li>



<li><em>Failed bank declares shut down after being hit by the crypto industry downturn.</em></li>



<li><em>About 230 job cuts will take effect from today.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Silvergate Capital shares are suspended from trading on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) on Wednesday, a large number of staffing will be cut today.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="683" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-1024x683.png" alt="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut" class="wp-image-186887" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-1024x683.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-300x200.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-768x512.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-2048x1365.png 2048w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-750x500.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-487-1140x760.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut 26"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>On Thursday, the New York Stock Exchange announced delisting proceedings for Silvergate stock, citing delayed financial reports.</p>



<p>The failed bank said in March that it would be shutting down after being hit by the downturn in the crypto industry, which is also cutting around 230 jobs, effective today.</p>



<p>Not stopping there, at least three more layoffs are expected, on June 30, August 30, and November 30 &#8220;or later,&#8221; the filing states. <a href="https://news.coincu.com/182697-3-silvergate-investor-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Silvergate</a> estimates the cost of layoffs will be around $13.6 million with severance, retention and bonus payments, and job referral programs.</p>



<p>Silvergate Bank&#8217;s parent company said in a securities filing that the approximately 80 remaining officers and employees at the company would focus on carrying out the bank&#8217;s liquidation, preserving the residual value of its assets while handling inquiries and investigations.</p>



<p>On March 9, the day Silvergate Capital said it was shutting down, shares fell 42% to $2.84. According to FactSet, the stock closed Wednesday at $1.25.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-488.png"><img decoding="async" width="685" height="437" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-488.png" alt="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut" class="wp-image-186888" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-488.png 685w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-488-300x191.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 685px) 100vw, 685px" title="NYSE Suspends Silvergate, 230 Jobs Will Be Cut 27"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>In addition, in a separate SEC filing dated May 11, the bank also said it was unable to file the legally required financial statements for the fiscal year 2022 and the first quarter of 2023 and &#8220;did not expect to be able&#8221; to file any similar reports in the future. It determines that it is in the &#8220;best interests&#8221; of stakeholders to &#8220;minimize costs and expenses&#8221; to preserve value. The company added that some of the staff cuts included were &#8220;critical&#8221; in the preparation of these filings.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Silvergate says it is done filing 10-Ks, 10-Qs and proxy statements, in large part because of &quot;the continuous developments relating to the regulatory and other inquiries and investigations that are pending with respect to the Company and the Bank&quot; <a href="https://t.co/1EpkRKAixt" target="_blank">https://t.co/1EpkRKAixt</a> <a href="https://t.co/i1D6S1daGP" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/i1D6S1daGP</a></p>&mdash; Bank Reg Blog (@bank_reg) <a href="https://twitter.com/bank_reg/status/1656654490731450368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">May 11, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>On March 8, Silvergate Capital announced for the first time that it would voluntarily liquidate Silvergate Bank.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#8217;s Shares: Report</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186874-binance-us-sell-changpeng-zhaos-shares/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CZ]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report 29">Binance US is working on founder Zhao Changpeng's strategy to reduce shareholding. CZ has been trying to sell his stake in the company since last summer.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-15-1.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report 32">
<p><strong>Key points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Binance US is looking to reduce the number of shares held by founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ).</em></li>



<li><em>CZ has been trying to sell his stake in the company since last summer.</em></li>



<li><em>The effort is said to be aimed at improving the exchange&#8217;s reputation with US regulators.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>According to <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/binance-us-explores-ways-to-cut-founder-changpeng-zhaos-majority-stake" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The Information</a>, Binance US is working on founder Zhao Changpeng&#8217;s strategy to reduce shareholding. Changpeng Zhao has been looking to sell his Binance US holdings since last summer.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-485.png"><img decoding="async" width="600" height="398" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-485.png" alt="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report" class="wp-image-186879" title="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report 30"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Executives at the US branch have considered accelerating CZ&#8217;s share reduction in recent weeks, ever since the Commodity Futures Trading Commission sued international crypto firm Binance and CZ for accused of violating US derivatives laws, which could help improve the company&#8217;s position in the eyes of US regulators.</p>



<p>The company is worried it may not be able to obtain some of the regulatory licenses it wants in the US while Zhao remains in a critical position, the report added.</p>



<p>In March, the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) <a href="https://news.coincu.com/176792-breaking-binance-and-cz-sued-by-cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sued</a> Binance and its CEO Zhao for operating what the regulator alleged was an &#8220;illegal&#8221; exchange and a &#8220;fake&#8221; compliance program.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-486.png"><img decoding="async" width="1280" height="720" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-486.png" alt="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report" class="wp-image-186880" title="Binance US Looking To Sell Most Of Changpeng Zhao&#039;s Shares: Report 31"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;The Commodity Futures Trading Commission today announced it has filed a civil enforcement action in the U.S. District Court for the Northern District of Illinois charging Changpeng Zhao and three entities that operate the Binance platform with numerous violations of the Commodity Exchange Act (CEA) and CFTC regulations. The complaint also charges Samuel Lim, Binance’s former chief compliance officer, with aiding and abetting Binance’s violations.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>



<p>In the course of ongoing litigation against the defendants, the agency seeks discord, civil fines, permanent registration, and trading bans, and permanent injunctions for further violations of the laws regulations of the CEA and CFTC, as charged.</p>



<p>Binance said the lawsuit was &#8220;unexpected and disappointing,&#8221; adding that it had made &#8220;substantial investments&#8221; over the past two years to ensure that US investors are not active on this platform.</p>



<p>The crypto industry is going through a tough time as tight regulatory constraints threaten the survival of industry service companies. Regulatory actions continued to erupt in early March after the industry lost two of its most significant connections to the mainstream financial world &#8211; Silvergate and Signature Bank.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186858-blockfi-customer-will-lose/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Kaplan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-482.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" title="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account 33">BlockFi was granted permission by a court on Thursday to restore $297 million to customers with non-interest-bearing accounts.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-482.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" title="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account 36">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BlockFi, the bankrupt cryptocurrency lender, was granted permission by a court on Thursday to restore $297 million to customers with non-interest-bearing accounts without compensating consumers who attempted to transfer cash into such accounts at the last minute, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-11/blockfi-crypto-customers-lose-fight-over-disputed-coin-transfers" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bloomberg</a></em> report.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-483.png"><img decoding="async" width="4000" height="3000" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-483.png" alt="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account" class="wp-image-186873" title="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account 34"></a></figure></div>


<p>Bankruptcy Judge Michael Kaplan decided against returning a further $375 million in cash that customers attempted to take from BlockFi&#8217;s interest-bearing accounts, known as BIA, after the business froze assets last year, as ripples from FTX&#8217;s demise swept across the crypto community.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p class="has-small-font-size">“The court finds that all digital assets held by the debtors in custodial omnibus wallets are indeed client property, and not property of the bankruptcy estates, subject, of course, to possible avoidance and clawback rights,” Kaplan said.</p>
</blockquote>



<p>Customers who owned custodial wallets, on the other hand, did not give up the same ownership rights.</p>



<p>Wallet transfers from interest-bearing accounts to custodial wallets did not occur after 8:15 p.m. EST on Nov. 10, according to Kaplan.</p>



<p>Customers who still had crypto in interest-bearing accounts &#8211; roughly $375 million in total &#8211; no longer had access to those assets, despite getting email and in-app confirmation from BlockFi.</p>



<p>BlockFi, situated in Jersey City, declared bankruptcy in November, intending to sell or restructure the firm to satisfy creditors. The decision is comparable to those reached in previous crypto-company bankruptcy proceedings. Celsius Network now controls the coins that users deposit in interest-bearing accounts, according to a federal court in New York.</p>



<p>BlockFi suspended transactions in early November of last year and declared bankruptcy on November 28. It rapidly followed FTX after the defunct exchange&#8217;s demise.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="683" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-1024x683.png" alt="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account" class="wp-image-186876" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-1024x683.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-300x200.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-768x512.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-2048x1365.png 2048w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-750x500.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-484-1140x760.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="BlockFi Customer Will Lose $375 Million In Interest Account 35"></a></figure></div>


<p>According to court documents, around $292 million in assets were stranded on the platform when users attempted to relocate them after the Nov. 10 suspension. Kaplan determined that the business may now terminate such transactions.</p>



<p>BlockFi was allowed further time in April to outline its bankruptcy plan. It has until May 15 to submit its departure strategy. Kaplan apparently granted the extension in the hopes of smoothing the case&#8217;s progression.</p>



<p>In an earlier court hearing, BlockFi attorney Michael Slade argued that allowing the $375 million in transfers would severely dilute the recovery for Wallet customers and could prevent BlockFi from returning any customer funds due to the practical difficulty of determining how to pay the additional Wallet claims from a fixed pool of assets.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Harold</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong> <strong>News</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports</title>
		<link>https://news.coincu.com/186860-coinbase-apologizes-pepe-reports/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foxy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[#Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pepe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.coincu.com/?p=186860</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports 37">Paul Grewal, the chief legal officer of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, tweeted that they misrepresented PEPE and apologized to the community.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1024" height="731" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-1024x731.png" class="webfeedsFeaturedVisual wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports" decoding="async" style="display: block; margin-bottom: 5px; clear:both;max-width: 100%;" link_thumbnail="" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-1024x731.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-300x214.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-768x549.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-120x86.png 120w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-350x250.png 350w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-750x536.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2-1140x814.png 1140w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Thumb-2023-Foxy-14-2.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports 40">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Paul Grewal, chief legal officer of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, apologized for Pepecoin&#8217;s inaccurate reports.</em></li>



<li><em>Earlier, the trading platform had released reports revealing the memecoin originated from an Internet meme and was seen as a symbol of right-wing hate, causing a storm of criticism on Twitter with the hashtag #deletecoinbase.</em></li>



<li><em>This has caused the PEPE token to drop more than 21% in the past 24 hours and Coinbase stock to drop more than 4%.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Paul Grewal, the chief legal officer of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, tweeted that they misrepresented PEPE and apologized to the community.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-481.png"><img decoding="async" width="889" height="500" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-481.png" alt="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports" class="wp-image-186868" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-481.png 889w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-481-300x169.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-481-768x432.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-481-750x422.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 889px) 100vw, 889px" title="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports 38"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>According to the Coinbase <a href="https://news.coincu.com/186732-coinbase-sparks-controversy-with-pepecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">newsletter</a>, the trading volume on the meme coin surpassed $2.3 billion last week, six times higher than the previous week and the highest level since May 2021. The rise of PEPE as the leading driving force behind the coin mania is an ongoing meme. PEPE has grown by nearly 55,000% since its release in mid-April, resulting in a market capitalization of $1.8 billion in less than three weeks, making it one of the fastest-growing tokens ever.</p>



<p>But the Cryptocurrency Exchange caused a stir by depicting the Pepe the Frog meme as originating from an Internet meme and seen as a symbol of right-wing hate. This led to a flurry of confusion on Twitter, with the hashtag #deletecoinbase trending on Twitter in the early hours of Thursday.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-small-font-size">
<p class="has-small-font-size">&#8220;The token is based on the Pepe the Frog meme, which first surfaced on the internet nearly 20 years ago as a comic-strip character,(…). Over time it has been co-opted as a hate symbol by alt-right groups, according to the Anti-Defamation League.&#8221;</p>
<cite>The Coinbase newsletter stated.</cite></blockquote>



<p>This prompted the exchange&#8217;s chief legal officer to post a tweet apologizing to the community for sharing a false introduction to PEPE, which did not accurately reflect the big picture, and Coinbase responded very sorry community. After receiving heavy criticism from the community, the report was immediately <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/bytes/archive/behind-the-memecoin-frenzy" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">edited</a>.</p>



<p>According to CoinMarketCap, PEPE has dropped more than 21% in the past 24 hours, and Coinbase stock has fallen more than 4%.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="466" src="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-1024x466.png" alt="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports" class="wp-image-186867" srcset="https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-1024x466.png 1024w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-300x136.png 300w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-768x349.png 768w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-1536x699.png 1536w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-2048x932.png 2048w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-750x341.png 750w, https://news.coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/image-480-1140x519.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Coinbase Legal Director Apologizes For Controversial PEPE Reports 39"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">24h PEPE price chart. Source: CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure></div>


<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news:&nbsp;<a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Foxy</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu</strong>&nbsp;<strong>News</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
