<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Avalanche soars as Ava Labs announces Amazon partnership</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-soars-as-ava-labs-announces-amazon-partnership/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-soars-as-ava-labs-announces-amazon-partnership/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-soars-as-ava-labs-announces-amazon-partnership/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche price soared more than 16% after Ava Labs announced new partnership with the Amazon Web Services (AWS). Avalanche will launch validator tools and its Subnet deployment feature on the AWS Marketplace. Ava Labs joins the AWS Activate and AWS Partner Network (APN). Avalanche price jumped more than 16% on Wednesday afternoon after Ava Labs, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-soars-as-ava-labs-announces-amazon-partnership/">Avalanche soars as Ava Labs announces Amazon partnership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Avalanche price soared more than 16% after Ava Labs announced new partnership with the Amazon Web Services (AWS).</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Avalanche will launch validator tools and its Subnet deployment feature on the AWS Marketplace.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Ava Labs joins the AWS Activate and AWS Partner Network (APN).</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche/">Avalanche price</a> jumped more than 16% on Wednesday afternoon after Ava Labs, the company helping to build the Avalanche blockchain, revealed a partnership with Amazon Web Services (AWS).</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time of writing, the native token AVAX was trading at $14.93, up 16.6% in the past 24 hours. Avalanche is currently trading 31% up over the past week.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The upside for the AVAX token followed the Ava Labs and AWS partnership news, with the collaboration between the two companies set &nbsp;to accelerate <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/blockchain/">blockchain</a> adoption for enterprises, institutions, and governments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership allows Avalanche users access to an easy infrastructure to deploy and manage nodes, the companies said.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bringing Avalanche Subnets to AWS Marketplace</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a <a href="https://medium.com/avalancheavax/ava-labs-and-aws-bring-scalable-blockchain-solutions-to-enterprises-and-governments-295040a34263" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> published on Wednesday, the companies said the collaboration will also strengthen the layer-1 blockchain network as well as increase its flexibility for developers. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AWS will support Avalanche&rsquo;s network infrastructure and decentralised applications (dApps) ecosystem, which will include one-click node deployment via the AWS Marketplace.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;I<em>&rsquo;m proud that we&rsquo;ve implemented a protocol that can accommodate millions of participants with near-instant finality</em>,&rdquo; said Emin G&uuml;n Sirer, founder and CEO of Ava Labs. &ldquo;<em>Our work with Amazon can accelerate the positive impact of Avalanche</em>,&rdquo; he added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership also means Avalanche nodes can now run in AWS GovCloud, while Ava Labs joins the AWS Partner Network (APN) and AWS Activate, the latter helping bring the benefits of AWS to the Avalanche ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>AWS Activate is an excellent resource for developers to bring apps to the masses with Avalanche&rsquo;s trailblazing speed, security, and scalability at their core</em>,&rdquo; John Wu, President of Ava Labs, said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With this affiliation, enterprises, institutions and governments can seamlessly launch custom Subnets, with the process involving only a few clicks, Avalanche wrote in a Medium post.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The blockchain platform will make this possible through integration of Subnet deployment, its scaling feature, as a managed service on the AWS Marketplace. Subnets help scale the Avalanche blockchain by diverting traffic, with users leveraging the functionality through the staking of AVAX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AWS connects over 100,000 partners and is available in more than 150 countries.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-soars-as-ava-labs-announces-amazon-partnership/">Avalanche soars as Ava Labs announces Amazon partnership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-soars-as-ava-labs-announces-amazon-partnership/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin SV price drops after Robinhood news</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-sv-price-drops-after-robinhood-news/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-sv-price-drops-after-robinhood-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 18:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SV News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-sv-price-drops-after-robinhood-news/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin SV dropped from highs near $45 to lows of $37 on major crypto exchanges. The BSV price fell as the market reacted to news from online trading app Robinhood, which will remove the coin from its crypto offerings later this month. BSV is a cryptocurrency forked from Bitcoin Cash in 2018. Bitcoin SV price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-sv-price-drops-after-robinhood-news/">Bitcoin SV price drops after Robinhood news</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Bitcoin SV dropped from highs near $45 to lows of $37 on major crypto exchanges.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The BSV price fell as the market reacted to news from online trading app Robinhood, which will remove the coin from its crypto offerings later this month.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>BSV is a cryptocurrency forked from Bitcoin Cash in 2018.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-sv/">Bitcoin SV price</a> fell more than 15% on Wednesday, trading down from highs near $45 to hit lows of $37 on major cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, the price of the native Bitcoin SV blockchain token had risen over the past week as crypto began 2023 with a relief rally.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But on Wednesday, the Bitcoin fork token plummeted amid news from online trading app Robinhood. Per a crypto <a href="https://robinhood.com/us/en/support/articles/bitcoin-sv-update/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">update</a> the platform provided on its website, support for BSV will end on 25 January 2023 at 06:59 pm ET.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What does this mean for users?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to Robinhood, customers can still buy, sell, hold or transfer BSV up to the indicated deadline. But while this is possible until then, the trading app will sell any BSV still held in Robinhood Crypto accounts at market value, the statement warned customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Once this step is taken, any proceeds from BSV sales will be credited to customers&rsquo; accounts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Robinhood explained its delisting of the BSV coin as a result of a regular review of the platform&rsquo;s crypto offerings. As of the announcement, the decision did not impact any other coins, with the statement emphasizing that users&rsquo; crypto remained safe on Robinhood.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin SV, or Bitcoin Satoshi Vision at the time of its fork from the Bitcoin Cash (BCH) coin in 2018, was trading around $40 at 13:02 pm ET. It remains more than 10% down in the past 24 hours and is over 91% down from its all-time high of $489 reached in April 2021.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-sv-price-drops-after-robinhood-news/">Bitcoin SV price drops after Robinhood news</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-sv-price-drops-after-robinhood-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Argo Blockchain mined 28% fewer bitcoins in December</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/argo-blockchain-mined-28-fewer-bitcoins-in-december/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/argo-blockchain-mined-28-fewer-bitcoins-in-december/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/argo-blockchain-mined-28-fewer-bitcoins-in-december/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Argo Blockchain mined 147 bitcoins in December 2022, down from 198 in November. Mining revenue was $2.49 million, compared to $3.46 million during the previous month. Argo sold its Helios facility to Galaxy Digital for $65 million as it looked to avoid nose-diving into bankruptcy. Argo Blockchain, a leading Bitcoin miner that endured a terrible [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/argo-blockchain-mined-28-fewer-bitcoins-in-december/">Argo Blockchain mined 28% fewer bitcoins in December</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Argo Blockchain mined 147 bitcoins in December 2022, down from 198 in November.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Mining revenue was $2.49 million, compared to $3.46 million during the previous month.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Argo sold its Helios facility to Galaxy Digital for $65 million as it looked to avoid nose-diving into bankruptcy.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Argo Blockchain, a leading <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/mine/">Bitcoin miner</a> that endured a terrible run in 2022 and came close to bankruptcy, has announced it mined 147 BTC only in December.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The publicly-traded company&rsquo;s total mined bitcoins for the month were lower than the 198 BTC mined in November &mdash; nearly 28% lower than its mining output in November.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mining revenue came in at $2.49 million (&pound;2.07 million), down from $3.46 million (&pound;2.94 million) in the previous month. &nbsp;The firm&rsquo;s mining margin in December 2022 was 48%, compared to 29% in November.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of 31 December, the miner held 141 bitcoins.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Argo CEO on reduced mining results</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to details provided in the miner&rsquo;s operational update <a href="https://argoblockchain.com/news-room/2022-december-operational-update" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> on 11 January, the decline in mining revenue (decreased mined coins) was mainly a result of the reduced mining operations following the winter storm that hit the United States in December.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Argo, like many other Texas Bitcoin miners, contributed to the stability of Texas&rsquo; power grid by cutting power usage during the storm.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While our mining results for December were lower than anticipated, the primary driver was the winter storm which led us to curtail operations at Helios. We made this decision in order to not only reduce power usage on the grid, but also to prioritise the needs of the local community and safety of our Helios employees,&nbsp;</em>Argo CEO Peter Wall said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, Argo sold its Helios facility for $65 million to Galaxy Digital and also agreed a $35 million loan as it sought to firm its balance sheet. But despite mining fewer BTC in December, and the sale of the Helios facility, Argo&rsquo;s total hashrate remains around 2.5 exahashes per second (EH/s).</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/argo-blockchain-mined-28-fewer-bitcoins-in-december/">Argo Blockchain mined 28% fewer bitcoins in December</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/argo-blockchain-mined-28-fewer-bitcoins-in-december/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX has recovered over $5B in assets: report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 16:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A bankruptcy attorney for crypto exchange FTX revealed on Wednesday that the platform had located over $5 billion in assets. The new assets includes cash and liquid crypto, adding to the $1 billion initially announced in December. FTX filed for bankruptcy in November 2022. In cryptocurrency news related to collapsed crypto exchange FTX, a bankruptcy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/">FTX has recovered over $5B in assets: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>A bankruptcy attorney for crypto exchange FTX revealed on Wednesday that the platform had located over $5 billion in assets.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The new assets includes cash and liquid crypto, adding to the $1 billion initially announced in December.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>FTX filed for bankruptcy in November 2022.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">cryptocurrency news</a> related to collapsed crypto exchange FTX, a bankruptcy attorney has revealed the recovery of over $5 billion worth of assets tied to the platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the latest <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/01/11/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-bankruptcy-attorney-says/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> on the matter, the recovered assets do not include roughly $425 million in digital assets being held by Bahamian regulator the Securities Commission of the Bahamas (SCB).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">FTX &lsquo;finds&rsquo; more assets</h2>
<p dir="ltr">FTX filed for bankruptcy in November 2022, with the exchange&rsquo;s new leadership stating in December that they could only locate $1 billion or so worth of assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, on Wednesday, FTX bankruptcy attorney noted the team had managed to find more than $5 billion. The amount includes cash, liquid crypto assets and investment securities whose value is pegged at prices when the petition was filed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the find adds to the claim holdings, it is yet to be established just how much the company owes creditors. When it filed for bankruptcy protection, it indicated an amount between $1 billion and $10 billion.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/">FTX has recovered over $5B in assets: report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reap Leverages Fireblocks to Enable Crypto Repayments with the Reap Card</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/reap-leverages-fireblocks-to-enable-crypto-repayments-with-the-reap-card/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/reap-leverages-fireblocks-to-enable-crypto-repayments-with-the-reap-card/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=99399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York, United States, 11th January, 2023, Chainwire Reap, the global fintech company powering expense management through the industry first Reap Visa Corporate Card (&#8220;Reap Card&#8221;) platform, launches industry-leading innovation by including cryptocurrency repayments functionality for the Web3 industry. Together with the Reap Card, Reap is offering expense management software that will enable web3 companies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/reap-leverages-fireblocks-to-enable-crypto-repayments-with-the-reap-card/">Reap Leverages Fireblocks to Enable Crypto Repayments with the Reap Card</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>New York, United States, 11th January, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://try.reap.global/en-hk/next-generation-reapcard/?utm_source=reap.global&amp;utm_medium=nav_bar&amp;utm_campaign=reap%20website&amp;_ga=2.199474606.1097810040.1673250951-958595543.1659576904&amp;_gac=1.19505738.1673250951.CjwKCAiA8OmdBhAgEiwAShr408DBrdEQZciQckawMWZHTq_lhL6hxcgD-IJAw55bd0n_U9yv9DV3-xoCKpgQAvD_BwE" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Reap</a>, the global fintech company powering expense management through the industry first Reap Visa Corporate Card (&ldquo;Reap Card&rdquo;) platform, launches industry-leading innovation by including cryptocurrency repayments functionality for the Web3 industry. Together with the Reap Card, Reap is offering expense management software that will enable web3 companies to settle their fiat payments with cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Daren Guo, Reap Co-Founder, said: &ldquo;We noticed a gap in the payments market involving web3 projects that face challenges for settling corporate expenses with non-fiat currencies like cryptocurrency. A seamless and scalable solution to convert crypto into fiat currently does not exist as traditional banks have not been able to settle on an industry standard for these web3 businesses. Reap is now able to bridge the gap between web3 businesses and the web2 fiat economy.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Security and stability are at the forefront of customers&rsquo; minds who leverage Web3 technologies. To build out a trusted ecosystem, Reap has integrated with Fireblocks, an easy-to-use platform to create new blockchain-based products and manage day-to-day digital asset operations.</p>
<p>Stephen Richardson, SVP of Financial Markets at Fireblocks, added: &nbsp;&ldquo;The security of digital assets is of paramount importance when it comes to building customer trust, which is why we are delighted to be working with Reap to power secure, frictionless payments for web3 creators. Reap&rsquo;s solution stands to improve operational efficiency for web3 projects, allowing founders and project owners to focus on building innovative products with greater peace of mind. We&rsquo;re proud to work with innovative companies like Reap that will enable the next generation of digital assets.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The Reap Card simplifies the process of settling global payments in fiat by using USDC, USDT, BTC, and ETH seamlessly to resolve the problem of costly handling fees that include multiple off-ramp parties. Digital provider Gnosis has already used this service to see firsthand how the Reap Card streamlines complicated currency conversion processes and billing issues, freeing up executive time to focus on core business operations.</p>
<p>&ldquo;As an early adopter of Reap Card, we have been able to take advantage of their innovative product suite and seamlessly settle payments in fiat currencies,&rdquo; said Dosh, Communication and Marketing Team at Gnosis. &ldquo;Reap&rsquo;s solution has been particularly useful for bypassing the difficulties and hurdles that often come with trying to use cryptocurrency to navigate the traditional banking system.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Reap envisions a future where every business, regardless of size and industry, has the opportunity to operate at its full potential by building and applying innovative financial solutions. Reap is committed to orchestrating success with all types of business to capture global opportunities, in an ever-changing competitive global marketplace.</p>
<h3><b>About Reap</b></h3>
<p><a href="https://try.reap.global/en-hk/next-generation-reapcard/?utm_source=reap.global&amp;utm_medium=nav_bar&amp;utm_campaign=reap%20website&amp;_ga=2.199474606.1097810040.1673250951-958595543.1659576904&amp;_gac=1.19505738.1673250951.CjwKCAiA8OmdBhAgEiwAShr408DBrdEQZciQckawMWZHTq_lhL6hxcgD-IJAw55bd0n_U9yv9DV3-xoCKpgQAvD_BwE" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Reap</a> is a financial platform that enables access and financial connectivity through innovation for companies of all sizes. Reap combines spend management software with a range of innovative payment products &mdash; including the flagship Reap Visa Corporate Credit Card. Reap is committed to helping businesses orchestrate success by providing the best financial tools that evolve with their customers and the market.</p>
<p>Reap is supported by industry-leading investors including Acorn Pacific Ventures, Arcadia Funds, HashKey Capital, Hustle Fund, Fresco Capital, Abacus Ventures and Payment Asia. Reap was founded in 2018 and has expanded to a team of over 40, working across offices in 7 countries.</p>
<p><a href="https://reap.global/en/newsroom/pressrelease/reap-raises-us-40-million-investment-in-their-series-a-funding-eyes-rapid-expansion/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Find out more here</u></a>. Media Inquiries- Reap <a href="http://media@reap.global/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>media@reap.global</u></a></p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Daniel Choy, daniel@reap.global</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/reap-leverages-fireblocks-to-enable-crypto-repayments-with-the-reap-card/">Reap Leverages Fireblocks to Enable Crypto Repayments with the Reap Card</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/reap-leverages-fireblocks-to-enable-crypto-repayments-with-the-reap-card/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fireblocks, Collider and MarketAcross to host Web3 startups event</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-collider-and-marketacross-to-host-web3-startups-event/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-collider-and-marketacross-to-host-web3-startups-event/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-collider-and-marketacross-to-host-web3-startups-event/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fireblocks, Collider and MarketAcross will host the Building Blocks 23 event in Tel Aviv on 7 February 2023. The ETH TLV event will feature speakers such as blockchain sceptic Udi Wertheimer and SSV Network CEO Alon Muroch. The one-day event seeks to boost Web3 entreprenuership. Building Blocks 23, a one-day web3-focused event set to bring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-collider-and-marketacross-to-host-web3-startups-event/">Fireblocks, Collider and MarketAcross to host Web3 startups event</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.buildingblockstlv.com/"></a><em><strong>Fireblocks, Collider and MarketAcross will host the Building Blocks 23 event in Tel Aviv on 7 February 2023.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The ETH TLV event will feature speakers such as blockchain sceptic Udi Wertheimer and SSV Network CEO Alon Muroch.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The one-day event seeks to boost Web3 entreprenuership.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Building Blocks 23, a one-day web3-focused event set to bring top together developers and community members in the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> ecosystem, will happen in Tel Aviv.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Details on the 7 February, 2023 ETH TLV event highlight three major Israeli companies as the hosts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Accordingly, the <a href="https://www.buildingblockstlv.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Building Blocks 23</a> event will be organised by digital assets focused venture capital fund Collider, blockchain PR and marketing firm MarketAcross, and enterprise-grade crypto platform Fireblocks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The hosts will collaborate with Israeli-based zero knowledge proof technology provider StarkWare, a press release shared with <em>CoinJournal</em> revealed.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The Who and what of Building Blocks 23</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Building Blocks 23 is targeted at forming the foundations of Web3 entrepreneurship and will offer participants access to a series of events &ndash; including workshops and panel discussions. The organisers will look to guide representatives of various projects through the process of building successful Web3 businesses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the topics to be covered are fundraising, product marketing, creating a security-first organisation and building teams and communities around projects. Valuable lessons on offer will be the art of building in Web3, mastery of leading protocols, and how to navigate the inevitable market turbulence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Delegates will also learn from industry leaders on issues such as treasury management, sustainable tokenomics and effective branding.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Udi Wertheimer, a blockchain sceptic and Ethereum expert is on the confirmed list of guest speakers, as is Alon Muroch, CEO of SSV Network. There will also be speakers from across the industry, including from The Graph, Aave, Safe, Avalanche, and Solidus Labs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-collider-and-marketacross-to-host-web3-startups-event/">Fireblocks, Collider and MarketAcross to host Web3 startups event</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/fireblocks-collider-and-marketacross-to-host-web3-startups-event/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venom Foundation in Partnership With Iceberg Capital Launches $1 Billion Venom Ventures Fund</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-in-partnership-with-iceberg-capital-launches-1-billion-venom-ventures-fund/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-in-partnership-with-iceberg-capital-launches-1-billion-venom-ventures-fund/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire  ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=99392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abu Dhabi, Abu Dhabi, 11th January, 2023, Chainwire Venom Foundation, the first Layer-1 blockchain licensed and regulated by the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), and Iceberg Capital, an ADGM regulated investment manager, officially announce that they have partnered to launch a $1 billion venture fund called Venom Ventures Fund (VVF). The blockchain-agnostic fund will invest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-in-partnership-with-iceberg-capital-launches-1-billion-venom-ventures-fund/">Venom Foundation in Partnership With Iceberg Capital Launches $1 Billion Venom Ventures Fund</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Abu Dhabi, Abu Dhabi, 11th January, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Venom Foundation, the first Layer-1 blockchain licensed and regulated by the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), and Iceberg Capital, an ADGM regulated investment manager, officially announce that they have partnered to launch a $1 billion venture fund called Venom Ventures Fund (VVF).</p>
<p>The blockchain-agnostic fund will invest in innovative protocols and Web3 dApps, focusing on long-term trends such as payments, asset management, DeFi, banking services, and GameFi. It aims to become the leading supporter of the next-generation digital technologies and entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>Venom Ventures Fund (VVF) will leverage Iceberg Capital&rsquo;s network, expertise, and capabilities to offer incubation programs and access to an extensive industry network. Furthermore, it will assist the investee projects with marketing, exchange listing, technical, legal, and regulatory support.</p>
<p>The fund&rsquo;s leadership team consists of some of the world&rsquo;s most experienced traditional finance and blockchain professionals; including Peter Knez, ex-CIO at BlackRock and Mustafa Kheriba, a seasoned and well-known investment professional with an impressive track record in the MENA region. Mustafa has served on the Board of Directors of several financial services and insurance companies in the Middle-east and Europe.</p>
<p>Operated by Iceberg Capital, the fund will be investing in projects and teams from pre-seed to Series A rounds. It will strive to accelerate the adoption of blockchain, DeFi, and Web3 while generating long-term value for investors.</p>
<p>Mustafa Kheriba, the Executive Chairman of Iceberg Capital, said &ldquo;<i>We are thrilled to partner with Venom Foundation, launching their new $1 billion fund. Even though the blockchain industry is witnessing a steep correction in prices, we believe that builders will continue to build and innovate. With Venom Ventures, we will be providing financial, technical, and marketing support to the most promising teams and projects in Web3 space to help them bring their visions to life.</i>&rdquo;</p>
<p>The Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM) is an international financial center and free zone that provides market participants with a world-class legal system and regulatory regime. Established and operated by ADGM regulated entities, Venom Ventures Fund (VVF) will be transparent and will adhere to the regulations.</p>
<p>Peter Knez, Chairman of Venom Ventures, said, <i>&ldquo;I am delighted to be a part of the launch of our new Venture Capital fund here in Abu Dhabi. I am excited to work with a team of experienced investment professionals and talented people from the crypto industry, and we are ready to allocate strategic investments in the most innovative web3 start-ups that are poised for mass adoption. Our mission is to transform digital asset management and make a lasting impact on the industry. Venom is the ideal platform for us to achieve this goal.&rdquo;</i></p>
<p>Venom Ventures Fund (VVF) leads the $20 million funding in N&uuml;mi Metaverse</p>
<p>The fund has made its first investment, leading N&uuml;mi Metaverse&rsquo;s $20 million funding round. N&uuml;mi Metaverse is a universal platform for creators, innovators, and followers. N&uuml;mi will launch its &lsquo;Visual Novel&rsquo; in 2023, a mini-game experience with a range of special prizes for players.</p>
<p>N&uuml;mi will also launch VR metaverse by the end of this year, followed by a PC and mobile version in 2024. The N&uuml;mi investment showcases the fund&rsquo;s investment strategy. Developers and builders working on innovative Web3 projects are invited to apply for funding through the<a href="https://www.venom.ventures/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u> Venom Ventures Fund website</u></a>.</p>
<h2>About Iceberg Capital</h2>
<p>Iceberg Capital Limited is regulated by FSRA as a Prudential Category 3C investment manager based in ADGM. Iceberg Capital is a fast-growing alternative asset management company that provides diversified investment management platforms that includes direct and private equity, venture capital, technology, and virtual assets. Iceberg Capital also offers traditional asset management services such as investment portfolios in local and international markets, financial instruments (equities, ETFs, commodities, derivatives, etc), as well as specialized platforms for securities, and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>For more information about Iceberg Capital, visit: <a href="http://www.icebergcapital.ae" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Website</u></a> | <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/icebergcapital/?" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>LinkedIn</u></a></p>
<h2>About Venom Foundation</h2>
<p>Venom is the world&rsquo;s first regulated blockchain. The decentralized network operates under the jurisdiction of the ADGM, with a license to issue utility tokens. The ADGM is an oasis for investors and financial services firms, positioning Venom as the world&rsquo;s first compliant blockchain, affording authorities and enterprises the freedom to build, innovate, and scale.</p>
<p>A portfolio of in-house dApps and protocols has been developed on the Venom blockchain by various companies. It now harbors the potential to become a bridge for the adoption of CBDCs in the Middle East, North Africa, and worldwide.</p>
<p>For more information about Venom Ventures, visit: <a href="http://www.venom.ventures" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Website</u></a> &nbsp;| &nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/VenomVentures" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Twitter</u></a></p>
<p>For more information about Venom Foundation, visit: <a href="http://www.venom.foundation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Website</u></a> &nbsp;| &nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/Venomfoundation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Twitter</u></a></p>
<h2>Contact</h2>
<p>Adam Newton, pr@venom.ventures</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-in-partnership-with-iceberg-capital-launches-1-billion-venom-ventures-fund/">Venom Foundation in Partnership With Iceberg Capital Launches $1 Billion Venom Ventures Fund</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-in-partnership-with-iceberg-capital-launches-1-billion-venom-ventures-fund/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GALA price falls after Gala Games deletes Hollywood star partnership tweet</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-price-falls-after-gala-games-deletes-hollywood-star-partnership-tweet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-price-falls-after-gala-games-deletes-hollywood-star-partnership-tweet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the time of writing, GALA token had dropped by more than 11%. Gala Games is under fire after secretly deleting a tweet announcing their partnership with Hollywood stars. This comes after GALA shot up by more than 70%to above $0.051. Metaverse cryptocurrency GALA price has dropped considerably in the past few hours after the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-price-falls-after-gala-games-deletes-hollywood-star-partnership-tweet/">GALA price falls after Gala Games deletes Hollywood star partnership tweet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At the time of writing, GALA token had dropped by more than 11%.</li>
<li>Gala Games is under fire after secretly deleting a tweet announcing their partnership with Hollywood stars.</li>
<li>This comes after GALA shot up by more than 70%to above $0.051.</li>
</ul>
<p>Metaverse cryptocurrency <a href="https://coinjournal.net/gala/">GALA price</a> has dropped considerably in the past few hours after the parent firm Gala Games deleted a <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames/status/1612299581731086337">tweet announcing its partnership</a> with several Hollywood stars including The Rock. &nbsp;What has irked most crypto followers is that Gala Games deleted the tweet without offering any explanation.</p>
<p>The tweet that Gala Games had posted on Monday stating that it was working with Dwayne &ldquo;The Rock&rdquo;, Mark Wahlberg, and Johnson pushed the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-token-soars-68-as-hollywood-stars-team-up-with-gala-games/">price of GALA up by more than 70%</a>, the highest price the token has reached since September 2022.</p>
<p>The tweet stated that the game development platform was <em>&ldquo;developing two films with the Rock (aka Dwayne Johnson) and Mark Wahlberg! Two absolutely huge forces in the entertainment industry. You&rsquo;ve seen their work on screen, but I think their presence might be even more powerful off the screen and we are so happy to get the chance to work with them.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Gala Game&rsquo;s silence after deleting post</h2>
<p>Several Twitter handles have been created questioning how genuine the announcement was. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Nevertheless, despite today&rsquo;s pullback, GALA still remains the top mover for the month among the gaming tokens. GALA has gained about 130% while The Sandbox&rsquo;s SAND token has only surged by 30%, and Decentraland&rsquo;s MANA has risen by 22%.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-price-falls-after-gala-games-deletes-hollywood-star-partnership-tweet/">GALA price falls after Gala Games deletes Hollywood star partnership tweet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AGIX price defies gravity as Singularity demand soars</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/agix-price-defies-gravity-as-singularity-demand-soars/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/agix-price-defies-gravity-as-singularity-demand-soars/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 13:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/agix-price-defies-gravity-as-singularity-demand-soars/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SingularityNET&#8217;s token has risen in the past six days and moved to its October high. It has surged by over 200% from its lowest point in 2022. AGIX price has defied gravity in the past few days. SingularityNET&#8217;s token has soared in the past six straight days and is trading at $0.10, the highest point [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/agix-price-defies-gravity-as-singularity-demand-soars/">AGIX price defies gravity as Singularity demand soars</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">SingularityNET&rsquo;s token has risen in the past six days and moved to its October high.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It has surged by over 200% from its lowest point in 2022.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">AGIX price has defied gravity in the past few days. SingularityNET&rsquo;s token has soared in the past six straight days and is trading at $0.10, the highest point since October 14. The coin has jumped by more than 204% from the lowest level in 2022. It has seen its market cap surge to more than $115 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is SingularityNET?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">SingularityNET is a blockchain project that seeks to incorporate concepts on artificial general intelligence (AGI) that is not dependent on any central entity. The platform is built on top of Cardano&rsquo;s blockchain. Some of its top partners are Ocean Protocol, Cisco, and Binance Connect.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Singularity&rsquo;s ecosystem has been growing. It includes projects in industries like DeFi, gaming, arts, and enterprise AI among others. Some of the top apps in its ecosystem are SingularityDAO, Nunet, Rejuve, Sophia Verse, Awakening Health, and Jam Galaxy among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SingularityDAO is a decentralised portfolio management protocol designed to enable anyone to safely and easy manage their crypto assets. Nunet, on the other hand, builds infrastructure providing distributed computing and storage for decentralised networks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the most important achievements made by SingularityNet in 2022 were its AI model training. It also initiated design for&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/"><u>Cardano</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>platform marketplace.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SingularityNET?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SingularityNET</a>&rsquo;s decentralized AI marketplace saw strong growth in 2022, and with projects funded by <a href="https://twitter.com/DeepFunding?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@DeepFunding</a> (Round 2 = open) actively developing <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AI</a> agents we'll see a massive expansion in 2023! Read our Year End review here:<a href="https://t.co/ZWJEdIDS4r">https://t.co/ZWJEdIDS4r</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BuildingOnCardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BuildingOnCardano</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AGI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AGI</a> <a href="https://t.co/c8wb6s6gUt">pic.twitter.com/c8wb6s6gUt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; SingularityNET (@Singularity_NET) <a href="https://twitter.com/Singularity_NET/status/1612167257593118721?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">It is still unclear why the AGIX price has jumped sharply in the past few days. A likely reason for the rally is the strong performance of Cardano, which has soared to the highest point in months. Another reason is that investors believe that the platform&rsquo;s ecosystem will continue growing this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">And like other cryptocurrencies, AGIX price has risen because of macro factors. Data published last Friday showed that wage inflation has started cooling. With the broad inflation falling, investors believe that the Fed will start turning a bit dovish.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AGIX price forecast</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/11/1673442352969-3638e6f7-0cb8-4161-9c02-e92a06234fa8.png" style="width: 558px;height: 258.54px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="558" height="258.54"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/AGIXUSD/?exchange=BINANCE"><u>AGIX/USD chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the SingularityNET price has done well in the past few days. It has risen in the past six straight days and moved to the highest point since October. As it rose, the token jumped above the important resistance level at $0.072, the highest point on December 12. It has rallied above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has soared above the overbought level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I suspect that this rebound will come to an end soon. If this happens, the next key support level to watch will be at $0.072.&nbsp;</p>
<h2><span dir="LTR">How to buy SingularityNET</span></h2>
<p><span dir="LTR"></span></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/agix-price-defies-gravity-as-singularity-demand-soars/">AGIX price defies gravity as Singularity demand soars</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/agix-price-defies-gravity-as-singularity-demand-soars/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
