<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:34:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin is not headed for new lows: Scott Melker</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-not-headed-for-new-lows-scott-melker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=150623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wolf of All Street&#8217;s host Scott Melker is constructive on Bitcoin. He explained why in an interview with Yahoo Finance today. BTC has tumbled from $31,000 to $26,000 in about six weeks. Bitcoin is still a bull market despite the sharp sell-off in recent weeks, says Scott Melker &#8211; Host of &#8220;The Wolf of All [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-not-headed-for-new-lows-scott-melker/">Bitcoin is not headed for new lows: Scott Melker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Wolf of All Street&rsquo;s host Scott Melker is constructive on Bitcoin.</li>
<li>He explained why in an interview with Yahoo Finance today.</li>
<li>BTC has tumbled from $31,000 to $26,000 in about six weeks.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> is still a bull market despite the sharp sell-off in recent weeks, says Scott Melker &ndash; Host of &ldquo;The Wolf of All Streets&rdquo; podcast.</p>
<h2>Melker remains constructive on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency has retreated from over $31,000 to the sub $26,000 level in about six weeks &ndash; fragility that Melker attributes to a &ldquo;long squeeze&rdquo;.</p>
<p>But he remains confident that Bitcoin is not at all doomed to make a new low in the coming months. Defending his view on <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/video/bitcoin-no-reason-suspect-headed-211158422.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Yahoo Finance</a>, the crypto trader and investor said:</p>
<blockquote><p>I don&rsquo;t think there&rsquo;s reason to suspect we&rsquo;ll go to new lows like we did after the FTC collapse unless we have some other massive black swan event. I don&rsquo;t see that in cards.</p></blockquote>
<p>Note that <a href="https://dailyhodl.com/2023/08/16/crypto-analyst-forecasts-big-bitcoin-btc-move-to-40000-heres-his-timeline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jason Pizzino</a> also recently said that BTC could soon be worth over $42,000.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin has strong support at $25,000 level</h2>
<p>Scott Melker announced $25,000 as a key level to watch in Bitcoin &ndash; as long it&rsquo;s trading above that level, it&rsquo;s still in a bull market, he added.</p>
<p>The crypto expert sticks the probability of a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-delays-decision-on-ark-invest-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> being approved by the Securities &amp; Exchange Commission this year at 65%. He&rsquo;s constructive on BTC also because the big players have been loading up on it for months.</p>
<blockquote><p>If you look at the way Bitcoin has moved over the past four years, we&rsquo;re in the midst of another four-year cycle in the exact same place that we were last time.</p></blockquote>
<p>The total supply of Bitcoin is slated to <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/au/investing/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halve</a> in the second quarter of 2024 &ndash; an event that&rsquo;s historically delivered a boost to its price.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-not-headed-for-new-lows-scott-melker/">Bitcoin is not headed for new lows: Scott Melker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu token is thriving despite the painful crypto sell-off</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 22:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies plunged hard last week. This decline happened amid a sense of fear in the financial market. Shiba Memu token sale has gained steam as the developers raised over $2.1 million. Cryptocurrency prices had their worst performance this year as Bitcoin plunged from $29,000 to below $26,000. Most coins and tokens were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/">Shiba Memu token is thriving despite the painful crypto sell-off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies plunged hard last week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This decline happened amid a sense of fear in the financial market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu token sale has gained steam as the developers raised over $2.1 million.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>Cryptocurrency prices</u></a> had their worst performance this year as Bitcoin plunged from $29,000 to below $26,000. Most coins and tokens were <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/over-a-billion-dollars-liquidated-in-cryptos-worst-day-since-ftx/"><u>deeply in the red</u></a> as demand waned and a sense of fear spread in the market. Despite this retreat, Shiba Memu&rsquo;s token sale continued, with the developers raising over $2.18 million.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did cryptocurrencies slip?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are several reasons why most cryptocurrencies plunged last week. First, the coins dropped because of a potential shakeout. A shakeout refers to a situation where a financuial asset dips sharply and then resumes the bullish trend.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The most recent shakeout happened when Bitcoin fell from $25,000 to $19,000 and then resumed the bullish comeback to the year-to-date high of $32,000. It is still unclear whether the current decline was a shakeout or the start of a new bear run.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, Bitcoin dropped because of technical reasons.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> formed a double-top pattern at $32,000. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually a bearish sign. Therefore, from these technicals, there is a likelihood that the coin will continue falling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Third, a sense of fear spread in the market as evidenced by the stock and bond market sell-off. Bond yields in most developed countries jumped, with US 10-year rising to 2012 highs and the 30-year reaching the 2007 highs. Bond yields move inversely to prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, cryptocurrency prices dropped because of the Chinese economy, which is going through the deepest slowdown in years. Data published last week showed that most parts of the economy like retail, industrial production, and fixed asset investments are slowing at a fast pace. China is still an integral part in the crypto industry, accounting for 20% of Binance volume.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is still thriving</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu, an upcoming cryptocurrency that combines aspects of meme coins and artificial intelligence, is thriving. Data available in its website shows that the developers have raised over $2.1 million from investors around the world. They have done that by raising over 68.1 million tokens in the past two months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s token sale is unique because the price of the token is raised every days. This means that investors who bought the token on the first day have seen their value jump sharply even without doing anything.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is thriving because of the industries that the developers are targeting. AI has become the fastest-growing industry this year, helping to push Nvidia&rsquo;s market cap to over $1 trillion. Similarly, meme coins have thrived, with some tokens like Pepe transforming some people into instant millionaires.</p>
<p>With the rising hype, there is a likelihood that the Shiba Memu price will also jump when it debuts in centralized and decentralized exchanges soon. You can buy the Shiba Memu token&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/">Shiba Memu token is thriving despite the painful crypto sell-off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB price: headwinds mount, bulls could fall off cliff</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-price-bnb-headwinds-mount-bulls-could-fall-off-cliff/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-price-bnb-headwinds-mount-bulls-could-fall-off-cliff/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Coin (BNB) price is traded to lows of $204 after breaking below $210 and $208. Declines for BNB come amid strong headwinds around Binance.&#160; BNB could drop to lows of $180 nad lower if bulls give up $200 zone. BNB price has broken below a key level as regulatory headwinds and latest issues around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-price-bnb-headwinds-mount-bulls-could-fall-off-cliff/">BNB price: headwinds mount, bulls could fall off cliff</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance Coin (BNB) price is traded to lows of $204 after breaking below $210 and $208.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Declines for BNB come amid strong headwinds around Binance.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">BNB could drop to lows of $180 nad lower if bulls give up $200 zone.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/">BNB price</a> has broken below a key level as regulatory headwinds and latest issues around payments partners add to the broader downside pressure around the native Binance coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, BNB traded to lows of $204 on Tuesday, with price down nearly 2% in the past 24 hours as of writing. Binance&rsquo;s native coin has declined more than 14% in the past week. At current levels BNB is trading below a key technical support line and weakness could see bears push for the crucial $200 area.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The last time BNB decisively broke below the zone was in June 2022 after the Terra and Three Arrows Capital collapse. Prices wicked to lows of $183 then.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is BNB price down today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has faced multiple regulatory hurdles over the past several months. Among them is a lawsuit by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which sued the crypto exchange in June. BNB price fell sharply at the time, dropping from highs of $306 to lows of $230.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency has struggled since, with the latest developments likely to have contributed to the downward pressure being reports that the support for euro deposits and withdrawals had been halted.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, Binances EUR payments partner Paysafe <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binances-eur-banking-partner-announces-plan-to-halts-support/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> in June that it would be halting support for the company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As reported <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/checkout-com-terminates-binance-support-over-aml-concerns-report/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>, Binance has also recently suffered a setback after digital payments platform Checkout.com ended its relationship with the crypto exchange.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance Coin price outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The confluence of Binance-related issues and the weakness across risk asset markets sees BNB price face potential dip to lowest level in more than a year. This scenario is strengthened by the technical outlook for BNB/USD as seen on the weekly chart.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/22/1692725569765-2b21db4b-27e7-493f-a2bf-88d3ffd73f28.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="267"><span class="fr-inner">BNB price on the weekly chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Y8OWdAnR/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>TradingView</u></a></span></span></span></div>
<p dir="ltr">On the 4-hour chart below, the RSI and MACD indicators suggest bearish strength as is the exponential moving average and funding rate. Erroneous&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/22/1692725671471-7e1b426c-9bdc-4808-94bb-bb0fdf12c821.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="267"><span class="fr-inner"></span></p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB price on the 4-hour chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/92st1ZGo/"><u>TradingView</u></a></p>
<p></p></span>
<p></p></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">In BNB&rsquo;s case, the path of least resistance appears to be downward and key to this is the $200 level. Break this and bears could have easy targets towards the $180 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">However, should price action push prices higher, reclaiming $210 will be critical to pulling bulls back to the $220-$250 region.</p>
</div>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-price-bnb-headwinds-mount-bulls-could-fall-off-cliff/">BNB price: headwinds mount, bulls could fall off cliff</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 travel ecosystem Camino Network passes Hexens security audit</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/web3-travel-ecosystem-camino-network-passes-hexens-security-audit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 16:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/web3-travel-ecosystem-camino-network-passes-hexens-security-audit/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Firms in the travel sector, including Lufthansa, EuroWings, Hahn Air, and Sunnycars, have backed the Camino Network consortium blockchain. Hexens has previously audited well-known projects like Polygon Labs, Celo, and Lido. Camino Network is also inviting white-hat hackers for a $50,000 bounty program. The Camino Network Foundation has announced that the Web3 travel ecosystem Camino [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/web3-travel-ecosystem-camino-network-passes-hexens-security-audit/">Web3 travel ecosystem Camino Network passes Hexens security audit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Firms in the travel sector, including Lufthansa, EuroWings, Hahn Air, and Sunnycars, have backed the Camino Network consortium blockchain.</li>
<li>Hexens has previously audited well-known projects like Polygon Labs, Celo, and Lido.</li>
<li>Camino Network is also inviting white-hat hackers for a $50,000 bounty program.</li>
</ul>
<p>The Camino Network Foundation has announced that the Web3 travel ecosystem Camino Network has successfully completed a security audit conducted by the renowned cybersecurity company Hexens with great results.</p>
<p>Camino Network, which was introduced earlier this year, is a public, permissioned Web3 blockchain that anyone may build on. By enabling users to create and deploy decentralized applications backed by smart contracts, it will revolutionize the travel sector and usher in a new era of travel-related goods and services. Numerous significant firms in the travel sector, including well-known names like Lufthansa, EuroWings, Hahn Air, and Sunnycars, have backed the Camino Network consortium blockchain.</p>
<h2>Camino Network security audit</h2>
<p>Since Camino Network has always placed a high focus on security, it set out to locate a dependable and trustworthy partner to audit its sizable codebase and offer suggestions for patching any vulnerabilities.</p>
<p>The Camino Network Foundation ultimately decided to collaborate with Hexens, which has considerable experience reviewing the code for smart contracts and blockchain infrastructure, having previously worked on well-known projects like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/what-is-polygon/">Polygon</a>, Celo, and Lido.</p>
<p>Hexens is regarded as a pioneer in the creation of fresh bug-finding methods and employs the industry&rsquo;s known procedures and workflows to uncover vulnerabilities and provide recommendations.</p>
<p>Nine minor flaws were found during Hexens&rsquo; audit of Camino Network&rsquo;s L1 codebase; each was swiftly fixed by the team to maintain the network&rsquo;s reliability. The adherence to excellent coding methods and emphasis on strong security is demonstrated by the absence of any significant vulnerabilities.</p>
<h2>Camino Network bug bounty program</h2>
<p>Following the audit, the Foundation hired Hexens to continually contribute actively to its security. Through cooperation, Camino Network can ensure the travel industry that maintaining the security of the ecosystem is one of its top goals.</p>
<p>To that aim, Camino Network has established a formal bug bounty program, asking white-hat hackers to evaluate the security of its network in exchange for payments of up to $50,000 for the discovery of serious flaws.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/web3-travel-ecosystem-camino-network-passes-hexens-security-audit/">Web3 travel ecosystem Camino Network passes Hexens security audit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Long-term holders weather brief volatility surge</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/long-term-holders-weather-brief-volatility-surge/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/long-term-holders-weather-brief-volatility-surge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/long-term-holders-weather-brief-volatility-surge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Long-term holders now hold 75% of the total circulating supply of Bitcoin The cohort has been growing steadily over the last eighteen months Enthusiasts hope the growth in the number of coins hoarded by long-term holders will cause a supply shortage and squeeze the price upward in the long-term The last eighteen months [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/long-term-holders-weather-brief-volatility-surge/">Long-term holders weather brief volatility surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Long-term holders now hold 75% of the total circulating supply of Bitcoin</li>
<li dir="ltr">The cohort has been growing steadily over the last eighteen months</li>
<li dir="ltr">Enthusiasts hope the growth in the number of coins hoarded by long-term holders will cause a supply shortage and squeeze the price upward in the long-term</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">The last eighteen months have been challenging for Bitcoin investors. While the asset has bounced back strongly thus far in 2023, it remains over 60% off its all-time high set in November 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The scale of the damage in 2022 can be seen when glancing at a price chart, portraying the extent of the fall.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14783018">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The asset careened downwards as the Federal Reserve transitioned to a tight monetary policy approach in response to spiralling inflation. From years of low interest rates, hikes came thick and fast as policymakers scrambled to get a lid on an overheating economy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14783063">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">With Bitcoin residing so far out on the risk curve, capital fled the asset amid the great tightening of global liquidity. However, while price charts don&rsquo;t make pretty reading, there has been one notable bright spot when looking at on-chain data.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That is the proportion of long-term holders, which has shown impressive growth throughout the turbulence. As the next chart from Glassnode shows, the cohort has grown since the start of 2022 aside from three periods (with one of those extremely short).</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/22/1692712555740-8ab763bc-8aaf-4eb7-8f54-b33594965818.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="337"><em>(As a note, Glassnode defines long and short-term holders via a logistic function centered at an age of 155 days and a transition width of 10 days).&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">The first period was between May and August 2022, when the crypto world was thrown into disarray. Already fighting a glum macro picture with newly-rising rates and rampant inflation, digital assets got hammered further with the startling death spiral of the UST stablecoin, leading to the collapse of all things Terra. This in turn sparked contagion across the sector, the summer filled with bankruptcies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second period which saw long-term holders waver was very brief, following the FTX collapse last November. The third was then March of this year, which saw apparent profit-taking as Bitcoin increased off the back of more dovish forecasts around the future path of interest rate rises following the regional bank crisis.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This has led to a position today whereby 14.6 million Bitcoin are held by long-term holders, equivalent to 75% of the total circulating supply.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/22/1692712602496-b4b0173b-ac64-446b-970d-0965bcad3270.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="337"><br>The portion of the supply claimed by long-term holders is interesting to track as it is an oft-referenced point by Bitcoin enthusiasts when forecasting the long-term price of the asset. With the overall supply capped at 21 million coins and the rate of increase in supply halving every fours years, they argue that a supply-side squeeze will push the price of Bitcoin up. As long-term holders hoard greater amounts of the supply, there will only be less Bitcoin to go around.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr">Obviously, the demand side of the equation needs to hold up its end of the bargain for this to be true. But amid an extremely challenging eighteen months for Bitcoin, the apparent resilience of long-term holders is certainly a silver lining, and may become more and more relevant as time goes on.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/long-term-holders-weather-brief-volatility-surge/">Long-term holders weather brief volatility surge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/long-term-holders-weather-brief-volatility-surge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu plans Shibarium&#8217;s public reopening after flawed launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-plans-shibariums-public-reopening-after-flawed-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-plans-shibariums-public-reopening-after-flawed-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 12:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-plans-shibariums-public-reopening-after-flawed-launch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The Shiba Inu team is working on reopening its Shibarium blockchain to the public in a few days. This comes after the team botched the blockchain&#8217;s launch last week Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium to reopen soon Shiba Inu developers are currently working to reopen the Shibarium network to the general public. This is according [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-plans-shibariums-public-reopening-after-flawed-launch/">Shiba Inu plans Shibarium&#8217;s public reopening after flawed launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Inu team is working on reopening its Shibarium blockchain to the public in a few days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This comes after the team botched the blockchain&rsquo;s launch last week</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Inu&rsquo;s Shibarium to reopen soon</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu developers are currently working to reopen the Shibarium network to the general public. This is according to the project&rsquo;s key developer, who goes by Shytoshi Kusama, earlier today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the&nbsp;<a href="https://blog.shib.io/shibarium-scaling-update-4/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blog post,</u></a> Kusama said the developers are monitoring validator data and transactions days after the Shibarium launch was marred by a faulty bridge and transaction issues.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kusama added that Shibarium was almost ready to reopen to the public, and the team has put in place mechanisms to prevent an outage similar to what was experienced last week. Kusama said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;After two days of testing and tweaking parameters to achieve a &ldquo;ready&rdquo; state, Shibarium is now enhanced and optimized. As mentioned, it is still in testing but producing blocks. Moreover, we have enabled a new monitoring system and additional fail-safes, including rate limiting at the RPC level and auto server reset in case we get a huge level of traffic again.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu&rsquo;s Shibarium is an Ethereum layer-2 network that utilises SHIB tokens are fees. The launch of Shibarium is set to strengthen Shiba Inu&rsquo;s position as one of the leading blockchain projects in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shibarium to focus on metaverse and gaming applications</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Shibarium blockchain is expected to focus heavily on metaverse and gaming applications while also making it cheaper for DeFi platforms to be built atop it.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Prior to&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-outlook-shib-army-digs-in-despite-shibarium-setback/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>last week&rsquo;s launch</u></a>, Shibarium underwent a testing phase that was very successful. Millions of wallets participated in the testnet and carried out over 2 million transactions over a four-month period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, last week&rsquo;s launch was flawed due to bridging issues. Transactions on the network were stalled for hours after the blockchain went live, with millions of dollars stuck on a bridge.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHIB, the native token of Shiba Inu, has lost more than 20% of its value over the past seven days. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Shiba Inu</u></a> stands at $0.00000798.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the time, developers said there were no bridge issues, and the delays were caused due to an unprecedented mass influx of transactions from users.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The developers claimed that servers failed due to the massive number of transactions on the network.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-plans-shibariums-public-reopening-after-flawed-launch/">Shiba Inu plans Shibarium&#8217;s public reopening after flawed launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-plans-shibariums-public-reopening-after-flawed-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin price prediction: is it safe to buy the FIL dip?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-the-fil-dip/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-the-fil-dip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 12:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FIL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Filecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-the-fil-dip/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Filecoin price remained under intense pressure this week. The coin has plunged to the lowest level since June 10th. The developers introduced slasher and lotus disputer. Filecoin price remained under intense pressure following last week&#8217;s crash. The token was trading at $3.37 on Tuesday, lower than last month&#8217;s high of $4.93. Its market cap has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-the-fil-dip/">Filecoin price prediction: is it safe to buy the FIL dip?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Filecoin price remained under intense pressure this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The coin has plunged to the lowest level since June 10th.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The developers introduced slasher and lotus disputer.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/filecoin/"><u>Filecoin</u></a> price remained under intense pressure following last week&rsquo;s crash. The token was trading at $3.37 on Tuesday, lower than last month&rsquo;s high of $4.93. Its market cap has slipped to more than $1.5 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Latest Filecoin news</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Filecoin, the giant blockchain network for the storage industry, introduced two important features on Monday. In a statement, they launched Lotus Slasher, a feature that will improve network security and integrity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lotus slasher look for consensus faults where block producers engage in malicious activities. When the network detects these activities, it will fine the producer by reducing the offender and rewarding the reporter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other product was Lotus Disputer, where disputers will be able to challenge and verify proof of storage and slash providers who submitted invalid WindowPosts in the network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The goal of these products is to strengthen the ecosystem by aligning incentives and allowing the community to self-police.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, Filecoin is a leading project that is in the storage and cloud computing industry. The network makes it possible for users to provide storage to other people and companies in a decentralized way.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Filecoin has also introduced new features that help them do computing. These features aim to position it as the best alternative to Amazon&rsquo;s AWS and Microsoft Azure. Also, Filecoin launched FVM, a platform that makes it possible for developers to launch dApps in its ecosystem.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Filecoin price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/22/1692706387406-fba097ce-7883-443a-8143-6ff0e4790c7a.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the FIL price has been in a bearish trend after peaking at $9.49 earlier this year. The decline gained steam after last week&rsquo;s crypto crash, which pushed it to the lowest level since June 10th. Filecoin has dropped below the descending trendline shown in black.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has also moved below the 50-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) and the MACD have drifted downwards. Therefore, the coin will likely have a bearish breakout, as sellers target the key support at $2.80, the lowest level on June 10th.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Filecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">
        </p><div class="relative">

            <div class="mb-3  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        eToro    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTUwNTcw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy FIL with eToro today">Buy FIL with eToro today</a>

    </div>

</div><div class="  pb-6  px-6  bg-slate-50  rounded-xl  ps-shadow-inner">

    <h3 class="inline-block">
        OKX    </h3>

            <p class="text-sm">OKX is a world-leading cryptocurrency exchange, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.</p>
    
    <div class="w-full  flex  flex-wrap  items-start  flex-col  gap-2">

        
<a href="/visit/okx-crypto?guid=MTUwNTcw&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" target="_self" class="inline-block  text-indigo-600  underline  hover:text-indigo-200  ease-in-out  duration-300  transition-all" title="Buy FIL with OKX today">Buy FIL with OKX today</a>

    </div>

</div>
        </div>



<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-the-fil-dip/">Filecoin price prediction: is it safe to buy the FIL dip?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/filecoin-price-prediction-is-it-safe-to-buy-the-fil-dip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer pulls in $1.6M from global investors. Buy amid the crypto correction?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-pulls-in-1-6m-from-global-investors-buy-amid-the-crypto-correction/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-pulls-in-1-6m-from-global-investors-buy-amid-the-crypto-correction/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-pulls-in-1-6m-from-global-investors-buy-amid-the-crypto-correction/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer has seen nearly $1.6 million raised in its presale. Interest in the prediction markets crypto project has increased despite recent crypto sell-off. Is the current crypto market landscape a good time to invest? Experts opine the correction offers yet another opportunity to buy low. The same could apply to new gems in the market [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-pulls-in-1-6m-from-global-investors-buy-amid-the-crypto-correction/">Chancer pulls in $1.6M from global investors. Buy amid the crypto correction?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer has seen nearly $1.6 million raised in its presale.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Interest in the prediction markets crypto project has increased despite recent crypto sell-off.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Is the current <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto market</a> landscape a good time to invest? Experts opine the correction offers yet another opportunity to buy low. The same could apply to new gems in the market &ndash; and the <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer presale</a> suggests investors see value in blockchain-based betting.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto correction sees altcoins slide further</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> and Ether prices are trading at critical levels after last week&rsquo;s sell-off pushed BTC to under $25k and ETH to below $1.6k. Bitcoin is currently 11% down this past week, while Ether has shed nearly 10%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite resilience creeping back into the outlook for the top two coins by market cap, the broader altcoin market is showing fresh weakness across many prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Double-digit losses for XRP, BNB, Polygon, Solana and Cardano over the weekly time frame threatens a strengthening of the short term bearish perspective. Analysts point to regulatory and macro headwinds are key factors in coming months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, despite the overall weakness, experts see a flip towards a bull market early next year. Potential upside catalysts include spot ETFs and regulatory clarity. The downswings could thus be opportunities for portfolio buffing.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is a new crypto project that could revolutionise not just the betting market but the entire gambling sector. The project offers a decentralised predictions market that takes control from the traditional, centralised bookmaker and hands it to individual bettors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s innovative social betting project is thus seen as a potential game-changer for the entire industry, particularly when it comes to removing the limitations created by traditional platforms&rsquo; central &ldquo;house&rdquo; approach.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Chancer, you can create bets on anything, including sports, elections and local community events.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">$CHANCER token and fast-selling presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer ecosystem will be powered by $CHANCER, a utility token to be launched on the Binance Smart Chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A presale for the token, which launched to a lot of buzz recently, has already attracted nearly $1.6 million from investors. Currently, the price of $CHANCER is $0.011 and will increase throughout the offer period to $0.021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer team has made it easier for investors to buy $CHANCER by adding support for BNB, ETH, USDT and BUSD</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why buy $CHANCER amid the current market downturn?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While you cannot predict what happens in the markets down the road, possible scenarios for market outlook can be drawn from possible tailwinds and headwinds. The pain witnessed during the crypto winter is not fully dissipated, but as noted above, analysts are increasingly bullish on crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, Chancer&rsquo;s roadmap suggests the platform&rsquo;s launch might slot in nicely with the uptick in crypto market returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is a case scenario that sees investors eye the opportunity in a blockchain technology project that promises to bring transparency to the global sports betting industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per a recent forecast <a href="https://www.thebusinessresearchcompany.com/report/sports-betting-global-market-report" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">report</a> for the industry, significant growth is expected over the next decade. Experts also contend that decentralised sports betting is gearing for a major adoption curve. Chancer could spearhead the P2P betting revolution.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In terms of what Chancer actually offers, the whitepaper outlines more than just a currency to creating bets, playing and winning payouts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Holders will also have passive income opportunities, including via staking and a Share2Earn feature that allows them to promote their bets to the global community. The more one shares with friends and family, the greater the rewards in $CHANCER tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Are you interested in learning more about this project? Visit <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer.com</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-pulls-in-1-6m-from-global-investors-buy-amid-the-crypto-correction/">Chancer pulls in $1.6M from global investors. Buy amid the crypto correction?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-pulls-in-1-6m-from-global-investors-buy-amid-the-crypto-correction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu burn rate up 800%: 1.8 billion SHIB tokens burned</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-up-800-1-8-billion-shib-tokens-burned/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-up-800-1-8-billion-shib-tokens-burned/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-up-800-1-8-billion-shib-tokens-burned/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Shiba Inu (SHIB) token has been on a bear trend following the unsuccessful Shibarium launch. SHIB&#8217;s value has dropped by 22.3% over the last seven days almost erasing all the last month&#8217;s gains. The increased burn rate has caused an increased curiosity within the ecosystem. Shiba Inu (SHIB) has experienced a startling 800% rise [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-up-800-1-8-billion-shib-tokens-burned/">Shiba Inu burn rate up 800%: 1.8 billion SHIB tokens burned</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The Shiba Inu (SHIB) token has been on a bear trend following the unsuccessful Shibarium launch.</li>
<li>SHIB&rsquo;s value has dropped by 22.3% over the last seven days almost erasing all the last month&rsquo;s gains.</li>
<li>The increased burn rate has caused an increased curiosity within the ecosystem.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> has experienced a startling 800% rise in burn rate, resulting in the massive removal of almost two billion SHIB tokens from circulation. The cryptocurrency ecosystem is ablaze with rumours and curiosity following this abrupt increase in the burn rate.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In the last 7 days, there have been a total of 1,840,593,165 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SHIB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$SHIB</a> tokens burned and 255 transactions. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/shib?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#shib</a> <a href="https://t.co/6r179JulIu">pic.twitter.com/6r179JulIu</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Shibburn (@shibburn) <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1693111382785265808?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </p>
<p>This increased burn rate may be caused by a number of circumstances. One of the main causes could be community-led efforts to decrease the amount of SHIB in circulation, which would increase scarcity and thus increase the token&rsquo;s value. The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/">price of SHIB</a> has dropped by 22.3% over the last seven days, dropping from $0.00001027 to $0.000007976 in just seven days.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/22/1692695318614-e3ce71e7-ce4c-4ba7-ba12-e420a667c280.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="383"></p>
<h2>Restoring confidence in Shiba Inu</h2>
<p>The Shiba Inu community may have been motivated to take proactive actions to rebuild faith in the token as a result of the recent <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-presale-hits-2-1m-as-shiba-inus-shibarium-faces-challenges/">disastrous launch of Shibarium</a>, in which more than 1,000 ETH became stranded in the project&rsquo;s ETH Bridge.</p>
<p>However, it is important to remember that while burning tokens can make them scarce, it does not always result in a price increase. Shiba Inu, which was at press time trading for around $0.000007976, has recently endured quite some difficulties and has demonstrated tenacity on the market.</p>
<p>The obvious decline in whale activity on the SHIB network is one of these difficulties. From a peak of 120 large transactions, there are now just 20 large transactions. This decrease in whale activity has potential drawbacks.</p>
<p>On the one hand, it can suggest significant holders lack confidence, which might result in price instability. However, it might also lead to a more decentralized distribution of SHIB tokens, minimizing the price impact of significant sell-offs.</p>
<p>The burn rate and its potential effects on the price of SHIB must be considered in light of other market factors. Although the Shibarium launch failure and the ETH bridge problem that followed were setbacks, the community&rsquo;s proactive approach to burning tokens shows how committed it is to the success of the meme coin.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-up-800-1-8-billion-shib-tokens-burned/">Shiba Inu burn rate up 800%: 1.8 billion SHIB tokens burned</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-burn-rate-up-800-1-8-billion-shib-tokens-burned/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
