<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:26:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Spotify Cuts Headcount by 2%, Offers Severance Package to 200 Staffs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spotify]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257813</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/">Spotify Cuts Headcount by 2%, Offers Severance Package to 200 Staffs</a></p>
<p>In addition to the series of layoffs, Spotify was forced to cancel 11 original podcasts from its in-house studios including ‘How to Save a Planet’, ‘Crime Show’, and ‘Medical Murders’.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/">Spotify Cuts Headcount by 2%, Offers Severance Package to 200 Staffs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/">Spotify Cuts Headcount by 2%, Offers Severance Package to 200 Staffs</a></p>
<p>Music streaming platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spotify/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spotify Technology SA</a> (NYSE: SPOT) has <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2023-06-05/an-update-on-changes-to-spotifys-podcast-business-june-2023/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> plans to cut its workforce by 2% leaving up to 200 employees without jobs.</p>
<p>According to the announcement, Spotify is carrying out this exercise as part of an effort to diversify how the company handles partnerships with podcasters globally. This retrenchment exercise is peculiar to the podcast division of the company and is coming after a general round of layoffs in January.</p>
<p>Spotify vice president Sahar Elhabashi announced the sad news in a memo to all staff. He believes that the move would help the organization channel the appropriate support to the creator community.</p>
<p>Per the published statement, after consulting with its HR team on optimizing the organization, the firm note it &#8220;made the difficult but necessary decision to make a strategic realignment of our group and reduce our global podcast vertical and other functions by approximately 200 people, or 2% of Spotify’s workforce&#8221;.</p>
<h2>Support for the Affected Spotify Employees</h2>
<p>Affected individuals will receive a severance package including extended healthcare coverage and immediate access to outplacement support. As of 2020, the digital music streaming giant had a huge workforce of 8,359 people with 4,332 of them in the United States, based on a Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) filing.</p>
<p>However, in October 2022, the company decided that the services of 38 employees from its Gimlet Media and Parcast podcast studio were no longer required, hence, a headcount reduction. Again in January 2023, Spotify <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-layoff-scheme-tech-downturn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hinted</a> at another layoff round but this time around, Spotify had a workforce of around 9,800.</p>
<p>In the current move, the layoff was attributed to a sustained economic slowdown. A statement by Paul Vogel, the Chief Financial Officer of Spotify suggested that the Stockholm-based company is “clearly aware of the increasing uncertainty regarding the global economy”.</p>
<p>In addition to the series of layoffs, Spotify was forced to cancel 11 original podcasts from its in-house studios including ‘How to Save a Planet’, ‘Crime Show’, and ‘Medical Murders’.</p>
<p>Moving forward, Parcast and Gimlet will be combined into a new Spotify Studios operation.</p>
<h2>Spotify Spends a Fortune on Podcast Unit</h2>
<p>Spotify’s market <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-new-markets-users/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expansion</a> drive over the year has been outstanding. The company attempted to diversify and increase its earnings from music streaming via aggressive expansion to other revenue-generating formats like podcasts.</p>
<p>Also, it is worth noting that Spotify has made so much effort into expanding its podcast unit including signing sponsorship deals with many top entities like Meghan Markle, the Duchess of Sussex, her husband Prince Harry, and Joe Rogan, the online personality.</p>
<p>At one time, the firm inked a podcast deal with renowned TV personality Kim Kardashian and this caused its shares to jump reasonably. The music streaming firm has spent over $1 billion in strategic business acquisitions of numerous audio broadcasting platforms.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/">Spotify Cuts Headcount by 2%, Offers Severance Package to 200 Staffs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/spotify-cut-headcount-200-employees/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stock to Hit All-Time High Following Upcoming Launch of AR/VR Headset at Developers Conference</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[macrumors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wwdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/">Apple Stock to Hit All-Time High Following Upcoming Launch of AR/VR Headset at Developers Conference</a></p>
<p>Observers are watching Apple stock, expecting that it would spike as Apple announces a new headset for augmented or virtual reality.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/">Apple Stock to Hit All-Time High Following Upcoming Launch of AR/VR Headset at Developers Conference</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/">Apple Stock to Hit All-Time High Following Upcoming Launch of AR/VR Headset at Developers Conference</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) stock is on track to open at a possible all-time high as the tech giant prepares to launch its first-ever augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) headset. The launch is considered by many as one of Apple’s most significant product launches in the company’s nearly 50-year history.</p>
<p>AAPL has climbed over 1% to more than $182 as the market pulses through premarket trading. So far, AAPL’s year-to-date (YTD) figures have risen 39,27%, with its 1-year gain at 23.82%, according to MarketWatch figures.</p>
<p>Apple’s figures seem relatively strong, especially considering its recent <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/05/apple-reports-second-quarter-results/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">earnings report</a> for Q2 2023. Interestingly, the iPhone maker reported a 3% year-over-year (YoY) decrease in quarterly revenue to $94.8 billion and $1.52 earnings per diluted share. However, CFO Luca Maestri said the company achieved $28.6 billion in operating cash flow. Maestri also said Apple returned more than $23 billion to shareholders during the quarter. The board of directors declared a common stock $0.24 per share cash dividend, a 4% increase.</p>
<p>Speaking on AAPL’s performance, DFD Partners’ chief executive officer Devon Drew said Apple is in a good place and is strong enough to withstand possible fluctuations. According to Drew:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Even with how much it has risen, it still feels like a quality company, with a lot of cash, continued innovation, a fortress balance sheet, and a large customer base upgrading their products. It should continue to grow, but it can also weather any storm. That means it works in both risk-on and risk-off environments, and that makes me very excited to own it.”</p></blockquote>
<p>If maintained, Apple’s price increase can give the company an added value of $16.5 billion.</p>
<h2>Apple Stock to Benefit from AR/VR Headset Launch</h2>
<p>The 2023 Apple World Wide Developers Conference (WWDC) kicks off today at the Apple Park campus in Cupertino, California. At the event, Apple plans multiple launches, including updates to its existing operating system and a new AR/VR headset.</p>
<p>Expected to cost around $3,000, the Reality Pro headset will have advanced eye and hand tracking, according to leaks. Users should be able to control objects or images simply by looking at it, and selecting by pinching the thumb and index fingers. The hardware will feature internal sensors to see the direction of the eyes, along with external cameras to pick up on hand movements.</p>
<p>MacRumors <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ar-vr/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">says</a> the new headset’s performance will compete favorably with Macs. Also, although users can pair the headset with an iPhone for easy data transfer or typing, pairing will not be necessary for use. The headset should come with 4k high-res micro OLED displays, each with up to 3,000 pixels per inch.</p>
<p>Apple’s stock will likely benefit from the buzz surrounding the headset announcement and features likely to be publicized. The company has reportedly built a structure dedicated to providing a few attendees with demos.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/">Apple Stock to Hit All-Time High Following Upcoming Launch of AR/VR Headset at Developers Conference</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-stock-ar-vr-headset/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s Neuralink Skyrockets from $2 Billion to $5 Billion in Record Time</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[neuralink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257815</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Neuralink Skyrockets from $2 Billion to $5 Billion in Record Time</a></p>
<p>Neuralink, the brain-computer interface company founded by Elon Musk, reached a valuation of $5 billion after gaining approval for human trials, increasing by over 150% in less than two years.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Neuralink Skyrockets from $2 Billion to $5 Billion in Record Time</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Neuralink Skyrockets from $2 Billion to $5 Billion in Record Time</a></p>
<p>Neuralink, the American neurotechnology company dedicated to the development of brain-computer interfaces, founded by Elon Musk, reached a valuation of $5 billion in private share transactions, according to several sources interviewed by Reuters.</p>
<p>The startup of billionaire <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> achieved this milestone thanks to the recent approval by US regulators to begin the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/neuralink-human-trials/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">human trials phase</a>.</p>
<h2>Neuralink Valuation Has Increased by Over 150% in Less Than Two Years</h2>
<p>Although some experts have stated that it may take several years for the company to obtain regulatory approval for commercial use, many investors are optimistic about the company&#8217;s potential, especially at a time when cutting-edge technology like artificial intelligence has become the talk of the town, thanks to its numerous advantages.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/musks-neuralink-valued-about-5-bln-despite-long-road-market-2023-06-05/#:~:text=June%205%20(Reuters)%20%2D%20Elon,with%20knowledge%20of%20the%20matter." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Reuters</a>, Neuralink&#8217;s valuation increased by 150% in less than two years. In the middle of 2021, the company&#8217;s valuation was $2 billion, a modest figure compared to the $7 billion ($55 per share) offered by some investors in the private market after the approval of human trials. Reuters could not confirm whether the seller who made the $7 billion share offer was able to close the deal.</p>
<p>Sim Desai, CEO of Hiive, an online platform for trading shares, pointed out that the demand for Neuralink shares has been &#8220;enormous&#8221;, valuing them at around $4.5 billion. However, other biomedical experts like Arun Sridhar believe that this valuation is exaggerated and unjustified due to the early stage of the company&#8217;s research.</p>
<h2>Investors Are Betting on Elon Musk and His Ambitions with Neuralink</h2>
<p>Many investors are not only betting on Neuralink as an innovative technology company but also on its creator, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-richest-person-arnault-4b/">Elon Musk</a>, who has so far managed to create multiple companies from scratch and turn them into technological giants capable of outperforming the largest existing companies.</p>
<p>For example, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-shares-elon-musk-us-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a>, one of Musk&#8217;s companies with less than 20 years in the automotive market, has far exceeded the market capitalization of two of its biggest competitors, Ford and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GM</a>, recording net income exceeding $12.6 billion during 2023.</p>
<p>Therefore, Musk&#8217;s grand ambitions with Neuralink may be the biggest attraction for investors, as the electric car magnate has repeatedly expressed his desire to use the new chips in the treatment of diseases such as autism, depression, and schizophrenia. Not to mention his claims of being able to cure obesity, enable web browsing, and perhaps even telepathy.</p>
<p>Will these chips fulfill all of Elon Musk&#8217;s claims? While it is impossible to provide a definite answer, one thing is certain: although his ideas may appear incredible and even seemingly impossible in the short term, the journey of the company is bound to be incredibly fascinating.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Neuralink Skyrockets from $2 Billion to $5 Billion in Record Time</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/elon-musk-neuralink-2-billion-5-billion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan: Bitcoin Retail Demand Will Continue to Remain Strong before Halving</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 14:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257793</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/">JPMorgan: Bitcoin Retail Demand Will Continue to Remain Strong before Halving</a></p>
<p>JPMorgan analysts believe that retail investors resolve to accumulate Bitcoins will only go stronger as we approach close to the next halving in mid-2024. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/">JPMorgan: Bitcoin Retail Demand Will Continue to Remain Strong before Halving</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/">JPMorgan: Bitcoin Retail Demand Will Continue to Remain Strong before Halving</a></p>
<p>After a strong start to the year 2023, Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has been facing some selling pressure over the last few weeks. Over the last 24 hours, the BTC price has tanked by 2% slipping under $27,000. However, banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> is confident that Bitcoin will continue to see retail demand until the next halving event of mid-2024. In a research report published last Thursday, JPMorgan strategists noted that Bitcoin retail demand will remain strong over the next year.</p>
<p>The report also notes that the recent retail demand for Bitcoin can be attributed partly to Bitcoin Ordinals and the BRC20 tokens. But it further <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/05/bitcoin-retail-demand-to-remain-strong-ahead-of-halving-event-jpmorgan/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">adds</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Retail investor demand for Bitcoin is likely to strengthen as we approach the April 2024 halving event.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The Bitcoin halving event happens once every four years and cuts the Bitcoin mining rewards in half by 50%. This “would mechanically double bitcoin production cost to around $40,000, creating a positive psychological effect”, JPMorgan analysts led by Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou wrote.</p>
<p>The report added that historically, the production cost has served as an effective lower boundary to Bitcoin&#8217;s price. The banking giant noted that previous halving events of 2016 and 2020 “were accompanied by a bullish trajectory for bitcoin prices” that accelerated after they occurred.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the institutional demand for Bitcoin has been falling with investors being discouraged by “fraud, heightened volatility, and a year-to-date US regulatory assault” leading to growing uncertainty in the market.</p>
<p>JPMorgan noted that following the banking crisis earlier this year in the US, both gold and Bitcoin had rallied. This is because institutional investors preferred buying Gold while retail bought Bitcoin as “hedges to a catastrophic scenario&#8221;.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Coders to Crush Memecoins</h2>
<p>While the BTC price showed little volatility and consolidated around $27,000 last month in May, the Bitcoin network saw a major boost in activity driven by Bitcoin Ordinals and other Bitcoin-based memecoins such as Pepecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PEPE</a>).</p>
<p>This led to a massive surge in the Bitcoin gas fee forcing crypto exchange Binance forced to temporarily halt Bitcoin withdrawals. Now, Bitcoin coders are contemplating whether to stop supporting Bitcoin-based memecoins that lead to a massive frenzy and disrupt Bitcoin’s use for payments and as a store of value.</p>
<p>Bitcoin developer Ali Sherief said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“I do think the system is being abused. Bitcoin was never intended to serve as a base layer for meme tokens.”</p></blockquote>
<p>He <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitcoin-coders-feud-over-whether-to-crush-1-billion-frenzy-for-memecoins-1.1928704" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a> that “worthless tokens threaten the smooth and normal use of the Bitcoin network as a peer-to-peer digital currency”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/">JPMorgan: Bitcoin Retail Demand Will Continue to Remain Strong before Halving</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-bitcoin-retail-demand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Met Museum Agrees to Return $550K in FTX Donations, Highlights Ethical Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[met museum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/">Met Museum Agrees to Return $550K in FTX Donations, Highlights Ethical Concerns</a></p>
<p>The Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York City cited ethical concerns surrounding the cryptocurrency exchange's operations while has announcion its decision to return $550,000 in donations received from FTX.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/">Met Museum Agrees to Return $550K in FTX Donations, Highlights Ethical Concerns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/">Met Museum Agrees to Return $550K in FTX Donations, Highlights Ethical Concerns</a></p>
<p>The Metropolitan Museum of Art (Met Museum), renowned as one of the United States&#8217; most esteemed cultural institutions, has made the decision to return a substantial donation of $550,000 that was generously contributed by the cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>.</p>
<p>Court filings to the United States Bankruptcy Court on Friday disclosed that the Met has chosen to return the donations it had received from FTX shortly before the unfortunate collapse of the crypto exchange in November.</p>
<p>According to the court documents filed on Friday, the museum has opted to return the entire amount of the payments, which were initially received in March and May of the previous year from FTX&#8217;s US entity known as West Realm Shires Services. This decision has been reached amicably, without the need for further legal proceedings or complications, as mentioned in the court filing.</p>
<p>“The Met wishes to return the Donations to the FTX Debtors, and the FTX Debtors and the Met have engaged in good faith, arm’s length negotiations concerning the return of the Donations,” Met <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metropolitan-museum-return-ftx-donation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> commenting on its agreement to make the huge refund.</p>
<h2>FTX Founder&#8217;s Alleged Illegal Political Donations Cast Shadows over Cryptocurrency Sector</h2>
<p>In a thought-provoking revelation, it seems that the Metropolitan Museum of Art may not be alone in considering the return of FTX&#8217;s donations. Recent reports have unveiled that FTX&#8217;s management has been actively seeking to recover its contributions from politicians and various organizations since December, merely a month after the crypto exchange filed for bankruptcy in Delaware.</p>
<p>Furthermore, debates surrounding the potential refund of the FTX donation by the Met Museum signify a wider trend permeating the art world. Recent revelations have shed light on the unsettling discovery that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, the founder of FTX, is facing charges linked to over 300 illegal political donations. These eyebrow-raising accusations involve an astonishing $42 million in contributions to Democratic candidates, while also allegedly funneling undisclosed &#8220;dark money&#8221; to Republican recipients.</p>
<p>However, the complete roster of politicians implicated in these transactions remains undisclosed, leaving lingering questions and concerns within the public sphere. These allegations not only cast a shadow over Bankman-Fried but also raise broader ethical concerns regarding the intersection of the cryptocurrency sector and political financing.</p>
<p>Due to this, museums and galleries find themselves grappling with the ethical quandaries associated with accepting funds from the cryptocurrency sector, particularly when connected to controversial or opaque practices. Institutions are now compelled to thoroughly evaluate the origin and impact of donations, and the values they inherently represent.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/">Met Museum Agrees to Return $550K in FTX Donations, Highlights Ethical Concerns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/met-museum-550k-ftx-donations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Eyes IPO as XRP Lawsuit Draws to End</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257791</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/">Ripple Eyes IPO as XRP Lawsuit Draws to End</a></p>
<p>XRP’s lawyer thinks the outcome could be determined by September based on recent events. In light of this, Ripple is allegedly meeting with investors to discuss their interest in an IPO.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/">Ripple Eyes IPO as XRP Lawsuit Draws to End</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/">Ripple Eyes IPO as XRP Lawsuit Draws to End</a></p>
<p>As its legal battle related to XRP with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) draws to a close, there are rumors that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> may conduct an IPO. Wall Street expert Linda Jones hinted at the possibility by outlining the advantages of a potential initial public offering. Linda used information from Linqto to determine the potential stock value of Ripple, from which she was able to determine each share&#8217;s price and its total worth. She concluded that with Ripple’s low price, having an IPO would most likely be favorable.</p>
<p>There are also reports that the company held a private roadshow in April. During the meeting, its executives discussed the potential and plan for an initial public offering.</p>
<p>&#8220;In April, @Ripple hosted a private’ road show’ (a marketing event where a company and its underwriters meet with potential investors to generate interest in an IPO). I’m told it was attended by just about every reputable institutional investment firm on the Street,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1664353814755909637" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> Eleanor Terrett.</p>
<p>Experts have various thoughts about how the potential Ripple IPO is likely to turn out, and one of them is from John Deaton, XRP’s lawyer. He believes that if Ripple wins the case or only gets a minor punishment, it could all turn out well for the company.</p>
<p>&#8220;If @Ripple wins the SEC lawsuit or gets the functional equivalent of a slap on the wrist, along with a ruling that ongoing and future sales of #XRP are not securities, the lawsuit will prove a blessing in disguise for Ripple,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1664353775744696326" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> he.</p>
<h2>Ripple’s Chance of Winning the Lawsuit</h2>
<p>The pro lawyer also mentioned a very slim possibility, which he described as less than 3%, that the SEC would have an outright win in the ongoing case. He expressed his view that Ripple has a 50% chance of getting a favorable judgment. However, he also recognized that the final ruling could disadvantage the two parties based on different factors.</p>
<h2>Investors Remain Positive about XRP’s Price as Court Judgment Nears</h2>
<p>Many investors and crypto enthusiasts also believe that the XRP lawsuit will end in favor of Ripple. This is shown in the large inflow of money the company has had in recent days. Investors paid $2.6 billion within a week, showing their faith in XRP, making the crypto’s market capitalization rise 10% within the same week, from $24.56 billion to $27.19 billion. The inflow of capital has also led to the rise of XRP’s price.</p>
<p>We cannot deny that the ongoing case is a dominant factor in the price rise. However, it is better to wait until the final ruling before drawing conclusions about the potential price of XRP.</p>
<p>Following the judge’s request for the document containing the speech that William Hinman, the former director of corporation finance at the SEC, gave in 2018, as well as other documents from the two parties that would make it more obvious if XRP is legally regarded as a security or not, John Deaton projects that the final judgment could be made by September.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/">Ripple Eyes IPO as XRP Lawsuit Draws to End</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UBS to Complete Acquisition of Credit Suisse by Mid-Month</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit suisse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ubs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257763</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/">UBS to Complete Acquisition of Credit Suisse by Mid-Month</a></p>
<p>As part of a government-backed rescue plan earlier this year as well as a bid to prevent any financial market instability, UBS acquired Credit Suisse in a $3.2 billion deal.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/">UBS to Complete Acquisition of Credit Suisse by Mid-Month</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/">UBS to Complete Acquisition of Credit Suisse by Mid-Month</a></p>
<p>The long-awaited conclusion of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/credit-suisse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Credit Suisse Group AG</a> (SWX: CSGN)  acquisition by investment banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ubs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">UBS Group AG</a> (SWX: UBSG) may happen “as early as June 12”.</p>
<p>This will signify the birth of a massive Swiss bank with a balance sheet of $1.6 trillion. All that is left for the deal to be completed is its registration statement and according to UBS, this covers shares to be delivered, being declared effective by the United States <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC), and other remaining closing conditions.</p>
<p>Once the take-over process is done, each Credit Suisse stakeholder will be eligible to receive one UBS share for every 22.48 shares they previously held. Also, a restructuring process will see that Credit Suisse shares and American Depositary Shares (ADS) are removed from the SIX Swiss Exchange and the New York Stock Exchange.</p>
<p>Zuercher Kantonalbank analyst Michael Klien said, &#8220;We consider the completion of the takeover to be an important step in initiating what we see as a protracted integration process and getting things done. Although the risk profile of UBS has changed significantly, we see good opportunities for investors.&#8221;</p>
<p>Together as a single unit, the new bank will have $5 trillion of invested assets.</p>
<h2>UBS Decides on Phased Integration of Credit Suisse</h2>
<p>The Swiss largest banking firm has been on the acquisition of Credit Suisse for a few months now. As part of a government-backed rescue plan earlier this year as well as a bid to prevent any financial market instability, UBS <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-3-2-billion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquired</a> Credit Suisse in a $3.2 billion deal. At that time, the cost of the acquisition was a 60% discount from the bank’s $8 billion market capitalization.</p>
<p>The deal attracted the attention of the Swiss National Bank, the Swiss Federal Department of Finance, and the Swiss Financial Market Supervisory Authority (FINMA). Specifically, the Swiss National Bank pledged debt support to facilitate the acquisition. Shortly after, the shares of both entities <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-shares-deal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plunged</a> significantly but this did not deter UBS as it went further to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-sergio-ermotti-new-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">appoint</a> Sergio Ermotti, UBS Group&#8217;s former Chief Executive Officer (CEO) as the new CEO to supervise the takeover.</p>
<p>Also, Ulrich Koerner, the CEO of Credit Suisse was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-credit-suisse-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">granted</a> a seat on the board of directors of the new venture. The plan was to keep Koerner in charge of maintaining Credit Suisse’s operational continuity and client focus while also assisting the integration process.</p>
<p>The deal was, however, about to take another turn last month when concerns were raised about the volume of losses which UBS could incur upon finalizing the acquisition. As reported by Coinspeaker, UBS was likely to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-record-17b-loss-credit-suisse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">incur</a> a financial loss of around $17 billion from the takeover. Precisely, $13 billion represents liability in fair value adjustments for the rebranded mega financial firm while the other $4 billion was from legal and regulatory costs.</p>
<p>Bearing this in mind, UBS decided to undergo a phased integration which could likely go on for the next couple of years.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/">UBS to Complete Acquisition of Credit Suisse by Mid-Month</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubs-complete-acquisition-credit-suisse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Treasury Set for Debt Issuance Worth $1T Following President Biden’s Signing of Debt Ceiling Bill</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bofa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[joe biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257757</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/">US Treasury Set for Debt Issuance Worth $1T Following President Biden&#8217;s Signing of Debt Ceiling Bill</a></p>
<p>Economists predict the US Treasury's forthcoming debt issuance will hit $1 trillion and may eventually cause economic stiffness.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/">US Treasury Set for Debt Issuance Worth $1T Following President Biden&#8217;s Signing of Debt Ceiling Bill</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/">US Treasury Set for Debt Issuance Worth $1T Following President Biden&#8217;s Signing of Debt Ceiling Bill</a></p>
<p>US President Joe Biden’s assent and signing of the bill suspending the federal debt ceiling will trigger new debt issuance. Already, observers expect the Treasury Department to sell $1 trillion worth of debt.</p>
<p>On Saturday, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">President Biden</a> officially signed the bill, which removed the US debt ceiling until Jan 1, 2025. Biden’s signature followed a relatively hurried process of deliberations and votes in the House of Representatives and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/senate-bill-31t-us-debt-ceiling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Senate</a>. The Senate approved the bill and sent it to Biden only a few days before the official default would have set in today. Before the approval, the US debt ceiling was $31.4 trillion.</p>
<p>The Treasury Department hit the debt ceiling in January and has been applying other methods to meet financial obligations. According to a letter Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen sent to House Speaker Kevin McCarthy in January, “extraordinary measures” were necessary until further notice. A CNN <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/06/02/investing/treasury-debt-ceiling-deal/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> specified that these measures include suspending reinvestments of certain funds and selling current investments. The Treasury Department could then begin performing its federal obligations using these funds. However, as of May 31, these extra funds remained only $33 billion.</p>
<h2>Effect of US Debt Ceiling Increase and Debt Issuance</h2>
<p>Although the Treasury got by, it must now return the funds used. In addition, the law requires the Treasury to pay interest for the period. Any measures taken could worsen its financial outlook, especially as it estimates a cash balance of $550 billion by the end of this month.</p>
<p>The Treasury is now likely to sell debt auctions worth more than $1 trillion. According to economists, this move could lead to a recession for several reasons. Firstly, the Treasury would be in the same pool for cash as banks, which could affect lenders’ funding rates. Eventually, lenders transfer these costs to households and businesses.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of America Corp</a>, the economic weight of this occurrence from US debt issuance would equal a Fed interest-rate increase of 25 basis points. This would also affect Treasury Bills as short-term yields would likely fall. However, according to Wisdomtree Investments head of fixed income strategy Kevin Flanagan, the fall might not be terribly steep. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“There will be a knee-jerk reaction in T-bills as that area of the market has borne the burden of uncertainty. So yields come down from their highs, but because the Treasury will increase issuance, there is a floor in yields for that market.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Morgan Stanley short-term interest rate strategist Efrain Tejeda’s forecast for the issuance of Treasury Bills is $730 billion sometime in the next three months. Also, Tejeda’s forecast for December puts issuance at $1.25 trillion.</p>
<p>The Treasury expects its General Account to hit $550 billion at the end of this month and climb by another $50 billion in September.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/">US Treasury Set for Debt Issuance Worth $1T Following President Biden&#8217;s Signing of Debt Ceiling Bill</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-debt-issuance-1t/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>JPMorgan Partners wit Six Indian Banks to Settle Dollar Trades on Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Onyx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/">JPMorgan Partners wit Six Indian Banks to Settle Dollar Trades on Blockchain</a></p>
<p>The goal of this project will be to settle dollar trades in real-time which is significantly faster than the current settlement periods of a few days. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/">JPMorgan Partners wit Six Indian Banks to Settle Dollar Trades on Blockchain</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/">JPMorgan Partners wit Six Indian Banks to Settle Dollar Trades on Blockchain</a></p>
<p>Banking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a> has partnered with six Indian banks to settle interbank dollar transactions over a blockchain platform in the country&#8217;s newest international financial hub of GIFT City.</p>
<p>JPMorgan has joined hands with some of the top private-sector Indian lenders such as HDFC Bank Ltd., ICICI Bank Ltd., Axis Bank Ltd., Yes Bank Ltd., and IndusInd Bank Ltd. Speaking in an interview, Kaustubh Kulkarni, senior country officer in India, and vice chairman for Asia Pacific, at JPMorgan, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-05/jpmorgan-to-use-blockchain-to-settle-usd-fx-trades-in-india-hub?srnd=technology-vp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We will be running a pilot project for the next few months as we need to analyze banks’ experience.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As said, the goal of this JPMorgan project will be to settle dollar trades in real-time as against the current settlement periods of a few days, which happen only on the weekly working days. Currently, it takes several hours to complete settlements in the existing system. Additionally, settlements do not occur on weekends or public holidays. However, the introduction of a real-time blockchain-based system will eliminate this limitation allowing settlements to occur 24/7.</p>
<p>“By leveraging blockchain technology to facilitate transactions on a 24&#215;7 basis, processing is instantaneous and enables GIFT City banks to support their own time zone and operating hours,” said Kulkarni.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan&#8217;s Onyx Platform</h2>
<p>JPMorgan&#8217;s Onyx platform established back in 2020 is its native digital assets network for settling wholesale payment transactions.</p>
<p>The government of India has been planning to position the Gujarat International Finance Tec-City, or GIFT City, as an alternative to some of the world&#8217;s top trading centers such as Dubai and Singapore. As a result, India&#8217;s central bank &#8211; the Reserve Bank of India &#8211; started a non-deliverable forward market settled in dollars at GIFT City.</p>
<p>Although JPMorgan has been bullish about the future of blockchain and its implementation within the global banking system. The bank has also initiated several measures in this regard.</p>
<p>JPMorgan has received approval from the International Financial Services Center Authority to conduct a pilot project on its blockchain platform called Onyx. Over the next few months, the project will analyze the experience of banks and will officially begin on Monday.</p>
<p>This development comes at a time when JPMorgan strategists have been pointing out the growing signs of de-dollarization. &#8220;De-dollarisation is evident in FX reserves where the dollar’s share has declined to a record as share in exports declined, but is still emerging in commodities,&#8221; the strategists noted.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/">JPMorgan Partners wit Six Indian Banks to Settle Dollar Trades on Blockchain</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jpmorgan-indian-banks-dollar-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMF Chief Assures Robust Lending despite Economic Uncertainty</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kristalina georgieva]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us federal reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257729</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/">IMF Chief Assures Robust Lending despite Economic Uncertainty</a></p>
<p>IMF director Kristalina Georgieva highlighted the stability of lending while urging the US Federal Reserve to consider further actions in response to an uncertain economic climate.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/">IMF Chief Assures Robust Lending despite Economic Uncertainty</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/">IMF Chief Assures Robust Lending despite Economic Uncertainty</a></p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/05/the-imf-interview-cnbc.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with CNBC, Kristalina Georgieva, the Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund (IMF), said that lending remains strong despite the uncertain economic environment affecting banks.</p>
<p>Georgieva&#8217;s remarks come as a reassuring voice amid concerns over the stability of lending in the current economic landscape. Despite the challenges faced by financial institutions, she underscored the resilience of lending activities.</p>
<p>The IMF chief urged the need to stay alert and flexible to adapt to changing trends. She further explained that despite concerns over the rigorous monetary policies adopted by major central banks worldwide to combat rising inflation, the IMF had not observed a significant decline in lending that would prompt the US Federal Reserve to alter its rate-hiking cycle.</p>
<p>&#8220;We don&#8217;t yet see a significant slowdown in lending. There are some, but not on the scale that would lead to the Fed stepping back,&#8221; Georgieva told CNBC in the interview.</p>
<h2>US Banks Tighten Lending Standards for Households and Businesses</h2>
<p>Her comments came in response to the Federal Reserve&#8217;s May <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-banks-tighten-lending-standards-small-business-consumers-2023-05-31/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, which cautioned about banks adopting stricter lending protocols for households and businesses. These adjustments were prompted by concerns surrounding future conditions and the difficulties faced by mid-sized financial institutions in the United States.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve&#8217;s loan officers anticipate these challenges persisting over the next year due to lowered growth forecasts, apprehensions regarding deposit outflows, and a decline in risk tolerance.</p>
<p>Highlighting the exceptional uncertainty surrounding the global economy, Georgieva stressed the importance of paying attention to trends and remaining adaptable. Previously, the IMF&#8217;s Chief Economist, Pierre-Olivier Gourinchas, expressed concerns about the precarious situation of banks, posing a risk to the organization&#8217;s projected global growth rate of 2.8% for this year.</p>
<p>While several major global central banks, including the US Federal Reserve, have implemented aggressive measures to tighten monetary policy, inflation remains a pressing issue. According to the Institute of International Finance (IIF), the world&#8217;s total debt has surged to approximately $305 trillion, reaching a near-record high. The IIF&#8217;s May report emphasized concerns about high debt levels and interest rates, raising the alarm about leverage within the financial system.</p>
<h2>US Employment Rates Could Skyrocket to 4.5%</h2>
<p>Considering the IMF&#8217;s assessment, Georgieva suggested that the Federal Reserve may need to take additional steps in conjunction with a resilient US jobs report on Friday last week.</p>
<p>&#8220;The pressure that comes from incomes going up and unemployment being still very, very low means that the Fed will have to stay the course, and perhaps, in our view, they may need to do a little bit more,&#8221; she said.</p>
<p>The IMF chief also stated during the interview, which took place in Dubrovnik, Croatia, that additional <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-increased-interest-rate-0-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rate hikes</a> by the Federal Reserve could result in the US unemployment rate exceeding 4%, potentially reaching 4.5%. The projection follows the rate&#8217;s recent increase to 3.7% in May, which marked the highest level since October last year.</p>
<p>Commenting on President <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Joe Biden&#8217;s</a> recent passage of a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-debt-ceiling-japanese-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">debt ceiling</a> bill, Georgieva acknowledged it as a generally positive outcome. However, she expressed concerns about the repetitive debate surrounding the debt ceiling, emphasizing the need to reconsider the approach to addressing this issue.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pro-ripple-lawyer-law-token/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/">IMF Chief Assures Robust Lending despite Economic Uncertainty</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/imf-chief-lending-economic-uncertainty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=3966 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=957070 metric#prefetches=185 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=192 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=96.71 metric#ms-cache=4.41 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2100 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.6 -->