<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum dApps settle on Solana with Neon EVM’s closed beta</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables Ethereum dApps to settle transactions on Solana. The EVM helps breach the gap between Ethereum and Solana. Since the Neon EVM beta is closed it will only accept transactions for those on the guest list. What is Neon EVM? Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/">Ethereum dApps settle on Solana with Neon EVM’s closed beta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables Ethereum dApps to settle transactions on Solana.</li>
<li>The EVM helps breach the gap between Ethereum and Solana.</li>
<li>Since the Neon EVM beta is closed it will only accept transactions for those on the guest list.</li>
</ul>
<h2>What is Neon EVM?</h2>
<p>Neon EVM is a low-friction solution that enables <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> dApps to settle transactions on Solana, eliminating the gap between these two leading blockchains.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neon EVM positions Ethereum developers to enjoy the best of Solana&rsquo;s network, from low fees to high transaction speeds, and parallel transaction execution capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Solana is one of the fastest, organically-growing chains, its incompatibility with EVM has left several hundred million in TVL, millions of users, and an entire ecosystem untouched by EVM multichain dApp developers &mdash; until now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neon EVM&rsquo;s pioneering solution is <em>the&nbsp;</em>anticipated innovation in the Solana ecosystem and makes Solana a viable option for multichain builders. Neon EVM brings together the best of both chains while ensuring the finality of settlements on Solana.</p>
<h2>What is Neon EVM closed beta?</h2>
<p>The launch of the closed beta version of Neon EVM, Neon EVM&beta;, to Solana&rsquo;s Mainnet is a significant milestone on the roadmap.</p>
<p>Neon EVM&beta; is a fully-functioning Neon EVM with one major alteration: it supports fee-free transactions.</p>
<p>This means that all transactions are settled to Solana&rsquo;s L1 and require payment in Sol, as per any Solana-settled transaction. However, in beta, the NEON token is not requested by the Proxy Operator responsible for accepting the transaction request and ensuring that it is finalized.</p>
<h2>Why launch in beta?</h2>
<p>The Neon EVM ecosystem includes many more players than just the Neon EVM and the Proxy Operators that accept and settle transaction requests. It includes DAO, oracles, indexers, wallets, multisigs, bridges, explorers, and more. Neon EVM&beta; provides an opportunity for all parties to deploy and test to ensure the seamless integration of their services before the official Solana Mainnet launch.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/26/1687776871651-caf251fa-2ab7-45fe-9fec-49c5be1fe00e.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="270"></p>
<p>While Neon EVM could have chosen to do a Shadow Mainnet launch on a fork of the Solana mainchain, launching directly to Mainnet offers significant advantages. Not least of which is that deployed and tested contracts will retain their addresses on Solana Mainnet.</p>
<h2>Why launch in closed beta?</h2>
<p>Launching in closed beta allows the Neon EVM team to onboard and test the services of ecosystem players in controlled phases. The first phase onboarded the infrastructure components, and the second phase accepted dApps and will test the connection of wallets.</p>
<p>Operating in closed beta also controls the budget by keeping the activity limited to an invite-only list. Remember, while the Proxy Operator is not charging a fee, the Solana network still does. It simply is not possible to provide an open beta and predict the cost in SOL for such an initiative (though it is possible to predict that the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/">SOL cost</a> will be less than the equivalent Eth cost would be for an EVM settling to Ethereum!).&nbsp;</p>
<p>When the testing period ends and NEON tokens are available on the market to pay for transactions, Neon EVM will switch back to its normal operation mode. This means that independent Proxy Operators (P2P and Everstake) will resume responsibility for accepting and processing transactions. The Proxy Operator&rsquo;s RPC endpoints will be made available on <u><a href="https://chainlist.org/?chain=245022926&amp;testnets=true&amp;search=Neon+EVM">ChainList</a></u>.</p>
<h2>Want to get involved?</h2>
<p>While Neon EVM is deployed to Solana Mainnet at address <a href="https://solscan.io/account/NeonVMyRX5GbCrsAHnUwx1nYYoJAtskU1bWUo6JGNyG">NeonVMyRX5GbCrsAHnUwx1nYYoJAtskU1bWUo6JGNyG</a>, as this is a closed beta, unless you are on the guest list, it won&rsquo;t accept your transactions yet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To engage with the community, you can find us on <a href="https://twitter.com/Neon_EVM">Twitter</a> and join Neon EVM&rsquo;s very active <a href="https://discord.gg/neonevm">Discord</a> to meet some of our long-term and loyal community builders. For a high-level overview of the technical architecture and features of Neon EVM, the whitepaper is available at <a href="https://neonevm.org/whitepaper.pdf">NeonEVM.org/whitepaper.pdf</a>. To follow the activity of the network, you can view Neon EVM transactions settled to Solana with the <a href="https://shadow.neonscan.org/">NeonScan</a> dashboard.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/closed-beta-version-of-neon-evm-launches-on-solanas-mainnet/">Ethereum dApps settle on Solana with Neon EVM’s closed beta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto investors see value proposition in Chancer’s P2P betting solution</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer presale has seen investors buy over 38 million tokens in a few days. The excitement about this project stems from its value proposition, particularly in disrupting the online betting industry. Current presale price for CHANCER token is $0.01, likely a bargain for early investors. The Chancer presale launched this month offering investors an early [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/">Crypto investors see value proposition in Chancer’s P2P betting solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer presale has seen investors buy over 38 million tokens in a few days.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The excitement about this project stems from its value proposition, particularly in disrupting the online betting industry.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Current presale price for CHANCER token is $0.01, likely a bargain for early investors.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer presale</u></a> launched this month offering investors an early opportunity to be part of a disruptive betting platform. Is this why the token sale has already seen investors scoop more than 38 million $CHANCER tokens?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s value proposition is the game-changer</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As an innovative blockchain-based market, Chancer&rsquo;s value proposition is in its approach to betting. Simply, control is seized from centralised bookmakers and handed to bettors. No central house means custom bets and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/smart-contracts/">smart contracts</a>-powered payouts, with wagers shared globally to create a real-time social environment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the base of it is Chancer&rsquo;s potential to completely change the gambling industry by tapping into the power of Web3. Early backers of this peer-to-peer online betting platform could be investing in the most disruptive project in the predictive markets industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is building the world&rsquo;s first truly decentralised predictions market. It employs <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-blockchain/">blockchain technology</a> to introduce the features of transparency and immutability, a trustless environment that contrasts to the heavily centralised traditional betting industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CHANCER token re-empowers bettors, allowing them to remain in control of their betting experience by offering a platform where they can create their own predictive markets. No bookmaker power to decide which markets to offer and which to restrict.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It means users can participate in all manner of wagers, from the biggest sports events and political contests to that mundane bet against friends and family. And if you are not creating your own custom bet, you can jump onto one from anywhere in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s P2P platform, which is Certik audited and integrated with Google&rsquo;s WebRTC, makes social betting not just fun but also likely more profitable.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is CHANCER presale the time to buy?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER is central to how Chancer works. The token grants its holders access to the prediction market and it&rsquo;s what makes it possible for participants to create all bets. Payouts are also processed in CHANCER.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer presale is why investors are flocking to the project. Projections are that the betting industry could in a few years be a $150 billion market, with an estimated 11% CAGR to 2030. Adding to this is Chancer&rsquo;s potential to disrupt the whole industry even as an expected crypto boon makes for a great opportunity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Going by these prospects, it appears investors buying CHANCER today could be early adopters of a project set to grow alongside as well as revolutionise the broader market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the current price of $0.01, CHANCER is arguably a massive bargain &ndash; especially given the presale will see the token&rsquo;s value jump more than 100% to $0.021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tokens are quickly selling out as can be seen on the presale page<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>here</u></a>, and that means interested investors may want to buy now to lock in the early gains as the platform moves through its 12 presale stages.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will CHANCER price reach $1 in 2024?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s industry-defining project is still in development, and the roadmap shows the Beta launch of the P2P betting platform is expected in Q3, 2023. Meanwhile, the token will go live on exchanges at the end of the presale, opening it up to more investors and increasing demand.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Availability on major exchanges could inject upside action in CHANCER price at a time the crypto market could be experiencing bullish moves. Product development for Chancer will continue through Q4, with testnet for market making, virtual betting and full node deployment adding to the growth impetus.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Mainnet launch is expected in Q1, 2024. Chancer will also integrate Filecoin data storage, migrate validator nodes and deploy quadratic governance. Certik auditing to verify decentralisation will also be undertaken. Amid these is Chancers tokenomics that outline a deflationary token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Taken as a whole, the Chancer roadmap points to a project poised to achieve key milestones. Investor confidence could spike due to this and cascade into more demand for the native token, aiding a bullish trajectory that could coincide with an anticipated bull cycle.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If CHANCER price breaks to $0.1 after it goes live, the prediction would be a run to the primary target of $1 later in 2024. However, any investor would know that prevailing market conditions remain key to future CHANCER price performance.</p>
<p>Interested in this project? Find out more on <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=media&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer.com</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/">Crypto investors see value proposition in Chancer’s P2P betting solution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-investors-see-value-proposition-in-chancers-p2p-betting-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, China, June 28th, 2023, Chainwire DWF Labs, the global digital asset market maker, and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, has further strengthened its commitment to support the growth of Conflux, the tree-graph consensus algorithm Layer-1 blockchain. Conflux has been gaining significant traction since February 2023 on the back of some key partnerships, including the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/">DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Hong Kong, China, June 28th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>DWF Labs, the global digital asset market maker, and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, has further strengthened its commitment to support the growth of Conflux, the tree-graph consensus algorithm Layer-1 blockchain. Conflux has been gaining significant traction since February 2023 on the back of some key partnerships, including the signature collaboration with China Telecom announced on February 15th, with the goal of developing a blockchain SIM (BSIM) card that was first unveiled in May.</p>
<p>DWF Labs recently purchased $18M in CFX token, cementing the long-term relationship between the investment firm and Conflux. This follows DFW Labs buying $10M worth of CFX tokens in March 2023.</p>
<p>More recently, Conflux joined Hong Kong&rsquo;s Web3 Institute, participated in the Singapore Digital Economy Roundtable organized by the Singaporean Government, and led the drafting of IEEE P3217, an international blockchain standard by the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers. In addition, Conflux announced key partnerships including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Supremacy &ndash; Web3 security platform</li>
<li>dappOS &ndash;&nbsp;an operating protocol that manages crypto infrastructures for users</li>
<li>NuLink &ndash; a privacy-preserving technology that provides APIs for decentralized applications</li>
<li>Smooth Labs &ndash; developing the Layer 2 solution that supports parallel execution</li>
<li>Opside &ndash;&nbsp;a decentralized ZK-RaaS network featuring PoW of ZKP mining</li>
</ul>
<p>DWF Labs has made significant contributions to placing Conflux on the global stage. Since then, Conflux has established ecosystem partnerships with Floki, Worldcoin, Blockbank, Luganodes, AirDAO, Mask, and OpenEden, with a growing list of ongoing partnerships being discussed. Conflux and DWF Labs have also co-hosted multiple events, including those organized in Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Paris.</p>
<p>Fan Long, Conflux Network&rsquo;s Co-Founder, stated: &ldquo;Conflux Network has experienced exponential growth since the start of 2023, pioneering advances in the Chinese NFT market and establishing fresh Web3 access through the BSIM card project with China Telecom. DWF Lab is one of the key supporters of Conflux. This infusion of capital not only strengthens our bond, but also acts as a catalyst for our shared ambition to expand the Conflux ecosystem. Conflux plans to leverage the raised funds to further fuel its ecosystem growth in Asia and Hong Kong, empower burgeoning developer communities, and bring an increasing number of real-world assets onto the Conflux chain.&rdquo;</p>
<blockquote><p>The Managing Partner of DWF Labs, Andrei Grachev stated: &ldquo;We take great pride in our role as supporters of Conflux throughout its remarkable growth trajectory. It exemplifies our commitment to backing projects with immense potential and providing the necessary support to fill in the missing pieces of the Web3 puzzle. Our deep understanding of the crypto market has served as a compass for Conflux, allowing it to fully express its potential on the global stage. We are delighted to have played a part in Conflux&rsquo;s journey towards success.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<h3>About Conflux</h3>
<p><a href="https://confluxnetwork.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Conflux</a> is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols.</p>
<p>Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p>
<p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities in the region on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p>
<h3>About DWF Labs</h3>
<p><a href="https://www.dwf-labs.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">DWF Labs</a> is the global digital asset market maker and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, supporting portfolio companies from token listing to market making to OTC trading solutions.</p>
<p>With offices in Singapore, Switzerland, the UAE, Hong Kong, South Korea and BVI, the investment company DWF Labs is an affiliate of Digital Wave Finance (DWF), which consistently ranks among the top 5 trading entities by volume in the cryptocurrency world through its proprietary technology for high-frequency trading.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Melissa Tirey<br>
conflux@shift6studios.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/">DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity may soon file for a spot bitcoin ETF</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-may-soon-file-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144404</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Block says Fidelity is next in line to file for a spot bitcoin ETF. Oanda analyst Edward Moya shares his view on the Fidelity news. BlackRock also filed for such an exchange-traded fund last week. Fidelity is in focus on Tuesday following a report that the asset manager was next in line to file [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-may-soon-file-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Fidelity may soon file for a spot bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The Block says Fidelity is next in line to file for a spot bitcoin ETF.</li>
<li>Oanda analyst Edward Moya shares his view on the Fidelity news.</li>
<li>BlackRock also filed for such an exchange-traded fund last week.</li>
</ul>
<p>Fidelity is in focus on Tuesday following a report that the asset manager was next in line to file for a spot bitcoin ETF.</p>
<h2>Analyst reacts to the Fidelity news</h2>
<p>The news arrives only days after peer BlackRock filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for such an exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-exchanges-fear-a-blackrock-etf/">find out more</a>).</p>
<p>Fidelity refused to comment on <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/236588/fidelity-preparing-to-submit-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-source" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Block&rsquo;s</a> report this morning. But a Senior Market Analyst at Oanda &ndash; Edward Moya said:</p>
<blockquote><p>There&rsquo;s a lot of optimism here that you&rsquo;re going to get a bitcoin ETF.</p></blockquote>
<p>Others that have recently filed for a spot bitcoin ETF include Invesco, WisdomTree, Bitwise, and VanEck. Such filings helped bitcoin hit $31,000 this week for the first time in more than a year.</p>
<h2>What a spot bitcoin ETF may mean for crypto</h2>
<p>It is noteworthy here that Fidelity had filed for a spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> ETF in 2021 as well. At the time, it had faced rejection.</p>
<p>But this time could be different considering its peer BlackRock has filed for one as well and BlackRock has a reputation for making such a move only when it&rsquo;s convinced that it will receive approval, as per Oanda&rsquo;s Moya.</p>
<blockquote><p>If that does get done, it could open the door for much more institutional money and probably some high-net-worth retail traders to get back into crypto.</p></blockquote>
<p>Last week, Fidelity backed crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/new-crypto-exchange-edx-markets-goes-live/">EDX Markets</a> went live in the United States. On the downside, though, the U.S. regulator has recently filed lawsuits against both Binance and Coinbase Global Inc.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fidelity-may-soon-file-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Fidelity may soon file for a spot bitcoin ETF</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex launches P2P platform in Venezuela, Argentina and Colombia</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitfinex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Latin america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[P2P]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitfinex P2P will support buying and selling of Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether tokens USDt and EURt. The company is looking to bolster financial freedom and inclusion across Latin America. Bitfinex completed an investment in Chile-based crypto bank OrionX in May. Bitfinex, one of the leading digital asset trading platforms, is making further inroads in Latin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/">Bitfinex launches P2P platform in Venezuela, Argentina and Colombia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitfinex P2P will support buying and selling of Bitcoin, Ethereum and Tether tokens USDt and EURt.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company is looking to bolster financial freedom and inclusion across Latin America.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitfinex completed an investment in Chile-based crypto bank OrionX in May.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/bitfinex/">Bitfinex</a>, one of the leading digital asset trading platforms, is making further inroads in Latin America as it seeks to bring financial freedom and inclusion to the region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the latest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitfinex/">Bitfinex news</a>, the company announced the launch of its peer-to-peer (P2P) platform for users in Venezuela, Colombia and Argentina.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitfinex P2P to support BTC, ETH and Tether</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Dubbed &lsquo;Bitfinex P2P,&rdquo; the platform will offer people in the three countries an avenue with which to directly buy and sell Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH). Users of Bitfinex P2P will also access Tether tokens (USDt and EURt) as well as Tether Gold (XAUt).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will also allow customers to swap digital tokens, according to details in a <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/media-releases/bitfinex-launches-peer-to-peer-platform-bitfinex-p2p-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> published on Tuesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Bitfinex said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>By offering a reliable and efficient platform for P2P token trading, we are empowering our customers to engage with the marketplace in a way that affords maximum convenience based on their needs and preferences. We believe in the transformative power of Bitcoin and other digital assets, as well as the importance of providing greater access to innovative financial technologies worldwide</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitfinex&rsquo;s entry into the P2P market in the region is likely to be welcome news to crypto users after two of the leading P2P marketplaces in LocalBitcoins and Paxful shut down their operations. The expansion also comes after Bitfinex <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-and-chiles-orionx-partner-to-accelerate-crypto-adoption-in-latin-america/">invested</a> in Chilean &ldquo;crypto bank&rdquo; OrionX, a deal completed in May.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/">Bitfinex launches P2P platform in Venezuela, Argentina and Colombia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitfinex-launches-p2p-platform-in-venezuela-argentina-and-colombia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chromia (CHR) hits milestone as My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 goes live</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chromia Appnet welcomes first ever decentralised token bridge with My Neighbor Alice collaboration. ALICE tokens can now be bridged from the Binance Smart Chain (BSC). Chromia token (CHR) was slightly lower on Tuesday afternoon, but was 12% higher in the past week. Chromia, a standalone public blockchain developed by Swedish company Chromaway AB, has hit [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/">Chromia (CHR) hits milestone as My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 goes live</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chromia Appnet welcomes first ever decentralised token bridge with My Neighbor Alice collaboration.</li>
<li dir="ltr">ALICE tokens can now be bridged from the Binance Smart Chain (BSC).</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chromia token (CHR) was slightly lower on Tuesday afternoon, but was 12% higher in the past week.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Chromia, a standalone public blockchain developed by Swedish company Chromaway AB, has hit a new milestone after blockchain-based game <a href="https://coinjournal.net/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice</a> Alpha Season 3 went live on the Appnet.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Decentralised token bridge on Chromia</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 launched on the first ever Chromia Appnet, a collaboration that is set to see the public have access to MNA&rsquo;s unique multiplayer game. There is a &lsquo;free trial&rsquo; where players can tap into the benefits of land ownership as well as use the native MNA token ALICE.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another milestone is the bridging of ALICE from Binance Smart Chain, the first bridged asset use on the Chromia Appnet.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#127800; My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 is now LIVE!</p>
<p>Join us and explore an array of exciting new features, like: </p>
<p>&#128736; Crafting System<br>&#127379; FREE TRIAL for non-landowners <br>&#128444; Plot-sharing by landowners through FREE-RENTING <br>&#128087; ELLE branded Quests and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/NFTs?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#NFTs</a> <br>&#129689; <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ALICE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ALICE</a> token utilization&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/rmTNLs5rHP">pic.twitter.com/rmTNLs5rHP</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Alice (@MyNeighborAlice) <a href="https://twitter.com/MyNeighborAlice/status/1673650229420097537?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Alpha Season 3 comes with all the popular game features, including fishing, farming and land decoration. However, there are also new exciting experiences such as sharing of land plots, staking ALICE and customising in-game avatars.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;T<em>oday, with the release of My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3, is a big milestone for both us and Chromia. We are the first app on Chromia appnet and the first project to utilise the decentralised token bridge in order to give in-game utility for $ALICE</em>,&rdquo; Viktor Plane, Technical Director at My Neighbor Alice<a href="https://twitter.com/snieking/status/1673566262843023361">&nbsp;<u>said</u></a> when commenting on the development.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chromia&rsquo;s open source blockchain offers EVM compatibility for Ethereum and the Binance Smart Chain. It provides for the development of next-generation decentralised applications through enhanced scalability, data and storage capabilities and customizable fees.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The applications include DeFi options trading protocol Hedget that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-launches-defi-protocol-for-options-trading/">launched</a> in 2020 and the increasingly popular MNA. Chromia also enables supply chains, with Chromia&rsquo;s technology used to trace product origins and integration of NFTs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chromia (CHR) price</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Chroma token (CHR), the native token of the Layer-1 blockchain network, hovered above $0.13, about 2.8% down in the past 24 hours at the time of writing. CHR however traded nearly 12% higher over the past week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ALICE price hovered at $1.06, just in the green over the past 24 hours and more than 20% up in the past seven days.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/">Chromia (CHR) hits milestone as My Neighbor Alice Alpha Season 3 goes live</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chromia-chr-hits-milestone-as-my-neighbor-alice-alpha-season-3-goes-live/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court denies Binance motion alleging SEC misconduct</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A US judge has said the court cannot wordsmith the SEC and Binance&#8217;s press releases. But in denying the crypto exchange&#8217;s motion, Judge Amy Berman Jackson said either party has to &#8220;adhere to their ethical obligations at all times.&#8221; SEC sued Binance in early June and published a press release alleging commingling of user funds. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/">Court denies Binance motion alleging SEC misconduct</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">A US judge has said the court cannot wordsmith the SEC and Binance&rsquo;s press releases.</li>
<li dir="ltr">But in denying the crypto exchange&rsquo;s motion, Judge Amy Berman Jackson said either party has to &ldquo;adhere to their ethical obligations at all times.&rdquo;</li>
<li dir="ltr">SEC sued Binance in early June and published a press release alleging commingling of user funds.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Judge Amy Berman Jackson on Monday June 26 denied a motion filed by crypto exchange Binance that sought to stop the SEC from making public statements on the SEC/Binance case.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/binance/">Binance</a> had alleged that the SEC had published misleading statements that could impact the case and taint the jury pool.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Three days on from the filing, the court pronounced itself on the motion, with Judge Jackson noting that the court cannot &ldquo;wordsmith&rdquo; either party&rsquo;s press releases. Her <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67474542/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-binance-holdings-limited/?order_by=desc#minute-entry-347478862" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">order</a> read:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While all of the lawyers in this case should adhere to their ethical obligations at all times, it is not apparent that Court intervention to reiterate that point is needed at this time, or that it is necessary or appropriate for the Court to get involved in wordsmithing the parties&rsquo; press releases. Nor is it clear that the agency&rsquo;s public relations efforts to date will materially affect proceedings in this case</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance questioned SEC&rsquo;s statements</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance&rsquo;s motion followed SEC&rsquo;s press release on June 21 in which the securities regulator had reiterated its allegations of commingling of user funds by the exchange&rsquo;s leadership.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The statements came after the two parties reached an agreement on the handling of assets of Binance.US. The agency had <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-is-seeking-court-order-to-freeze-binance-uss-assets/">filed for a freeze on the exchange&rsquo;s assets</a> suggesting the need to protect US customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In its response to the SEC&rsquo;s press release, Binance said the regulator had published misleading facts about Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao mishandling Binance.US customer funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The motion sought orders against the regulator &ndash; specifically the motion wanted Judge Jackson to order counsel to comply with ethical obligations and not to make &ldquo;<em>misleading extrajudicial statements that may materially impact court proceedings</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">&ldquo;Not a great result for Binance&rdquo;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">John Reed Stark, Former Chief, SEC office of Internet Enforcement, <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1673400620944859149" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">commented</a> on the court&rsquo;s decision, suggesting that Binance&rsquo;s filing may not have been worth it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>It seemed so frivolous on its face and more akin to marketing theater than legal argument</em>,&rdquo; he noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">James &ldquo;MetaLawMan&rdquo; Murphy, a securities lawyer, said the judge&rsquo;s order isn&rsquo;t a great one for Binance &ndash; even if it doesn&rsquo;t impact the merits of its case.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Judge Jackson has issued a brief order denying the <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Binance</a> motion before the SEC filed its response.<br>The judge wrote that it was not necessary to reiterate both side's obligations to comply with ethics rules, and she will not get involved in "wordsmithing the parties' press&hellip;</p>
<p>&mdash; MetaLawMan (@MetaLawMan) <a href="https://twitter.com/MetaLawMan/status/1673433720068657153?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Separately, the court set forth a timeline for the early proceedings. Binance will plead its case on September 21, 2023 before the plaintiff presents their legal arguments on 7 November 7, 2023. The court will listen to replies starting December 12.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/">Court denies Binance motion alleging SEC misconduct</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-denies-binance-motion-alleging-sec-misconduct/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price action records decoupling from gold and silver</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s 30-day correlation with gold is at cycle lows after BTC price action in 2023. BTC has outperformed the precious metal even as its correlation with stocks also fell. Gold traded near $1,928 per ounce while silver price was at $22.94 per ounce on Tuesday morning. Gold continues to hover above $1,900 after its recent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/">Bitcoin price action records decoupling from gold and silver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s 30-day correlation with gold is at cycle lows after BTC price action in 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC has outperformed the precious metal even as its correlation with stocks also fell.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Gold traded near $1,928 per ounce while silver price was at $22.94 per ounce on Tuesday morning.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/gold/">Gold</a> continues to hover above $1,900 after its recent breakdown from year-to-date highs above $2,052 per ounce threatened a retreat to February lows. But at $1,928 per ounce, gold is negative in the past 30 days and just over 6% higher in the past six months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Silver prices are also just slightly up at $22.94 per ounce as of writing. However, Silver is down 1.6% in the past 30 days and 3.3% in the red over the past six months.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin decoupling from gold, silver</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On-chain data platform Glassnode has<a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1673648546103402496" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>shared</u></a> fresh details showing <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> action has continued to decouple from the metals. In 2023, BTC has reached highs of $31,500 and is 14% up in the past 30 days and +85% YTD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The correlation with gold and silver has reached near cycle lows for XAU/USD and new cycle low for XAG/USD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Local Bitcoin price action has recorded a decoupling from both Gold and Silver, with the 30 day correlation to gold residing near cycle lows of -0.78, whilst the correlation to Silver has reached a cycle low of -0.9 respectively</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Local <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> price action has recorded a decoupling from both <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Gold?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Gold</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Silver?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Silver</a>, with the 30 day correlation to Gold residing near cycle lows of -0.78, whilst the correlation to Silver has reached a cycle low of -0.9 respectively. <a href="https://t.co/066EGsFWNI">pic.twitter.com/066EGsFWNI</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1673648546103402496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Although commodities are likely to see a boost with the upcoming US CB Consumer Confidence report on Tuesday, gold and silver remain largely constrained. The main hurdles are at $1,930 and $23.04 for XAU/USD and XAG/USD respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, BTC is showing resilience above $30k and could rip upwards amid the recent spot ETF related news.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The probability that BTC/USD rises further is highlighted in the chart below by Santiment analysts. They say that following crypto markets&rsquo;s jump to local tops last Friday, expectation among traders has been for a retracement for buy the dip opportunities in the $27k-$29k region.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128552; After <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#crypto</a> markets topped out last Friday, traders came into the start of the week with expecting that prices would continue to retrace &amp; provide opportunities to buy in the $27k-$29k level. High <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bearish?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#bearish</a> sentiment increases further rise probability. <a href="https://t.co/bEkYCdNqVH">https://t.co/bEkYCdNqVH</a> <a href="https://t.co/PxJQBTN1Us">pic.twitter.com/PxJQBTN1Us</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1673511851165122560?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a scenario for increased bearish sentiment, which the analysts suggest could be an ingredient for new upward action.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-down-to-3-year-low/">reported</a> on Monday, latest data also shows Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with the Nasdaq 100 is at a three-year low.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-action-records-decoupling-from-gold-and-silver/">Bitcoin price action records decoupling from gold and silver</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chibi Finance allegedly executes $1M rug pull on Arbitrum, CHIBI plummets 98%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chibi Finance has allegedly executed a $1M rug pull on Layer 2 blockchain Arbitrum. The team has vanished and their social media accounts are inaccessible. Security platform Peckshield says the team channeled the funds via Tornado Cash. Arbitrum-based DeFi project Chibi Finance has disappeared into thin air with $1 million in what is reported to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/">Chibi Finance allegedly executes $1M rug pull on Arbitrum, CHIBI plummets 98%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chibi Finance has allegedly executed a $1M rug pull on Layer 2 blockchain Arbitrum.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The team has vanished and their social media accounts are inaccessible.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Security platform Peckshield says the team channeled the funds via Tornado Cash.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Arbitrum-based <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> project Chibi Finance has disappeared into thin air with $1 million in what is reported to be a potential rug pull.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chibi Finance, which went live only recently on Arbitrum&rsquo;s Layer 2 network, is said to have drained its liquidity pool, vanishing with 555 ether (ETH). At current market prices, that&rsquo;s about $1 million worth of user deposits.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chibi Finance latest in rug pulls</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to an <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1673615238758006786" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">alert</a> by blockchain security and data analystic firm PeckShield, the Chibi Finance team withdrew staked tokens by converting them to ETH and then funneling them to the Ethereum network via the crypto mixing service Tornado Cash.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PeckShieldAlert?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#PeckShieldAlert</a> Seems like <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Chibifinance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Chibifinance</a> rugged. ~$1M worth of cryptocurrencies were drained.<br>The stolen funds, which have been swapped for ~555 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>, were bridged from <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Arbitrum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Arbitrum</a> to Ethereum. <br>They have already been transferred into Tornado Cash<a href="https://t.co/HmVeZmWJS4">https://t.co/HmVeZmWJS4</a> <a href="https://t.co/1wM8j86fS4">pic.twitter.com/1wM8j86fS4</a></p>
<p>&mdash; PeckShieldAlert (@PeckShieldAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1673615238758006786?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chibi Finance team has allegedly also &ldquo;disappeared&rdquo; with the DeFi projects social media accounts on <a href="https://twitter.com/Chibi_Fi" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Twitter</a> and Telegram deleted. The platform&rsquo;s website is also offline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chibi Finance&rsquo;s apparent rug pull adds to the recent spate of bad actors in the Arbitrum and Ethereum ecosystems. In April, zkSync project Merlin allegedly siphoned off $2 million from its users. Meanwhile, Arbitrum-based Swaprun vanished in May, with close to $3 million of user funds in another rug pull.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHIBI, the native Chibi Finance token, has plummeted following the news. After trading above $1.62 on Monday, CHIB price fell sharply on Tuesday morning to almost zero. Data from CoinGecko shows the crypto token has lost 98.7% of its value in the past 24 hours and currently hovers near $0.017.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chibi-finance-allegedly-executes-1m-rug-pull-on-arbitrum-chib-plummets-98/">Chibi Finance allegedly executes $1M rug pull on Arbitrum, CHIBI plummets 98%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
