<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:50:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Samsung Investment Arm to Launch Bitcoin Futures ETF in Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures Active ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung asset management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Samsung Investment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232353</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/">Samsung Investment Arm to Launch Bitcoin Futures ETF in Hong Kong</a></p>
<p>When the ETF goes live, it will offer diversification and a means for investors to meet their demands.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/">Samsung Investment Arm to Launch Bitcoin Futures ETF in Hong Kong</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/">Samsung Investment Arm to Launch Bitcoin Futures ETF in Hong Kong</a></p>
<p>Samsung Asset Management, the investment arm of the financial services giant, has announced its plans to launch a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) product, giving investors a new way to gain exposure to the digital currency. As <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/samsung-investment-arm-to-launch-bitcoin-futures-etf-amid-rising-crypto-interest" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Cointelegraph, the proposed product, dubbed the &#8220;Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF&#8221; is billed to float on January 13 and will be trading on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange.</p>
<p>The proposed product will offer both retail and institutional investors in Hong Kong an avenue to invest in the nascent asset class. Per the report, the Bitcoin Futures ETF will invest in Bitcoin futures products listed on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME). Two of these products include the CME Bitcoin Futures and the CME Micro Bitcoin Futures.</p>
<p>Hong Kong has continued to gain a reputation as one of the top financial epicenters in the Asian region. The country is the only location in the whole of Asia where investors can gain exposure to Bitcoin Futures ETF. This rare scenario now places at par with other regions including the United States, Canada, and Switzerland amongst others.</p>
<p>The Samsung Bitcoin Futures ETF will go on to complement the Hong Kong Crypto Futures ETF which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-ether-etfs-hkex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">made its debut</a> in the region last year and has gained traction, riding on the $70 million it raised prior to its listing for trading.</p>
<p>“Hong Kong is the only market in Asia where Bitcoin futures ETFs are listed and traded in the institutional market. It will be a new option for investors who are interested in Bitcoin as a competitive product that reflects their experience in risk management,” said Park Seong-jin, head of Samsung Asset Management Hong Kong.</p>
<p>When the ETF goes live, it will offer diversification and a means for investors to meet their demands.</p>
<h2>Samsung Bitcoin Futures: Testament to Hong Kong’s Crypto Stance</h2>
<p>In the early days of crypto, many startups trailing the blaze in the industry moved their headquarters to Hong Kong as the region was considered a vibrant place for the ecosystem. Over time, the regulatory approaches got stricter and firms including the now-bankrupt FTX left the shores of the country to set up camp elsewhere.</p>
<p>In 2022, the Hong Kong financial regulator decided to ease up on some of its strict market entry yardsticks and unveiled plans to scrap the $1 million crypto trading capital that was required to be a trader in the industry. With this move, retail investors could now join the ecosystem without much hindrance.</p>
<p>By permitting Samsung Asset Management to float the Bitcoin Futures product that is useful to both retail and institutional investors, the region can be said to be making good on its promises. Meanwhile, Samsung as a brand has continued to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-theta-labs-reward-program/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">show unwavering support for Web 3.0</a> and innovative solutions that are powered by blockchain technology.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/">Samsung Investment Arm to Launch Bitcoin Futures ETF in Hong Kong</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bitcoin-futures-etf-hong-kong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysts Predict: Europe Economy to Take Spotlight in 2023, Not US</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232359</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/">Analysts Predict: Europe Economy to Take Spotlight in 2023, Not US</a></p>
<p>Economic strategists predict that the economy of Europe is in a better position to outperform its US counterpart in 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/">Analysts Predict: Europe Economy to Take Spotlight in 2023, Not US</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/">Analysts Predict: Europe Economy to Take Spotlight in 2023, Not US</a></p>
<p>Several analysts <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/12/europe-could-outperform-the-us-in-equities-and-growth-this-year.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">believe</a> that the US economy and stocks could face a challenging 2023 run, even trailing Europe in the process. For instance, Deutsche Bank’s chief investment officer (CIO) for EMEA, Zeynep Ozturk-Unlu, predicted that Europe would outperform the US in economic growth and capital markets this year. Ozturk-Unlu added that contraction and recession fears could accelerate more in America than in the eurozone.</p>
<h2>US Economy Could Trail Europe in 2023 despite Latter’s Peculiar Macroeconomic Constraints</h2>
<p>Ozturk-Unlu expects Europe to lead the US economy in 2023 despite the region’s peculiar set of challenges. These include the ongoing war in Ukraine, sustained energy crisis, and inflation yet to peak. Commenting on Europe’s energy crisis and inflation that would not hit the European Central Bank’s 2% target anytime soon, Ozturk-Unlu explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Europe has been in expansionary fiscal policy mode for quite a while, especially due to the energy crisis. But beyond that, Europe is also betting on the reopening of China, and it is going to give positive tailwinds to the European growth story.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Nonetheless, the Deutsche Bank EMEA chief investment officer highlighted areas that could spur the European economy further in 2023. These include the diversification of sectors across Europe compared to the US. In addition, Ozturk-Unlu argues that Europe currently boasts more sustainable growth production, especially in Germany and France. She also compared stock potential between the US and Europe. According to the CIO:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It doesn’t mean Europe [stocks] is completely immune and is in great shape, but in relative terms, the shift from growth [stocks] to value actually gives a little bit more opportunity to Europe compared to the US.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>US Tech Stock 2022 Drubbing</h2>
<p>US tech stocks, usually called growth stocks, took a hard hit last year amid continued interest rate hikes by the Federal Reserve. That unsavory development also encroached on the future earnings potential of these stocks and triggered a major selloff in 2022. By comparison, value stocks tend to outperform as rates ride higher, and Europe has an abundance of value stocks compared to its peers.</p>
<p>The European Stoxx 600 index has already risen 5% on a year-to-date basis compared to the US <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P’s</a> 3.4% rise for the same period. Furthermore, European shares also outperformed the US in 2022 despite registering their worst performance since 2018. Last year, European stocks ended with a 13% loss versus the 19.4% recorded by the S&amp;P 500 for the same period.</p>
<p>Ozturk-Unlu concluded, saying, “the world outside of the US will outperform the US, and Europe in relative terms, in equities, will outperform.”</p>
<p>Besides Deutsche Bank, other economic analysts and strategists also make strong cases that Europe <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/euro-bullish-sentiments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">will thrive</a> in 2023. These analysts point to further Fed rate tightening, eurozone fiscal stimulus, and China’s reopening.</p>
<p>Safra Sarasin’s chief economist Karsten Junius maintains that there will be a flat GDP growth in Europe this year. This economic forecast fares better than Junius’s projected 0.5% contraction in the US. However, he does not expect his guidance to result in outperformance in equity markets. According to Junius, the recent euro appreciation could weigh on earnings with a three-month delay.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/">Analysts Predict: Europe Economy to Take Spotlight in 2023, Not US</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/europe-economy-2023-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paytm Shares Decline Following Alibaba Affiliate’s Alleged Sale of Stake Worth $125M </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ant financial]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan stanley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paytm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/">Paytm Shares Decline Following Alibaba Affiliate&#8217;s Alleged Sale of Stake Worth $125M </a></p>
<p>Digital payments firm Paytm saw its stock decline markedly after a shareholder offloaded 19.20 million shares.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/">Paytm Shares Decline Following Alibaba Affiliate&#8217;s Alleged Sale of Stake Worth $125M </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/">Paytm Shares Decline Following Alibaba Affiliate&#8217;s Alleged Sale of Stake Worth $125M </a></p>

<p>Paytm shares <a href="https://www.cnbctv18.com/market/stocks/paytm-large-trade-2-crore-shares-540-apiece-stock-declines-15650041.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">suffered</a> an 8.8% decline on Thursday following a series of block deals recorded by parent One97 Communications Ltd. According to reports, roughly 19.20 million shares or a 3% stake in the digital payments and financial services platform changed hands. The monetary value of the recent sale is around $125 million. Reports also stated that the likely seller in the Paytm block deal is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group</a> affiliate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ant-financial/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ant Financial</a>. As of September last year, Ant Financial held 164.42 million shares, or a 24.88% stake, in Paytm. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> (NYSE: MS) reportedly advised Alibaba on the deal.</p>



<p>The recent decline in Paytm shares marks the steepest plunge since November 22nd. The company&#8217;s stock was trading at Rs 528 a share as of press time. In addition, Paytm was trading down 5% from its previous close on the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE). Before this development, the company&#8217;s stock had accrued 15% since December 26th. It traded up in 12 out of the last 14 sessions in that same period.</p>



<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) estimates that Antfin Netherlands Holding procured Paytm shares between 2015 and 2019. Furthermore, the average stock price was Rs 300 a share during this acquisitional period. Meanwhile, the Alibaba Group-affiliated organization also invested in Paytm in 2015 at an average Rs 330 cost of acquisition. As of the end of September 2022, Alibaba held a 6.26% stake in the Indian &#8220;pay through mobile&#8221; initiative.</p>



<h2>Other Supporting Details to the Paytm Shares Decline Report</h2>



<p>On Monday, Paytm reported to exchanges the disbursement of 3.7 million loans valued at Rs 3,665 crore in December. This development represents an on-year jump of 330% and a 357% disbursement climb for the December quarter.</p>



<p>With total disbursements for the December quarter at Rs 9,958 crore, the number of monthly transacting users also spiked 32% to 85 million. This figure stood at 65 million a year ago.</p>



<p>Paytm&#8217;s processed gross merchandise value experienced a 38% surge year-over-year to Rs 3.64 lakh crore last December. In addition, the Indian digital payments platform also added one million payment devices between October and December. Furthermore, the number of subscribed merchants for payment devices reached 5.8 million in December 2022.</p>



<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM) previously weighed in on Paytm&#8217;s approved share buyback scheme last December. JPMorgan wrote in a December 14th note to investors:</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>&#8220;We expect it to burn $33 million over the next three quarters before turning Adj Ebitda breakeven in 2QFY24. We expect the buyback announcement at a 50 percent premium to provide support to the stock price in the near term. The reduction in cash because of the buyback offsets the reduction in share count, thereby keeping our price target unchanged. Reiterate Overweight.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>



<p>The Paytm board approved the buyback of shares worth Rs 850 crore, or $103 million, via the open market route. The number of shares repurchased could total 10.5 million at the optimum buyback price of Rs 810.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/">Paytm Shares Decline Following Alibaba Affiliate&#8217;s Alleged Sale of Stake Worth $125M </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/paytm-shares-decline-alibaba-affiliate-stake/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stripe Cuts Internal Valuation for Second Time in 6 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[block]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232329</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/">Stripe Cuts Internal Valuation for Second Time in 6 Months</a></p>
<p>In reaction to the current market outlook, in November last year, Stripe laid off as many as 1,120 of its workers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/">Stripe Cuts Internal Valuation for Second Time in 6 Months</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/">Stripe Cuts Internal Valuation for Second Time in 6 Months</a></p>
<p>Irish-American financial services and SaaS company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/stripe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stripe</a> has received its second valuation cut in 6 months, a sign that the fintech ecosystem is yet to recover from the underlying strain in the sector across the board. As <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation-by-11-implying-63-billion-valuation" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by The Information, the latest valuation pegs the company’s internal value at $63 billion after an 11% cut in its share price.</p>
<p>Unlike publicly listed companies whose valuation can easily be showcased through their market capitalization, the case is different for private outfits like Stripe. Rather than depend on the market capitalization of its stock, private entities get valued after a funding round or through a third-party estimation using a benchmark of factors.</p>
<p>In the case of Stripe’s recent valuation cut, no funding was raised, and the estimation was done through the 409A price change. The valuation from 409A is done by third parties under the rules that are put in place by the Internal Revenue Service (IRS).</p>
<p>This valuation approach does not impact the outlook of the firm by venture capital investors, and it is particularly essential to help set a benchmark value for a firm against its publicly listed competitors. Per its design, companies are expected to be getting a 409A valuation once every year, however, Stripe’s valuation now seems to be more frequent than normal</p>
<p>The new valuation that Stripe got places the fintech giant’s internal share price at $24.71, a price point that is 40% below its All-Time High (ATH) value.  As a financial services provider, Stripe plies its trade in the same industry as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/square/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Block Inc</a> (NYSE: SQ) to mention a few. Of these, Paypal boasts of a market capitalization of $89.54 while Block is pegged at $42.86 billion.</p>
<h2>Stripe Renewed Valuation: Potential Benefits</h2>
<p>Getting a 409A valuation can present a number of benefits for a company, should it choose to maximize the potential of the event. Most companies particularly use the valuation to offer staff members a cheaper-than-expected stock option while a number of others utilize it to attract new talents to the company.</p>
<p>With the global economy still hitting most financial service providers very hard, so many companies have had to devise another avenue to cut and manage their cost of operations and this latest Stripe 409A valuation can give the firm a number of ways to actualize this.</p>
<p>In reaction to the current market outlook, in November last year, Stripe laid off as many as 1,120 of its workers, in what seems antagonistic to the subtle usage of the 409A valuation. The laid-off staff at the time represented 14% of its workforce with a handful retrenched from one of its acquired subsidiaries, TaxJar back in August.</p>
<p>The company’s CEO, Patrick Collison <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/11/stripe-internal-valuation-63-billion-409a/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">justified</a> the layoffs saying the firm projected growth too fast for 2022 and this year and “underestimated both the likelihood and impact of a broader slowdown.”</p>
<p>Learning from its mistakes, the company may use its 409A valuation to project a realistic public market debut.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/">Stripe Cuts Internal Valuation for Second Time in 6 Months</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-cuts-internal-valuation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ubisoft Latest Game Cancelation and More Bad News Causes Shares to Plunge 20%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ubisoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ubisoft stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/">Ubisoft Latest Game Cancelation and More Bad News Causes Shares to Plunge 20%</a></p>
<p>Due to the bad news, which includes the canceled games and financial challenges, Ubisoft plans to "depreciate around €500m of capitalized R&#038;D".</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/">Ubisoft Latest Game Cancelation and More Bad News Causes Shares to Plunge 20%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/">Ubisoft Latest Game Cancelation and More Bad News Causes Shares to Plunge 20%</a></p>
<p>French video game publisher Ubisoft saw its shares slump 20% after the company shared some bad news. The video game publisher announced delaying the release of its game &#8220;Skull and Bones&#8221;. It is indeed bad news from Ubisoft as the Skull and Bones game will be delayed again. That means that it will no longer launch on the 9th of March which was the most recent schedule. With no specific date fixed, the French company now expects to release the game anytime from April 2023 to March 2024.</p>
<h2>Bad News from Ubisoft</h2>
<p>In addition to the postponement of the Skull and Bones Game, Ubisoft also mentioned canceling three other projects. The Assassin&#8217;s Creed creator said it is dismissing the three projects to focus on its existing brands and live services. The delayed game, unannounced game cancellations, and disappointing sales all summed up the bad news, leading to a lower share price for Ubisoft. Ubisoft also mentioned the underperformance of Mario + Rabbids: Sparks of Hope toward the end of last year and early this year. It also complained about the poor performance of Just Dance 2023.</p>
<p>The latest game cancellations make it seven games in total that Ubisoft canceled in the last six months. Some of the tried and failed games included Prince of Persia and Avatar: Frontiers of Pandora, which will be delayed until 2023-2024. At the same time, the company has ceased the development of the Splinter Cell VR title, Ghost Recon Frontline</p>
<p>Evidently, the recent report indicated that Ubisoft may be struggling, and investors did not take the bad news in good faith. The French video game publisher&#8217;s stock on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinspeaker-advent-dow-jones-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones</a> took an initial hit of 10.5% and continued in its downturn. Also, the stock prices have plunged to reach their seven-year low.</p>
<h2>Ubisoft&#8217;s Plans Amid Downturns</h2>
<p>Due to the bad news, which includes the canceled games and financial challenges, Ubisoft plans to &#8220;depreciate around €500m of capitalized R&amp;D&#8221;. The company is also looking to reduce internal costs by €200m for the next two years. The reductions will cut across reselling off assets, restructuring, and &#8220;natural attrition.&#8221;</p>
<p>Recent years have seen the game industry shift toward mega-brands and sustainable titles that can reach audiences around the world. The shift also focuses on reaching players on different platforms and business models. Although Ubisoft has attempted to do the same, it has yet to be successful. CEO Yves Guillemot stated that the company is disappointed in its recent performance. He <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/11/ubisoft-cancels-three-games-slashes-targets-on-worsening-conditions.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are facing contrasted market dynamics as the industry continues to shift towards mega-brands and everlasting live games, in the context of worsening economic conditions affecting consumer spending.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other business news <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/">Ubisoft Latest Game Cancelation and More Bad News Causes Shares to Plunge 20%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ubisoft-bad-news-shares/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TSMC Releases 2022 Q4 Earnings, Profit Climbs 78%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/">TSMC Releases 2022 Q4 Earnings, Profit Climbs 78%</a></p>
<p>During Q4 2022, TSMC reported 52% in its operating margin, gross margin was 62.2%, and net profit margin was 47.3%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/">TSMC Releases 2022 Q4 Earnings, Profit Climbs 78%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/">TSMC Releases 2022 Q4 Earnings, Profit Climbs 78%</a></p>
<p>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/">TSMC</a>) has posted another quarterly record and a 78% surge in net profit during 2022 Q4. The company saw exponential growth in its net profit due to the solid sales of advanced chips. The sales helped <a href="https://investor.tsmc.com/english/encrypt/files/encrypt_file/reports/2023-01/1a8d67b6664e51d49cbbbd2b16fcd2ec36b3acab/4Q22EarningsRelease.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">TSMC in 2022 Q4</a>, evading the industry-wide downtown that affected other manufacturers.</p>
<p>During the December quarter, the semiconductor company and Apple’s major supplier noted that its net profit moved from T$166.2 billion in the previous year to T$295.9 billion. Meanwhile, the average estimate by analysts was T$289.44 billion. Analysts explained that the company’s dominance as one of the world’s top advanced chip manufacturers had helped its earnings. In addition to the increase in net profit, TSMC reported that its revenue in 2022 Q4 rose 26.7% YoY to $19.93 billion but fell 1.5% from Q3. The company projected that its YoY revenue would come between $19.9 billion and $20.7 billion. After losing 27.1% in its share price in 2022, TSMC has gained 8.5% since the year started, resulting in a $412.78 billion market valuation.</p>
<p>Generally, rising interest rates by the Feds to combat inflation has affected different sectors, including chip manufacturers. The chip industry has struggled with lower demand for gadgets amid the economic downturn. TSMC cut its annual budget by at least 10% for 2022 back in October. The company also pushed out a cautious note on upcoming demand. It referred to challenges associated with rising inflationary costs and predicted a hit on the chip market in 2023.</p>
<h2>TSMC in 2022 Q4</h2>
<p>During Q4 2022, TSMC reported 52% in its operating margin, gross margin was 62.2%, and net profit margin was 47.3%. Shipments of 5-nanometer accounted for 32% of total wafer revenue during the period. At the same time, 7-nanometer of the total wafer was 22%. Advanced technologies was 54% of total wafer revenue. TSMC vice president and chief financial officer Wendell Huang spoke about the 2022 Q4 performance:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our fourth quarter business was dampened by end market demand softness, and customers’ inventory adjustment, despite the continued ramp-up for our industry-leading 5nm technologies. Moving into first quarter 2023, as overall macroeconomic conditions remain weak, we expect our business to be further impacted by continued end market demand softness, and customer’s further inventory adjustment.”</p></blockquote>
<p>On 2023 Q1 guidance, TSMC expects revenue to come between $16.7 billion and $17.5 billion. The company is also predicted to realize between 53.5% and 55.5% in gross profit margin and between 41.5% and 43.5% in operating profit margin. The capital budget expected for the new year is between $32 billion and $36 billion.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/">TSMC Releases 2022 Q4 Earnings, Profit Climbs 78%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-2022-q4-earnings-profit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Arena Naming Rights Deal Officially Terminated</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/">FTX Arena Naming Rights Deal Officially Terminated</a></p>
<p>Naming rights have been a popular initiative for crypto firms before the commencement of the crypto winter of 2022.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/">FTX Arena Naming Rights Deal Officially Terminated</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/">FTX Arena Naming Rights Deal Officially Terminated</a></p>
<p>FTX Arena is a thing of the past. As the crypto industry is slowly coming to terms with the massive fall of crypto exchange platform FTX, a judge from Florida declined <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> its naming rights to the home of the Miami Heat on Wednesday.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.nba.com/news/miami-dade-county-wins-right-to-strip-ftx-name-off-heat-arena" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">news</a> follows a court verdict in the Bankruptcy Court of Delaware, where the lawyers argued that the funds from Alameda Research sponsored the deal with Miami-Dade county. The county had already obtained approval to remove FTX signage after the exchange directive for Chapter 11 bankruptcy safekeeping last November.</p>
<p>The order on Wednesday confirmed the parties&#8217; division and enable the owners of the Miami Heat arena to search for newer collaborations on the enterprise. According to Legal Analyst David Weinstein, while monetary compensation will be provided to redeem the money lost under the contract, this is one of those scenarios where collaborations end up slashing ties and moving on.</p>
<p>According to Weinstein, Miami-Dade will however, have to decide on what the county will do with the money accepted by FTX in the deal, or alternatively, return the money over to bankruptcy court reviewing the FTX case. The court will then examine how Miami-Dade received the money, and if they were conned like any other investor in this case.</p>
<p>The two-hundred and thirteen million, eighteen thousand seating capacity which was inaugurated in 1999 as American Airlines Arena, was signed in for a nineteen-year contract by FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried with Miami-Dade, the arena&#8217;s owners. This was done for a cumulative naming rights deal of $135 million which would have paid the county $2 million every year.</p>
<p>The deal had also been an eyebrow-raiser for the crypto industry, since not only was the amount large, but also that FTX had only been 2 years old at that time.</p>
<p>FTX collapsed from being a multibillion-dollar company to a bankruptcy story within weeks. The number of FTX investors and customers who lost a total amount of $8 billion is most likely to go over 1 million. FTX co-founder and CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman Fried</a> was charged last month in an eight-count indictment with defrauding clients of and lenders to the crypto exchange. He has also been charged with defrauding lenders to his privately-controlled hedge fund Alameda Research.</p>
<p>Naming rights have been a popular initiative for crypto firms before the commencement of the crypto winter of 2022. In November 2021, Crypto.com, which was also a competitor cryptocurrency exchange signed a deal for $700 million with the owners of the then Staples Center, the home of the Los Angeles Lakers and Clippers.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/">FTX Arena Naming Rights Deal Officially Terminated</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-arena-naming-rights-deal-terminated/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Logitech Lowers Performance Forecast after Q3 Revenue Miss</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logitech]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/">Logitech Lowers Performance Forecast after Q3 Revenue Miss</a></p>
<p>Considering the current business state of the company, it has revised its target for the year and it said it now expects its overall revenue to drop by 13-15%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/">Logitech Lowers Performance Forecast after Q3 Revenue Miss</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/">Logitech Lowers Performance Forecast after Q3 Revenue Miss</a></p>
<p>Swiss multinational manufacturer of computer peripherals and software, Logitech International SA (SWX: LOG) has tapered down its expectations and business outlook for the 2023 Fiscal Year. The company <a href="https://infotechlead.com/devices/logitech-lowers-revenue-and-profit-outlook-76251">reduced</a> its forecast for the year following a relatively poor performance as recorded in the third quarter of the 2023 fiscal year ended December 31, 2022.</p>
<p>According to Logitech, the third quarter net sales fell in between the range of $1.26 billion and $1.27 billion, down between 22 and 23% in US dollars. The sales also fall between 17 and 18% in constant currency, compared to Q3 of the prior fiscal year.</p>
<p>“We are disappointed in these preliminary third-quarter results. They reflect challenging macroeconomic conditions including a slowdown in sales to enterprise customers in the quarter. Based on the softer than expected third-quarter results, and uncertainty in supply availability related to the current Covid outbreak in China, we are reducing our full-year outlook,” said Bracken Darrell, Logitech president, and chief executive officer.</p>
<p>As a tech gadget manufacturer, the disruptions to the manufacturing processes and the global supply chain had a major toll on its operations in the third quarter and over the past year. The company reported a shunted operating income which is pegged between $171 million and $176 million, down between 33 and 35%, compared to $263 million in the same quarter a year ago.</p>
<p>While Logitech’s preliminary operating margin for the quarter is expected to be between 13.5 and 13.8%, The company’s gross margin came in between 37.5 and 37.6% respectively. Amid the plunging revenue and cash flow, the company’s top executive said more attempts will be made to cut costs and improve profitability in the near future.</p>
<p>“We will continue to manage our costs to drive solid operating performance and will provide more detail on our earnings call later this month. We remain confident in our strategy and the long-term trends that fuel our business,” Bracken said.</p>
<h2>Logitech Renewed Forecast</h2>
<p>Considering the current business state of the company, it has revised its target for the year and it said it now expects its overall revenue to drop by 13-15%. These revised bearish estimates compare to an earlier drop of 4-8%. This will effectively place its operating income at a range of $550 to $600 million as against the earlier guidance of $650-$750 million.</p>
<p>Logitech is hoping to do many things differently in order to correct the losses. At this time, it remains unclear if the cost management plans will entail the laying off of its workforce as has been done by many tech giants including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN) which recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-record-layoff-economic-crisis/">laid off</a> 18,000 of its workers.</p>
<p>The company’s shares trading in Switzerland plummeted by 14.13% to CHF 53.84 while the company’s shares on the NASDAQ Global Select Market slumped by 13.18% in the Pre-Market in what looks like a vote of no confidence from investors on the future potentials of the firm.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/">Logitech Lowers Performance Forecast after Q3 Revenue Miss</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-forecast-q3-revenue-miss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador Passes Law Paving Way for Bitcoin Bond Issuance</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bonds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232276</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/">El Salvador Passes Law Paving Way for Bitcoin Bond Issuance</a></p>
<p>Lawmakers in El Salvador have greenlit a law that could facilitate the country’s long-standing Bitcoin bond initiative. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/">El Salvador Passes Law Paving Way for Bitcoin Bond Issuance</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/">El Salvador Passes Law Paving Way for Bitcoin Bond Issuance</a></p>
<p>El Salvador has taken a monumental step toward adopting and issuing the first-ever sovereign Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) bond. On Wednesday, Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-11/el-salvador-passes-law-that-would-enable-bitcoin-bond-issuance?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that the Central American nation’s Congress recently approved a digital securities law potentially underpinning Bitcoin bond sales. This law allows El Salvador to generate funds through the world’s first sovereign Bitcoin bond. The bill, which secured an overwhelming 62 Congress votes in favor, will head to El Salvador President Nayib Bukele for signing.</p>
<p>16 Congress members voted against the proposed El Salvador Bitcoin bond law.</p>
<h2>El Salvador Bitcoin Bond Law</h2>
<p>Also known as the Volcano bond, the bill constitutes a legal framework that underscores Bukele’s intentions to sell blockchain bonds. In addition, the securities could raise $500 million to help establish a tax-free coastal town called Bitcoin City. The El Salvadoran government intends to situate Bitcoin City at the foot of a volcano, where it would draw geothermal energy. This natural resource would provide the energy required to mine digital coins at the site.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the government’s proposal also includes another $500 million to purchase BTC. Bondholders would also be privy to any appreciation in the leading digital currency.</p>
<p>The proposed Bitcoin bond law has come under criticism by credit ratings agencies and the International Monetary Fund (IMF). Meanwhile, El Salvador’s sovereign bonds are trading at a discount to peers as investors factor in the risk of default.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Journey So Far</h2>
<p>In 2021, the nation of El Salvador became the first in the world to adopt Bitcoin as legal tender. Shortly afterward, Bukele <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-city-1-billion-tokenized-btc-bonds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">intimated plans</a> for the volcano bond during a presentation to BTC enthusiasts in November 2021. According to the government’s initial proposal, the tokenized bonds would see a US-dollar denomination and pay 6.5% annually for 10 years.</p>
<p>El Salvador planned to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-bitcoin-bonds-risks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">raise $1 billion in BTC-backed bonds</a> in the first quarter of 2022. At the time of the announcement, Bitfinex chief technology officer Paolo Ardoino said the exchange would play a pivotal supporting role. This role would entail the establishment of a securities platform to hold El Salvador’s Bitcoin bonds. Ardoino also added at the time:</p>
<blockquote><p>“[The platform] will soon be home to many local and foreign digital assets offerings developing new digital asset regulation for the country! El Salvador, Bitfinex, and Blockstream are making history together.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the bond issuance saw several postponements due to the brutal crypto market downturn that characterized much of 2022. On separate occasions in <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-postpones-bitcoin-bond/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">March</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-postpones-bitcoin-bond-second/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">June</a> last year, El Salvador finance minister Alejandro Zelaya announced the postponements. At the time, Zelaya said the Central American country would wait for a more favorable market environment. Furthermore, he stressed that Bitcoin’s price decline had hurt investor sentiments.</p>
<p>El Salvador finally paved the way for its Bitcoin bonds by introducing a digital assets bill last November. The country has shored up on BTC since it adopted the prominent crypto in 2021.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/">El Salvador Passes Law Paving Way for Bitcoin Bond Issuance</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/el-salvador-law-bitcoin-bond-issuance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple May Launch Touchscreen Mac Laptop from 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=232278</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/">Apple May Launch Touchscreen Mac Laptop from 2025</a></p>
<p>Reports say that tech powerhouse Apple could soon release touchscreen versions of its Mac laptop lineup in 2 years. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/">Apple May Launch Touchscreen Mac Laptop from 2025</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/">Apple May Launch Touchscreen Mac Laptop from 2025</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/">Apple</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) is mulling releasing a touchscreen version of its Mac laptop line in the near future. According to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-11/apple-working-on-adding-touch-screens-to-macs-in-major-turnabout?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, the tech giant could release a touchscreen-enabled MacBook Pro laptop as early as 2025. This potential move marks a significant U-turn for Apple, which, on numerous occasions, previously described touchscreen laptops as ergonomically inferior.</p>
<p>Former Apple CEO, the late Steve Jobs, once argued about the practicality of touchscreen laptops. According to Jobs, reaching up to touch an upright screen &#8220;doesn&#8217;t work.&#8221; As Jobs put it back in 2010:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Touch surfaces don&#8217;t want to be vertical. After an extended period of time, your arm wants to fall off.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The California-based multinational tech company also previously worried that touchscreen Macs could encroach on iPad sales.</p>
<p>Although Apple might disrupt its production trend by releasing a laptop with touchscreen functionality, it does not need a sales boost. Sales in the tech giant&#8217;s Mac business are up 40% since the pandemic-riddled year of 2020. Furthermore, Apple&#8217;s decision to replace Intel processors with its own silicon in most of its computers contributed immensely to increased sales. The change improved Mac&#8217;s battery life and reduced overheating, helping the computer brand generate $40.1 billion in revenue during Apple&#8217;s fiscal 2022. The sales surge also represented a 14% increase from 2021.</p>
<h2>What We Know So Far on Potential Apple Touchscreen Laptop</h2>
<p>The proposed Apple touchscreen laptop may sport an OLED screen instead of the standard Mini LED displays. In addition, the model&#8217;s first design would also include the standard trackpad and keyboard.</p>
<p>As teams inside Apple continue to work on the touchscreen Mac project, observers also ponder the implied functionality changes. For example, a touchscreen-enabled Mac would require notable software alterations to accept finger taps and pokes. These changes could also demand larger buttons instead of the traditional mouse clicks. For instance, Apple&#8217;s iPhones and iPads use an operating system specifically designed for touchscreens. Conversely, the company&#8217;s macOS software is currently only controllable with a mouse and keyboard.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-11/apple-working-on-adding-touch-screens-to-macs-in-major-turnabout?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bloomberg&#8217;s</a> Mark Gurman stresses that there are no final plans regarding the launch of a touchscreen Mac. Gurman also pointed out that Apple could always change its plans, as evidenced by <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/6/23542525/apple-iphone-se-4-2024-canceled-rumor-qualcomm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">previously scrapped projects</a>. The company once made prototype Macs with touchscreens that never materialized in its product lineup.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Gurman opines that the rumored Apple touchscreen Mac would retain the same form factor as current models. According to him, the only difference in functionality would be the ability to gesture and tap on the screen.</p>
<h2>Apple to Start Manufacturing In-House Screens in 2024, Decreasing Supply Dependency on Samsung</h2>
<p>In other related news, Apple recently <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-11/apple-to-begin-making-in-house-screens-in-2024-in-shift-away-from-samsung?fromMostRead=true&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> plans to start using its own custom mobile display by 2024. This development marks a shift away from an over-reliance on technology partners such as Samsung and LG.</p>
<p>Apple&#8217;s stock rose 2.1% to $133.49 on Wednesday and is up 2.7% this year.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-sell-user-names-revenue/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/">Apple May Launch Touchscreen Mac Laptop from 2025</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-touchscreen-mac-laptop-2025/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>