<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:50:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitgo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mt gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
<p>Despite challenging market conditions, BitGo secures massive funding as it successfully navigates through the uncertainties in crypto regulations. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, August 16, crypto custodian <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bitgo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BitGo</a> announced its plans to raise $100 million at a staggering valuation of $1.75 billion. The company said that it will use these funds for strategic acquisitions as well as to expand its secure and regulated wallet, custody, and other solutions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BitGo has secured $100M Series C funding.</p>
<p>Trust is not given, it is earned. We believe in delivering it to our clients and the industry. Being a custodial and infrastructure leader is an undertaking, one we have consistently provided for over a decade.</p>
<p>This funding will allow… <a href="https://t.co/TlPO7722Ha">pic.twitter.com/TlPO7722Ha</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BitGo (@BitGo) <a href="https://twitter.com/BitGo/status/1691802052849201443?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>From January 2023 onwards, BitGo has experienced a 60% surge in newly registered clients and a 20% growth in Assets Under Custody (AUC). Besides, it has also registered a remarkable 200% rise in fiat custody, and an extraordinary 40-fold expansion in staked assets. Notably, BitGo also handles custody services for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> creditors&#8217; funds under the leadership of John Ray III. Previously, it was serving as the distributor for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mt-gox/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mt. Gox</a> creditors as well.</p>
<p>Mike Belshe, the Chief Executive Officer, recognized that the current market is undoubtedly challenging. However, he pointed out that the company&#8217;s emphasis on obtaining licenses and adhering to regulations has distinguished it in the midst of a legal environment characterized by uncertainties regarding the classification of digital assets as securities. &#8220;Regulatory safety is a top concern for everyone at the moment,&#8221; Belshe stated. Speaking further on the matter, Belshe <a href="https://www.prweb.com/releases/bitgo-secures-100m-series-c-funding-at-1-75b-valuation-301901731.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Not only are we seeing growing demand for regulated custody solutions in the US, but we&#8217;re also seeing the demand on a global scale. We are very pleased to announce our <span class="xn-money">$100M</span> Series C for the purpose of meeting this growing need and to provide institutions, brands, coin foundations, and others with secure and seamless participation in the digital asset ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Latest Funding from New Investors</h2>
<p>The company, headquartered in Palo Alto, California, secured the funding exclusively from fresh investors, as <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitgo-bucks-crypto-downturn-to-raise-funding-at-1-75-billion-valuation-1.1959756" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> by Belshe. While he refrained from revealing the participants in the round, he did mention that they hailed from both the US and Asia, and some were not from the cryptocurrency sector. Among BitGo&#8217;s earlier investors were <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs Group Inc.</a>, DRW Holdings, and Galaxy Digital Ventures.</p>
<p>The startup&#8217;s current valuation significantly exceeds its value in 2021, a period during which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/galaxy-digital/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Galaxy Digital Holdings</a> intended to acquire the company for $1.2 billion. However, this deal was eventually abandoned.</p>
<p>BitGo&#8217;s previous fundraising was in 2017, during which it obtained a Series B funding of $42.5 million. This round was spearheaded by Valor Equity Partners and saw involvement from individuals like former PayPal COO David Sacks, former Remarq CEO Bill Lee, and the trading firm DRW. Notably, the list of earlier investors in the crypto custodian encompasses names like Goldman Sachs, Craft Ventures, and Pantera Capital.</p>
<p>Recently, crypto custodian BitGo <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-cancels-acquisition-prime-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decided</a> to cancel the acquisition of Prime Trust, just after a few days of its preliminary agreement.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/">BitGo Successfully Completes $100 Million Fundraise Despite Rough Market Conditions</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitgo-100-million-fundraise/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone 15]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united states]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
<p>Apple CEO Tim Cook is claiming that India simply offers a “huge opportunity”, so, the firm has been ramping up iPhone production in the region.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
<p>It appears that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) may be attempting to diversify the production of its iPhones from its manufacturing base in China. This follows after a recent Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-16/apple-supplier-foxconn-begins-iphone-15-production-in-india">report</a> revealed that Apple supplier Foxconn is set to begin producing the company&#8217;s next-generation iPhone 15 in India. Interestingly, this will be the first time that a new iPhone will be made outside China before an official unveiling.</p>
<p>According to the report, the new phones will be manufactured at a Foxconn plant in Sriperumbudur, Tamil Nadu. And more importantly, they will be ready for delivery only a few weeks after they begin shipping from China-based factories.</p>
<h2>Apple Says There&#8217;s Huge Opportunity in India</h2>
<p>It might be worth noting that Apple has been aiming to make some key changes to its supply chain. That is even as tensions continue to grow between the United States and China. While the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Biden</a>-led administration has been sceptical about allowing the flow of key technologies and investments into China, China <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/intel-drops-tower-acquisition-us-china-tension/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">has also placed</a> regulatory pressure on many US entities.</p>
<p>However, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/tim-cook/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tim Cook</a> is claiming that India simply offers a “huge opportunity”. And in line with this potential, the firm has been ramping up iPhone production in the region. According to Bloomberg, Apple assembled over $7 billion worth of devices in India in the last fiscal year.</p>
<p>It is also worth mentioning that, before the iPhone 14 was released, iPhone production in India lagged behind that of China by up to six to nine months. However, that difference in the production timeline is now set to significantly change.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth though, the scale of ‌iPhone 15‌ production in India will certainly depend on the availability of imported components and the ramp-up of production lines. But Pegatron and Wistron factories will soon be joining Foxconn to assemble the ‌iPhone 15‌.</p>
<p>Apple will unveil the iPhone 15 at its annual event in September. The model is expected to have major camera updates and an improved processor.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 996px; top: 224.778px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/">Apple Begins iPhone 15 Production Outside China</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-iphone-15-production-outside-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
<p>In an announcement on August 16, the company said it had integrated its Ledger Live app with PayPal.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
<p>Crypto security firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ledger/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ledger</a>, known for its hardware wallets, has joined forces with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal,</a> an online payment platform based in the United States, to provide on-ramp payment solutions to users. Through this integration, customers can purchase cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>), Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>), Litecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LTC</a>), and Bitcoin cash (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BCH</a>) directly through the Ledger Live app using their verified PayPal accounts.</p>
<p>Ledger Live, known for its user-friendly interface, presents a smooth experience for both novices and seasoned crypto enthusiasts. The platform, which has about 1.5 million active users, allows customers to buy crypto using fiat currencies.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.ledger.com/ledger-and-paypal-team-up-to-simplify-entry-into-the-world-of-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, users who have previously transacted cryptocurrencies through PayPal will not have to undergo additional verification while using the app. However, new users must create a PayPal account and undergo compulsory know-your-customer (KYC) verification before using the services.</p>
<h2>PayPal Joins Ledger List of Partners for On-ramp Solutions</h2>
<p>Through this collaboration with Ledger, PayPal has joined the list of payment partners for on-ramp solutions. Before the partnership, Ledger users had alternatives such as MoonPay, Wyre, and Coinify to choose from for on-ramp solutions.</p>
<p>However, the new integration with PayPal has a twist as it eliminates the need for intermediary steps. Once a purchase is made using PayPal, the acquired digital currencies are promptly transferred to the user&#8217;s Ledger wallet, reducing customer wait times.</p>
<p>&#8220;We&#8217;re combining the uncompromising security of Ledger with PayPal&#8217;s leadership in protected payments technology to help facilitate a seamless platform for user crypto transactions. Ledger is committed to simplifying the world of crypto, and PayPal is committed to making the movement of money as simple, reliable, and affordable as possible,&#8221; said Pascal Gauthier, Chairman and CEO of Ledger.</p>
<h2>PayPal Integration Only Available to US Customers</h2>
<p>Ledger said in the announcement that the PayPal integration is currently limited to US users only. However, the usage is subject to applicable state laws. Over time, the company plans to make the service available in other jurisdictions.</p>
<p>Additionally, both Ledger and PayPal plan to roll out more features to the on-ramp solution in the coming months. The collaboration between PayPal and Ledger comes as the payment firm faces competition from new ventures introduced by tech giants like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a>. Due to the increased competition in the payment market, the company has expanded its involvement with crypto to establish a stronger presence.</p>
<p>The firm recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> its native stablecoin pegged 1:1 to the value of the US dollar. The stablecoin dubbed PYUSD is based on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>Shortly after the launch of the stablecoin the company also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-cryptocurrencies-hub-pyusd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introduced</a> its Cryptocurrency Hub, where users can interact with different digital assets directly on the platform.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/">Ledger Partners with PayPal to Allow Users Make Crypto Purchases</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ledger-partners-paypal-crypto-purchases/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[valkyrie]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
<p>Along with investing in Ether Futures, the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF will invest in other instruments like cash, cash-like instruments, or high-quality securities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, August 16, Valkyrie Funds filed with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for a new fund that would specifically invest in Ether Futures. With this, Valkyrie joins the likes of Volatility Shares, Bitwise, and others, who have already submitted their applications for the Ethereum futures ETF.</p>
<p>Dubbed the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF, the fund aims to offer investors capital appreciation by investing in the ETF contracts on Ether as well as other &#8220;collateral investments&#8221;. This includes high-quality securities such as commercial papers and Treasury bonds. Note that, unlike the spot ETF contracts, the fund won&#8217;t directly invest in Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>). In its filing on Wednesday, August 16, Valkyrie <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1877493/000138713123009893/valkyrie-485apos_081523.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Ether and ether futures are a relatively new asset class. They are subject to unique and substantial risks, and historically, have been subject to significant price volatility. The value of an investment in the Fund could decline significantly and without warning, including to zero. You should be prepared to lose your entire investment.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The filed document highlights that Ether&#8217;s classification could vary as either a currency or digital commodity, depending on its role in specific transactions. While some retailers accept it as payment, its use for commercial and retail transactions remains limited. Additionally, Ether can serve as a store of value, despite experiencing notable price volatility at times.</p>
<p>Along with investing in Ether Futures, the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF will invest in other instruments like cash, cash-like instruments, or high-quality securities. Valkyrie&#8217;s application notes that the ETF investment in Ether futures contracts shall be limited to 8,000 contracts per month. This will be in compliance with position limits offered by the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cme-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME</a>).</p>
<h2>Race for Ethereum Futures ETFs</h2>
<p>After a strong wave of spot bitcoin ETF applications, the race for Ethereum futures ETFs is also catching up fast. Applications for Ethereum futures ETFs have been submitted by Bitwise, VanEck, ProShares, Grayscale, Volatility Shares, and Roundhill, totaling six companies.</p>
<p>Volatility Shares has been leading the race and was the first to apply on July 28. Volatility Shares has recently stated that its Ethereum Strategy ETF will be live on October 12. The ETF by Volatility Shares centers around trading cash-settled Ethereum futures contracts on the CBOE.</p>
<p>Some market analysts believe that the US SEC is more likely to approve the Ethereum futures ETF than the spot Bitcoin ETF. Bloomberg ETF analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas have raised the likelihood of the US SEC approving a spot Bitcoin ETF this year to 65% from the previous estimate of 50% a few weeks ago. Meanwhile, the probability of an Ethereum ETF approval stands at 75%, although Balchunas suggests a 95% likelihood for Ether futures.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/">Valkyrie Funds File for New Ethereum Strategy ETF with the US SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/valkyrie-ethereum-strategy-etf-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment Banking Declarant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs inc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
<p>This move holds significant implications for the case as it introduces a new perspective to the legal proceedings.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
<p>In a recent development, Judge Analisa Torres has granted <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.888.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">permission</a> for an investment banker declarant to make an appearance in the legal proceedings involving <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple Labs Inc</a> and the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<h2>The Role of the Investment Banker Declarant</h2>
<p>An investment banker declarant is an individual who provides expert testimony and insights based on their professional experience in the financial and investment sector. In this case, Andrew A. Kunsak, a representative from the law firm Sidley Austin LLP, will serve as an investment banker declarant in the SEC vs Ripple Labs lawsuit.</p>
<p>One of the main issues in the ongoing case is the rejection of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>’s plea to seal documents related to the Hinman speech. This speech, delivered by former SEC official William Hinman in 2018, has immense significance as it could potentially shed light on the SEC’s stance on whether <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a> qualifies as a security.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, Ripple’s request to seal information about XRP sales, including programmatic and institutional sales, further adds to the complexity. Amidst these intricate legal maneuvers, Kunsak’s role becomes pivotal. As an expert in the financial and investment sector, his insights hold the potential to reshape the court&#8217;s understanding of XRP&#8217;s nature and implications.</p>
<p>Kunsak’s objective aligns with safeguarding stakeholders- a group that encompasses investors, market participants, and Ripple itself. His expert testimony will seek to present a holistic view of the financial aspects surrounding XRP, offering a counterpoint to the SEC’s arguments.</p>
<h2>SEC Submits an Interlocutory Appeal Motion</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the SEC is <a href="https://www.docdroid.net/jbnzuoG/latest-file-pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">seeking</a> an interlocutory appeal following Judge Analisa Torres’ verdict,  marking a significant shift in the legal proceedings. The verdict, which ruled that programmatic sales of XRP did not fall under the classification of securities as per the Howey Test, has implications that resonate beyond the immediate case.</p>
<p>The SEC’s appeal seeks to challenge this determination and potentially redefine the regulatory boundaries for digital assets like XRP.</p>
<p>Additionally, the SEC has taken the additional step of requesting a suspension of ongoing proceedings until its concerns are adequately addressed through court clarification. This move, while procedural, holds the potential to influence the pace and trajectory of legal proceedings.</p>
<p>In response to these developments, Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer, Stuart Alderoty, has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-sec-appeal-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">offered</a> a clarification that sheds light on Ripple’s intentions. Alderoty emphasized that the organization’s pursuit of court authorization to lodge an appeal is not indicative of a challenge to the ruling on XRP&#8217;s classification.</p>
<p>This clarification underscores Ripple’s commitment to pursuing legal avenues within the established framework. Recently, some lawmakers in the US have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-legislation-coinbase-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">chastised</a> the SEC for using enforcement action against the crypto business rather than developing a solid framework for legal clarity.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 443px; top: 200.778px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/">Ripple vs SEC: Court Approves Investment Banker Declarant</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-vs-sec-investment-banker-declarant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Startups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fintech companies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fintech hub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk fintech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uk fintech growth fund]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
<p>Such companies as Barclays plc, National Westminster Bank (NatWest), Mastercard Incorporated (NYSE: MA), London Stock Exchange Group, and Peel Hunt have backed FinTech Growth Fund.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
<p>UK FinTech Growth Partners LLP has <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230815937510/en/UK-FinTech-Growth-Partners-Announces-the-Launch-of-its-Growth-Stage-FinTech-Fund" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of the FinTech Growth Fund – an investment fund aimed at supporting companies at the early stages of their business until they can go public. The move aims to back UK&#8217;s image as a fintech hub as well as allow the country to compete with Silicon Valley.</p>
<p>Basically, FinTech Growth Fund will provide four to eight investments per year, with investments between £10 million and £100 million, as well as offer strategic support to its portfolio companies to help them bring their corporate ambitions to life. The fund is set to make the first investments as soon as the fourth quarter of this year.</p>
<p>Such companies as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/barclays/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Barclays plc</a>, National Westminster Bank (NatWest), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mastercard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mastercard Incorporated</a> (NYSE: MA), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/london-stock-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">London Stock Exchange Group</a>, and Peel Hunt have backed FinTech Growth Fund.</p>
<p>Lord Dominic Johnson CBE, Minister of State, Department for Business and Trade, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;UK Fintech remains one of this country’s crown jewels, casting a shining light to global investors that attracted $12.5 billion of inward investment in 2022. Second only to the US and larger than the next 13 European markets combined, UK Fintech can still reach new heights with new UK-based growth funds. I welcome the launch of the Fintech Growth Fund and wish them well in their fundraising.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The leading team of the fund has also been formed. Its board of partners includes experts in the industry, such as Angel Issa &#8211; former Global Head of Corporate Development &amp; Strategic Investments at Nomura, Joe Parkin – former Managing Director &#8211; Head of Banks, Digital Channels and UK Inorganic at BlackRock, Kaushalya Somasundaram &#8211; Former Executive Director and UK Head of Payments, Partnerships &amp; Industry Relations at Square; and Phil Vidler – CEO of FinTech Alliance.</p>
<h2>UK&#8217;s FinTech Climate</h2>
<p>Earlier, Britain was facing criticism saying that the UK government put barriers to fintech entrepreneurs and forced them to consider listings overseas, especially after the country’s exit from the European Union, which undermined the UK&#8217;s status as a global financial centre.</p>
<p>In response to scepticism, the London Stock Exchange has undergone a number of reforms to encourage fintech firms to float in the UK rather than in the US. Besides, the government created initiatives to promote innovation and growth, such as the Fintech Delivery Panel and the Fintech Sector Strategy. As a result, the UK is now the leading fintech hub in Europe.</p>
<p>Fintech is one of the UK&#8217;s strongest startup sectors, with more than 1,500 high-growth fintech companies currently active, 20 fintech unicorns (around half of the UK&#8217;s billion-dollar startups), and more venture capital investment than any other industry. The sector is home to many of the world’s largest fintech companies and is comprised of more than 1,600 firms. This number is projected to double by 2030.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/">UK Launches £1 Billion FinTech Growth Fund to Support Growth Stage Companies</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/uk-1b-fintech-fund-support-growth-stage-companies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fed’s Caution on Inflation Drags US Equities Down, Nasdaq Corrects 1% for Second Day</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 07:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dow jones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq composite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/">Fed&#8217;s Caution on Inflation Drags US Equities Down, Nasdaq Corrects 1% for Second Day</a></p>
<p>Market's bullish sentiment dampens with the Fed hinting that more rate hikes are on the cards amid the sticky inflation. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/">Fed&#8217;s Caution on Inflation Drags US Equities Down, Nasdaq Corrects 1% for Second Day</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/">Fed&#8217;s Caution on Inflation Drags US Equities Down, Nasdaq Corrects 1% for Second Day</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, August 16, stocks continued to fall on Wall Street for the second day in a row as investors grappled with Fed&#8217;s July meeting thereby hinting at potentially higher interest rates ahead. All of the top three US indices turned negative for the second consecutive day.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones Industrial Average</a> (INDEXDJX: .DJI) fell by 0.52%, shedding 180.65 points to reach 34,765.74. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> (INDEXSP: .INX) decreased by 0.76%, closing at 4,404.33. In the same period, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-nasdaq-composite-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq Composite</a> (INDEXNASDAQ: .IXIC) dropped by 1.15% to finish the day at 13,474.63.</p>
<p>During the July meeting, the Fed officials noted that additional monetary policy tightening was necessary in order to bring inflation down. The meeting <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/15/stock-market-today-live-updates.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">summary</a> notes:</p>
<blockquote><p>“With inflation still well above the Committee’s longer-run goal and the labor market remaining tight, most participants continued to see significant upside risks to inflation, which could require further tightening of monetary policy.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The federal funds rate is already at its 22-year high and is currently between 5.25% to 5.5%. The Intel stock saw a decline of over 3%, dragging Dow Jones lower. Sectors like communications services, real estate, and consumer discretionary, each faced losses of more than 1% in the S&amp;P 500.</p>
<p>Amidst this, the corporate earnings season continued. Target&#8217;s shares rose by around 3%, despite the retailer lowering its full-year outlook. Progressive, an insurance company, experienced an increase of nearly 9% due to positive earnings results.</p>
<p>Equities faced a challenging period in August, with the S&amp;P 500 hovering around lows not seen in a month. Data highlighting persistent inflation and a strong economy are fueling concerns that interest rates could remain elevated for an extended duration. Although investors mostly anticipate that the Fed&#8217;s monetary tightening is approaching its conclusion, there are concerns that the central bank might prolong the current rate levels.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Experts Share Their Views</h2>
<p>Market analysts chipped in sharing their views on the Fed&#8217;s comments and what follows ahead. Peter Tuz, president of Chase Investment Counsel in Charlottesville, Virginia <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-edge-up-focus-shifts-fed-meeting-minutes-2023-08-16/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="text__text__1FZLe text__dark-grey__3Ml43 text__regular__2N1Xr text__small__1kGq2 body__full_width__ekUdw body__small_body__2vQyf article-body__paragraph__2-BtD" data-testid="paragraph-5">&#8220;I agree with the governors that we’re not convinced that inflation is totally in the rearview mirror. I think the markets will be on pins and needles regarding what the Fed will do all through September and into October.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p data-testid="paragraph-5">According to Quincy Krosby, LPL Financial&#8217;s Chief Global Strategist, market sell-offs persist as the recent Fed minutes highlight the necessity for the economic backdrop to scale back, thus leading to a softening in demand.</p>
<p data-testid="paragraph-5">“Recent third-quarter GDP estimates, coupled with fresh retail sales data, suggest a much more robust underpinning to the economy, certainly not what the Fed wants to see as they navigate the so-called ‘last mile’ towards achieving price stability,” Krosby added.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/">Fed&#8217;s Caution on Inflation Drags US Equities Down, Nasdaq Corrects 1% for Second Day</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-equities-down-nasdaq-corrects-fed-inflation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vietnamese EV Maker VinFast Is Worth More than BMW and Ford Following Spike in Shares after Us Trading Debut</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 07:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bmw]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ford]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vinfast]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/">Vietnamese EV Maker VinFast Is Worth More than BMW and Ford Following Spike in Shares after Us Trading Debut</a></p>
<p>VinFast shares jumped nearly 70% following its trading debut and is worth more than Kia and Hyundai combined. However, VFS may be too costly.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/">Vietnamese EV Maker VinFast Is Worth More than BMW and Ford Following Spike in Shares after Us Trading Debut</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/">Vietnamese EV Maker VinFast Is Worth More than BMW and Ford Following Spike in Shares after Us Trading Debut</a></p>
<p>Vietnamese-founded electric vehicle (EV) maker VinFast (VFS) has seen a significant share price spike after its US trading debut. After <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">listing</a> on the Nasdaq, VinFast shares rose, resulting in a market value larger than global heavyweights like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GM</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bmw/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BMW</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/volkswagen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Volkswagen</a>, or <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ford/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ford</a>. The EV maker&#8217;s valuation, at Tuesday&#8217;s close, was also higher than the combined valuations of Kia Corporation and Hyundai Motor Company.</p>
<p>VinFast completed its Nasdaq launch on Tuesday after merging with BlackSpade Acquisition, a special purpose acquisition company (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-special-purpose-acquisition-company-spac/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SPAC</a>). A SPAC typically uses an initial public offering (IPO) to raise funds to acquire an existing company. The SPAC method is a popular way foreign companies list outside their primary jurisdiction.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, VinFast closed at $37.06, 68.4% higher than its $22 opening price. Unfortunately, VFS fell 18.75% on Wednesday and closed at $30.11. The EV maker&#8217;s shares have fallen further in after-hours trading, losing another 4.68% and ending at $28.70.</p>
<p>In a recent interview, VinFast CEO Lê Thị Thu Thủy said the company&#8217;s initial plan was to list via a regular initial public offering (IPO). However, VinFast decided to go the SPAC route due to market conditions.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We were ready to do a traditional IPO. We pursued the path for almost two years but the markets have been challenging so we decided to decouple the listing from the fundraising. We got the financial backing from our parent company and we went ahead with the listing by way of SPAC.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The CEO has also added that the SPAC method was &#8220;just a way&#8221; to list in the US. Lê Thị Thu Thủy said the company did not necessarily consider the reputation of SPACs.</p>
<h2>Are VinFast Shares Too Expensive?</h2>
<p>VinFast shares may be too expensive. The continuous fall in share price might directly reflect this price bloating, especially if VinFast is worth more than some of the more established automakers.</p>
<p>The Vietnamese company does have a few things working for it. For instance, VinFast already has the capacity to produce 300,000 units annually. The company also manufactures several other electric products, including scooters and buses. In the first half of 2023, VinFast sold 850 VF8 electric SUVs in California. The company is also building another production plant in North Carolina to shore up its numbers.</p>
<p>Regardless, there is still the worry that VinFast shares may be a little too overpriced. However, since VFS only just debuted, it is too early to properly evaluate the share price from an educated perspective. Analysts on Wall Street would need a few weeks at best, maybe longer, since VFS&#8217; trading debut was a SPAC merger. At the moment, investors would have to look at the numbers and read meaning into them on their own. Also, since the EV maker is not yet profitable, sales may be the primary metric for calculation. Nonetheless, shares might also fall further after the initial trading debut excitement fades.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/">Vietnamese EV Maker VinFast Is Worth More than BMW and Ford Following Spike in Shares after Us Trading Debut</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/vinfast-worth-more-bmw-ford-trading-debut/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Secures Regulatory Approval for US Crypto Futures Trading </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267150</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/">Coinbase Secures Regulatory Approval for US Crypto Futures Trading </a></p>
<p>With the approval, Coinbase has become the first native crypto company to provide both derivatives and spot trading services directly to customers. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/">Coinbase Secures Regulatory Approval for US Crypto Futures Trading </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/">Coinbase Secures Regulatory Approval for US Crypto Futures Trading </a></p>
<p>Leading American crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Coinbase</a> has received regulatory approval to offer eligible customers in the United States the opportunity to trade Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) and Ethereum (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>) futures contracts. The company will serve as a Futures Commission Merchant (FCM), a type of derivatives exchange controlled by the National Futures Association (NFA).</p>
<p>NFA is a self-regulatory organization under the Commodities Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>). The group is tasked with overseeing the country&#8217;s derivatives industry, including on-exchange traded futures, retail off-exchange foreign currency, and OTC derivatives.</p>
<h2>First Crypto Native to Offer Both Spot and Futures Trading</h2>
<p>Coinbase said in a <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-financial-markets-inc-secures-fcm-approval-to-bring-regulated" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> on 16 August that the NFA approved the license, allowing it to engage with futures trading officially. According to the company, the FCM application was submitted to regulators in September 2021. After two years of deliberations, the firm has finally been greenlighted to offer a derivatives exchange alongside its spot trading options.</p>
<p>With the approval, Coinbase has become the first native crypto company to provide both derivatives and spot trading services directly to customers.</p>
<p>&#8220;Coinbase will now be the first crypto-native leader to directly offer traditional spot crypto trading alongside regulated and leveraged crypto futures on an integrated trading solution for our verified customers,&#8221; the company said.</p>
<p>The exchange described its latest achievement as a &#8220;critical milestone&#8221;, noting that it had passed through stringent requirements to obtain the approval.</p>
<p>While Coinbase&#8217;s customers will soon be able to access futures trading directly through its platform, the company has already laid the groundwork for its derivatives offering. Last year, the exchange acquired FairX, which now operates as the Coinbase Derivatives Exchange.</p>
<p>The platform is open to third-party brokers, FCMs, and market makers, and it has accumulated substantial liquidity, facilitating notable trading volumes in BTC and ETH futures.</p>
<p>In June, Coinbase announced its intentions to launch BTC and ETH futures trading specially designed for institutional investors. Before that, the company said it was considering launching a derivatives platform in Bermuda.</p>
<h2>75% of Crypto Trading Volume Comes from Derivatives Market</h2>
<p>Coinbase also said in its blog post that a large chunk, approximately 75%, of the entire crypto trading volume is generated within the derivatives market worldwide. The company also claimed that &#8220;margin&#8221; trading gives customers an edge over the market compared to those trading spot options.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The global crypto derivatives market represents ~75% of crypto trading volumes worldwide and is a critical trader access point. The ability to trade using margins gives customers leverage and access to the crypto market with less upfront investment than traditional spot trading.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, it is worth noting that Coinbase&#8217;s regulatory milestone comes at a time when the exchange is also dealing with legal challenges. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) filed a lawsuit against the company in June, alleging that it operated as an unregistered exchange in the country.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/">Coinbase Secures Regulatory Approval for US Crypto Futures Trading </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-approval-crypto-futures-trading/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Crypto Mining Industry Forms DEC to Address Wrong Beliefs About Sustainability </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 14:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital energy council]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267152</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/">US Crypto Mining Industry Forms DEC to Address Wrong Beliefs About Sustainability </a></p>
<p>Dubbed the Digital Energy Council (DEC), the team is in Washington DC and was established on the 15th of August.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/">US Crypto Mining Industry Forms DEC to Address Wrong Beliefs About Sustainability </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/">US Crypto Mining Industry Forms DEC to Address Wrong Beliefs About Sustainability </a></p>
<p>The US crypto mining sector has created a lobby group targeted at dispelling misconceptions about its sustainability. Majorly, the DEC wants to address the misbelief about its sustainability with policymakers. The US government has kept an eagle eye over the crypto-mining industry for a while. As much as exchanges have had their share of the persisting scrutiny, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/biden-tax-crypto-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">miners are also in the same boat</a>. The sector has been at the receiving end of multiple actions and has been queried about sustainability and emissions.</p>
<p>The Crypto-Asset Environmental Transparency Act was introduced in Congress in March. At the time, miners were accused of exploiting large amounts of power from public grids. Part of the accusation was that the crypto miners emit vast greenhouse gasses. Hence, the bill seeks that mining firms disclose emissions that utilize over 5 megawatts of power.</p>
<h2>Digital Energy Council (DEC) Kickstarts in US</h2>
<p>Now, the DEC founder and president Thomas Mapes stated that it was high time digital asset miners had a unified voice in Washington. As a matter of fact, Mapes said the action was “long overdue”. As the first member associated, the founder <a href="https://twitter.com/tommapes88/status/1691609288953725032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1691609288953725032%7Ctwgr%5Ee9e3be63c068bb19e1d3602401d73b003422270c%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fcrypto-mining-lobby-digital-energy-council-launched-in-united-states" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> the group will focus on the “intersection of digital asset mining and energy policy at the federal level”.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Its official 🚨 first member association solely focused on the intersection of digital asset mining and energy ⚡️ policy at the federal level, look forward to working with digital asset and energy leaders check it out: <a href="https://t.co/kBFRkXHTNy">https://t.co/kBFRkXHTNy</a> <a href="https://t.co/kzNhtfxYZi">https://t.co/kzNhtfxYZi</a></p>
<p>— Tom Mapes (@tommapes88) <a href="https://twitter.com/tommapes88/status/1691609288953725032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>After years of service as the chief of staff at the US Department of Energy’s Office of International Affairs, the DEC president was also the director of energy at the Chamber of Digital Commerce. According to Mapes, he began to understand the importance of crypto-mining firms to the energy ecosystem. Referring to some of the advantages, he mentioned purchasing excess energy that would have been useless. He also noted providing energy to the grid during demand. He declared his vision about crypto companies serving the same roles as energy companies in the future.</p>
<blockquote><p>“I see energy companies, utility companies, power providers &#8211; the big majors &#8211; all taking a look at this new technology and figuring out ways they can get involved in this.”</p></blockquote>
<p>His opinion about crypto companies appears to be different from US lawmakers, which is why the DEC is committed to correcting misconceptions. Besides clearing the air around the sustainability of mining activities, the DEC also plans to advocate for policies supporting US crypto mining and energy development.</p>
<p>The CEO of one of the DEC member companies, Zach Bradford, said the DEC is the only group in Washington in the US that targets mining and energy abundance. He also referred to politics as a team sport requiring dedication and intense efforts.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-bitcoin-etf-approval-2024/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/">US Crypto Mining Industry Forms DEC to Address Wrong Beliefs About Sustainability </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-crypto-mining-industry-forms-dec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4112 metric#misses=42 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1066447 metric#prefetches=203 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=209 metric#store-misses=3 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=98.21 metric#ms-cache=4.75 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2264 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->