<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:27:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US Senate’s new bill proposes “unworkable obligations for DeFi”, Crypto Council says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senates-new-bill-proposes-unworkable-obligations-for-defi-crypto-council-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AML]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senates-new-bill-proposes-unworkable-obligations-for-defi-crypto-council-says/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Crypto Council for Innovation says the new AML bill provides no workable framework for illicit finance in DeFi. According to the crypto alliance, the bill&#8217;s proposals go &#8220;in the opposite direction&#8221; to what the proper approach should be. The CCI says legal obligations highlighted in the bill are &#8220;arbitrarily placed on persons&#8221;. A bill [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senates-new-bill-proposes-unworkable-obligations-for-defi-crypto-council-says/">US Senate’s new bill proposes “unworkable obligations for DeFi”, Crypto Council says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The Crypto Council for Innovation says the new AML bill provides no workable framework for illicit finance in DeFi.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to the crypto alliance, the bill&rsquo;s proposals go &ldquo;in the opposite direction&rdquo; to what the proper approach should be.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The CCI says legal obligations highlighted in the bill are &ldquo;arbitrarily placed on persons&rdquo;.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A bill introduced in the US Senate on anti-money laundering and other illicit finance activities in the decentralised finance (DeFi) space &ldquo;fails to provide a workable framework&rdquo;, the Crypto Council for Innovation has said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bill was introduced by Senators Jack Reed (Rhode Island) Mike Rounds (South Dakota), Mark Warner (Virginia) and Mitt Romney (Utah). Its proposals include the application of AML obligations to DeFi protocols and crypto ATMs. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senate-introduces-bill-seeking-to-regulate-defi-like-traditional-banks/">reported</a> on the new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">DeFi</a> bill&rsquo;s proposals earlier today.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Legal obligations are arbitrarily placed on persons</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The CCI, which represents a group of industry leaders and players committed to advancing the crypto industry, has released a <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto_council/status/1681680900633837570" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">statement</a> noting that the bills&rsquo; proposals, including the proposed requirements aimed at backers and facilitators of DeFi fall short of a &ldquo;workable framework.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">2/ TL;DR: the proposal fails to provide a workable framework to actually address illicit finance in these sectors. <a href="https://t.co/CIbbbYuIkk">https://t.co/CIbbbYuIkk</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto Council for Innovation (@crypto_council) <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto_council/status/1681680900633837570?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Although it notes that illicit finance is a legitimate national security concern, the council faults the bill&rsquo;s framers for going &ldquo;in the opposite direction&rdquo; with regard to the DeFi sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Illicit finance is a legitimate national security concern, and while its volume is tiny in crypto compared to TradFi, leveraging the transparency &amp; programmability inherent in blockchain systems to derive appropriate compliance measures unique to crypto is a good idea. Unfortunately, this bill goes the opposite direction. It places legal obligations arbitrarily on persons who have no actual way to influence protocols once they are deployed, and completely fails to account for the unique attributes of blockchain-backed systems</em>,&rdquo; the Council said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the issues the CCI points out from the bill is the obligation put on supposed &ldquo;Digital Asset Protocol Backers.&rdquo; Per the bill, this would be any person holding more than $25 million worth of a DeFi protocol&rsquo;s governance token or has invested $25 million or more into the protocol&rsquo;s development.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It also places obligations on so-called &ldquo;Digital Asset Transaction Facilitators&rdquo;, who would be any person deemed to have control over the protocol or offers access to an application that facilitates transactions on the said crypto protocol.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Council says these proposals are not only &ldquo;weird&rdquo;, but advance vagueness with regard to the definition of &ldquo;facilitators.&rdquo; More than that, the group says the bill contains &ldquo;unworkable obligations&rdquo; and offers &ldquo;no actual guidance.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;&ldquo;<em>The proposal offers no actual guidance on technical ways for decentralised protocols to comply with BSA reporting requirements. It is not feasible to collect personal identification information from such protocols, and the bill neither tackles this technical complexity nor provides solutions on how to address this limitation</em>.&rdquo; the Crypto Council noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of its input on the issue of DeFi regulation, the CCI says it&rsquo;s collaborating with industry experts, regulators both in the US and from elsewhere to draft a framework for the appropriate <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/regulation/">regulation</a> of the sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are consulting with industry experts and regulators in the U.S. and other leading jurisdictions to develop a technologically sound approach to mitigating illicit finance in DeFi</em>,&rdquo; the statement reads in part.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While its strong-worded statement highlighted what&rsquo;s not right with the bill, the CCI acknowledges that it is still in the early stages and that its authors are open to dialogue on best way forward. The expectation is that the bill will see &ldquo;plenty of edits&rdquo; going forward.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">22/ CCI will continue to work tirelessly to ensure policymakers have accurate info about the operations of DeFi protocols and crypto ATMs. It is critical that regulation strike the careful balance between establishing safeguards and fostering innovation in the U.S.</p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto Council for Innovation (@crypto_council) <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto_council/status/1681680922465259521?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senates-new-bill-proposes-unworkable-obligations-for-defi-crypto-council-says/">US Senate’s new bill proposes “unworkable obligations for DeFi”, Crypto Council says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin may be near its next leg up – analyst says</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-near-next-leg-up-canaccord-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 19:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=146918</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Canaccord Genuity analyst sees upside in Bitcoin to over $38,000. Javed Mirza explained his bullish view in a research note today. Bitcoin is already up about 80% versus the start of the year. It&#8217;s a suitable time for long-term investors to build their positions in Bitcoin as the chart suggests it may be about to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-near-next-leg-up-canaccord-analyst/">Bitcoin may be near its next leg up – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Canaccord Genuity analyst sees upside in Bitcoin to over $38,000.</li>
<li>Javed Mirza explained his bullish view in a research note today.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is already up about 80% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p>It&rsquo;s a suitable time for long-term investors to build their positions in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> as the chart suggests it may be about to start a new cycle, says Javed Mirza &ndash; a Canaccord Genuity analyst.</p>
<h2>Recent price trends signal further upside</h2>
<p>Bitcoin remains around the $30,000 level even after peer <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-wins-sec-case-xrp-not-a-security/">Ripple</a> announced a big win against the U.S. Securities &amp; Exchange Commission.</p>
<p>Still, Mirza remains bullish on price trends that he says support further upside. In his research note today, the analyst told investors:</p>
<blockquote><p>Utilise pending near-term weakness to add exposure near important technical support at its 50-day moving averages.</p></blockquote>
<p>The 50-day MA currently sits at about $28,700 for Bitcoin. Mirza has a similar view on Ethereum as well.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin could beat the $38,000 level</h2>
<p>Mirza sees potential for a 28% rally in Bitcoin to over $38,000 level as long as it&rsquo;s holding the aforementioned key support.</p>
<p>In his note this morning, he also pointed to the four-year moving average that the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency has recently reclaimed.</p>
<blockquote><p>This confirms the long-term trend is now up, a strong technical positive, and is consistent with a four-year cycle taking hold in cryptocurrencies.</p></blockquote>
<p>Note that the total supply of BTC is scheduled to halve in April or May of 2024 that typically tends to be a tailwind for its price. On top of that, <a href="https://decrypt.co/147177/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-sec-coinbase-surveillance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> and several other asset managers have recently filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF that signals institutional interest in cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-near-next-leg-up-canaccord-analyst/">Bitcoin may be near its next leg up – analyst says</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XLM outperforms XRP as top altcoins eye fresh bounce</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xlm-outperforms-xrp-as-top-altcoins-eye-fresh-bounce/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XLM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/xlm-outperforms-xrp-as-top-altcoins-eye-fresh-bounce/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XLM price rose by 26% to lead the top 100 cryptocurrencies and outshine XRP&#8217;s 9% gains in the past 24 hours. Stellar has had a series of positive developments, including its partnership with Bitso announced on Wednesday. XLM could bounce to $0.20 if today&#8217;s momentum continues. Stellar (XLM) is currently the top performing altcoin among [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xlm-outperforms-xrp-as-top-altcoins-eye-fresh-bounce/">XLM outperforms XRP as top altcoins eye fresh bounce</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">XLM price rose by 26% to lead the top 100 cryptocurrencies and outshine XRP&rsquo;s 9% gains in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Stellar has had a series of positive developments, including its partnership with Bitso announced on Wednesday.</li>
<li dir="ltr">XLM could bounce to $0.20 if today&rsquo;s momentum continues.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/stellar-lumens/">Stellar (XLM)</a> is currently the top performing altcoin among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, XLM price has spiked more than 26% in the past 24 hours as of 2 pm ET on July 19. Stellar&rsquo;s native token was trading above $0.16, with a short term bullish outlook that suggests bulls could have a fresh go at the $0.20 supply wall.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stellar&rsquo;s XLM outpaces XRP</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In recent days, its been <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/">Ripple&rsquo;s XRP</a> token that led the market in an upward push following its market-defining win against the US Securities and Exchange (SEC). Stellar rode that wave to hit highs of $0.19 last week. [<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xlm-price-soars-as-stellar-rides-ripples-xrp-wave/">Read more</a>].</p>
<p dir="ltr">But while XRP remains above prices it traded at prior to Judge Analisa Torres&rsquo; ruling that XRP was not a security, its XLM that is outshining the rest of the top 100 coins today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XRP is trading near $0.83 at the time of writing, roughly 9% up in the past 24 hours. Meanwhile, XLM has jumped from lows of $0.14 to an intraday peak above $0.16. On Tuesday, XLM/USD rebounded off the demand zone near $0.12 to give bulls new impetus seen today.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/19/1689791700537-00be689c-48b3-4b69-9205-e6803e7e5ee7.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="287"><span class="fr-inner">Stellar XLM price movement on the daily chart. Source: <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/7FJdh0jD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">XLM/USD is looking for a buffer at the resistance zone near $0.15. If the price holds above this level, it is possible buyers would go for the aforementioned primary target or higher. The bullish outlook is largely helped by the technical picture and the sentiment catalysed by Stellar&rsquo;s recent series of great news.</p>
</div>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is Stellar price up today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/">highlighted</a> earlier today, Stellar has partnered with Latin American crypto firm Bitso to bolster international payments to Colombia, Argentina and Mexico using USDC. &nbsp;This came after Stellar and crypto platform fonbnk1 teamed up to help millions of unbanked across Africa to tap into the blockchain benefits via their prepaid SIM cards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">350 million people in Africa don't have access to bank accounts, and only 20% of families have formal bank accounts.<a href="https://twitter.com/fonbnk1?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@fonbnk1</a> provides a real-world solution to this problem by turning 8 billion active prepaid SIM cards globally into virtual debit cards with Stellar. (1/3)</p>
<p>&mdash; Stellar (@StellarOrg) <a href="https://twitter.com/StellarOrg/status/1681396712756379648?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Stellar also recently announced a partnership with Honeycoin App to enable users across Kenya, Uganda, Tanzania, Nigeria, Ghana and the UK to cash out using their USDC balances at any MoneyGram location in these countries.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xlm-outperforms-xrp-as-top-altcoins-eye-fresh-bounce/">XLM outperforms XRP as top altcoins eye fresh bounce</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk&#8217;s tweet causes Dogecoin to pop</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/elon-musks-tweet-causes-dogecoin-to-pop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/elon-musks-tweet-causes-dogecoin-to-pop/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, Dogecoin (DOGE) was trading at $0.07018 up 3.13% in the last 24 hours. Elon Musk today mentioned &#8220;doges&#8221; in a tweet. Besides Dogecoin, Musk&#8217;s tweet also caused Shiba Inu to a daily high of &#160;$0.00000784. Well-known dog-themed meme coin Dogecoin (DOGE) today surged to a daily high of $0.07121 after Elon Musk [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/elon-musks-tweet-causes-dogecoin-to-pop/">Elon Musk&#8217;s tweet causes Dogecoin to pop</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>At press time, Dogecoin (DOGE) was trading at $0.07018 up 3.13% in the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>Elon Musk today mentioned &ldquo;doges&rdquo; in a tweet.</li>
<li>Besides Dogecoin, Musk&rsquo;s tweet also caused Shiba Inu to a daily high of &nbsp;$0.00000784.</li>
</ul>
<p>Well-known dog-themed meme coin <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> today surged to a daily high of $0.07121 after Elon Musk mentioned &ldquo;Doge&rdquo; in one of his tweets today.</p>
<p>Musk&rsquo;s post caused the price of DOGE to surge from $0.069 to $0.07121 in seconds before quickly giving up some of the gains afterwards.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Doges ftw <a href="https://t.co/bl0trQ7BdU">pic.twitter.com/bl0trQ7BdU</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1681691639922806784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Elon Musk&rsquo;s history with meme coins</h2>
<p>Besides Dogecoin, Elon&rsquo;s tweet also caused the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> to also pop.</p>
<p>This is not the first time the crypto markets are reacting to Elon Musk&rsquo;s tweets. The markets have a long history of responding quickly to Elon Musk&rsquo;s public comments about cryptocurrencies in general and Dogecoin in particular.</p>
<p>When Musk unveiled an AI-focused company last week to compete with ChatGPT, a well-known chatbot, it caused tokens related to artificial intelligence to soar.</p>
<p>Given his particular interest in DOGE, there is speculation in the cryptocurrency community that Musk could be a significant DOGE holder. Musk&rsquo;s interest in DOGE came to the limelight when he appeared on &ldquo;Saturday Night Live&rdquo; in May 2021, and devoted some time to the meme coin causing its price to surge to its all-time high price of 73 cents.</p>
<p>Today&rsquo;s tweet mentioning doge came ahead of Tesla (TSLA) second-quarter earnings report expected to be released later Wednesday afternoon.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/elon-musks-tweet-causes-dogecoin-to-pop/">Elon Musk&#8217;s tweet causes Dogecoin to pop</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar and Bitso partner to facilitate international USDC payments</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 16:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitso]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Latin america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stellar and Bitso are collaborating to promote international USDC payments to Latin America. Bitso will use Stellar&#8217;s Anchor Network to facilitate cross-border payments and remittances to Argentina, Mexico and Colombia. Stellar recently partnered with HoneyComb and Coinme for similar USDC transactions. Bitso, a Latin American crypto-powered financial services platform and crypto exchange, has announced a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/">Stellar and Bitso partner to facilitate international USDC payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Stellar and Bitso are collaborating to promote international USDC payments to Latin America.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitso will use Stellar&rsquo;s Anchor Network to facilitate cross-border payments and remittances to Argentina, Mexico and Colombia.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Stellar recently partnered with HoneyComb and Coinme for similar USDC transactions.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitso, a Latin American crypto-powered financial services platform and crypto exchange, has <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitso/status/1681671631456829440" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> a partnership with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stellar/">Stellar</a> in an effort that will see the two collaborate in advancing international payments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership will see Bitso integrate Stellar&rsquo;s Anchor Network to allow companies from across the world make USDC payments across Latin America, starting with Mexico, Colombia and Argentina.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Bitso, supported transactions are from US dollars via Circle&rsquo;s USDC stablecoin, with this enabled through the crypto exchange&rsquo;s direct connection with the local banking system.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The alliance means companies worldwide will be able to make international payments to the region without the need of an intermediary. Leveraging blockchain technology in such transactions greatly improves the settlement speed and overall costs of cross-border payments and remittances, Bitso SVP of Institutional Product Santiago Alvarado said.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Stellar&rsquo;s push in USDC payments</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Stellar&rsquo;s collaboration with Bitso comes on the back of increased adoption of its technology in cross-border remittances.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this month, the Stellar Foundation Development announced it had partnered with crypto ATM provider Coinme to allow users send and receive USDC on Stellar. The service will be available across all Coinme platforms.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On July 17, Stellar <a href="https://twitter.com/StellarOrg/status/1681014631048024064" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">revealed</a> another collaboration for USDC, this time partnering with cross-border remittance app HoneyComb to enable anyone across Kenya, Uganda, Tanzania, Nigeria, Ghana, and the UK to withdraw cash with USDC balances. The service will be available at all supported MoneyGram locations in these countries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XLM, the native <a href="https://coinjournal.net/stellar-lumens/">Stellar token</a>, was up 13% in the past 24 hours at $0.14 following the news and as Ripple&rsquo;s XRP pumped by 8% to above $0.80.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/">Stellar and Bitso partner to facilitate international USDC payments</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/stellar-and-bitso-partner-to-facilitate-international-usdc-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Labs unveils Solang to enhance Ethereum compatibility</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-labs-unveils-solang-to-enhance-ethereum-compatibility/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-labs-unveils-solang-to-enhance-ethereum-compatibility/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-labs-unveils-solang-to-enhance-ethereum-compatibility/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Solana Labs has unveiled its Solang compiler. Solang will make it easier for Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) developers to transition to the Solana ecosystem. Solang compiler goes live Solana Labs has announced the launch of &#160;Solang, a new compiler designed to smooth the transition for Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) developers into the Solana [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-labs-unveils-solang-to-enhance-ethereum-compatibility/">Solana Labs unveils Solang to enhance Ethereum compatibility</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Solana Labs has unveiled its Solang compiler.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Solang will make it easier for Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) developers to transition to the Solana ecosystem.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solang compiler goes live</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Solana Labs has announced the launch of &nbsp;Solang, a new compiler designed to smooth the transition for Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) developers into the Solana ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a&nbsp;<a href="https://solana.com/news/solang-solana-solidity-evm" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blog post</u></a> on Wednesday, Solana Labs said developers familiar with Solidity can use Solang to write apps on the Solana network. Solidity is Ethereum&rsquo;s primary smart contract programming language.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes a few hours after Neon EVM&rsquo;s release of a similar tool. Solang seeks further to bridge the gap between the Solana and Ethereum ecosystems.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solang is compatible with Ethereum Solidity V0.8</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Solana Labs revealed that Solang has numerous features. One of its core features is that it is compatible with Ethereum Solidity version 0.8.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other features of Solang include;&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Ability to call other Solana smart contracts</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Supports Solana SPL tokens</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Supports program-derived addresses</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Enables development with Anchor</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Builds native Solana smart contracts</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Access to native Solana built-in functionality</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Solana Labs explained that Solana development had been centered around using languages like Rust or C for scripting smart contracts. However, they added that development was evolving toward greater accessibility via Solidity and EVM.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With Solang, developers can now build on Solana with Solidity, a new compiler that helps bridge the gap between EVM developers and the Solana ecosystem.</p>
<p>SOL, the native coin of the Solana ecosystem, has been performing well so far today. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Solana</u></a> stands at $26.146, up by more than 2% in the last 24 hours.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-labs-unveils-solang-to-enhance-ethereum-compatibility/">Solana Labs unveils Solang to enhance Ethereum compatibility</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-labs-unveils-solang-to-enhance-ethereum-compatibility/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Senate introduces bill seeking to regulate DeFi like traditional banks</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senate-introduces-bill-seeking-to-regulate-defi-like-traditional-banks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senate-introduces-bill-seeking-to-regulate-defi-like-traditional-banks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bill aims at ensuring DeFi protocol operating in the US imposes strict controls on their users. The controls proposed in the bill resemble those that apply to traditional banks. The bill also places identity verification requirements on crypto kiosks. The US Senate is prepared to attempt to regulate the cryptocurrency industry once more with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senate-introduces-bill-seeking-to-regulate-defi-like-traditional-banks/">US Senate introduces bill seeking to regulate DeFi like traditional banks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The bill aims at ensuring DeFi protocol operating in the US imposes strict controls on their users.</li>
<li>The controls proposed in the bill resemble those that apply to traditional banks.</li>
<li>The bill also places identity verification requirements on crypto kiosks.</li>
</ul>
<p>The US Senate is prepared to attempt to regulate the cryptocurrency industry once more with a new bill that aims at imposing strict anti-money laundering (AML) requirements on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">decentralised finance (DeFi)</a> protocols.</p>
<p>According to the description of the bill, the Crypto-Asset National Security Enhancement Act of 2023 would mandate DeFi protocols to impose bank-like controls on their user base. According to the briefing document, the bill aims &ldquo;to combat the rise in crypto-facilitated crime and close off avenues for the evasion of money laundering and sanctions measures that are critical to our national security.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>Vetting and collecting information on customers,</h2>
<p>Anyone with a cryptocurrency wallet can use DeFi protocols, which are financial applications that allow borrowing, lending, and trading digital currency using smart contracts. &nbsp;They use of permissionless blockchains making them more difficult to regulate than centralised crypto businesses like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>The proposed legislation aims to deal with the problem of regulating DeFi protocols by imposing obligations on &ldquo;anyone who &lsquo;controls&rsquo; a DeFi protocol or makes available an application to use a DeFi protocol.&rdquo; This is most likely refers to organisations like Unswap Labs that create complex smart contracts for streamlined frontends for protocols like the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/uniswap/what-is-uniswap/">Uniswap</a> decentralized exchange. &nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the bill&rsquo;s briefing document, &ldquo;if nobody controls a DeFi protocol, then&mdash;as a backstop&mdash;anyone who invests more than $25 million in developing the protocol will be responsible for these obligations.&rdquo;</p>
<p>These controlling entities would have to screen and compile data on their clients, keep anti-money laundering programmes up to date, alert the authorities to any suspicious activity, and prevent those who have been sanctioned from using their protocol.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-senate-introduces-bill-seeking-to-regulate-defi-like-traditional-banks/">US Senate introduces bill seeking to regulate DeFi like traditional banks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moxy launches token sale, esports platform</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/moxy-launches-token-sale-esports-platform/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/moxy-launches-token-sale-esports-platform/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/moxy-launches-token-sale-esports-platform/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moxy announced the public sale on Wednesday that its native token MOXY was now available in &#160;a public sale. The company also officially launched its Moxy esports platform and Battle of the Influencers competition. Moxy, a leading blockchain-based esports company, has officially launched its token sale. The team has also announced that its esports platform [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/moxy-launches-token-sale-esports-platform/">Moxy launches token sale, esports platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Moxy announced the public sale on Wednesday that its native token MOXY was now available in &nbsp;a public sale.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company also officially launched its Moxy esports platform and Battle of the Influencers competition.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://moxy.io/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Moxy</a>, a leading blockchain-based esports company, has officially launched its token sale. The team has also announced that its esports platform and the highly anticipated <em>Battle of the Influencers</em> contest is live.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Moxy team revealed the historic triple launch in a press release shared with CoinJournal on Wednesday.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Moxy launches public sale of native token</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MOXY is the native asset of the Moxy ecosystem and is now available to the public in a token sale. According to Moxy, the total supply will be 1.5 billion MOXY tokens. About 17.5% of the total supply was set aside for the, token sale, which includes a private sale, club sale and public sale.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s public sale stage will see esports fans, crypto enthusiasts and the general investor community have a chance to acquire from a pool of 11 million tokens. The public sale price has been set at a starting $0.06, according to details on the platform&rsquo;s <a href="https://moxy.io/tokenomics/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tokenomics page</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for its utility, MOXY will power a global gaming ecosystem. Holders get access to Moxy&rsquo;s on-demand esports platform where they can participate in numerous <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/gaming/">gaming</a> contests for payouts in the native token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Tournaments such as the <em>Battle of the Influencers</em>, an esports challenge for top internet influencers, will be available to the community. Participants will not only be able to battle each other in a blockchain-powered gaming environment, but also compete for a chance to earn MOXY tokens.</p>
<p>Moxy recently <a href="https://twitter.com/Moxyio/status/1679283566851788801" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>partnered</u></a> with service providers to increase the token&rsquo;s visibility. The esports platform also inked a deal with British video game developer Stainless Games in a collaboration that saw it add the shooter game Shock Rods to its catalog.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/moxy-launches-token-sale-esports-platform/">Moxy launches token sale, esports platform</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/moxy-launches-token-sale-esports-platform/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nasdaq suspends the launch of its own cryptocurrency custody</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-suspends-the-launch-of-its-own-cryptocurrency-custody/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-suspends-the-launch-of-its-own-cryptocurrency-custody/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nasdaq]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-suspends-the-launch-of-its-own-cryptocurrency-custody/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nasdaq had announced it will launch the crypto custody services before the end of Q2, 2023. The global securities marketplace has however suspended launching the services. Nasdaq has cited the shifting business and regulatory environment in the United States. The launch of Nasdaq&#8217;s own cryptocurrency custody, which it had previously planned to roll out by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-suspends-the-launch-of-its-own-cryptocurrency-custody/">Nasdaq suspends the launch of its own cryptocurrency custody</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Nasdaq had announced it will launch the crypto custody services before the end of Q2, 2023.</li>
<li>The global securities marketplace has however suspended launching the services.</li>
<li>Nasdaq has cited the shifting business and regulatory environment in the United States.</li>
</ul>
<p>The launch of Nasdaq&rsquo;s own cryptocurrency custody, which it had previously <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-to-launch-its-crypto-custody-services-by-the-end-of-q2-bloomberg/">planned to roll out</a> by the end of the second quarter of 2023, has been put on hold.</p>
<p>According to CEO Adena Friedman, during the Q2 results call, Nasdaq has postponed the launch of its digital asset custody business due to regulatory risks in the United States.</p>
<p>Confirming the suspension of the launch, the CEO said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;This quarter, considering the shifting business and regulatory environment in the United States, we have made the decision to halt our launch of the U.S. digital assets custodian business and our related efforts to pursue relevant license.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Nasdaq still committed to cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>While the global securities marketplace has suspended the launch of its own crypto custody services, it has emphasized that it remains committed to digital asset business development.</p>
<p>While affirming to customers that Nasdaq will closely monitor the market for potential regulatory events in the coming months, Adena Friedman said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We continue to build and deliver technology capabilities that position Nasdaq as a leading digital assets software solutions provider to the broader global industry. This includes advancing our custody solution as a technology platform to serve the broader, global digital assets marketplace.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>The news comes as major crypto-affiliated companies resubmit their spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> exchange-traded funds (ETF) applications with the SEC. &nbsp; Almost all of the firms planning to issue BTC ETFs are working on listing them on the Nasdaq exchange. The SEC is expected to go through the resubmitted applications and determine whether to approve or reject them. The most recent Bitcoin ETF application to be accepted by the SEC is the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF application</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-suspends-the-launch-of-its-own-cryptocurrency-custody/">Nasdaq suspends the launch of its own cryptocurrency custody</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/nasdaq-suspends-the-launch-of-its-own-cryptocurrency-custody/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
