<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This week in crypto: SBF extradited to the United States</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SBF is finally in the United States after signing an agreement earlier this year. The SEC chair said the agency would continue cracking down on cryptocurrency companies. Paxful removes Ether from their trading platform. SBF is now in the United States Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX, is now back in the US after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/">This week in crypto: SBF extradited to the United States</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">SBF is finally in the United States after signing an agreement earlier this year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The SEC chair said the agency would continue cracking down on cryptocurrency companies.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Paxful removes Ether from their trading platform.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>SBF is now in the United States</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sam Bankman-Fried, the former CEO of FTX, is now back in the US after he was extradited from the Bahamas earlier this week. He&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sbf-signs-us-extradition-papers-expected-in-the-us-on-wednesday/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>signed US extradition papers</u></a> earlier this week and was moved to the United States on Thursday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the extradition, SBF was issued a $250 million bail which he paid a few hours later. However, he still has a lot to answer for in the United States.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this week, former Alameda CEO Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/former-alameda-ceo-caroline-ellison-and-ftx-co-founder-gary-wang-plead-guilty/"><u>pleaded guilty</u></a>, after they were charged with committing fraud that resulted in the collapse of the FTX cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the US Attorney for South District of New York (SDNY) Damian Williams, this is likely not the last major development in relation to the FTX investigations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The US SEC also announced earlier this week that it had charged Wang and Ellison for their roles in a multiyear scheme to defraud FTX equity investors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>The SEC to continues its crackdown on crypto</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The SEC chair, Gary Gensler, revealed earlier this week that the agency would continue to clamp down on cryptocurrency companies. He called for the regulation of crypto issuers and exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In an interview earlier this week, Gensler said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Financial history would tell you that most of these tokens [native tokens of crypto exchanges] will fail. [Insiders] sell the public on an idea while they&rsquo;re potentially fraudulently pumping up the stock. This leads to distorted incentives and puts the public further at risk of the token not being properly registered and having proper disclosures and complying with the various provisions of the securities law about anti-fraud and anti-manipulation.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Paxful removes ETH from its platform</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Peer-to-peer trading exchange Paxful announced earlier this week that it had&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paxful-removes-ethereum-eth-from-its-platform/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>removed Ether from its platform</u></a>. The Paxful CEO &nbsp;cited the prevalence of scams among Ethereum-based tokens as one of the major reasons why ETH was removed.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Tezos activates the Lima upgrade</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Tezos team announced earlier this week that it had&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tezos-activates-the-12th-upgrade-lima/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>completed the 12th upgrade</u></a> on its blockchain. The upgrade, called Lima, introduces several new features while also reducing the risk of bugs in smart contracts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lima marks the fourth protocol upgrade in 2022 as Tezos seeks to improve its blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Waves planning to launch another stablecoin</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Waves already has the USDN stablecoin, but that might not be enough. The Waves CEO and founder, Sasha Ivanov, promised that he would launch a new stablecoin, one that cannot be deppeged from the US Dollar.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the CEO said the new stablecoin would not be launched until the USDN plan resolution is implemented.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance.US acquires Voyager assets</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">BAM Trading Services Inc.&rsquo;s bid (operating as Binance.US) was chosen by Voyager Digital LLC, the operating unit of Voyager Digital Ltd., to acquire its assets after reviewing strategic options.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Voyager Digital said it chose Binance.US because it wants to maximise the value returned to clients and creditors as soon as possible. The bid from Binance.US is valued at around $1.022 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Voyager, the bid consists of the to-be-set fair market value of its crypto portfolio, valued at $1.002 billion at current market prices.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/">This week in crypto: SBF extradited to the United States</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-extradited-to-the-united-states/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Classic Price Prediction: ETC seems stable whilst Metacade (MCADE) doesn&#8217;t stop rising</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Classic News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Web3 is a constantly expanding industry and crypto price action tends to favour projects that can adapt to its fast-changing environment. ETC is a classic example of a project that has been left behind due to its inability to scale with the rest of the industry, which has resulted in some pessimistic price predictions for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/">Ethereum Classic Price Prediction: ETC seems stable whilst Metacade (MCADE) doesn&#8217;t stop rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Web3 is a constantly expanding industry and crypto price action tends to favour projects that can adapt to its fast-changing environment. ETC is a classic example of a project that has been left behind due to its inability to scale with the rest of the industry, which has resulted in some pessimistic price predictions for the Ethereum Classic token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In contrast, the latest Ethereum blockchain (ETH) continues to grow. There are some key differences between the two Ethereum chains, including ETH being home to fast-growing projects like Metacade.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Ethereum Classic?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ethereum-classic/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum Classic (ETC)</u></a> is a cryptocurrency that was created as a result of a fork in the Ethereum blockchain. Unlike Ethereum (ETH), Ethereum Classic does not support the use of smart contracts. Since ETC is not Turing Complete, developers cannot create decentralised applications (dApps) on the Ethereum Classic blockchain and this has always placed negative pressure on the Ethereum Classic price prediction.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum Classic is often referred to as &ldquo;Ethereum&rsquo;s original chain&rdquo; because it retains the original Ethereum blockchain. After the Ethereum hard fork in October 2016, Ethereum Classic was kept online by nodes all over the world. This means that crypto users can still make transactions on the Ethereum Classic network, despite Ethereum Mainnet moving in a different direction over the past 6 years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In recent times, Ethereum Mainnet has made the switch from a Proof of Work consensus mechanism to Proof of Stake. This has reduced the cost of supporting network infrastructure. While ETH is now Proof of Stake, ETC remains a Proof of Work blockchain. The result is that Ethereum Classic is slower and more expensive to run with a block time of 14 seconds and high transaction fees due to its energy-intensive mining system.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Price action lacking in ETC</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The current price of ETC is $25.19. Since&nbsp;<a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/au/investing/cryptocurrency/what-is-ethereum-classic/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum Classic is the oldest Ethereum chain</u></a> and is restricted by its inability to support dApps, it has much lower transaction activity than Ethereum Mainnet. With fewer people buying the token, ETC price is now a fraction as high as ETH, with poor Ethereum Classic price prediction assessments coming from analysts looking at its mid- to long-term prospects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite this, the Ethereum Classic market cap is over $3 billion. However, the chain&rsquo;s lack of functionality within the world of Web3 means it has lower growth potential for the long term. In trying to choose the correct Ethereum Classic price prediction, it&rsquo;ll be important to think about the situation from a development perspective. For developers looking to build exciting digital services using blockchain technology, Ethereum Classic is not an option.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The expected result is that new projects building on ETH will continue to gain value while the Ethereum Classic price prediction shows ETC falling even further in the future. It all boils down to utility.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">A New Project in the ETH Ecosystem Making Major Gains</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While ETC price action leaves much to be desired due to its lack of functionality, one token that continues to impress is&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a>. Built using the latest Ethereum blockchain, this project offers broad utility to crypto holders who are looking to make the most out of the Web3 user experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade aims to support the expansion of GameFi as a core sector of blockchain technology. It is a community-driven initiative that rewards crypto natives for providing value to the ecosystem, among a host of other exciting features that are attracting widespread interest.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is a broad gaming platform that aims to support the expansion of GameFi. Play-to-Earn projects are revolutionising the gaming industry, as players gain financial rewards for the time they spend in-game. This is a core reason why so many are predicting high growth potential for the GameFi sector over the coming years and Metacade is positioning itself as a key player.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Millions Expected to Join the Metaverse</h3>
<p dir="ltr">There are many exciting new&nbsp;<a href="https://www.coin98.net/what-is-gamefi" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>P2E</u></a> projects being developed and the scope of what is possible in the metaverse is constantly being expanded. As blockchain technology becomes increasingly more advanced, and the world becomes increasingly more digital, millions of people are expected to jump into the metaverse to enjoy the hottest new Play-to-Earn games.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Supporting GameFi Developers</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade supports this expansion directly through its Metagrants program. The community will get to decide which new GameFi projects sound the most promising, and vote to use the Metacade treasury to directly fund the development teams. Metacade&rsquo;s aim is to drive growth in Play-to-Earn gaming. For innovative developers that have exciting new ideas, this is an extremely valuable service. The Metacade ecosystem could become a hub of technological progress as a result, pushing the limits and ensuring a fresh supply of awesome titles.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Rewarding Play-to-Earn Gamers</h3>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to supporting the continued development of blockchain-based gaming, Metacade offers some unique features to P2E gamers in its own metaverse scope. Active members of the Metacade community can earn MCADE rewards for their contributions. This includes sharing tips, tricks, and useful knowledge about how to optimise your GameFi playing experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The gaming community is at the centre of Metacade&rsquo;s plans for the future. The project aims to connect avid gamers with the best Play-to-Earn opportunities, creating a virtual arcade where users can collaborate and share their insights. Power is given back to the community, as players can share their suggestions with game developers directly and earn MCADE tokens in the process.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MCADE vs ETC: Which Token Should You Buy?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Ethereum Classic continues to hold its price above the $20 mark, investors are favouring projects that support the Web3 ecosystem, giving a relatively negative outlook for Ethereum Classic price prediction. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum Mainnet, on the other hand, remains the most-used network of decentralised applications, and people are bullish on the long-term future of dApps themselves. ETH stands to fare much better than any Ethereum Classic price prediction currently available, and for good reasons: its upcoming projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A prime example of a high-potential project being built on Ethereum is Metacade. Through supporting the expansion of GameFi and offering exclusive benefits to P2E players in an immersive digital world, Metacade is an attractive option for long-term crypto investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE presale is starting out at $0.008 per token. It has high long-term potential, and the price of each token will be increasing as it progresses through presale stages. In contrast, ETC continues to experience slow growth, as the latest Ethereum blockchain offers a vastly improved user experience.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy ETC on eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://www.etoro.com/markets/etc" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ethereum-classic-price-prediction-etc-seems-stable-whilst-metacade-mcade-doesnt-stop-rising/">Ethereum Classic Price Prediction: ETC seems stable whilst Metacade (MCADE) doesn&#8217;t stop rising</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade signs terms to list on BitMart</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metacade is expected to list on BitMart after signing the listing terms. Metacade presale is currently in the Beta Sale stage. The Beta round price of the MCADE token is 0.01 USDT for 1 MCADE. After a successful Metacade (MCADE) presale amid the current crypto bear market, Metacade has today announced that it has signed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/">Metacade signs terms to list on BitMart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Metacade is expected to list on BitMart after signing the listing terms.</li>
<li>Metacade presale is currently in the Beta Sale stage.</li>
<li>The Beta round price of the MCADE token is 0.01 USDT for 1 MCADE.</li>
</ul>
<p>After a successful <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-presale-for-web3s-first-ever-p2e-crypto-arcade-raises-over-670k-in-under-2-weeks/">Metacade (MCADE) presale</a> amid the current crypto bear market, Metacade has today announced that it has signed the terms to get listed on BitMart, a leading crypto exchange ranked at position 21 by CoinMarketCap with an average daily trading volume of about $447M.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&#128680;&#128680;&#128680; BREAKING &#128680;&#128680;&#128680;</p>
<p>We are delighted to announce that we have signed terms with one of the leading exchanges in the crypto space, <a href="https://twitter.com/BitMartExchange?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BitMartExchange</a>! &#9889;&#9889;&#9889;</p>
<p>With over $447m of trading volume in the last 24 hours, they stand 21st in the <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinMarketCap?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@CoinMarketCap</a> exchange rankings! &#128293; <a href="https://t.co/4fxrM0ul6I">pic.twitter.com/4fxrM0ul6I</a></p>
<p>&mdash; METACADE (@Metacade_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Metacade_/status/1606280441190907904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 23, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>If the listing process is to be completed successfully, BitMart will be among the first cryptocurrency exchanges to allow its customers to trade the decentralized GameFi token that has been making headlines in the past month.</p>
<h2>MCADE token performance so far</h2>
<p>Before delving into the performance of the Metacade (MCADE) token, it is important to mention that Metacade is disrupting the crypto market as we know it by creating a decentralized GameFi hub that will bring everything related to Play-to-Earn (P2E) on one platform. P2E games have been such a hit within the blockchain and crypto world, which is likely the reason behind the great performance of the MCADE token at a time when even the likes of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) are struggling.</p>
<p>The MCADE token is currently in the <a href="https://metacade.co/?utm_contentlaunch&amp;utm_term=external&amp;utm_mediumpr=&amp;utm_source=media&amp;utm_campaign=chainwire">Beta presale round</a> and 54% of the available MCADE tokens have already been sold out raising a whopping $1,340,966. One MCADE token is going for 0.01 USDT and the price is expected to rise to 0.012 USDT for one MCADE token in the next stage.</p>
<p>The next phase for Metacade is expected to be highly exciting as gamers and blockchain fanatics collaborate, communicate, and participate in things like dynamic virtual hangouts on the platform.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-signs-terms-to-list-on-bitmart/">Metacade signs terms to list on BitMart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin versus Ethereum: Which one should you buy when the bull market returns</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum rank #1 and #2, respectively by market cap Bitcoin is a digital version of currency while Ethereum powers smart contracts Both cryptocurrencies are attractive in a bull market Bitcoin and Ethereum rank as the biggest cryptocurrencies. To an investor, deciding which one to buy can be confusing. However, it should be easy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/">Bitcoin versus Ethereum: Which one should you buy when the bull market returns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum rank #1 and #2, respectively by market cap</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is a digital version of currency while Ethereum powers smart contracts</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Both cryptocurrencies are attractive in a bull market</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum rank as the biggest cryptocurrencies. To an investor, deciding which one to buy can be confusing. However, it should be easy if you understand the role that each plays in the crypto evolution.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Bitcoin (BTC)</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Think of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> (BTC/USD) as a digital version of your local currency. The biggest cryptocurrency is, however, different since it is based on a peer-to-peer network. It is decentralised, hence distinct from the conventional currencies, which are controlled by states and national central banks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As money evolves and digitisation takes over, Bitcoin could become the new form of money. That will see it become a means of payment and a store of value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Invented in 2009, BTC has immensely grown in value. In 2021, the cryptocurrency tapped an all-time high of above $68,000. That compares to a price of just $500 in 2016 before the cryptocurrency embarked on a sustained surge. Bitcoin now trades above $16,000 after a sustained bear market this year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy BTC</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Ethereum (ETH)</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Ranked as the second largest cryptocurrency,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Ethereum</u></a> (ETH) is viewed as the epitome of smart contracts. Like Bitcoin, Ethereum is decentralised and acts as a store of value, means of payment, and collateral.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, unlike Bitcoin, which is a dedicated form of digital money, Ethereum aims to power smart contracts, dApps, NFTs, and DeFi. It is also relatively newer compared to Bitcoin since it was created in 2015.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ethereum price also had its fair share of strengths, reaching nearly $4,800 in 2021. Ethereum traded at less than $10 in 2016 before the start of a sustained climb. It now trades at $1,200 in a bear market. Investors anticipate that a recent move from proof of work consensus to proof of stake could power Ethereum to previous heights when the bull market returns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy ETH</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTgyNDY&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ETH with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Final verdict</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and Ethereum are very strong&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>cryptocurrencies</u></a>. Their price movement is almost similar, making it difficult to choose one over another. The selection of which cryptocurrency to invest in depends on what you like about each. The technical outlook and fundamentals emerging from each can also help when making a decision.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/">Bitcoin versus Ethereum: Which one should you buy when the bull market returns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-versus-ethereum-which-one-should-you-buy-when-the-bull-market-returns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helium token jumps 36%. Is this a bull trap?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Helium token rose by 36% on Thursday before correcting Helium powers IoT devices through its &#8220;hotspots&#8221; The cryptocurrency remains on a clear downtrend A few&#160;cryptocurrencies embarked on relief rallies on Thursday, although a low-cap coin was among the top gainers. Helium (HNT/USD), a cryptocurrency ranked #91 by market cap, rose by 36% before shedding nearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/">Helium token jumps 36%. Is this a bull trap?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Helium token rose by 36% on Thursday before correcting</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Helium powers IoT devices through its &ldquo;hotspots&rdquo;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency remains on a clear downtrend</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A few&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>cryptocurrencies</u></a> embarked on relief rallies on Thursday, although a low-cap coin was among the top gainers. Helium (HNT/USD), a cryptocurrency ranked #91 by market cap, rose by 36% before shedding nearly half of the gains by Friday. In an exceedingly bearish crypto market, the small-cap token warranted investors&rsquo; attention. What is it?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Helium is a blockchain-powered network that was created in July 2019. It is made to power Internet of Things devices. For instance, it enables wireless devices to communicate and share data through its nodes or &ldquo;hotspots.&rdquo; The network also lets users profitably earn by sharing their broadband. </p>
<p dir="ltr">You would be forgiven for thinking that Helium is less used. Companies that use the IoT technology service of Helium include Abeeway, Agulus, and Airly. The network has been witnessing increasing growth and now connects nearly 1,000k hotspots. In September, Helium announced a migration to Solana to grow its ecosystem. That was after more than 6,000 members voted in favour. The goal of moving to Solana was inspired by the need to cut reliance entirely on its network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Helium token price could be earning boosts from the recent changes, the price is unconvincing. Trading at just $2.0, HNT remains on a clear downtrend. The cryptocurrency has lost 96% of value since its $57 all-time high price in November 2021. The cryptocurrency faces resistance at the 50-day MA.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Helium token rejected at the 50-day MA</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/23/1671805626594-3b76406d-93ac-494c-bda4-368b1cf50f24.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="321"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/HNTUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>HNT/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Helium outlook shows the price coming under pressure as it touched the 50-day MA. From the volume indicators, a price spike happened at $1.6, indicating that buyers were very active. The cryptocurrency traded with an intraday 1,500% jump in volumes at the bottom price.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What next for HNT?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the intraday gains,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/helium/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>HNT price</u></a> lacks a clear path to recovery as the trend is still bearish. The gains could be a bull trap, especially after getting rejected at the moving averages.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy HNT</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance</h3>

    <p>Binance is one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world. It is better suited to more experienced investors and it offers a large number of cryptocurrencies to choose from, at over 600.

Binance is also known for having low trading fees and a multiple of trading options that its users can benefit from, such as; peer-to-peer trading, margin trading and spot trading.
</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-crypto?guid=OTgyNDE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy HNT with Binance today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Vindax</h3>

    <p>VinDAX Exchange has been live for cryptocurrency trading for global users since March 2019. VinDAX focuses on providing exchange services for digital cryptocurrency transcations with high security level, excellent efficiency and well-optmized trading fee.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/vindax-crypto?guid=OTgyNDE&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy HNT with Vindax today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/">Helium token jumps 36%. Is this a bull trap?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/helium-token-jumps-36-is-this-a-bull-trap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin struggles but Okcoin CEO thinks 3 catalysts will make it bullish</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-struggles-but-okcoin-ceo-thinks-3-catalysts-will-make-it-bullish/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-struggles-but-okcoin-ceo-thinks-3-catalysts-will-make-it-bullish/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-struggles-but-okcoin-ceo-thinks-3-catalysts-will-make-it-bullish/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has steadied above $16,000 Okcoin CEO expects Bitcoin&#8217;s bear market to be driven by key developments The cryptocurrency could come under pressure after falling below moving averages No Santa Claus rally for Bitcoin (BTC/USD) lovers? This is the clearest sign as the&#160;BTC price crashed below the moving averages. Despite bulls successfully defending $16,000, Bitcoin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-struggles-but-okcoin-ceo-thinks-3-catalysts-will-make-it-bullish/">Bitcoin struggles but Okcoin CEO thinks 3 catalysts will make it bullish</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has steadied above $16,000</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Okcoin CEO expects Bitcoin&rsquo;s bear market to be driven by key developments</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency could come under pressure after falling below moving averages</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">No Santa Claus rally for Bitcoin (BTC/USD) lovers? This is the clearest sign as the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/#:~:text=The%20price%20of%20BTC%20today,trading%20volume%20of%20%2412.40B." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>BTC price</u></a> crashed below the moving averages. Despite bulls successfully defending $16,000, Bitcoin is far away from a bullish market. However, the CEO of the crypto exchange Okcoin is throwing insights on what to look at for a bullish Bitcoin movement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hong Fang opines that the need for strong monetary systems would drive Bitcoin and crypto. According to the Okcoin CEO, the failures and shortcomings of the existing centralised currency systems could spur bullish markets. Already, a few countries are testing their monetary systems with Bitcoin and crypto. The notable ones in this pack are El Salvador and the Central African Republic. Will more countries join? Fang thinks so.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second event is the Bitcoin halving event in 2024. Fang wonders whether it is coincidental that past halving events have been associated with bullish crypto markets. In this regard, he expects the next cycle to be associated with a bullish market for Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then there is the final and third bullish trigger &ndash; use cases. The CEO says a lot of projects continue to be created in crypto in a bear market. He expects the projects being created right now to be the next trigger of the bull cycle.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">From Okcoin CEO&rsquo;s thoughts, it is clear that he refers to the BTC&rsquo;s long-term focus. However, a technical outlook paints a different picture of the short term.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>BTC price outlook and analysis</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2022/11/23/1671805313109-031997df-190f-4fe6-a6f2-1000037309d7.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="317"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>BTC/USD Chart by TradingView</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">A technical outlook shows Bitcoin struggling after a slight descent. The moving averages are providing resistance to the BTC price. The RSI remains below the midpoint.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is BTC set to touch lower prices?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> lacks a directional movement. $16,000 is the price to watch, although the cryptocurrency has stabilised at this level. On the bullish side, $19,000 is the price ceiling. A recovery above could welcome further gains.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Where to buy BTC</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTgyMzg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTgyMzg&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=VA&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BTC with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-struggles-but-okcoin-ceo-thinks-3-catalysts-will-make-it-bullish/">Bitcoin struggles but Okcoin CEO thinks 3 catalysts will make it bullish</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-struggles-but-okcoin-ceo-thinks-3-catalysts-will-make-it-bullish/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto exchange Binance expands its holiday-themed gift cards</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-expands-its-holiday-themed-gift-cards/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-expands-its-holiday-themed-gift-cards/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance introduced its Gift Cards last year. The cryptocurrency exchange has expanded its Gift Cards selection to include over 238 designs. The Secret Santa promotion will end on December 28th. Binance Gift Cards has new designs Binance, the leading cryptocurrency exchange, announced earlier this week that it had expanded its Gift Cards selection.&#160; The cryptocurrency [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-expands-its-holiday-themed-gift-cards/">Crypto exchange Binance expands its holiday-themed gift cards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Binance introduced its Gift Cards last year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange has expanded its Gift Cards selection to include over 238 designs.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Secret Santa promotion will end on December 28th.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance Gift Cards has new designs</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/"><u>Binance</u></a>, the leading cryptocurrency exchange, announced earlier this week that it had expanded its Gift Cards selection.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange revealed that it launched its Gift Cards last year, empowering users to gift cryptocurrency in a unique and non-traditional way. Binance added that the gift cards had experienced significant demand, with over 1.8 million traded between July 2021 and October 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2022, the crypto exchange expanded its Gift Cards selection to include over 238 unique holiday-themed designs. In addition to this, Binance said it is hosting a series of promotional events, including Mystery Boxes and a Secret Santa promotion with more than $70,000 in rewards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While expanding on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Binance revealed that the Secret Santa promotion will end on December 28th and will give away 36,000 &ldquo;New User Exclusive (NUE) Gift Cards&rdquo; to fresh users worth up to $5.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance will select the recipients randomly, with 6,000 new users receiving $5 each, 10,000 users awarded $2 each, and 20,000 users collecting $1 each.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Winners can claim their winnings via the Binance app or website, and to redeem the gift cards, recipients must access the platform&rsquo;s official Gift Card website.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Binance launches new features for the Binance Feed</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes a few days after Binance&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-rolls-out-new-features-for-web3-focused-social-platform-binance-feed/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>unveiled new features</u></a> for its Web3-focused social platform, Binance Feed. Binance said the new features would enable users to experience crypto news and content creation seamlessly on different devices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Mystery Box event began on December 19 and is set to be concluded on December 25. During the event, Binance said each of its Gift Cards would include a Mystery Box containing random rewards.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance users can also purchase a Mystery Box for $1 for a chance to multiply the value of their participation fee. Following the end of the event, users can claim their respective rewards from the Mystery Boxes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency exchange revealed that the grand prize in the Mystery Box event on Binance is $2,000, with second and third-place winners receiving $1,500 and $500, respectively.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Binance said it would allow its users to recover their participation cost (entry fee) by opening the Mystery Box within the specified time frame and participating in other seasonal events throughout December.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain ecosystem and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider with a financial product suite that includes the largest digital asset exchange by volume.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-expands-its-holiday-themed-gift-cards/">Crypto exchange Binance expands its holiday-themed gift cards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Astar Network Named Product of the Year At the JBA Annual Blockchain Award</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire ]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=98232</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, 23rd December, 2022, Chainwire Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, has been awarded the Product of the Year at the 4th annual Blockchain Award by the Japan Blockchain Association. Astar Network&#8217;s founder and CEO Sota Watanabe bagged the Person of the Year award for the second consecutive year at the same [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/">Astar Network Named Product of the Year At the JBA Annual Blockchain Award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tokyo, Japan, 23rd December, 2022, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://astar.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Astar Network</u></a>, the smart contract platform for multichain, has been awarded the Product of the Year at the 4th annual Blockchain Award by the Japan Blockchain Association. Astar Network&rsquo;s founder and CEO Sota Watanabe bagged the Person of the Year award for the second consecutive year at the same event.</p>
<p>Both Astar Network and Sota Watanabe emerged as the favorites of the Japanese Web3 community in a survey conducted by the Japan Blockchain Association (JBA). The JBA is the largest blockchain association in Japan, consisting of 171 companies including bitFlyer, Coincheck, Microsoft, GMO, EY, Deloitte, PwC, KPMG, Toyota, and ConsenSys.</p>
<p>Sota Watanabe, the founder and CEO of Astar Network, said, &ldquo;<i>We are delighted to have been recognized by the Japanese Web3 community. As Japan&rsquo;s leading blockchain project, we remain committed to accelerating Web3 innovation through Astar. In 2023 and beyond, we will leverage our presence in Japan to unlock opportunities for entrepreneurs, developers, and users alike.&rdquo;</i></p>
<p>Astar Network is the leading Layer-1 chain in Japan. As a parachain of Polkadot, it enables developers to build interoperable dApps. It supports both EVM and WASM smart contracts with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine messaging (XVM).</p>
<p>As the Japanese government has made Web3 a part of its national strategy, Sota Watanabe is helping the government on the path forward. Sota has also been featured in the Forbes 30 Under 30 for both Asia and Japan. He has also been picked as one of the top entrepreneurs in Japan, and graces the cover of the latest edition of the Forbes Japan magazine.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/test_1671802038FRb9O1zcNf.jpg" alt=""></p>
<p>Astar Network is the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. It&rsquo;s also the first public blockchain from the country to be listed there despite Japan&rsquo;s strict listing regulations. Astar&rsquo;s native token ASTR is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p>
<h3>About Astar Network</h3>
<p>Astar Network supports the building of dApps with EVM and WASM smart contracts and offers developers true interoperability, with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine (XVM). We are made by developers and for developers. Astar&rsquo;s unique Build2Earn model empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the code they write and dApps they build.</p>
<p>Astar&rsquo;s vibrant ecosystem has become Polkadot&rsquo;s leading Parachain globally, supported by all major exchanges and tier 1 VCs. Astar offers the flexibility of all Ethereum and WASM toolings for developers to start building their dApps.</p>
<p>For more information, visit:<u></u></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://astar.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Website</u></a></li>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/AstarNetwork" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Twitter</u></a></li>
<li><a href="https://discord.com/invite/Z3nC9U4" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Discord</u></a></li>
<li><a href="https://t.me/PlasmOfficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Telegram</u></a></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/AstarNetwork" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>GitHub</u></a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Astar_Network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>Reddit</u></a></li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Maarten Henskens, press@astar.network</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/">Astar Network Named Product of the Year At the JBA Annual Blockchain Award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Astar Network scoops Product of the Year award at the JBA Annual Blockchain Award</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-scoops-product-of-the-year-award-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-scoops-product-of-the-year-award-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-scoops-product-of-the-year-award-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Astar Network has been named the Product of the Year at the JBA Annual Blockchain Award. Astar Network&#8217;s founder bagged the &#8216;Person of the Year&#8217; award for a second-consecutive time. The JBA comprises some of the leading Japanese companies. Astar Network becomes the Product of the Year Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-scoops-product-of-the-year-award-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/">Astar Network scoops Product of the Year award at the JBA Annual Blockchain Award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Astar Network has been named the Product of the Year at the JBA Annual Blockchain Award.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Astar Network&rsquo;s founder bagged the &lsquo;Person of the Year&rsquo; award for a second-consecutive time.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The JBA comprises some of the leading Japanese companies.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Astar Network becomes the Product of the Year</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, announced on Friday, December 23rd, that it had been awarded the Product of the Year at the 4th annual Blockchain Award by the Japan Blockchain Association (JBA).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, Astar Network added that its founder and CEO, Sota Watanabe, also bagged the Person of the Year award for the second consecutive year at the same event.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The JBA is currently the largest blockchain association in Japan and comprises some of the leading global companies, including, bitFlyer, Coincheck, Microsoft, GMO, EY, Deloitte, PwC, KPMG, Toyota, and ConsenSys.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Sota Watanabe, the founder and CEO of Astar Network, said;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We are delighted to have been recognized by the Japanese Web3 community. As Japan&rsquo;s leading blockchain project, we remain committed to accelerating Web3 innovation through Astar. In 2023 and beyond, we will leverage our presence in Japan to unlock opportunities for entrepreneurs, developers, and users alike.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Astar Network&rsquo;s win doesn&rsquo;t come as a surprise</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Astar Network has shown itself to be one of the leading blockchain projects in Japan. It is a leading Layer-1 chain in Japan. As a parachain of Polkadot, it enables developers to build interoperable dApps. It supports both EVM and WASM smart contracts with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine messaging (XVM).</p>
<p dir="ltr">This latest development comes barely a month after the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-introduces-its-all-in-one-tool-for-wasm-smart-contract-developers/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Astar Network launched Swanky</u></a>, an all-in-one tool that gives developers what they need to build WebAssembly (WASM) smart contracts easily.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Astar Network&rsquo;s CEO is helping the Japanese government chart the path forward for web3 development in the country. He has also been featured in the Forbes 30 Under 30 for both Asia and Japan.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Astar Network has become the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. Furthermore, it is the first public blockchain in Japan to be listed there despite the country&rsquo;s strict listing regulations</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to that, Astar&rsquo;s native token, ASTR, is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-scoops-product-of-the-year-award-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/">Astar Network scoops Product of the Year award at the JBA Annual Blockchain Award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/astar-network-scoops-product-of-the-year-award-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
