<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:26:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lamborghini Aims for Record-breaking Sales of 10,000 Cars in 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electric Vehicles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lamborghini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265149</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/">Lamborghini Aims for Record-breaking Sales of 10,000 Cars in 2023</a></p>
<p>Lamborghini’s success in recent years can be largely attributed to the strong performance of its Urus SUV, which has played a pivotal role in the Italian automaker's expansion.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/">Lamborghini Aims for Record-breaking Sales of 10,000 Cars in 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/">Lamborghini Aims for Record-breaking Sales of 10,000 Cars in 2023</a></p>
<p dir="ltr">Luxury sports car manufacturer Lamborghini is gearing ready for a spectacular year ahead with respect to its projected sales. With its sights set on breaking records, the Italian automaker’s CEO Stephan Winkelmann has boldly proclaimed that the company could sell a staggering 10,000 cars in 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“It is not something we are obliged to achieve, but it’s important to show what the health of the company is and how big (clients’) willingness to buy our cars is,” Winkelmann said in a statement.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lamborghini Sales Forecasts: Successful H1 Driver</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This optimistic projection comes as Lamborghini celebrates a successful first half of the year, reporting remarkable increases in both profit and revenues. According to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/lamborghini-could-hit-10000-sales-this-year-ceo-says-2023-07-31/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> from Reuters, the company recorded a total of 5,341 car sales between January and June, marking an impressive 4.9% increase compared to the same period in the previous year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The brand, which is a subsidiary of Germany’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/volkswagen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Volkswagen Group</a> (ETR: VOW3) reported a remarkable 6.7% increase in revenues, reaching an impressive 1.42 billion euros. Furthermore, Lamborghini’s operating income soared to a record-breaking 456 million euros, marking a remarkable 7.2% rise.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The United States stood out as Lamborghini&#8217;s largest single market among the various regions contributing to this outstanding growth. With a total of 1,625 car deliveries during the first half of the year, the American market has demonstrated a strong affinity for the brand&#8217;s iconic vehicles.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Lamborghini’s success in recent years can be largely attributed to the strong performance of its Urus SUV, which has played a pivotal role in the Italian automaker&#8217;s expansion. Priced at around 200,000 Euros ($219,900) before tax, the Urus has proven to be a game-changer for Lamborghini.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Over 9,200 vehicles delivered in 2022 demonstrated the automaker’s capacity to adapt and diversify its product offers while maintaining the exclusive and iconic characteristics that define the brand. On the other hand, its rival, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ferrari/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ferrari NV</a> (BIT: RACE) shipped more than 13,200 cars last year.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lamborghini Moves towards an Electric Future</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Following its optimistic outlook, Lamborghini has announced an ambitious investment of 1.9 billion Euros to shift towards hybrid and electric vehicles by 2027.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Remarkably, Lamborghini introduced its first plug-in hybrid model, the Revuelto, earlier this year. This addition to the lineup complements the existing Huracan 10-cylinder sports car and the highly successful Urus SUV.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking ahead to the future, Lamborghini is also setting its sights on launching its first fully-electric model in 2028. While this is three years after the promised debut of Ferrari&#8217;s electric vehicle, Lamborghini&#8217;s CEO Winkelmann, is resolute in prioritizing the company&#8217;s readiness and ensuring it enters the Electric Vehicle (EV) market at the opportune moment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the electric model&#8217;s debut, Lamborghini aims to introduce a battery-powered version of the Urus in 2029.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Lamborghini&#8217;s Crypto Connection</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, a new wave of speculation is emerging, suggesting that the interest in Lamborghini in the crypto space and the upcoming <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/next-bitcoin-halving-800000th-block/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin halving</a> could potentially lead to a surge in vehicle sales.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As Bitcoin enthusiasts speculate on potential price surges, it&#8217;s not far-fetched to wonder if this excitement could inadvertently spill over into the realm of the luxury car that successful crypto investors cherishes.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While “When Lambo” may remain a fun joke in the crypto community, it underscores the intersection of two dynamic industries and the allure they hold for enthusiasts worldwide. As both luxury automotive and crypto markets continue to evolve, who knows what intriguing crossovers and captivating stories await on the horizon?</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/">Lamborghini Aims for Record-breaking Sales of 10,000 Cars in 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lamborghini-breaking-sales-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>eToro Investors Cash Out $120M in Secondary Share Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etoro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265076</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/">eToro Investors Cash Out $120M in Secondary Share Sale</a></p>
<p>eToro planned to go public in 2022. However, a market downturn in equity and crypto prices forced the company to abandon its IPO plans.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/">eToro Investors Cash Out $120M in Secondary Share Sale</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/">eToro Investors Cash Out $120M in Secondary Share Sale</a></p>

<p>Popular trading platform <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/etoro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eToro</a> has offered $120 million worth of its stocks to existing investors in a secondary share sale. The deal, announced by the company on Friday, slightly lowered its valuation from $3.5 billion in March when it raised $250 million from investors.</p>
<p>The secondary share sale will allow some of eToro&#8217;s early backers to cash out some of their stakes in the company. Consequently, it appears only some employees and investors will get a chance to sell shares. eToro&#8217;s co-founder and CEO Yoni Assia noted that qualified investors will be contacted.</p>
<p>Assia also stated that the company did not issue any new securities and would not profit from the transaction. He emphasized that the firm continues to attract potential investors interested in its prospects.</p>
<p>“As a business which continues to demonstrate sustainable, profitable growth we are considered an attractive investment opportunity by many investors,” he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/31/robinhood-rival-etoro-agrees-120-million-secondary-share-sale.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">concluded</a>.</p>
<h2>eToro Secondary Share Sale Lowers Valuation</h2>
<p>Since its establishment in 2007 in Israel, eToro has grown rapidly. Like many wealth management firms, it tapped into the surge of interest in online trading among retail investors during and after the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
<p>eToro planned to go public in 2022 after merging with FinTech Acquisition Corp V. This pushed the company’s valuation to about $10.5 billion. However, a market downturn in equity and crypto prices forced the company to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-pull-plug-spac-merger/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">abandon its IPO plans</a>. Soon the company’s valuation was cut to $8.8 billion. By March, eToro&#8217;s valuation was just $3.5 billion. The secondary share sale means the valuation is now lower than $3.5 billion.</p>
<p>Despite these, eToro has over 28 million <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/1262787/etoro-registered-users/">registered users</a> from more than 100 countries. Its funded accounts are about 3 million and assets worth $7.8 billion are under administration (AuA). Also, the company generated profits exceeding $50 million in the first half of the year.</p>
<h2>A Commitment to Innovation</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, eToro has been innovating to stay ahead of its competitors like Robinhood. Earlier, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-etoro-trade-stocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eToro partnered with Twitter</a> (now X corp) to allow Twitter users to access stocks and crypto trading using cashtags. It also partnered with MoneyFarm to bring ISA solutions to its clients.</p>
<p>Further, the company upgraded its trading chart through a partnership with TradingView. It also launched a new AI assistant and a trading academy. As a social investing network, eToro claims to empower people to grow their knowledge and wealth as part of a global community of investors.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/">eToro Investors Cash Out $120M in Secondary Share Sale</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/etoro-120m-secondary-share-sale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SoFi Technologies Reports Impressive Q2 2023 Earnings, Surpassing Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sofi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/">SoFi Technologies Reports Impressive Q2 2023 Earnings, Surpassing Expectations</a></p>
<p>The company reported record-breaking new member additions, surpassing the 584,000 mark.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/">SoFi Technologies Reports Impressive Q2 2023 Earnings, Surpassing Expectations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/">SoFi Technologies Reports Impressive Q2 2023 Earnings, Surpassing Expectations</a></p>
<p>SoFi Technologies Inc (NASDAQ: SOFI), one of the leading fintech companies in the US, has released its Q2 2023 financial earnings report, beating expectations and impressing investors with its growth trajectory. According to an official <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230731284667/en/SoFi-Technologies-Inc.-Reports-Second-Quarter-2023-Results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> on July 31, the company reported a net loss of $58 million, or 6 cents per share, a significant improvement compared to the $106 million loss, or 12 cents per share, recorded in the same period last year.  Market experts had earlier projected a 7-cent loss per share, making this a notable 14.29% beat.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s revenue also witnessed a robust surge, climbing to $498 million from $363 million in the previous year&#8217;s quarter. The FactSet consensus estimated income at $486 million on a GAAP basis, but <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sofi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SoFi</a> outperformed predictions by 2.47%.</p>
<h2>SoFi Reported to $2.7 Billion in Deposits in Q2</h2>
<p>SoFi&#8217;s impressive earnings result is evident in its strong financial metrics. Earnings per share surged by 50% compared to the same period last year, highlighting the company&#8217;s improved financial performance. Sales skyrocketed by 37.32%, underscoring SoFi&#8217;s ability to capture a larger market share.</p>
<p>&#8220;We delivered another quarter of record financial results and generated our ninth consecutive quarter of record adjusted net revenue, which was up 37% year-over-year,&#8221; said the company&#8217;s CEO Anthony Noto.</p>
<p>The San Francisco-based company also saw a 26% increase in total deposits during the quarter at $2.7 billion. Notably, over 90% of SoFi Money deposits, including Checking and Savings accounts and cash management accounts, were from direct deposit members.</p>
<p>Buoyed by the news of the over-than-expected financial result, the company&#8217;s stock saw a positive performance on Monday morning, opening the market at $9.36, slightly higher than the previous day&#8217;s close of $9.09.</p>
<p>The stock stayed within the range of $9.16 to $9.60, with an elevated trading volume of 58,205,326 shares, exceeding the three-month average of 47,091,484. Last year, the company&#8217;s stock plunged drastically after the firm mistakenly released incompleted earnings results for Q1 2022.</p>
<p>With the new report, the company&#8217;s market capitalization stood at $9.0 billion, solidifying its position in the financial technology industry.</p>
<h2>SoFi&#8217;s Growth Prospects Remain Strong</h2>
<p>SoFi&#8217;s growth prospects remain strong, with a projected earnings growth rate of 43.00% over the next five years. The company&#8217;s revenue growth in the previous year was an impressive 62.08%, a testament to its ability to generate income effectively.</p>
<p>Despite a negative net profit margin of -18.18%, investors remain confident in SoFi&#8217;s potential. The price/sales ratio of 2.36 signifies investors&#8217; willingness to pay $2.36 for every dollar of the company&#8217;s revenue, showcasing positive market sentiment. Moreover, the price/book ratio of 1.71 indicates that the stock is reasonably priced relative to its book value.</p>
<p>SoFi&#8217;s journey to success extends beyond the positive earnings results as the firm continues to expand its market presence and customer base. The fintech company said it witnessed impressive year-over-year growth in its member base and product offerings during the quarter.</p>
<p>The company reported record-breaking new member additions, surpassing the 584,000 mark, which brought the total number of members to over 6.2 million by the end of the quarter. This achievement represents an increase of over 1.9 million members, or 44%, compared to the end of the second quarter of 2022.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/">SoFi Technologies Reports Impressive Q2 2023 Earnings, Surpassing Expectations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sofi-q2-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoin Frenzy Hits Coinbase-backed Base with Increased Risks of Rug Pulls</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bald]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[base]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brian armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[okex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265126</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/">Memecoin Frenzy Hits Coinbase-backed Base with Increased Risks of Rug Pulls</a></p>
<p>Some memecoin traders were lucky to make huge returns from a small investment while others were rug pulled with a promise of future return.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/">Memecoin Frenzy Hits Coinbase-backed Base with Increased Risks of Rug Pulls</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/">Memecoin Frenzy Hits Coinbase-backed Base with Increased Risks of Rug Pulls</a></p>
<p>The memecoin industry has been used by most crypto traders to fetch higher gains in a bid to accumulate Bitcoins, which is not only expensive to mine but also acquire. Moreover, the memecoin industry is composed of altcoins with higher volatility compared to Bitcoin which has been registering diminished returns. Over the weekend, some cryptocurrency traders had a chance to make decent profits while others were affected by scams.</p>
<h2>Top Memecoins that Made Headlines over the Weekend</h2>
<p>Over the weekend, some crypto traders swapped their Ether tokens for questionable memecoins on Coinbase Global Inc (NASDAQ: COIN)-backed layer two scaling solution dubbed Base. Among the crypto tokens that <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bald-memecoin-base-coinbase-brian-armstrong" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">recorded</a> heightened traded volume over the weekend on Base include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brian Armstrong</a>-themed memecoin dubbed BALD, which experienced a 289,000 percent gain within its first few hours of launch.</p>
<p>According to an on-chain analysis provided by Lookonchain, four Ethereum-based addresses swapped approximately $1k worth of Ether to purchase about 5 percent of the circulating supply of BALD tokens. Interestingly, the said addresses cashed out approximately $1.04 million of Ether a day after trading launched. Notably, the four addresses withdrew 0.5 $ETH from the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bybit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bybit</a> crypto exchange at the same time, cross-chained the assets to the Base network, and purchased $BALD within 4 mins of $BALD starting trading, thus suggesting it was the same person involved in the trades.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">These 4 addresses spent 0.534 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>($1K) to buy 50M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BALD&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BALD</a> (50% of the total supply) within 4 mins of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BALD&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BALD</a> starting trading.</p>
<p>Then sold 37M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BALD&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BALD</a> for 554 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a>($1.04M).</p>
<p>Earned $1M with $1K in 1 day! <a href="https://t.co/gXIDRjbhic">pic.twitter.com/gXIDRjbhic</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1685656638328557569?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to market data provided by Coingecko, BALD traded around $0.081828 on Monday, up approximately 61 percent in the past 24 hours. Although the exact BALD circulating supply was not determined at reporting time, its 24-hour trading volume was about $87 million. Nonetheless, cryptocurrency traders are warned to take extra caution as the BALD project did not have an official website or audited infrastructure and tokenomics.</p>
<p>Another memecoin that made headlines, according to analytics provided by Dexscreener is BASED, which had surged over 1,000,000 percent in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Rug Pull Fears</h2>
<p>However, these meme coins had very thin liquidity, which ultimately trapped crypto traders trying to enter their market. As a result, cryptocurrency traders are exposed to the risks of rug pulls without proper protection.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">OMG some presale on Base just rugged and dev sent a whole ass apology letter <a href="https://t.co/rcmMcP7F7i">pic.twitter.com/rcmMcP7F7i</a></p>
<p>&mdash; punished echo (@OHEXE_ECHO) <a href="https://twitter.com/OHEXE_ECHO/status/1685674734409650176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>For instance, a developer made away with users&#8217; funds with a promise to return them after profit gains. Notably, the developer promised to return funds after profits from the investment hit more than five times, which is basically gambling the money. As a result, cryptocurrency traders have been warned to keep away from risky meme coins as the gain have already been registered.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/">Memecoin Frenzy Hits Coinbase-backed Base with Increased Risks of Rug Pulls</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/memecoin-coinbase-base/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of Korea to Explore CBDC Testing in Selected Regions Outside Seoul </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bok]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265120</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/">Bank of Korea to Explore CBDC Testing in Selected Regions Outside Seoul </a></p>
<p>While the CBDC testing is scheduled for next year, the road to CBDC implementation is not without its challenges.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/">Bank of Korea to Explore CBDC Testing in Selected Regions Outside Seoul </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/">Bank of Korea to Explore CBDC Testing in Selected Regions Outside Seoul </a></p>
<p>The Bank of Korea (BoK) is making headway in its quest to develop and test its central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>). According to a new <a href="https://it.chosun.com/site/data/html_dir/2023/07/31/2023073101135.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from the country&#8217;s local news outlet, the bank has selected three regions for the &#8220;private target CBDC test bed&#8221; outside Seoul, the capital of South Korea. The chosen cities for the closed CBDC pilot program are Jeju, Busan, and Incheon.</p>
<p>The BoK&#8217;s plan includes selecting one of these regions for further experimentation, involving public payments and distribution, as well as establishing franchises capable of accepting CBDC payments. The bank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/samsung-bank-of-korea-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">teamed up</a> with the electronics giant Samsung to work together to build a platform that will enable offline payment of CBDC.</p>
<p>According to a commercial bank official in Korea, the number of eligible citizens in Busan is reportedly substantial, leading the bank to face several challenges. As a result, the bank&#8217;s preference leaned significantly towards Jeju, which boasts the second-largest population among the selected regions.</p>
<h2>South Korea to Allow Tourists to Use Its CBDC For Payments</h2>
<p>The closed tests of the CBDC program in Jeju, Busan, and Incheon are expected to mirror the issuance and distribution structures of their existing local currency schemes.</p>
<p>Each region&#8217;s local currency, such as &#8220;Tamranjeon&#8221; in Jeju, &#8220;Dongbaekjeon&#8221; in Busan, and &#8220;Incheon e-Eum&#8221; in Incheon, has been a vital economic stimulant during challenging times like the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
<p>However, the CBDC&#8217;s ambitions go beyond being just a local currency alternative. The Bank of Korea envisions its CBDC electronic wallet app to cater not only to South Korean residents but also to tourists and civilians, transforming the payment landscape and fostering financial inclusion.</p>
<p>&#8220;The CBDC electronic wallet app will allow not only residents but also many civilians, such as tourists, to [partake],&#8221; an undisclosed bank official told the local news media.</p>
<h2>South Korea in Need of IT Experts to Support Its CBDC Program</h2>
<p>While the CBDC testing is scheduled for next year, the road to CBDC implementation is not without its challenges. The bank acknowledged that the central bank-issued currency has much more significant technical barriers that need to be overcome than traditional currencies.</p>
<p>During preliminary tests, the CBDC mock system faced processing speed issues compared to major domestic micropayment operators. According to the report, addressing these concerns will be crucial for the CBDC&#8217;s successful adoption in real-world scenarios. Speaking to the news media, an official from the IT industry in South Korea disclosed that the country would require more human resources from the IT sector to support its CDBC plan.</p>
<p>&#8220;As the Bank of Korea is planning a large-scale retail payment system project soon, it is in need of an exceptionally large number of IT personnel. A large number of related personnel, including large companies, are on the move,&#8221; said the expert.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/">Bank of Korea to Explore CBDC Testing in Selected Regions Outside Seoul </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-korea-cbdc-testing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Operational MVP License in Dubai</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/">Binance Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Operational MVP License in Dubai</a></p>
<p>With this license, Binance can now offer approved virtual asset services, further solidifying its reputation as a responsible player in the crypto market. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/">Binance Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Operational MVP License in Dubai</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/">Binance Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Operational MVP License in Dubai</a></p>
<p>Binance has become the world’s first exchange to secure an operational Minimum Viable Product (MVP) license from Dubai&#8217;s Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA). This milestone grants Binance the privilege to provide exchange and broker-dealer services to institutional and retail investors under VARA’s authorization.</p>
<p>The journey began when <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> acquired its provisional license in Dubai in March 2022, followed by a preparatory MVP in September of the same year. The preparatory MVP allowed the exchange to offer a curated selection of assets exclusively to some qualified clients.</p>
<p>With the operational MVP license, Binance can offer approved virtual asset services, further solidifying its reputation as a responsible player in the crypto market. It also shows the crypto exchange’s commitment to compliance with local regulators across its service jurisdictions.</p>
<p>This milestone translates to an expanded scope of services for users, enhanced security, and collaborative efforts with Dubai’s regulatory authorities to ensure efficient operations. Users can now safely convert virtual assets to fiat while adhering to the highest regulatory standards. These instil trust and confidence in the Dubai Binance community.</p>
<p>Dubai-based clients of Binance can now enjoy the platform, knowing they are safeguarded by VARA’s investor protection provisions and market assurance standards that ensure a safe and reliable trading environment.</p>
<p>Alexander Chehade, the general manager for Binance in Dubai, expressing his enthusiasm about the new operational license, <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-is-the-first-virtual-asset-exchange-to-receive-an-operational-mvp-license-in-dubai-7342057061995039467" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Dubai has solidified its position as a global virtual asset hub, and we are thrilled to be part of this growth story as we continue to prioritize market and investor security. With the operational MVP license, all users onboarded through our platform can expect access to a trusted and regulated service that places a premium on security and adherence to VARA’s virtual asset regulations.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance’s Regulatory Moves Could Increase Trust in Crypto</h2>
<p>For Binance, securing the operational MVP license reinforces its commitment to collaborative efforts with regulators worldwide. This achievement is poised to instill greater trust in cryptocurrencies and crypto exchanges, particularly as other companies emulate a similar commitment to due diligence processes.</p>
<p>While global adherence to various regulatory standards proves beneficial for the entire crypto ecosystem, it’s important to recognize that many countries are still in the nascent stages of implementing proper regulations for virtual currencies. With that, crypto exchanges often run into trouble, as the unclear regulatory procedures could be tricky to interpret.</p>
<p>The UAE has consistently embraced crypto and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-blockchain-technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain</a> solutions. Binance’s progress toward obtaining a Full Market Product License can help other crypto exchanges get properly licensed in the country faster, facilitating the establishment of proper licensing and regulation for the crypto industry.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/">Binance Becomes First Crypto Exchange to Get Operational MVP License in Dubai</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-crypto-mvp-license-in-dubai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upbit Suspends CRV Trading after Curve Finance Exploit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybersecurity News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[curve finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[upbit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264742</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/">Upbit Suspends CRV Trading after Curve Finance Exploit</a></p>
<p>Upbit noted that CRV has experienced increased volatility.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/">Upbit Suspends CRV Trading after Curve Finance Exploit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/">Upbit Suspends CRV Trading after Curve Finance Exploit</a></p>

<p>South Korean exchange Upbit has halted trading of the Curve Finance (CRV) token after the project suffered a major exploit over the weekend. According to an <a href="https://sg.upbit.com/service_center/notice?id=2745" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Upbit announcement</a>, the exchange temporarily halted CRV deposits and withdrawals to safeguard all transactions and protect users from potential losses.</p>
<h2>How the Curve Finance Exploit Happened</h2>
<p>Curve Finance, the second-largest DeFi exchange on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> after Uniswap, was hit by a reentrancy bug that exploited a vulnerability in its Vyper programming language. The attack exposed several stablecoin pools on the platform, putting more than $100 million worth of crypto assets at <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/curve-finance-exploit-100m-risk/">risk</a>. The affected pools include alETH, msETH, and pETH, which are used for pricing and liquidity on various DeFi services.</p>
<p>Upbit said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“Today, certain vulnerabilities have been discovered in some of the stablecoin pools associated with Curve (CRV). We advise exercising caution when considering any investments related to CRV.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Curve team said they are assessing the situation and will update the community as things develop. At the time, all affected pools had been white-hacked. They also assured that other pools are safe and not affected by the exploit.</p>
<p>While Upbit has suspended withdrawals and deposits, other exchanges like Binance, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/huobi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Huobi</a>, and OKEx have yet to suspend trading. However, Huobi said that it&#8217;s “monitoring the situation closely.”</p>
<h2>CRV Price Falls after Curve Finance Exploit</h2>
<p>Following the attack, Upbit noted that CRV has experienced increased volatility. The token price dropped by 12.36 % on July 30 and was $0.61 at the time of writing. The price crash also threatened to trigger a liquidation on the founder of Curve&#8217;s $70 million borrowing position on Aave, another DeFi lending platform.</p>
<p>The Curve Finance exploit also threatened to cause wider volatility in the broader cryptocurrency market. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and Ether faced slight fluctuations but soon stabilized at $29,450 and $1,870 respectively.</p>
<h2>DeFi Attacks</h2>
<p>The Curve exploit is the latest in a series of attacks that have plagued the DeFi sector. In April, Hundred Finance lost about $7 million on the Ethereum layer-2 blockchain Optimism. Merlin DEX also lost about $1.8 million from the protocol in April. Also in March, hackers stole $197 million from DeFi protocol Euler Finance.</p>
<p>These incidents highlight the risks and challenges that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> users and developers face as they seek to innovate and disrupt the traditional financial system.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/">Upbit Suspends CRV Trading after Curve Finance Exploit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/upbit-crv-trading-curve-exploit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Celebrates 8th Anniversary with Impressive Feat</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[consensys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/">Ethereum Celebrates 8th Anniversary with Impressive Feat</a></p>
<p>Ethereum has achieved a significant feat of $400 billion in secured value, generating annualized profits of $3.6 billion and a total of 17.8 million blocks of digital assets.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/">Ethereum Celebrates 8th Anniversary with Impressive Feat</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/">Ethereum Celebrates 8th Anniversary with Impressive Feat</a></p>
<p>In the fast-paced world of blockchain and cryptocurrencies, few projects have made a lasting impact, like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>. On July 30, 2023, the crypto community celebrated the eighth anniversary of Ethereum, marking eight years of continuous innovation, technological advancements, and a market capitalization of around $227 billion.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s journey began in November 2013, when <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/vitalik-buterin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Vitalik Buterin</a> published the Ethereum whitepaper, introducing the concept of a decentralized platform capable of executing smart contracts. In January 2014, the blockchain project was formally announced at The North American Bitcoin Conference in Miami, marking the start of a new era.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Generates Annual Profit of $3.6 Billion</h2>
<p>The protocol created its genesis block on July 30, 2015. The news was shared in a <a href="https://blog.ethereum.org/2015/07/30/ethereum-launches" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> by Stephan Tual, the then CCO of the Ethereum Foundation, the nonprofit organization responsible for overseeing the network.</p>
<p>Eight years after the genesis block, the protocol, along with its native crypto Ether (ETH), has become the second largest network in the world, after Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<p>According to Bankless co-host Ryan Sean Adams, Ethereum has achieved a significant feat of $400 billion in secured value, generating annualized profits of $3.6 billion and a total of 17.8 million blocks of digital assets.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Happy birthday Ethereum! 🎂</p>
<p>$400 billion in secured value, $3.6 billion in annualized profits, and a total of 17.8 million blocks of uncensorable digital property.</p>
<p>Not bad for an 8 year old.</p>
<p>&mdash; RYAN SΞAN ADAMS &#8211; rsa.eth (@RyanSAdams) <a href="https://twitter.com/RyanSAdams/status/1685672504616968192?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Empowering Developers and Fostering Innovation</h2>
<p>As a decentralized network with smart contract capabilities, the launch of Ethereum brought many opportunities for developers and entrepreneurs. The protocol paved the way for the explosive growth of the decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) ecosystem, allowing developers to build and deploy applications on top of its chain.</p>
<p>Some of the projects built on Ethereum enabled lending, borrowing, and yield farming, revolutionizing traditional finance and creating new opportunities for users around the world.</p>
<p>Projects within the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/consensys/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ConsenSys</a> ecosystem, like MetaMask and Infura, provided crucial tools to bootstrap the network and make it accessible to the masses.</p>
<p>MetaMask revolutionized how users interacted with the Ethereum network. The non-custodial wallet also serves as a browser extension, simplifying the process of sending ether and interacting with other decentralized applications (dApps).</p>
<p>Infura, launched in November 2016, played a vital role in driving adoption by providing a reliable and scalable Ethereum API. Developers could focus on building innovative applications without the complexities of managing their own infrastructure.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Migration to a PoS Chain</h2>
<p>When non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-non-fungible-tokens-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) emerged as another sector in the crypto ecosystem, Ethereum allowed artists and creators to tokenize their digital assets, opening up new avenues for ownership, provenance, and monetization in the digital art and collectibles space.</p>
<p>The protocol is the home to the largest NFT marketplace, OpenSea, launched in 2017 by Devin Finzer and Alex Atallah.</p>
<p>As Ethereum continued to flourish, it also faced challenges related to scalability and environmental impact. In response, Ethereum embarked on a journey towards Ethereum 2.0, a major upgrade that transitions the network from Proof of Work (PoW) to Proof of Stake (PoS).</p>
<p>Last year, the protocol successfully migrated to the PoS chain through a process known as the Merge in September. This transition has made the protocol more scalable, energy-efficient, and poised to support even greater adoption.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s native currency is also widely accepted by different companies across various industries as a payment option. Some of these brands include Gucci, Balenciaga, Chipotle, and Newegg.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/">Ethereum Celebrates 8th Anniversary with Impressive Feat</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-8th-anniversary/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panasonic Records Impressive Fiscal Q12024 Profit Surge</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[panasonic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265087</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/">Panasonic Records Impressive Fiscal Q12024 Profit Surge</a></p>
<p>Amid the euphoria of a robust first quarter, Panasonic has decided to maintain its full-year profit predictions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/">Panasonic Records Impressive Fiscal Q12024 Profit Surge</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/">Panasonic Records Impressive Fiscal Q12024 Profit Surge</a></p>
<p>Japanese electronics giant, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/panasonic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Panasonic Holdings Corp</a> (TYO: 6752) renowned for its diverse product portfolio has recently reported a stellar Q1 profit performance.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.marketscreener.com/quote/stock/PANASONIC-HOLDINGS-CORPOR-6492473/news/Panasonic-Q1-profit-jumps-maintains-FY-forecast-44465151/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, the company’s operating profit came in at an impressive 90.37 billion yen ($637 million), showcasing a remarkable 42% rise in the three months ending June. This result was just slightly lower than the 91.18 billion yen average predicted by analysts according to a Refinitiv survey.</p>
<p>The modest difference between actual and forecasted outcomes illustrates the challenges and uncertainty that businesses encounter in an ever-changing economic landscape.</p>
<h2>The Force Behind the Panasonic Q1 Profit Increase</h2>
<p>One of the crucial factors that contributed to Panasonic’s impressive financial performance in Q1 was the depreciation of the Japanese Yen.</p>
<p>As an international conglomerate with widespread operations, Panasonic exports its products worldwide. A weaker Yen makes its goods more attractive and affordable for foreign buyers, consequently boosting export revenues and driving up profitability.</p>
<p>The company’s automotive and energy divisions have also played a pivotal role in this success. Panasonic&#8217;s involvement in the development and supply of batteries for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has been a significant driver of its revenue growth in recent years, especially as the demand for Electric Vehicles (EVs) continues to surge worldwide.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Panasonic&#8217;s battery unit, Panasonic Energy, recently announced the initiation of talks with Subaru to establish a battery supply partnership. The collaboration aims to provide cylindrical lithium-ion batteries to Subaru for their electric vehicles.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, its renewable energy products, including solar panels and energy storage systems, have witnessed rising demand as countries strive to embrace clean energy alternatives.</p>
<h2>Panasonic Is Maintaining Profit Projections</h2>
<p>Amid the euphoria of a robust first quarter, Panasonic has decided to maintain its full-year profit predictions, a move that underscores the company&#8217;s confidence in its future performance.</p>
<p>The company said its full-year profit expectation remains at an astonishing 430 billion yen. The company’s commitment to this ambitious target has garnered attention, as it exceeds the average profit forecast of 413.96 billion yen predicted by a poll of 20 analysts by Refinitiv.</p>
<p>The company’s diverse product portfolio, ranging from consumer electronics to delivery robots, sensing cameras, and self-checkout systems, has played a crucial role in sustaining its business resilience. Panasonic&#8217;s ability to adapt to shifting market demands and capitalize on various industries’ growth opportunities contributes to its confidence in achieving its ambitious financial targets.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Panasonic&#8217;s battery division has set lofty targets for the EV battery market, with plans to construct four new plants to reach a significant increase in annual capacity by 2031.</p>
<p>With its determined approach, Panasonic is poised to achieve its financial targets and solidify its status as a global leader in the electronics and electric vehicle battery sectors. Investors and stakeholders can look forward to witnessing the company’s strategic vision unfold as it continues to pave the way toward a more sustainable and technology-driven future.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/">Panasonic Records Impressive Fiscal Q12024 Profit Surge</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/panasonic-q1-profit-surge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eurozone Q2 GDP Beats Expectations, Inflation Down but Economists Still Fear Recession</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=265080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/">Eurozone Q2 GDP Beats Expectations, Inflation Down but Economists Still Fear Recession</a></p>
<p>While inflation in Eurozone shows signs of slowing down, it still remains much higher than the targeted 2%. Economists also pointed out other cracks in the Eurozone economy. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/">Eurozone Q2 GDP Beats Expectations, Inflation Down but Economists Still Fear Recession</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/">Eurozone Q2 GDP Beats Expectations, Inflation Down but Economists Still Fear Recession</a></p>
<p>For the month of July 2023, the Eurozone has delivered a robust set of GDP numbers beyond market expectations. The new growth numbers show economic activity picking up during the second quarter with inflation slowing down. However, economists still fear that a recession could be on the cards.</p>
<p>In July, headline inflation in the euro area was 5.3%, lower than the 5.5% in June. However, it is still much higher than the European Central Bank&#8217;s target of 2%. Core inflation, which excludes food and energy prices, stayed the same at 5.5% in July. This outcome might be a &#8220;disappointment for policymakers,&#8221; according to Andrew Kenningham, chief Europe economist at Capital Economics.</p>
<p>For the past year, Eurozone has been facing high inflation, leading the ECB to implement consecutive rate hikes in an attempt to control prices. Last week, the central bank raised rates by another quarter percentage point, bringing the main interest rate to 3.75%.</p>
<p>Initially, the inflation was mainly driven by high energy costs, but in recent months, food prices have become the primary contributor. In July, food, alcohol, and tobacco prices increased by 10.8%, although this hike was lower than in previous months.</p>
<h2>Eurozone GDP Beats Expectations</h2>
<p>The inflation numbers came amid previously sluggish economic growth, with GDP remaining stagnant in the first quarter of the year. However, a separate data release on Monday revealed that growth picked up in the second quarter, expanding by 0.3%, surpassing the 0.2% forecasted by Reuters&#8217; analysts.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, Capital Economics&#8217; Kenningham believes that the second-quarter GDP increase in France and Ireland was due to one-off factors, which may present a misleading impression of the economy&#8217;s actual strength. In a research note, Kenningham <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/31/euro-zone-inflation-july-and-second-quarter-gdp-economic-growth-data.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>″[It] does not change our view that the economy is heading for recession. Excluding [France and Ireland] GDP growth would have been only 0.04% q/q, or zero to one decimal place! As these factors are unlikely to be repeated in the coming quarters and the impact of monetary policy tightening is still intensifying, we think euro-zone GDP will contract in the second half of the year.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In the second quarter, both France&#8217;s and Ireland&#8217;s economies showed resilience, with France&#8217;s GDP rate being 0.5% and Ireland&#8217;s expanding by 3.3%. However, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ing-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ING</a>&#8216;s Senior Euro Zone Economist Bert Colijn pointed out that Ireland&#8217;s growth was exceptional and without it, the overall growth would have been much lower. According to survey data, the economy has remained relatively stagnant, and there are concerns that the coming quarters may face downside risks.</p>
<p>Spain also performed well, experiencing growth of 0.4%. In contrast, Germany had weaker growth during the same three-month period.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-cloud-web-3-0-nes/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/">Eurozone Q2 GDP Beats Expectations, Inflation Down but Economists Still Fear Recession</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eurozone-q2-gdp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4069 metric#misses=50 metric#hit-ratio=98.8 metric#bytes=1040408 metric#prefetches=190 metric#store-reads=27 metric#store-writes=6 metric#store-hits=197 metric#store-misses=11 metric#sql-queries=37 metric#ms-total=125.48 metric#ms-cache=6.33 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1978 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.0 sample#redis-hits=118247762 sample#redis-misses=6521821 sample#redis-hit-ratio=94.8 sample#redis-ops-per-sec=88 sample#redis-evicted-keys=1583350 sample#redis-used-memory=413135816 sample#redis-used-memory-rss=434274304 sample#redis-memory-fragmentation-ratio=1.1 sample#redis-connected-clients=2 sample#redis-tracking-clients=0 sample#redis-rejected-connections=0 sample#redis-keys=990964 -->