<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 20:54:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Meets SEC Amid Moving Offshore Reports; What’s Happening?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/coinbase-ceo-meets-sec-amid-moving-offshore-reports/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 20:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase (COIN)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145955</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase News: Coinbase, US biggest crypto exchange is reportedly seeking to move offshore as the Securities and Exchange Commission fails to provide clear rules for the crypto industry. However, it looks like Coinbase is not cutting the chase here as it is gearing up for a long legal battle ahead. Also Read: Coinbase Set To <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-ceo-meets-sec-amid-moving-offshore-reports/" title="Coinbase CEO Meets SEC Amid Moving Offshore Reports; What’s Happening?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-ceo-meets-sec-amid-moving-offshore-reports/">Coinbase CEO Meets SEC Amid Moving Offshore Reports; What’s Happening?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/04184833/coinbase.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="CEO Brian Armstrong To Sell His 2% Stake In Coinbase crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Coinbase News: Coinbase, US biggest crypto exchange is reportedly seeking to move offshore as the Securities and Exchange Commission fails to provide clear rules for the crypto industry. However, it looks like Coinbase is not cutting the chase here as it is gearing up for a long legal battle ahead.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-set-to-launch-base-mainnet-within-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Set To Launch Base Mainnet Within 2023</a></strong></p>
<h2>Coinbase Plans To Go Against SEC</h2>
<p>Brian Armstrong, Coinbase CEO in a tweet highlighted a special meeting with the US SEC. He stated that the crypto exchange we’ll continue to push for a clear rule book in the U.S. for crypto firms. This development comes in when the financial regulator severed the crypto exchange with a “Wells notice” regarding listing of several digital assets, staking and wallet services.</p>
<p>Armstrong added that the U.S. can’t afford to lose this chance to update the financial system. However, it is important for regulators to set policy right and then move to enforce it. He added that this is the apt point where congress needs to step in.</p>
<p>The meeting between Coinbase boss and the commission comes after his recent summit with some members of congress. Coingape reported Armstrong stated that the SEC has caused untold harm to the nation with its policies. He intended that the crypto industry needs to fight back.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-sec-settlement-hydro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">U.S. SEC Cracks Down On Crypto Firm, Secures Historic $2.8 Mn Settlement</a></strong></p>
<p>However, Armstrong left a message that he is flying back to the west coast to focus on improving products.</p>
<blockquote><p>The best thing we can do for policy is drive utility and make crypto more useful, growing from a couple hundred million crypto users to a billion (as an industry). It’s time to build!, Coinbase CEO wrote</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-ceo-meets-sec-amid-moving-offshore-reports/">Coinbase CEO Meets SEC Amid Moving Offshore Reports; What’s Happening?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/04184833/coinbase.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Layer 1, Layer 2 And Layer 3 In Blockchain? Key Differences With Examples</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/education/whats-layer-1-layer-2-and-layer-3-in-blockchain-key-differences-with-examples/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 18:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer 1 Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of work]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=138118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When we talk about blockchain protocols there are 3 different types that come to our mind: Layer 1, Layer 2, and Layer 3. What is Layer 1 in Blockchain? The foundation blockchain is often referred to as the layer-1 network. It serves as the primary network of the ecosystem, blockchain is referred to as layer <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/education/whats-layer-1-layer-2-and-layer-3-in-blockchain-key-differences-with-examples/" title="What&#8217;s Layer 1, Layer 2 And Layer 3 In Blockchain? Key Differences With Examples"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/education/whats-layer-1-layer-2-and-layer-3-in-blockchain-key-differences-with-examples/">What&#8217;s Layer 1, Layer 2 And Layer 3 In Blockchain? Key Differences With Examples</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/09175428/Layer-1-vs-Layer-2-vs-Layer-3-Blockchain.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Layer 1" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>When we talk about blockchain protocols there are 3 different types that come to our mind: Layer 1, Layer 2, and Layer 3.</p>
<h2>What is Layer 1 in Blockchain?</h2>
<p>The foundation blockchain is often referred to as the layer-1 network. It serves as the primary network of the ecosystem, blockchain is referred to as layer 1. The term &#8220;on-chain networking&#8221; is also frequently used to describe these Layer-1 scaling methods.</p>
<p>The blockchain network&#8217;s foundational technology is referred to as Layer 1. The basis for the other levels is provided by this layer. It contains the data structures, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptography/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cryptographic</a> techniques, and consensus processes required for the blockchain network to function.</p>
<p>How transactions are verified and new blocks are added to the blockchain are both governed by the consensus process. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/proof-of-work-pow/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proof of Work (PoW)</a> and <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/proof-of-stake-pos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proof of Stake (PoS)</a> are the two consensus procedures that are most frequently utilized. PoW is used by the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> network and requires participants to perform computationally intensive tasks in order to validate transactions and create new blocks. PoS is used by <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and other networks and requires participants to hold a certain amount of the network&#8217;s native token in order to participate in validation.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/education/explained-scalping-in-crypto-and-how-does-scalp-trading-works/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Explained: Scalping in Crypto and How does Scalp Trading Works?</a></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>How a Layer 1 Blockchain works?</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>The cryptographic algorithms used in Layer 1 provide security for transactions and ensure the immutability of the blockchain. For example, the Bitcoin network uses the SHA-256 hash function to secure transactions, while Ethereum uses the Ethash algorithm.</p>
<p>The data structures used in Layer 1 are responsible for storing blocks of transactions. Additionally, maintains the integrity of the blockchain. In a blockchain, transactions are grouped into blocks and linked in a chain. Each block contains a hash of the previous block. This ensures that the blockchain is a secure and tamper-proof ledger of all transactions.</p>
<p>The blockchain is a secure and impenetrable ledger of all transactions since each block contains a hash of the previous block.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/education/explained-what-is-layer-0-in-blockchain-layer-zero-crypto-examples/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Explained: What is Layer 0 in Blockchain? Layer Zero Crypto Examples</a></p>
<h2>What is Layer 2 in Blockchain?</h2>
<p>A network or system that runs on top of the underlying blockchain protocol to improve its scalability and efficiency is referred to as layer-2. This method calls for transferring a portion of the blockchain protocol&#8217;s transactional burden at layer-2 scaling in order to modify the system architecture. Once the network processing burden has been managed, it simply reports the results back to the primary blockchain for finalization.</p>
<p>The primary blockchain that serves as the base layer becomes less crowded and ultimately more scalable by abstracting the majority of the data processing into different designs.</p>
<p>Examples of layer-2 used on the Ethereum blockchain network are <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/polygon-matic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> and Immutable X.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>How a Layer 2 Blockchain functions?</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>In layer-2, three techniques have been applied: rollup, sidechain, and state channel.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/education/what-are-blockchain-bridges-heres-everything-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What are Blockchain Bridges? Here’s Everything You Need To Know</a></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h4>One roll-up</h4>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Layer-2 off-chain transactions are combined and sent as a single transaction on the main chain using zero-knowledge rollups, which are the most popular variant. To verify the accuracy of commerce, the system uses Proof of Validity. On the main chain, which is connected by smart contracts, assets will be kept. The roll-up process will then be verified by the smart contract. The original network can have security using this technique.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h4>Sidechain</h4>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Blockchain sidechains are separate networks with their own validators. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/smart-contract/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Smart contracts</a> serve as a link between the sidechain and the main chain as well as a means of validating the sidechain network. The sidechain can manage the assets on the main chain, thus you must ensure that it is functioning correctly.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h4>State Channel 3</h4>
</li>
</ul>
<p>A State channel is a two-way channel of communication for the parties to a transaction. The parties connect it to an off-chain transaction channel and encrypt a portion of the underlying blockchain. Typically, a pre-negotiated or multi-signature smart contract is used to do this. Without immediately sending the transaction data to the underlying distributed ledger or main chain, the parties subsequently carry out the transaction or collection of off-chain transactions.</p>
<p>The final status of the channel is broadcast to the blockchain for validation when each transaction in the set has been completed. This method exists to speed up transactions and expand the network&#8217;s total capacity.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/education/explained-what-is-a-merkle-tree-in-blockchain-and-how-does-it-work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Explained: What is a Merkle Tree In Blockchain And How Does It Work?</a></p>
<h2>What is Layer 3 in Blockchain?</h2>
<p>Applications that are constructed on top of the blockchain network are referred to as layer 3. These applications use the immutability and security of the underlying blockchain architecture to offer fresh and creative answers to a variety of issues.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/decentralized-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decentralized exchange (DEX)</a>, which enables users to trade <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">cryptocurrencies</a> in a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/decentralized-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">decentralized</a> and trustless way, is an illustration of a layer 3 application. Trades on a DEX are made on the blockchain. The assets being traded are not under the exchange&#8217;s direct control. This does away with the requirement for a reliable third party.</p>
<h2>Key differences between Layer 1, Layer 2, and Layer 3</h2>
<p>On the Ethereum Layer 1 blockchain, the price of mining and transferring varies every day. However, it typically ranges between $50 and $125. On the Polygon Layer 2 lightning network, the cost of minting and transmitting coins is approximately $0.05. This is 2,000 times less expensive than on the Layer 1 blockchain.</p>
<p>It shows that Layer 2 blockchains, which have more effective topologies than Layer 1 blockchains, are much less expensive.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/education/erc-721-vs-erc-1155-which-is-better-for-nft-marketplace/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ERC 721 vs ERC 1155: Which Is Better For NFT Marketplace?</a></p>
<p>As more first-generation and next-generation blockchains adopt PoS and other more efficient models, this is projected to improve. Layer 1 and Layer 2 blockchains are commonly inefficient because of out-of-date Layer 1 consensus processes. The environmental impact of more efficient algorithms and designs is reduced, while transaction efficiency is increased.</p>
<p>Finally, it&#8217;s important to note that not all of these various scaling solutions options are equal and that there is no standardized definition of a layer-2 crypto network when it comes to Layer 2 protocols. For instance, while Lightning Network transactions do not offer the same level of security and censorship resistance as on-chain transactions, they do offer much greater guarantees than conventional, centralized transaction servers.</p>
<p>Others propose higher requirements for a platform to function as a simple layer-2 cryptosystem, however, some people consider pending transactions on controlled exchanges to be Layer 2 networks since they allow users to trade custody of coins off-chain.</p>
<p><strong>Also read: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/education/what-is-ethereum-staking-how-does-it-work-pros-and-cons-of-ethereum-staking/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">What Is Ethereum Staking, How Does It Work? Pros and Cons of Ethereum Staking</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/education/whats-layer-1-layer-2-and-layer-3-in-blockchain-key-differences-with-examples/">What&#8217;s Layer 1, Layer 2 And Layer 3 In Blockchain? Key Differences With Examples</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/09175428/Layer-1-vs-Layer-2-vs-Layer-3-Blockchain.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just-In: U.S. SEC Cracks Down On Crypto Firm, Secures Historic $2.8 Mn Settlement</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-sec-settlement-hydro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: A lawsuit by the U.S. SEC that dates back to September of 2022 against a crypto firm, has finally ended in a settlement worth $2.8 million. The lawsuit in question charged Hydro Technology Corp. and its former CEO Michael Ross Kane for their roles in effectuating the unregistered offers and sales of crypto <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-sec-settlement-hydro/" title="Just-In: U.S. SEC Cracks Down On Crypto Firm, Secures Historic $2.8 Mn Settlement"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-sec-settlement-hydro/">Just-In: U.S. SEC Cracks Down On Crypto Firm, Secures Historic $2.8 Mn Settlement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/22014930/sec-gensler.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News:</strong> A lawsuit by the U.S. SEC that dates back to September of 2022 against a crypto firm, has finally ended in a settlement worth $2.8 million. The lawsuit in question charged Hydro Technology Corp. and its former CEO Michael Ross Kane for their roles in effectuating the unregistered offers and sales of crypto securities called “Hydro”. Additionally, they were alleged to perpetrate a scheme to manipulate the trading volume and price of those securities, which generated more than $2 million for Hydrogen.</p>
<h2>SEC Settles Big With Hydrogen</h2>
<p>On Thursday, a New York federal judge approved a settlement agreement between the SEC and Miami-based Hydrogen Technology Corp. Co-founder and former CEO Michael Kane also consented to end the legal dispute. In September, the regulatory body filed a lawsuit against two individuals, alleging that they had paid a third party to manipulate trade of the company&#8217;s Hydro token in order to artificially boost its price. The day after the complaint was brought forward, the third party in question, Tyler Ostern, reached an agreement to settle the case for $41,000.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/" rel="bookmark">Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy</a></strong></em></p>
<p>As part of the settlement, Hydrogen has consented to pay a total of nearly $2.8 million, comprised of nearly $1.5 million in disgorged profits &#8212; which refers to the profits yielded from illegal or wrongful conduct &#8212; a penalty of more than $1 million, and prejudgment interest. Michael Kane, on the other hand, has agreed to pay a fine of approximately $260,000.</p>
<h2>Strict Terms Set For Hydrogen</h2>
<p>Both the corporation and Kane are bound by the conditions of the settlement, which stipulates that they cannot confirm nor refute the claims that have been leveled against them. Additionally, they will not be allowed to sell any additional <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency/">cryptocurrencies</a> unless they have passed a Howey test and received SEC approval. However, Kane will still be able to engage in the broader <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/?utm_source=menubar">crypto market</a>, where he could continue trading cryptocurrencies for himself.</p>
<p>According to the complaint filed by the SEC, Michael Kane, who also controlled Hedgeable Inc &#8212; an SEC registered investment adviser &#8212; needed to obtain fresh capital, which led to the formation of Hydrogen in the peak <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bull-market/">bull market</a> of December 2017. On January 2018, Hydrogen minted more than 11 billion Hydro tokens which were distributed through giveaways to its employees, retail investors and to those who promoted the project as a reward.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="Top VC’s Deny Investing In 3AC Founders’ OPNX Exchange, Who’s Saying The Truth?" href="https://coingape.com/vc-deny-investing-in-3ac-founders-opnx-exchange/" rel="bookmark">Top VC’s Deny Investing In 3AC Founders’ OPNX Exchange, Who’s Saying The Truth?</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-sec-settlement-hydro/">Just-In: U.S. SEC Cracks Down On Crypto Firm, Secures Historic $2.8 Mn Settlement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/22014930/sec-gensler.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 3 Low Cap Cryptocurrencies to Maximize your Investment Returns in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/top-3-low-cap-cryptocurrencies-to-maximize-your-investment-returns-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arweave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ImmutableX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MultiversX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=145947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Low Cap Assets are always one of the crucial parts of a balanced portfolio. These gems can be bought at a discounted price and offer massive returns during bull runs. Thus, today we’ll analyze three Low Cap cryptocurrencies with a strong bullish setup that hold massive growth potential in the near future.  MultiversX(EGLD) Source- Tradingview  <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-3-low-cap-cryptocurrencies-to-maximize-your-investment-returns-in-2023/" title="Top 3 Low Cap Cryptocurrencies to Maximize your Investment Returns in 2023"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-3-low-cap-cryptocurrencies-to-maximize-your-investment-returns-in-2023/">Top 3 Low Cap Cryptocurrencies to Maximize your Investment Returns in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1600" height="1120" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/09224431/altcoins3.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Cryptocurrency Price Prediction Today" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Low Cap Assets are always one of the crucial parts of a balanced portfolio. These gems can be bought at a discounted price and offer massive returns during bull runs. Thus, today we’ll analyze three Low Cap cryptocurrencies with a strong bullish setup that hold massive growth potential in the near future. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">MultiversX(EGLD)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/a/AzIwyJ6Y.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the daily time frame chart, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/multiversx/">MultiversX coin</a> price shows the formation of an inverted head and shoulder pattern. This pattern consists of a large swing low- the head, and two shorter swing lows- the shoulders and key resistance called the neckline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of now, the coin price currently trades at $39.9 and trying to sustain above local support of $39.5. If the coin price manages to sustain above the aforementioned support, the buyers may drive a 15% rally to challenge the pattern’s resistance trendline. Thus, a potential breakout from the trendline will signal an early sign of a trend change.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Ideal conditions, the neckline breakout may push the EDLG price to the $69.3 mark</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Immutable(IMX)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/s/sUSOO56Q.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Similar to EGLD, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/immutablex/">Immutable price</a> has been forming an inverted head and shoulder pattern for the past 11 months. This pattern is one of the most commonly observed reversal patterns at market bottoms, offering long entry opportunities upon the breakout of neckline resistance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IMX price is currently forming the right shoulder pattern of the pattern, which may find support at $0.94 or $0.8. By the press time, this altcoin traded at $0.957 with an intraday loss of 1.54%. If the coin price manages to sustain above the aforementioned support, the buyers would replenish the bullish momentum and rise back to the overhead trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under favorable conditions, a breakout above the trendline will drive the price to $2.846.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/new-cryptocurrencies-to-buy/">15 New Cryptocurrencies To Buy In 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Arweave(AR)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/e/EwuD8Di6.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- Tradingview </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past nine months, the Arweave(AR) has been in a steady downtrend under the influence of two converging trendlines. In the weekly time frame chart, these trend lines reveal the formation of a <a href="https://coingape.com/education/falling-wedge-pattern-what-to-do-if-it-appears-on-a-crypto-chart/">falling wedge pattern</a>, which offers a massive upswing upon the breakout of the overhead trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of now, the AR price traders at $7.85 and is chasing the lower support trendline of this pattern. Anyhow, interested buyers can look for any entry opportunity when the price rebounds from the support trendline or breach the overhead resistance trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A successful breakout from this pattern could lead the AR price to the $17.68 mark.</span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-3-low-cap-cryptocurrencies-to-maximize-your-investment-returns-in-2023/">Top 3 Low Cap Cryptocurrencies to Maximize your Investment Returns in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/09224431/altcoins3.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top VCs Deny Investing In 3AC Founders&#8217; OPNX Exchange, Who&#8217;s Saying The Truth?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/vc-deny-investing-in-3ac-founders-opnx-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3AC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[three arrows capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The recently launched OPNX cryptocurrency exchange, which was founded by Su Zhu and Kyle Davies after the failure of their hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), publicly announced the names of their financial backers in an official tweet today. However, a number of them later refuted the claims and dissociated themselves from any form of <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/vc-deny-investing-in-3ac-founders-opnx-exchange/" title="Top VCs Deny Investing In 3AC Founders&#8217; OPNX Exchange, Who&#8217;s Saying The Truth?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/vc-deny-investing-in-3ac-founders-opnx-exchange/">Top VCs Deny Investing In 3AC Founders&#8217; OPNX Exchange, Who&#8217;s Saying The Truth?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="600" height="315" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21233754/timthumb.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="opnx" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The recently launched OPNX cryptocurrency exchange, which was founded by Su Zhu and Kyle Davies after the failure of their hedge fund <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/three-arrows-capital/">Three Arrows Capital (3AC)</a>, publicly announced the names of their financial backers in an official tweet today. However, a number of them later refuted the claims and dissociated themselves from any form of involvement with the exchange.</p>
<h2>VCs Deny Any Investments</h2>
<p>DRW and Nascent, two of the many investors identified, have both denied claims that they were investors in OPNX, which was initiated by the owners of 3AC. Following the exchange&#8217;s announcement, DRW explicitly stated that there was no participation from the parent company or any of its subsidiaries.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Just-In: Telegram Users Can Now Buy, Withdraw &amp; Exchange Bitcoin" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-telegram-adds-support-buy-bitcoin/" rel="bookmark">Telegram Users Can Now Buy, Withdraw &amp; Exchange Bitcoin</a></strong></em></p>
<p>Nascent, on the other hand, provided a response to a question on OPNX&#8217;s ongoing Twitter thread  &#8212; claiming to have invested in FLEX tokens two years back rather than in OPNX.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Just to clarify, Nascent did not participate in an OPNX fundraising round, we invested in FLEX tokens in early 2021.</p>
<p>&mdash; Nascent (@nascentxyz) <a href="https://twitter.com/nascentxyz/status/1649464652102004737?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Who&#8217;s Saying The Truth?</h2>
<p>OPNX was formerly known as CoinFlex, a trading platform which is currently undergoing reorganization in Seychelles. In early 2023, Su Zhu and Kyle Davies collaborated with CoinFlex to establish their new <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/">crypto exchange</a> that trades bankruptcy claims instead of <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency/">cryptocurrencies</a>. Now, since DRW and Nascent had previously been investors in CoinFlex, the 3AC duo claimed to have them as investors for their venture as well &#8212; which if technically examined isn&#8217;t the case.</p>
<p>OPNX earlier mentioned that some of its backers included investors like the high-frequency trading firm Susquehanna and the Taiwanese venture capital firm AppWorks. Apart from them, the firm mentioned a number of other investors in the thread including MIAX Group, Token Bay Capital and Tuwaiq, which is a digital asset fund based in Saudi Arabia.</p>
<p>In the wake of this news, CoinFlex&#8217;s FLEX token which serves as the native token of the OPNX platform, dropped by 17.09% in the past one hour and is currently trading at around $1.04 at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/" rel="bookmark">Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/vc-deny-investing-in-3ac-founders-opnx-exchange/">Top VCs Deny Investing In 3AC Founders&#8217; OPNX Exchange, Who&#8217;s Saying The Truth?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21233754/timthumb.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just-In: Telegram Users Can Now Buy, Withdraw &#038; Exchange Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-telegram-adds-support-buy-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 17:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telegram]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: Telegram is widely recognized as an advocate of digital assets and has lately been working to extend its presence in the sector of cryptocurrencies. Users of Telegram who make use of the wallet bot were informed today of a new feature that made it possible for anyone to purchase, withdraw, exchange and make <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-telegram-adds-support-buy-bitcoin/" title="Just-In: Telegram Users Can Now Buy, Withdraw &#038; Exchange Bitcoin"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-telegram-adds-support-buy-bitcoin/">Just-In: Telegram Users Can Now Buy, Withdraw &#038; Exchange Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1140" height="600" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21215026/telegram-bitcoin-1140x600-1.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News: </strong>Telegram is widely recognized as an advocate of digital assets and has lately been working to extend its presence in the sector of <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency/">cryptocurrencies</a>. Users of Telegram who make use of the wallet bot were informed today of a new feature that made it possible for anyone to purchase, withdraw, exchange and make P2P transactions utilizing <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>.</p>
<h2>Telegram Adds Support For Bitcoin</h2>
<p>According to the recent <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://t.me/wallet" rel="nofollow">notification</a>, users could now perform multiple operations with Bitcoin through Telegram&#8217;s web interface, while an app-based update is currently under development. This action expands upon the already popular services surrounding cryptocurrency that are now available within the chat program.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/" rel="bookmark">Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The notification also served to inform users that the platform&#8217;s &#8220;Exchange&#8221; had been modified and as a result, they are now able to instantaneously trade Bitcoin, Tether (USDT), and <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ton/">Telegram Open Network (TON)</a> with one another.</p>
<p>The official statement was quoted to be:</p>
<blockquote><p>It is now possible to buy Bitcoin using a bank card or the P2P market in the “Buy &amp; Sell” section of our user-friendly interface.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Telegram Drives Crypto Adoption</h2>
<p>In general, Telegram&#8217;s most recent decision to launch peer-to-peer trading for Bitcoin and to broaden the scope of cryptocurrencies is a big step forward in the company&#8217;s efforts to become a key participant in the fast-developing world of <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/defi-decentralized-finance/">decentralized finance (DeFi)</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Bitcoin in @wallet web interface</p>
<p>Starting today, all @wallet users have the opportunity to buy, withdraw and exchange Bitcoin directly through a convenient web interface.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TON?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TON</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/toncoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#toncoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/telegram?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#telegram</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/web3?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#web3</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/ton_blockchain?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ton_blockchain</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/uae?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#uae</a> <a href="https://t.co/XzEwZddvv1">pic.twitter.com/XzEwZddvv1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f48e.png" alt="💎" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> TON Daily News <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@TonDailyNews) <a href="https://twitter.com/TonDailyNews/status/1649355244441149442?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>It will be interesting to observe how <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/why-telegram-is-popular-in-crypto/">Telegram</a> and other chat-based applications like WeChat, WhatsApp and Messenger evolve and adapt to suit the changing requirements &amp; expectations of users all over the world &#8212; as the popularity of cryptocurrencies continue to grow.</p>
<p>As a direct consequence of this crypto news, the price of Telegram&#8217;s TON token gained by 0.45% in the past 1 hour in contrast to an increase of 2.27% recorded over the past 24 hours. It is currently exchanging hands at $2.40 at the time of writing.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-gary-gensler-sec-jay-clayton/" target="_blank" rel="bookmark noopener">Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-telegram-adds-support-buy-bitcoin/">Just-In: Telegram Users Can Now Buy, Withdraw &#038; Exchange Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21215026/telegram-bitcoin-1140x600-1.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Coinbase Set To Launch Base Mainnet Within 2023</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/coinbase-set-to-launch-base-mainnet-within-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145938</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: Crypto exchange Coinbase&#8217;s entry into the Layer 2 space is apparently making steady strides towards a mainnet launch soon. A testnet version of the Ethereum Layer 2 network has been unveiled in February 2023. Base was launched as a platform that makes it easy for developers to build apps and plug into the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-set-to-launch-base-mainnet-within-2023/" title="Breaking: Coinbase Set To Launch Base Mainnet Within 2023"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-set-to-launch-base-mainnet-within-2023/">Breaking: Coinbase Set To Launch Base Mainnet Within 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/05140435/Coinbase-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Coinbase Base mainnet launch" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News</strong>: Crypto exchange Coinbase&#8217;s entry into the Layer 2 space is apparently making steady strides towards a mainnet launch soon. A testnet version of the Ethereum <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/top-layer-2-crypto-projects-to-watch-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Layer 2 network</a> has been unveiled in February 2023. Base was <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-coinbase-base-layer-2-networks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> as a platform that makes it easy for developers to build apps and plug into the Coinbase product suite for user convenience. The developers said in a latest update that the Base mainnet is being considered as a priority.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-eye-major-pullback-risk-tips-bloomberg-analyst" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Bitcoin, Ethereum Eye Major Pullback Risk, Tips Bloomberg Analyst</strong></a></p>
<h2>Base Mainnet Launch</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, a Coinbase executive spilled the beans on the potential timeline for Base mainnet launch. The mainnet launch is planned for 2023, as the team is prioritizing for delivering it as soon as possible. However, the official dates for the launch are yet to be ascertained. Jesse Pollak, the Base lead, said the overall vision is to unite builders and users on the blockchain.</p>
<p>The Ethereum layer 2 blockchain comes as a potential rival to existing layer 2 blockchains, considering the wide reach of the crypto exchange. Pollak <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/04/21/coinbases-layer-2-blockchain-base-plans-for-2023-mainnet-launch/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> the launch is now a number one priority, as per a TechCrunch report:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s coming soon, we are working hard on it. It’s our number one priority alongside decentralization goals and the rest of the year is really about making sure we get there as quickly as possible.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The executive said the larger plan is to unite Base along with Coinbase to bring &#8220;million developers and billions of users on chain.&#8221;</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-creditors-lauds-former-us-secret-service-agent-in-bankruptcy-case" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>FTX Creditors Lauds Former US Secret Service Agent In Bankruptcy Case</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/coinbase-set-to-launch-base-mainnet-within-2023/">Breaking: Coinbase Set To Launch Base Mainnet Within 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/05140435/Coinbase-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SOL Price Prediction: Solana Price Offers Last Pullback Opportunity Before a 55% Rally</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/sol-price-prediction-solana-price-offers-last-pullback-opportunity-before-a-55-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EMA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RSI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=145934</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SOL Price Prediction: On April 11th, the Solana price gave a high momentum breakout from a resistance trendline which carried a sustained downtrend for the past 10 months. After witnessing multiple reversals from this dynamic resistance, a bullish breakout is an early sign of trend reversal which could drive the SOL price for a massive <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/sol-price-prediction-solana-price-offers-last-pullback-opportunity-before-a-55-rally/" title="SOL Price Prediction: Solana Price Offers Last Pullback Opportunity Before a 55% Rally"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/sol-price-prediction-solana-price-offers-last-pullback-opportunity-before-a-55-rally/">SOL Price Prediction: Solana Price Offers Last Pullback Opportunity Before a 55% Rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/29163146/solana1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="SOL Price Prediction" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://coingape.com/markets/solana-price-prediction/">SOL Price Prediction</a>: On April 11th, the Solana price gave a high momentum breakout from a resistance trendline which carried a sustained downtrend for the past 10 months. After witnessing multiple reversals from this dynamic resistance, a bullish breakout is an early sign of trend reversal which could drive the SOL price for a massive rally. As of now, the coin price is retesting this breached trendline validating whether this breakout is genuine or not.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key Points</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Solana price hints at a temporary pullback to $21.68 or $19.8 before the bull run continue </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The multiple support concentrated near the $21.8 level offers a strong accumulation zone for Solana buyers.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 24-hour trading volume in the Solana coin is $510.2 Million, indicating a 15.2% loss.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/p/P8CoM5Ym.png" alt="SOL Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1104" />Source-Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amid the recent sell-off in the crypto market, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/solana/#:~:text=Solana%20is%20spotted%20trading%20at,in%20the%20last%2024%20hours.">Solana coin price</a> turned down from a local resistance of $26 on April 17. This correction has tumbled the coin price by 16.5% in the last five days and plunged to its current price of $22.19.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $21.68 and the breached trendline level at $19.8 are two crucial support that potential buyers should keep their eyes on. If the coin price manages to sustain above these supports, the recuperating bullish momentum will bolster buyers to kick-start a new recovery rally.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/best-crypto-exchanges-for-recurring-purchases/">Best Crypto Exchanges For Recurring Purchases In 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With sustained buying, the Solana price may rise to potential targets of $26, $30.5, and $34.5 which is 100% growth as per Trend-based Fibonacci Extension tools. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a contrary note, a breakdown below $19.8 could undermine the aforementioned bullish thesis.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><b>Relative strength index: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> plunged below the midline indicating the negative sentiment in the market is rising.</span></p>
<p><b>Exponential Moving Average: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">The daily <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMAs</a> (50 and 100) wavering around the $21.68 level offer additional support to prevent a bearish breakdown.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana Coin Price Intraday Level</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot price: $22.03</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bearish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Low</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels: $23.88 and $26</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels: $21.68 and $19.88</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/sol-price-prediction-solana-price-offers-last-pullback-opportunity-before-a-55-rally/">SOL Price Prediction: Solana Price Offers Last Pullback Opportunity Before a 55% Rally</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/29163146/solana1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: On Friday, a crypto whale that has been dormant for the past ten years transferred 279 Bitcoins, which are currently worth 7.8 million dollars, to three new addresses. The on-chain research platform Lookonchain reports that the wallet was credited with a total of 1,128 Bitcoins in the months of October 2012 and May <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/" title="Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/">Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="982" height="726" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21194355/bitcoin-price-all-time-high1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News: </strong>On Friday, a crypto whale that has been dormant for the past ten years transferred 279 <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/">Bitcoins</a>, which are currently worth 7.8 million dollars, to three new addresses. The on-chain research platform Lookonchain <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1649387289745977344" rel="nofollow">reports</a> that the wallet was credited with a total of 1,128 Bitcoins in the months of October 2012 and May 2013. When those transactions took place, the price of one Bitcoin was roughly around $12 and $195 respectively.</p>
<h2>Dormant Bitcoin Wallet Moves 279 BTC</h2>
<p>Taking into account the price of Bitcoin at the time of writing, the amount of Bitcoin that is stored in the <a href="https://coingape.com/top-5-crypto-wallets-for-security-in-2023/">crypto wallet</a> would translate to be around roughly 31 million USD. This comes on the heels of another bitcoin whale transferring 2,071.5 BTC yesterday &#8212; which is equivalent to 60.7 million USD &#8212; after a lengthy nine-year hiatus.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: <a title="Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-gary-gensler-sec-jay-clayton/" rel="bookmark">Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair</a></strong></em></p>
<p>While many fear an incoming BTC dump due to such developments, most of the transactions have been made to other standalone Bitcoin wallets rather than <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/">crypto exchanges</a>.</p>
<h2>Reason Behind Reawakening?</h2>
<p>Although the fact that the cause for the move is unknown, there is widespread conjecture that some long-time crypto HODLers are moving old funds to new <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/wallet-address/">wallet addresses</a> in the midst of a massive wallet-draining operation that is purportedly targeting old wallets. On the other hand, some users opine it to be a normal movement of funds to wallets like <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/hardware-wallets-are-they-safe/">hardware wallets</a> which tend to offer greater security.</p>
<p>On Friday, the price of Bitcoin dipped below $28,000 for a short period of time as the broader <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/">crypto market</a> continued its decline for three consecutive days. In the wake of this crypto news, <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin’s price</a> is currently exchanging hands at $28,110 which represents a drop of 1.15% over the past 24 hours in comparison to a loss of 6.87% recorded over the past seven days.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read: <a title="Just-In: Texas Passes Landmark Crypto Bill For Exchanges To Comply" href="https://coingape.com/texas-crypto-bill-exchanges-transparency/" rel="bookmark">Texas Passes Landmark Crypto Bill For Exchanges To Comply</a></strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-satoshi-era-bitcoin-wallet-comes-to-life/">Satoshi Era Bitcoin Wallet Comes To Life, Moves $7.8 Million After Decade Of Dormancy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21194355/bitcoin-price-all-time-high1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC News: Allnodes Supports Terra Rebels Controversial Terra Classic Proposal</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/lunc-news-allnodes-supports-terra-rebels-controversial-terra-classic-proposal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LUNC price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Validator Allnodes favors the controversial Proposal 11479 by the Terra Rebels developer group, while the Terra Classic community remains divided on providing funds for the Rebel Station. The community believes Terra Rebels mismanaged funds provided earlier for the Rebel Station and caused FUD that caused LUNC price to fall massively. LUNC Proposal By Terra Rebels <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-allnodes-supports-terra-rebels-controversial-terra-classic-proposal/" title="LUNC News: Allnodes Supports Terra Rebels Controversial Terra Classic Proposal"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-allnodes-supports-terra-rebels-controversial-terra-classic-proposal/">LUNC News: Allnodes Supports Terra Rebels Controversial Terra Classic Proposal</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="730" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/07212440/Terra-Classic-LUNC-01.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="LUNC News: Allnodes Supports Terra Rebels Controversial Terra Classic Proposal" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Validator Allnodes favors the controversial <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://station.terra.money/proposal/columbus-5/11479" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proposal 11479</a> by the Terra Rebels developer group, while the Terra Classic community remains divided on providing funds for the Rebel Station. The community believes Terra Rebels mismanaged funds provided earlier for the Rebel Station and caused FUD that caused LUNC price to fall massively.</p>
<h2>LUNC Proposal By Terra Rebels Almost Passed</h2>
<p>Last week, <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-classic-community-remains-divided-on-key-proposal-lunc-price-to-fall/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proposal 11459 by Terra Rebels</a> was almost passed, but validator Allnodes, with 15% voting power, voted “No” on the proposal. Allnodes said it voted “No” on Proposal 11459 due to a lack of transparency on nodes deployed and requests being handled by Terra Rebels.</p>
<p>Terra Rebels has provided all details including nodes and servers handling endpoint scalability and distributed storage. Terra Classic validator Allnodes has also stress-tested Terra Rebels&#8217; infrastructure by diverting all volume of Allnodes&#8217; public node to Terra Rebels. The test has been successful and Allnodes support Rebel Station.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Terra Classic blockchain requires at least two independent endpoints. While there is still plenty of room for growth, I think that currently Terra Rebels endpoint is a good choice as backup endpoint for Terra Classic blockchain.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>After Allnodes voted &#8220;Yes&#8221;, the proposal is almost passed with 2 days still remaining. The Proposal 11479 has received 47% in favor, with 41% &#8220;No&#8221; and 12% &#8220;No with veto&#8221; votes. Other 13 validators including MAX, JESUSisLORD, Autism Staking, and Crypto Genesis support the proposal. Whereas, 13 validators such as TCB, Luna Station 88, HappyCattyCrypto, and LUNC DAO rejected the proposal.</p>
<p>Terra Rebels is seeking $37,593 worth of LUNC tokens from the community pool, with $7,593 for running costs and $30,000 for wages. The funds will help with running costs and technical support of Rebel Station Infrastructure for 3 months.</p>
<h2>Terra Classic (LUNC) Price Breaks Below Support Level</h2>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/terra-luna-classic" target="_blank" rel="noopener">LUNC price</a> fell 2% in the last 24 hours, with the price currently trading at $0.000113. The 24-hour low and high are $0.000112 and $0.000115, respectively. Furthermore, the trading volume has decreased by 11% in the last 24 hours, indicating a decline in interest among traders.</p>
<p>Terra Classic has broken below the key support level of 0.00012 as the community is <a href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-core-developers-edward-kim-zaradar-leave-joint-l1-task-force/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">facing a crisis</a> as core developers <strong>Ed Kim</strong> and <strong>Tobias “Zaradar” Andersen </strong>left the Joint L1 Task Force developer team.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-allnodes-supports-terra-rebels-controversial-terra-classic-proposal/">LUNC News: Allnodes Supports Terra Rebels Controversial Terra Classic Proposal</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/07212440/Terra-Classic-LUNC-01.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Bard Tries To Gain &#8216;Coding Assist&#8217; Edge Over ChatGPT</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/google-bard-tries-to-gain-coding-assist-edge-over-chatgpt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145928</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a major update since the launch of Bard in March 2023, Google said its conversational AI service will now be able to help with programming and software development tasks. Although it is very early into the development, it is not clear as to whether Google is trying to become the top AI chatbot for <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/google-bard-tries-to-gain-coding-assist-edge-over-chatgpt/" title="Google Bard Tries To Gain &#8216;Coding Assist&#8217; Edge Over ChatGPT"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/google-bard-tries-to-gain-coding-assist-edge-over-chatgpt/">Google Bard Tries To Gain &#8216;Coding Assist&#8217; Edge Over ChatGPT</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="2560" height="915" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21190657/Google-Bard-Webp-scaled-1.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Google Bard chatgpt" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>In a major update since the launch of Bard in March 2023, Google said its conversational AI service will now be able to help with programming and software development tasks. Although it is very early into the development, it is not clear as to whether Google is trying to become the top AI chatbot for software professionals while OpenAI&#8217;s <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/chatgpt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a> is developed for general purposes. The search engine giant said coding has been on top of its list of requests from our users for embedding into the AI service.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</strong></a></p>
<h2>Google Bard For Software Developers</h2>
<p>In a fresh <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://blog.google/technology/ai/code-with-bard/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">update</a> on its generative AI project, Google said Bard can assist developers in tasks like code generation, debugging and code explanation. Bard can help craft SQL queries for user database, translate software from one language to another, debug lines of source code and explain code line by line. However, the company warned that Bard is still in early stages and that it may sometimes provide inaccurate, misleading or false information.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are launching these capabilities in more than 20 programming languages including C++, Go, Java, Javascript, Python and Typescript. And you can easily export Python code to Google Colab — no copy and paste required.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Similarly, ChatGPT, on the other hand, can also demystify technical content like software code in laymen terms, while also helping in fixing coding errors. With Google&#8217;s large range of G Suite products and its strength in reach among software professionals, Bard could potentially have an early advantage in the coding assist space. However, the rapid pace of development in the generative AI space could also give a share of the market to new entrants.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-eye-major-pullback-risk-tips-bloomberg-analyst" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Bitcoin, Ethereum Eye Major Pullback Risk, Tips Bloomberg Analyst</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/google-bard-tries-to-gain-coding-assist-edge-over-chatgpt/">Google Bard Tries To Gain &#8216;Coding Assist&#8217; Edge Over ChatGPT</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21190657/Google-Bard-Webp-scaled-1.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Price Prediction: Bull Trap Puts Ethereum Price at 7% Downside Risk</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/eth-price-prediction-bull-trap-puts-ethereum-price-at-7-downside-risk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH price prediction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=145919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Price Prediction: On April 13th, the Ethereum coin price gave a bullish breakout from the crucial psychological resistance of $2000. This breached level was supposed to bolster buyers for further recovery but the broader market sell-off plunged the price back below the $2000 mark again. On April 19th, a massive outflow in ETH price <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/eth-price-prediction-bull-trap-puts-ethereum-price-at-7-downside-risk/" title="ETH Price Prediction: Bull Trap Puts Ethereum Price at 7% Downside Risk"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/eth-price-prediction-bull-trap-puts-ethereum-price-at-7-downside-risk/">ETH Price Prediction: Bull Trap Puts Ethereum Price at 7% Downside Risk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1140" height="641" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/28215251/ethereum-price-prediction-1140x641-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ETH Price Prediction" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://coingape.com/markets/ethereum-eth-price-prediction/">Ethereum Price Prediction</a>: On April 13th, the Ethereum coin price gave a bullish breakout from the crucial psychological resistance of $2000. This breached level was supposed to bolster buyers for further recovery but the broader market sell-off plunged the price back below the $2000 mark again. On April 19th, a massive outflow in <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/">ETH price</a> formed a massive daily red candle which may have forced liquidated aggressive buyers with narrow stop loss, fueling more selling pressure in the market.</span></p>
<h2><b>Key Points: </b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ongoing correction phase in Ethereum price may face significant demand pressure at $1780</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The daily EMAs(50, 100, and 200) may offer dynamic support to resume a bullish recovery</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Ether is $11.4 Billion, indicating a 2.74% loss.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/x/xhIMxwnu.png" alt="ETH Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1104" />Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amid the increasing selling pressure in the market, the Ethereum price has witnessed a 9% drop in the last three days and plunged to the current price of $1913. With this downfall, the coin holders lost the 23.6% <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/fibonacci-retracement/">Fibonacci retracement</a> and a support trendline maintaining sustained recovery in ETH price for the last four weeks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, a breakdown below the dynamic support will likely accelerate selling pressure in the market and tumble the Ethereum price more 7-8% down to hit the combined support of $1780 and 50% FIB level.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/new-cryptocurrencies-to-buy/">15 New Cryptocurrencies To Buy In 2023</a>e</p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This high area of interest may assist buyers in sustaining the higher levels of the chart and resuming the prior recovery. Thus, the $1780 is a key level to watch in the coming weeks.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While overall the price trend remains bullish a breakdown below $1780 will gradually weaken the buyers’ grip over the Ethereum price.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><b>Moving Average Convergence Divergence: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">A sell signal from the bearish crossover between the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/macd-moving-average-convergence-divergnece/">MACD</a>(blue) and the signal(orange) line hints at prolonged correction in ETH price.</span></p>
<p><b>Exponential Moving Average: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Along with the ascending support trendline, the Ethereum price breached below the 20-day <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMA</a> offering an additional edge in the short-seller&#8217;s favor.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethereum Coin Price Intraday Levels-</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $1915</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bearish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Low</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance level- $2000 and $2140</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support level- $1850 and $1780</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/eth-price-prediction-bull-trap-puts-ethereum-price-at-7-downside-risk/">ETH Price Prediction: Bull Trap Puts Ethereum Price at 7% Downside Risk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/28215251/ethereum-price-prediction-1140x641-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-gary-gensler-sec-jay-clayton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145913</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News: Former U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Jay Clayton became a subject of criticism on Friday with his support to Gary Gensler over crypto token classification. While the bigwigs of crypto market pinned their hopes on gaining an edge over regulatory agencies through legal proceedings, Clayton said courts are after all not <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-gary-gensler-sec-jay-clayton/" title="Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-gary-gensler-sec-jay-clayton/">Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1201" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/17151938/Gary_Gensler.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Gary Gensler crypto" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News</strong>: Former U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Jay Clayton became a subject of criticism on Friday with his support to Gary Gensler over crypto token classification. While the bigwigs of <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto market</a> pinned their hopes on gaining an edge over regulatory agencies through legal proceedings, Clayton said courts are after all not efficient in clearing the air around securities Vs commodities differentiation. He made the comments at the back of Gensler&#8217;s failure to answer specifically on whether Ethereum (ETH) is a security or commodity.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/banks-vcs-pension-funds-once-crypto-friendly-steering-away-from-crypto" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Banks, VCs, Pension Funds Once Crypto-Friendly Steering Away From Crypto</strong></a></p>
<p>During the recent House Financial Services Committee hearing, Gary Gensler <a href="https://coingape.com/gary-gensler-hearing-crypto-firms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dodged</a> the question on explaining how crypto firms should comply with the laws. The Committee Chair Patrick McHenry came down heavily against Gensler&#8217;s stance that existing securities laws are already compatible with the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Jay Clayton Supports Gensler</h2>
<p>Speaking about the state of the crypto market and the debate around regulation, Clayton said securities can eventually become commodities but currently many cryptocurrencies appear to be securities. He explained that these assets now give a first mover advantage to early investors in crypto projects, hence acting as securities. During a discussion on CNBC on Friday, he also <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/TimR614/status/1649389078415015937" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The courts are not an efficient place to resolve classification issues around securities and commodities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>His comments attracted criticism from the crypto community, which was buoyed by the Gensler&#8217;s grilling on lack of clarity during the Congressional hearing. Meanwhile, the US regulators are facing fresh wave of angst after the European Union&#8217;s <a href="https://coingape.com/eu-parliament-votes-in-to-pass-mica-bitcoin-drops-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">voting</a> to pass the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation. MiCA is touted as the first comprehensive rules for digital crypto asset service providers.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-gary-gensler-sec-jay-clayton/">Gary Gensler Gets Rare Support On Crypto From Former SEC Chair</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/17151938/Gary_Gensler.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Eye Major Pullback Risk, Tips Bloomberg Analyst</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-eye-major-pullback-risk-tips-bloomberg-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price News: The global digital asset market witnessed a major pullback as more than $100 billion went out of the market. Bitcoin (BTC), the world’s largest crypto dropped by around 9% in the last 7 days to lose the crucial $30 price level. As the market trades in increased uncertainty, Bloomberg analyst hints major <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-eye-major-pullback-risk-tips-bloomberg-analyst/" title="Bitcoin, Ethereum Eye Major Pullback Risk, Tips Bloomberg Analyst"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-eye-major-pullback-risk-tips-bloomberg-analyst/">Bitcoin, Ethereum Eye Major Pullback Risk, Tips Bloomberg Analyst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21183759/bitcoin-ethereum.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="bitcoin price news ethereum" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Bitcoin price News:</strong> The global digital asset market witnessed a major pullback as more than $100 billion went out of the market. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>, the world’s largest crypto dropped by around 9% in the last 7 days to lose the crucial $30 price level. As the market trades in increased uncertainty, Bloomberg analyst hints major pullback ahead.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-sec-caused-untold-harm-to-us-coinbase-ceo-after-mica-approval/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC Caused Untold Harm To US; Coinbase CEO After MiCA Approval</a></strong></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price To Decline More Ahead</h2>
<p>Mike McGlone, Senior Macro Strategist at Bloomberg Intelligence <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/mikemcglone11/status/1649376033362042880" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a> Bitcoin (BTC) and <a href="https://coingape.com/price/ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH) may</a> be running into a wall of resistance ahead. However, Bitcoin price went surged over the $30K level to encounter multiple resistance. Same with ETH, the second largest crypto price breached the $2K level but faced multiple resistances there.</p>
<p>Bloomberg Analyst is still bullish on the biggest of the cryptos in the long term. Meanwhile, a force generated by the dropping stock market in accordance with the tightening Federal Reserve policies leading to recession holds the potential to lower the tide for all the risk assets. He marks Bitcoin and Ethereum among the riskiest assets.</p>
<p>As per the data, $30,000 and $2,000 have been pivotal points for Bitcoin and Ethereum, respectively. McGlone mentioned that the diminishing supply and low and increasing adoption make the bullish case in the long term. However, growing consensus shows that worse is over ahead of a U.S. recession. It is indicated by the yield curve at the highest probability since 1982.</p>
<figure id="attachment_145923" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145923" style="width: 1200px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-145923" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21190223/bt.jpg" alt="bitcoin" width="1200" height="800" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-145923" class="wp-caption-text dfdfdf1">Source: Bloomberg Intelligence</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</a></strong></p>
<p>Bitcoin price is down by around 8% in the last 7 days. BTC is trading at an average price of $28,127, at the press time. Its 24 hour trading volume is down by over 2% to stand at $20 billion. While Ethereum price declined by 9% over the past 7 days. ETH is trading at an average price of $1,910, at the press time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-eye-major-pullback-risk-tips-bloomberg-analyst/">Bitcoin, Ethereum Eye Major Pullback Risk, Tips Bloomberg Analyst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21183759/bitcoin-ethereum.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Whales Fail To Rurn The Tide, Token Remains In Red</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/shib-whales-fail-to-rurn-the-tide-token-remains-in-red/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=145890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/shib-whales-fail-to-rurn-the-tide-token-remains-in-red/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21181028/shiba_inu_remains_in_red_despite_whales_shib_buying_spree_720.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="SHIB Whales Fail To Rurn The Tide, Token Remains In Red"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/shib-whales-fail-to-rurn-the-tide-token-remains-in-red/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21181028/shiba_inu_remains_in_red_despite_whales_shib_buying_spree_720.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="SHIB Whales Fail To Rurn The Tide, Token Remains In Red"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21181028/shiba_inu_remains_in_red_despite_whales_shib_buying_spree_720.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stronghold BTC Miner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nasdaq-listed Stronghold Digital Mining (SDIG) plans to purchase bitcoin mining machines through $10 million in private equity financing. The Bitcoin mining company plans to purchase miners worth millions to increase production and introduce new mining machines. SDIG stock price is rallying nearly 4% in pre-market hours. Strong Digital Mining To Purchase Miners Worth Millions Strong <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions/" title="Breaking: Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions/">Breaking: Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="814" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/17180842/Bitcoin-mining-6-e1653307843986.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Nasdaq-listed Stronghold Digital Mining (SDIG) plans to purchase bitcoin mining machines through $10 million in private equity financing. The Bitcoin <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-mining/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mining</a> company plans to purchase miners worth millions to increase production and introduce new mining machines. SDIG stock price is rallying nearly 4% in pre-market hours.</p>
<h2>Strong Digital Mining To Purchase Miners Worth Millions</h2>
<p>Strong Digital Mining signed a securities purchase agreement with institutional investors to sell 9 million Class A shares and Stronghold CEO Greg Beard to sell 1 million Class A shares under private placement to purchase Bitcoin miners.</p>
<p>Stronghold entered into a Master Sales and Purchase Agreement to acquire 5,000 new, latest-generation MicroBT Whatsminer M50 miners.</p>
<p>Also, the Company will issue to the Purchasers warrants to purchase an aggregate of 10 million Class A shares, with an initial exercise price of $1.10 per share, as per a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/04/21/2651839/0/en/Stronghold-Digital-Mining-Announces-10-Million-Private-Placement-to-Fund-Purchase-of-Bitcoin-Miners.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> on April 21.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Gross proceeds from the Private Placement are expected to be $10 million, before deducting offering expenses, and are expected to be used to acquire additional Bitcoin miners. The closing of the Private Placement is expected to occur on April 21, 2023.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/banks-vcs-pension-funds-once-crypto-friendly-steering-away-from-crypto" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Banks, VCs, Pension Funds Once Crypto-Friendly Steering Away From Crypto</a></strong></p>
<p>Strong Digital Mining is restricted from issuing equity until 30 days after registration for the sale of securities and effecting variable rate transactions for a period of 6 months.</p>
<p>The stock price of Strong Digital Mining (SDIG) jumped over 4% in pre-market hours. SDIG shares fell over 5% to $1 on Thursday. The SDIG shares price has rallied 132% this year as Bitcoin price surged above $30,000.</p>
<p>The revenue for the December quarter beat market estimates by 15.59% and the loss reduced as compared to the September quarter.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price</a> is currently trading at $28,189, down 3% in the last 24 hours. The 24-hour low and high are $27,855 and $28,906, respectively.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-expiry-bitcoin-and-ethereum-bearish-price-move-to-break-key-support-levels" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Crypto Expiry: Bitcoin and Ethereum Bearish Price Move To Break Key Support Levels?</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/stronghold-digital-mining-bitcoin-mining-miners-millions/">Breaking: Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Mining Company Buying Miners Worth Millions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/17180842/Bitcoin-mining-6-e1653307843986.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis Hints More 4-5% Fall this Week; Is it Time to Reaccumulate?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-hints-more-4-5-fall-this-week-is-it-time-to-reaccumulate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 12:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=145903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Price Analysis: Amid the recent sell-off in the crypto market, the Bitcoin price failed to sustain above the recently reclaimed $30000 psychological level. As a result, the coin price falling for three consecutive days has registered an 8% drop and plunged to the current price of $28065. Moreover, this recent downfall also breached a <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-hints-more-4-5-fall-this-week-is-it-time-to-reaccumulate/" title="Bitcoin Price Analysis Hints More 4-5% Fall this Week; Is it Time to Reaccumulate?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-hints-more-4-5-fall-this-week-is-it-time-to-reaccumulate/">Bitcoin Price Analysis Hints More 4-5% Fall this Week; Is it Time to Reaccumulate?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/13143034/bitcoin.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="bitcoin news crypto" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Analysis: </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amid the recent sell-off in the crypto market, the <a href="https://coingape.com/price/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> failed to sustain above the recently reclaimed $30000 psychological level. As a result, the coin price falling for three consecutive days has registered an 8% drop and plunged to the current price of $28065. Moreover, this recent downfall also breached a support trendline of a rising channel pattern, indicating a higher possibility of a significant correction. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key Points</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multiple technical support concentrate near the $27000 creates a strong accumulation zone</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Breakdown below $27000 will put Bitcoin price under 7.3% downside risk</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Bitcoin is $21.5 Billion, indicating a 7% gain</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/y/yPTLw6jp.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Analysis" width="1946" height="1104" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the last four weeks, the Bitcoin price witnessed a sustained recovery under the influence of a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/parallel-channel-pattern/">rising channel pattern</a>. The buyers have been using this dynamic support as stepping stones to reclaim the higher levels of the chart.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, amid the increasing selling pressure, the BTC price breached the pattern’s support trendline on April 20th. As of now, the coin price trades at $28065 but with sustained selling the coin holders would likely witness another 4% to reach $27000.</span></p>
<blockquote><p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-expiry-bitcoin-and-ethereum-bearish-price-move-to-break-key-support-levels/?utm_source=24hrsupdateall">Crypto Expiry: Bitcoin and Ethereum Bearish Price Move To Break Key Support Levels?</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aforementioned support aligned with the 0.236 <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/fibonacci-retracement/">Fibonacci retracement level</a> and 50-day EMA offers a significant footing for buyers to prevent further loss. If the Bitcoin price manages to sustain above the $27000 support, a new higher low formation could bolster the resumption of prevailing recovery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a contrary note, a breakdown below $27000 with a daily closing will tumble the price 7.3% and plunge it to the $25200 level.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative strength index</strong>: The daily <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> dropped below the midline accentuating the increasing negativity in the crypto market and the possibility of a longer correction.</span></p>
<p><b>Exponential Moving Average: </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">In case of potential recovery, the buyers need to successfully flip the recently breached 20-day <a href="https://coingape.com/education/exponential-moving-average-how-to-leverage-it-in-crypto-market/">EMA</a> slope into viable support to gain additional confirmation for a price rally.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $28132</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bearish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Low</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $28680 and $31000</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $27000 and $25200</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-analysis-hints-more-4-5-fall-this-week-is-it-time-to-reaccumulate/">Bitcoin Price Analysis Hints More 4-5% Fall this Week; Is it Time to Reaccumulate?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/13143034/bitcoin.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big AI Launches: Is the Takeover Here?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/big-ai-launches-is-the-takeover-here/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=145900</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/big-ai-launches-is-the-takeover-here/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/18124137/AI-Could-Replace-Millions-Of-Software-Engineers-In-India.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Big AI Launches: Is the Takeover Here?"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/big-ai-launches-is-the-takeover-here/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/18124137/AI-Could-Replace-Millions-Of-Software-Engineers-In-India.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Big AI Launches: Is the Takeover Here?"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/18124137/AI-Could-Replace-Millions-Of-Software-Engineers-In-India.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Creditors Lauds Former US Secret Service Agent In Bankruptcy Case</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ftx-creditors-lauds-former-us-secret-service-agent-in-bankruptcy-case/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[24/7 Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=145884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX Debtors and the Official Committee Of Unsecured Creditors filed a motion in the court to redact or withhold confidential information and personal details of FTX creditors in any court filings related to the bankruptcy case. Former US Secret Service Agent Jeremy A. Sheridan supported anonymity for creditors citing risks of identity theft or unlawful <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-creditors-lauds-former-us-secret-service-agent-in-bankruptcy-case/" title="FTX Creditors Lauds Former US Secret Service Agent In Bankruptcy Case"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-creditors-lauds-former-us-secret-service-agent-in-bankruptcy-case/">FTX Creditors Lauds Former US Secret Service Agent In Bankruptcy Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/20222048/FTX-court.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="FTX Creditors Lauds Former US Secret Service Agent In Bankruptcy Case" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>FTX Debtors and the Official Committee Of Unsecured Creditors filed a motion in the court to redact or withhold confidential information and personal details of FTX creditors in any court filings related to the bankruptcy case. Former US Secret Service Agent Jeremy A. Sheridan <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://document.epiq11.com/document/getdocumentsbydocket/?docketId=999153&amp;projectCode=FTX&amp;docketNumber=1325&amp;source=DM" target="_blank" rel="noopener">supported</a> anonymity for creditors citing risks of identity theft or unlawful injury.</p>
<h2>FTX Debtors and Creditors Filed Motion To Keep Names Anonymous</h2>
<p>According to a court <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://dm.epiq11.com/case/ftx/dockets" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> dated April 20, FTX and the Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors submitted a motion in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware. The motion aims to redact and withhold the names, addresses, and e-mail addresses of any creditors or entity.</p>
<p>The Debtors and Committee <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/FTX_Committee/status/1649241295301271552" target="_blank" rel="noopener">believe</a> the names of customers who are natural persons should be kept private to protect them from potential harm caused by scams and other threats. The Court has already ordered that customers’ email and physical addresses be sealed.</p>
<p>Former US Secret Service Agent Jeremy A. Sheridan, who is managing director of FTI Consulting Inc, filed a declaration in support of the motion. FTI Consulting is the financial adviser for the Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors.</p>
<p>Sheridan asserts identifying FTX customers imposes a severe and unusual risk of identity theft, asset theft, personal attack, and further online victimization.</p>
<p>The US Trustee and media companies, including Bloomberg, claimed to make the names of FTX customers public, arguing that it would help identify if the individuals are creditors in any other bankruptcy case. However, the Bankruptcy Code authorizes a court to protect an individual&#8217;s details as it may lead to identity theft or unlawful harm.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-news-bankrupt-exchange-250m-offer-relaunch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tribe Capital mulling a fresh capital</a> injection of $250 million to restart the crypto exchange FTX. The committee of unsecured creditors announced to begin work with the debtors to analyze all of the potential options to either reboot or sell the exchanges.</p>
<p><strong>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/banks-vcs-pension-funds-once-crypto-friendly-steering-away-from-crypto/?utm_source=sidebartabnews">Banks, VCs, Pension Funds Once Crypto-Friendly Steering Away From Crypto</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-creditors-lauds-former-us-secret-service-agent-in-bankruptcy-case/">FTX Creditors Lauds Former US Secret Service Agent In Bankruptcy Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/20222048/FTX-court.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BAYC Floor Price Drops Below 50 ETH</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/bayc-floor-price-drops-below-50-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=145887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/bayc-floor-price-drops-below-50-eth/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21163806/BAYC-Floor-Price-Drops-Below-50-ETH.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="BAYC Floor Price Drops Below 50 ETH"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/bayc-floor-price-drops-below-50-eth/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21163806/BAYC-Floor-Price-Drops-Below-50-ETH.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="BAYC Floor Price Drops Below 50 ETH"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/21163806/BAYC-Floor-Price-Drops-Below-50-ETH.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
