<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 20:26:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>First-ever Bored Ape Yacht Party Set to Take Place in Europe at BlockDown Festival</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Svetlana Soroka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 20:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockdown festival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bored ape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bored ape yacht club]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/">First-ever Bored Ape Yacht Party Set to Take Place in Europe at BlockDown Festival</a></p>
<p>A stunning Yacht Party and Afterparty experience with DJ Ape, who’ll perform using the latest AI technologies that merges the virtual and physical world showcased live at Europe's biggest Web3 Festival this July. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/">First-ever Bored Ape Yacht Party Set to Take Place in Europe at BlockDown Festival</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/">First-ever Bored Ape Yacht Party Set to Take Place in Europe at BlockDown Festival</a></p>
<div>
<dl id="attachment_252660">
<dt><img decoding="async" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival.png" alt="First-ever Bored Ape Yacht Party Set to Take Place in Europe at BlockDown Festival" width="1500" height="500" /></dt>
</dl>
</div>
<p><a href="https://blockdownconf.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BlockDown Festival: Portugal</a>, is excited to reveal two exclusive <a href="https://boredapeyachtparty.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bored Ape parties</a> featuring DJ Ape and friends at this summer&#8217;s top European Web3 festival. Attendees can anticipate Europe&#8217;s inaugural Bored Ape Yacht Party on July 10th, on a beautiful yacht showcasing the stunning Algarve coast and iconic Benagil Cave for an unparalleled Bored Ape IRL adventure.</p>
<p>The Bored Ape Afterparty on July 12th, open to all BlockDown Festival visitors, will include a live performance by DJ Ape, exclusive Bored Ape merchandise, and a one-of-a-kind Bored Ape show that combines physical IRL elements with digital effects that blur the boundaries of of the physical and the metaverse to new heights in a first of its kind Bored Ape experience. This groundbreaking event, hosted by Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) and Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC) holders, will offer an extraordinary fusion of music, art, culture, and technology for Web3 enthusiasts worldwide.</p>
<p>DJ Ape shared their enthusiasm, stating,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Bored Ape events at BlockDown Festival: Portugal will be a celebration of creativity, originality, and community. The party is going to be epic; I&#8217;m excited to share my music with these incredible communities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>BlockDown Festival Founder Erhan Korhaliller added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Bored Ape Yacht Club has had a huge impact on Web3 culture, and having the Bored Ape community take part is another piece of the puzzle to make BlockDown Festival Portugal a truly remarkable experience for our guests.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>At the Bored Ape Afterparty, attendees can expect an unforgettable performance by DJ Ape and the opportunity to get exclusive BAYC and MAYC merchandise. Hosted by Web3 Creative Marketing and Communications Agency EAK Digital, BlockDown Festival will take place at the Lick venue in Vilamoura, Portugal, from July 10-12, 2023.</p>
<p>BlockDown Festival is a unique Web3 event that celebrates the convergence of Web3 and culture, including music, fashion, sports, media, gaming, and entertainment. Attendees can enjoy VIP networking opportunities with industry leaders, stunning sunsets, parties, private beaches, and boat tours.</p>
<h3>About Bored Ape Yacht Party</h3>
<p>The <a href="https://boredapeyachtparty.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Bored Ape Yacht Party</a> premiered in Dubai as an official satellite event of this year&#8217;s Dubai International Boat Show organized by Bored Ape and Mutant Ape NFT holders for the global community (Disclaimer: This is not officially affiliated with Yuga Labs). The BAYC and MAYC community revolves around a collection of 10,000 unique hand-drawn Apes and 30k Mutant Apes, each with its distinct personality and traits. Bored Ape NFTs have become some of the most sought-after digital assets globally, with prices reaching millions of dollars.</p>
<h3>About BlockDown Festival</h3>
<p><a href="https://blockdownconf.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">BlockDown Festival</a> emerged in response to the international Covid-19 crisis in spring 2020, uniting the blockchain and crypto communities from around the world. The eighth edition, BlockDown Festival: Portugal, will be held on the breathtaking Algarve Coast in Portugal. Past guest speakers include Changpeng Zhao, Charles Hoskinson, Akon, Edward Snowden, and Miami Mayor Francis Suarez.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/">First-ever Bored Ape Yacht Party Set to Take Place in Europe at BlockDown Festival</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/first-ever-bored-ape-yacht-party-set-to-take-place-in-europe-at-blockdown-festival/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin Launches FWS, Decentralized Alternative to Amazon Web Service</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 16:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cloud Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aws]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FWS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/">Filecoin Launches FWS, Decentralized Alternative to Amazon Web Service</a></p>
<p>Prior to the launch of the FWS, the protocol launched its Filecoin Virtual Machine Compatibility which supports smart contracts.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/">Filecoin Launches FWS, Decentralized Alternative to Amazon Web Service</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/">Filecoin Launches FWS, Decentralized Alternative to Amazon Web Service</a></p>
<p>Blockchain-based storage network, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/filecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Filecoin Network</a> has <a href="https://medium.com/@fw.services/announcing-fws-5e874e949fc6" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of its proprietary Filecoin Web Service (FWS) a cloud-based decentralized alternative to tech giants like the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/explaining-the-concept-of-aws-and-revealing-its-benefits-for-business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon Web Service</a> (AWS), and Microsoft Azure amongst others.</p>
<p>As announced by the protocol, the launch of FWS marks a very big milestone for its engineering team and the new protocol will be based on the Filecoin protocol. In describing the new service, Filecoin said its new FWS product is a compute and storage technology that is designed to work in a peer-to-peer manner.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Filecoin Web Services (FWS) launched this week to build an open-source alternative to AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure. 🔥 </p>
<p>FWS is a stack of compute, storage, and networking services that developers can use to build decentralized applications.<a href="https://t.co/kutvMbo8Li" target="_blank">https://t.co/kutvMbo8Li</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Filecoin (@Filecoin) <a href="https://twitter.com/Filecoin/status/1651564100663623680?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">April 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Owing to its deep understanding as a successful decentralized network, the Filecoin team said they recognized “that the cloud has a great developer experience, therefore it is an ambition of ours to achieve the benefits of cloud-level DX alongside the transparent and open source incentivization layers decentralized networks can provide”.</p>
<p>Users around the world are now getting by with Cloud Services as dominated by Google Cloud, AWS, and Microsoft Azure amongst others. These mainstream options work with the centralization of data centers. While they are reliable and can handle massive workloads, there are instances where the data centers associated with these giants crash and cause discomfort to users around the world.</p>
<h2>Showcasing the Filecoin FWS Difference</h2>
<p>In a bid to change the narrative and provide a relatively better experience for users around the world, Filecoin said its FWS product will come with a number of unique components that will generally aid the usage of the cloud service.</p>
<p>“This technology stack includes various components such as computing, storage, and networking resources that can be used by developers to build decentralized applications. The components provided by Filecoin Web Services are designed to be scalable, flexible, and secure, making the offering suitable for a wide range of use cases,” it said.</p>
<p>Among the components includes the Estuary which includes the Node and Dashboard with both serving unique purposes. The Estuary also has a number of APIs and SDKs that generally helps developers looking to build on top of the Filecoin protocol.</p>
<p>Filecoin Web Service is also engineered to harbor the Delta Technology Stack, a suite of open-source tools for creating and managing Filecoin storage network deals. While these are crucial components that help distinguish the FWS, the Delta Asset Manager, the Delta Importer, Edge-UR, Ptolemy, FWI and Storage Market also complement the underlying provisions.</p>
<h2>Offering Value for Money</h2>
<p>Filecoin is a very proactive blockchain protocol with innovative ideas to help expand its ecosystem. Prior to the launch of the FWS, the protocol <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-virtual-machine-live-mainnet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launched</a> its Filecoin Virtual Machine Compatibility, making it supportive of smart contracts.</p>
<p>This has helped turn the protocol into a smart contract hub that has accessibility to the biggest liquidity blockchain in the world. With the FWS, all Filecoin users can now get broader access to every product on offer by the protocol, thus enhancing their overall value addition.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/">Filecoin Launches FWS, Decentralized Alternative to Amazon Web Service</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-fws-decentralized-aws/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meme Coins that Are to Change Your Mind on Crypto Investing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Watson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[babydoge coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[big]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[big eyes coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pitbull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shiba inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252605</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/">Meme Coins that Are to Change Your Mind on Crypto Investing</a></p>
<p>Meme coins may be fun, but it’s obviously not just that. Tokens such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are clear proof that this kind of asset can have real gain potential</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/">Meme Coins that Are to Change Your Mind on Crypto Investing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/">Meme Coins that Are to Change Your Mind on Crypto Investing</a></p>
<p>Crypto investing has long been all about <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a>, but have you ever considered diversifying your portfolio? There are so many alternatives to these big-name cryptocurrencies that it’s hard to choose something, but let’s take it easy. We’ll focus on a specific type of digital coin that has managed to catch investors’ attention in a relatively short period of time &#8211; meme coins.</p>
<p>Meme coins entered the crypto market as mere jokes, no one being able to assess their real potential at that moment. But they have somehow managed to lure the crypto community, ballooned in value, and generate substantial returns on investment. So, meme coins are definitely purchased not only for entertainment value. They appear to be the very future of virtual currency based on the records observed in recent crypto history, but there are mixed opinions on this. No one could tell for sure if meme coins really have the power to change the crypto space forever (honestly, there is a slight chance for them to do so), but their popularity can’t be denied. Meme coins often climbed several thousand percent, generating significant returns and even turning some investors into millionaires in past bull runs, so they’re undoubtedly a thing. Moreover, experts advise diversifying your portfolio by adding some Bitcoin alternatives, including meme coins such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. Nonetheless, before rushing to purchase, ensure you look at these coins’ carefully, preferably on an exchange like <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/price/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, where you can also buy Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Without further ado, here are the meme coins you should watch out for in 2023.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin (DOGE)</h2>
<p>Dogecoin may need no introduction since it has been so hyped in recent years. It existed before Shiba Inu, Tamadoge, or other meme coin projects and is regarded as the first-ever meme coin and also one of the largest cryptocurrencies by market cap. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dogecoin</a> was released in 2013 as a comic relief to the chaotic situation at that time when many crypto projects copying Bitcoin’s source code appeared. Its developers, Billy Markus and Jackson Palmer, decided to fork the coin from Litecoin, with which it was initially associated, as a fun crypto asset. However, it remained underground for years until Elon Musk’s support announcement. Musk’s many tweets about the token have resulted in a surge in DOGE’s popularity and numerous investors taking the meme coin route. It also has a significant mainstream acceptance, especially since Elon Musk embraced it as a form of payment for his Tesla cars. GameStop, Newegg, and Twitch are other big-name businesses accepting Dogecoin.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu (SHIB)</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu is the second largest meme coin by market cap, having one of the most impressive prices in the crypto market. The meme coin is designed as a community-driven, decentralized alternative to DOGE, the first and biggest meme coin by market cap at the time being. Shiba Inu’s creator, Ryoshi, aimed to create a crypto project that brings truly remarkable returns on investments, and if we allude to the coin price’s evolution, we could say its intention has been fulfilled. Nonetheless, part of this success is attributed to Shiba’s compatibility with the second-generation blockchain, Ethereum, which has allowed its ecosystem to develop much more rapidly than Dogecoin. For instance, it has its own decentralized exchange, ShibaSwap, which enables users to join the DAO, stake SSLP, purchase NFTs, and add to the liquidity pool.</p>
<p>So, even if it uses a lighthearted and playful marketing approach, this project will likely overtake Dogecoin in the following years, even in 2023, if things keep going as they do now.</p>
<h2>The Baby of all Doges (BABYDOGE)</h2>
<p>BabyDoge Coin is, as expected, inspired by Dogecoin, but it aims to be something more than its bigger brother. Anonymous developers created the crypto project on the Binance Smart Chain and launched it on June 1, 2021. Although it was initially perceived as just another fish in the sea, BabyDoge Coin, or ‘the baby of all Doges’, has caught the public’s attention due to its approach toward transaction security. Its main purpose is to grow scarce over time by decreasing the diluted market capitalization. Thereby, each 5 percent of the fee of a transaction taking place over the BabyDoge ecosystem is sent to the user’s wallet. Interestingly, the token supply is continuously reduced utilizing various actions, including coin burning, reflection, and liquidity pair acquisition, which gives it a highly deflationary nature.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, BabyDoge Coin has a far more profound purpose: to support charity partners and help dogs in need. So, yes, a significant part of the money accumulated will contribute to saving dogs worldwide.</p>
<h2>Pitbull (PIT)</h2>
<p>Pitbull is another dog-themed cryptocurrency that, just like BabyDoge Coin, is built on the Binance Smart Chain. Nevertheless, Pitbull is believed to have a special trait: it uses an auto-staking mechanism to prize investors when transactions are performed using PIT. The PIT coin is a BEP-20 token considered an interesting approach to meme coins, and that’s probably one of the reasons it’s aimed to be given a higher purpose. However, what will happen with this crypto only remains to be seen, but you’d better watch out for it.</p>
<h2>Big Eyes Coin (BIG)</h2>
<p>Probably the cutest of them all, Big Eyes Coin is a meme coin project with massive prospects. It’s also different from the other meme coins, as it’s a cat-themed rather than dog-focused project. Big Eyes Coin managed to grab investors’ attention due to its strength during its presale and exciting narrative. It has raised over $30 million on presale, and that’s despite the bearish market threats. Many people may embark on the BIG journey because this presale status allows them to immediately sell the coins for profit when the project is released or just hold them long-term to maximize profits.</p>
<p>And to make things even spicier, Big Eyes has just launched its own mystery boxes, allowing buyers to earn even more rewards. Simply put, no one is going to lose this game, as every gain will be at least the purchaser’s money back.</p>
<p>Meme coins may be fun, but it’s obviously not just that. Tokens such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are clear proof that this kind of asset can have real gain potential, so don’t be surprised if others of the likes mentioned above get in the spotlight.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/">Meme Coins that Are to Change Your Mind on Crypto Investing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coins-crypto-investing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stays Stagnant with Strengthened DXY Negative Correlation as US GDP Slows</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dollar index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dxy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us gdp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252607</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/">Bitcoin Stays Stagnant with Strengthened DXY Negative Correlation as US GDP Slows</a></p>
<p>The US Commerce Department's recent shows that economic growth and GDP have slowed even as Bitcoin struggles to regain $30,000.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/">Bitcoin Stays Stagnant with Strengthened DXY Negative Correlation as US GDP Slows</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/">Bitcoin Stays Stagnant with Strengthened DXY Negative Correlation as US GDP Slows</a></p>
<p>The price of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) has remained relatively stagnant for about a week as the US gross domestic product (GDP) is slowing. Currently trading at $28,870 according to CoinMarketCap data, BTC has been unable to hit $30,000, last seen briefly on the 19th of April, and not seen in the first quarter of the year. This trend follows the GDP’s slowing in the same period.</p>
<p>An economic downturn characterized the year’s first quarter as several factors affecting growth. The US economy consistently struggled with increases in the interest rate, along with inflation. According to a Commerce Department <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/27/gdp-q1-2023-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> referenced by CNBC, the US GDP rose at an annualized rate of 1.1 in the first quarter. This figure is even worse than the 2% expected by economists the Dow Jones had surveyed. In comparison, the GDP for Q4 rose 2.6%, with the full-year 2022 GDP pulling a 2.1% rise. GDP is a metric used to measure the production of goods and services in a specified period.</p>
<p>The Commerce Department report also included figures on expenditure. The personal consumption expenditures price index beat the 3.7% estimate, reaching 4.2%. Consumer spending climbed 3.7%, with exports rising by 4.8%. However, gross private domestic investment crashed by 12.5%.</p>
<p>Speaking on the situation, LPL Financial’s chief economist, Jeffrey Roach, implied the possibility of a pivotal moment in the economy. Roach suggested that consumers may not be satisfied about the near future and may be slowly suspending consumption and spending. According to Roach:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The US economy is likely at an inflection point as consumer spending has softened in recent months. The backward nature of the GDP report is possibly misleading for markets as we know consumers were still spending in January but since March, have pulled back as consumers are getting more pessimistic about the future.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bitcoin, US GDP, and the Dollar Index</h2>
<p>Historically, the correlation between Bitcoin and the dollar index (DXY) has been negative. The DXY is an index that evaluates the dollar’s exchange rate in comparison with other major fiat currencies. Currently, this negative correlation has strengthened.</p>
<p>According to data from charting and market platform TradingView, the DXY and Bitcoin’s 90-day coefficient has hit -0.70, not seen in two months. This figure was -0.11 about four weeks ago. Except in specific scenarios, the native correlation has withstood for more than three years. The recent strengthening suggests a possible rise in the price of Bitcoin as the US GDP, along with other figures from the Commerce Department, shows disappointing numbers.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, some analysts are still considerably optimistic. Although consumer spending may be waning, the strong job market is still resilient enough to keep general economic activity optimum. However, most other analysts believe the US economy might see a recession later this year. The Federal Reserve has spiked interest rates by over 4.75% in a year. Although inflation fell to 5% last month, it is still much higher than the Fed’s 2% destination.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/">Bitcoin Stays Stagnant with Strengthened DXY Negative Correlation as US GDP Slows</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dxy-us-gdp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Crypto Custody Raises $36M in Funding Round Led by SBI Holdings</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChainLink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[link]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbi holdings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[standard chartered]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uni]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wrapped bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zodia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/">Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Crypto Custody Raises $36M in Funding Round Led by SBI Holdings</a></p>
<p>With the SBI investment, Zodia Custody will increase its Japan presence amid increased demand for digital assets from institutional investors in the country.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/">Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Crypto Custody Raises $36M in Funding Round Led by SBI Holdings</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/">Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Crypto Custody Raises $36M in Funding Round Led by SBI Holdings</a></p>
<p>Zodia Custody, an institutional-grade crypto asset custodial platform backed by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/standard-chartered/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Standard Chartered</a> in association with Northern Trust, has announced that it raised approximately $36 million led by Japanese financial conglomerate <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sbi-holdings/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SBI Holdings</a>. The London-headquartered crypto startup announced that the funding round also saw participation from SC Ventures, Standard Chartered’s venture arm. As a result, SBI Holdings is now the second-largest shareholder in Zodia Custody after Standard Chartered which owns the majority.</p>
<p>According to the startup, the funds are expected to be channeled to help increase its crypto token coverage and enhance its settlement product, Interchange, which protects clients&#8217; assets that are traded on exchanges. With the SBI investment, Zodia Custody will increase its Japan presence amid increased demand for digital assets from institutional investors in the country.</p>
<p>“The future direction of the digital asset ecosystem is clear,” CEO Julian Sawyer said. “As investors demand greater assurance and rigour, compliance is crucial to the future evolution of our sector.”</p>
<p>Moreover, there is a reported increase in demand for crypto assets in East Asia with Hong ready to enact digital asset’s friendly regulatory framework. Additionally, the European Union recently passed the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation, a comprehensive framework to regulate the issuance and servicing of most crypto assets in the region. As a result, the emergence of institutional-grade crypto custodial services is imminent before the next crypto bull market.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Zodia intends to expand its services to global markets as it waits for the United States to enact friendly crypto regulations.</p>
<p>“As an industry, there’s a challenge in terms of which regulatory body is managing crypto, and what assets are classed as securities,” Julian <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-26/standard-chartered-s-crypto-custodian-zodia-raises-36-million-from-japan-s-sbi?leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">added</a>. “We hope the US creates that clarity, but at the moment, it’s fair to say that it’s difficult to see what that will be in the next 12 to 18 months.”</p>
<h2>Zodia Custody and the Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Established in 2020, Zodia Custody is well-positioned to attract institutional investors from all over the world. More so now that there is an increased risk of the American banking system collapse. With a looming recession, forecasted to hit major markets by the second half of this year, digital assets have been viewed as a better hedge against inflation. Moreover, the industry is about a year away from the historical halving event that triggers major crypto bull markets.</p>
<p>Reportedly, Zodia intends to further venture into the second-largest digital asset market, Ethereum, through its staking program. Moreover, the Shanghai upgrade enabled withdrawals of staked ethers, thus welcoming more institutional investors.</p>
<p>Currently, Zodia offers custody services for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ether</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Litecoin</a>, Chainlink, Uniswap, Wrapped Bitcoin, and USD Coin.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/">Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Crypto Custody Raises $36M in Funding Round Led by SBI Holdings</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zodia-crypto-custody-36m-funding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merck Q1 2023 Report Shows Revenue Drop as COVID Treatment Sales Crash, MRK Stock Down 1%</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[merck]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[merck stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pfizer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Seagen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/">Merck Q1 2023 Report Shows Revenue Drop as COVID Treatment Sales Crash, MRK Stock Down 1%</a></p>
<p>Affected by reduced demand for Covid drug Molnupiravir, Merck has published reduced revenue figures according to its Q1 2023 report.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/">Merck Q1 2023 Report Shows Revenue Drop as COVID Treatment Sales Crash, MRK Stock Down 1%</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/">Merck Q1 2023 Report Shows Revenue Drop as COVID Treatment Sales Crash, MRK Stock Down 1%</a></p>
<p>Multinational pharmaceutical giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/merck-co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Merck &amp; Co Inc</a> (NYSE: MRK) has released its Q1 2023 report. The company’s figures show a reduction in revenue due to several factors, including a plunge in sales. According to published figures, Merck’s Q1 revenue is 9% lower than reported in Q1 2022. This is mainly because its Molnupiravir Covid treatment drug has seen a considerable drop in demand. At the press time, MRK stock is 1% down, trading at $112.23.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230427005188/en/Merck-Announces-First-Quarter-2023-Financial-Results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, Merck pulled in $14.5 billion in total revenue for the quarter, a $1.5 billion reduction from the first quarter of last year. However, Merck said its revenue climbed 11%, outside of the Molnupiravir sales crash. In the first three months of 2023, Merck sold $392 million’s worth of the antiviral treatment. This is a heavy 88% crash compared to the $3.2 billion recorded for the same period in 2022. According to Merck, this plunge was largely felt in Australia, Japan, the US, and the UK.</p>
<p>Molnupiravir was one of the first drugs approved for the treatment of COVID. In 2021, the UK’s Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-mrk-stock-up-1-uk-regulator-approves-its-covid-19-pill-molnupiravir/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">approved</a> the drug under the name Lagevrio. In the same year, the FDA also issued an emergency use authorization (EUA) for Molnupiravir. Following the approval, Merck said it would deliver up to 10 million courses that year, and more than 20 million last year.</p>
<h2>Merck Q1 2023 Figures</h2>
<p>Merck’s total revenue of $14.49 billion beat the $13.78 billion expected by analysts surveyed by Refinitiv. The analysts also expected adjusted earnings per share (EPS) of $1.32, lower than the $1.40 reported. For net income, Merck said it pulled in $2.82 billion ($1.11 per share), much lower than the $4.31 billion ($1.70) the company reported for Q1 2022.</p>
<p>The New Jersey-based pharma giant has now raised its forecast for 2023. In early February, Merck’s sales guidance was $57.2 to $58.7 billion, now slightly changed to the $57.7 billion to $58.9 billion range. This new figure accounts for $1 billion in expected Molnupiravir sales. In addition to raised sales, Merck increased its 2023 adjusted earnings outlook to between $6.88 and $7.00 per share. This is higher than the earlier $6.80 to $6.95 forecast.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Merck’s official report specifies that the projected outlook does not accommodate any impact from its planned acquisition of biotech firm Prometheus Biosciences. The acquisition should finalize sometime in Q3 2023.</p>
<h2>Merck and Seagen</h2>
<p>The expected deal with Prometheus Biosciences is not Merck’s first attempt at acquiring a biotech company. Last year, Merck <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-talks-buy-biotech-seagen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">entered advanced talks</a> with biotech and drug manufacturing firm Seagen Inc (NASDAQ: SGEN). The deal was reportedly worth $40 billion at approximately $200 per Seagen share. Unfortunately, the deal fell through for antitrust reasons. There were more than a few concerns that the deal would attract an antitrust investigation from the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). As of last month, Pfizer (NYSE: PFE), Pfizer is now <a href="https://www.pfizer.com/news/press-release/press-release-detail/pfizer-invests-43-billion-battle-cancer" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">set to acquire Seagen</a> for $43 billion or $229 per share. Pfizer said it hopes to advance the battle against cancer through Seagen.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/">Merck Q1 2023 Report Shows Revenue Drop as COVID Treatment Sales Crash, MRK Stock Down 1%</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/merck-q1-2023-report-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>False Trigger about Mt. Gox Bitcoin Wallet Transfer Tanks BTC Price to $27,000 but It Recovers Fast</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mt gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/">False Trigger about Mt. Gox Bitcoin Wallet Transfer Tanks BTC Price to $27,000 but It Recovers Fast</a></p>
<p>Arkham Intelligence issued a clarification that a bug caused to send the alerts regarding Mt. Gox and Us government selling Bitcoin. The BTC price recovered fast after the clarification. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/">False Trigger about Mt. Gox Bitcoin Wallet Transfer Tanks BTC Price to $27,000 but It Recovers Fast</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/">False Trigger about Mt. Gox Bitcoin Wallet Transfer Tanks BTC Price to $27,000 but It Recovers Fast</a></p>
<p>Over the last 48 hours, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> price witnessed massive volatility sending jitters across the entire investor community. Earlier this week on Tuesday, the Bitcoin price shot up all the way to $30,000 following the news of a crisis-like situation at the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/first-republic-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">First Republic Bank</a>. But during Wednesday&#8217;s trading session, Bitcoin faced strong selling pressure with the BTC price tanking all the way to $27,000. The BTC price fall came as news circulated that the US government has liquidated a significant portion of its remaining Mt. Gox Bitcoin (BTC) holdings. This pushed the market into a panic-like situation leading to strong volatility and market instability.</p>
<p>Citing an alert from Arkham Intelligence, a popular crypto news account on Twitter &#8211; DB (tier10k) &#8211; tweeted that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/mt-gox/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mt. Gox</a> and US government wallets have been selling in heavy numbers.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">[DB] Mt Gox and US Govt Wallets Making Transactions: Arkham Alert</p>
<p>&mdash; db (@tier10k) <a href="https://twitter.com/tier10k/status/1651317391626846214?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">April 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>This led to a frenzy of sell orders for Bitcoin in the open market thereby dragging its price down. Soon as the news regarding the notifications from Arkham Intelligence spread in the market, it issued a clarification on the matter.</p>
<h2>Arkham Intelligence Issues Clarification</h2>
<p>Through its official Twitter handle, Arkham Intelligence issued a clarification noting that DB has set two alerts on BTC transactions of more than $10,000 while naming those alerts as &#8220;Mt. Gox&#8221; and &#8220;US Gov&#8221;.</p>
<p>Arkham said that DB inferred those certain Bitcoin addresses were transacting based on the labels that he had himself set. In a message, Arkham <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1651366459547713537" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have conducted an investigation of the DB Alert situation, and determined that the Arkham alerts were sent accurately in this case. DB set two alerts on all Bitcoin transactions above $10k USD, with no counterparties set, then named the alerts “Mt Gox” and “US Gov”. When we fixed a bug causing us to not send alerts on configs like this, he then correctly received many alerts based on his parameters. No one received inaccurate alerts, they simply began receiving the alerts they had previously set.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>&#8220;Neither the alert nor the tweet could have caused the sharp BTC price drop today, as the drop occurred between 19:17 and 20:01 UTC, and the alerts and tweet were sent afterward at 20:07 UTC and 20:08 UTC respectively,&#8221; added the company.</p>
<p>Soon as Arkham issued the clarification, Bitcoin (BTC) is once again back on the recovery path and is currently trading at $29,000 with a market cap of $562 billion. Market analysts expect that the BTC price can continue to rise from here onwards.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/">False Trigger about Mt. Gox Bitcoin Wallet Transfer Tanks BTC Price to $27,000 but It Recovers Fast</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/false-mt-gox-bitcoin-wallet-transfer-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Comcast Shares Up 3% after Impressive Q1 2023 Report</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cnbc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comcast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comcast corporation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comcast stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nbcuniversal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/">Comcast Shares Up 3% after Impressive Q1 2023 Report</a></p>
<p>The company said its Peacock subscribers grew by more than 60% or 22 million compared year-over-year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/">Comcast Shares Up 3% after Impressive Q1 2023 Report</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/">Comcast Shares Up 3% after Impressive Q1 2023 Report</a></p>
<p>American telecommunications and media giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/comcast/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Comcast Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: CMCSA) has shared a better-than-expected first quarter (Q1) performance report. <a href="https://www.cmcsa.com/news-releases/news-release-details/comcast-reports-1st-quarter-2023-results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">According</a> to the company’s report, it recorded a total revenue of $29.69 billion for the quarter, a figure that is larger than the $29.3 billion expected from Refinitiv’s analysts.</p>
<p>Comcast’s history dates back to the 1960s and the company has evolved to be one of the most dominant providers of mainstream telecom services in the United States of today. As a media giant, Comcast is also the parent company of media house CNBC which is a part of the firm’s content distribution subsidiary NBCUniversal.</p>
<h2>Comcast Q1 Report Highlights</h2>
<p>The company said its Earnings Per Share (EPS) as adjusted came in at 92 cents, a peg that surpasses the 82 cents that was projected by Refinitiv analysts. That Comcast beat its earnings estimates does not necessarily imply that the company had a comparatively stellar quarter. The firm recorded a significant plunge in its revenue which came in at 4%. The firm reported $31.01 billion in revenue this same period last year.</p>
<p>The company attributed the 4% drop to the comparative hedge it recorded in the first quarter of 2022 when it broadcasted both the Super Bowl and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-plans-digital-yuan-olympics-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Beijing Olympics</a> event respectively. In addition to this, Comcast noted that its broadband business saw a 21,000 decline in the number of total subscribers. This loss, however, was compensated for by the growth in its business clients.</p>
<p>The company said its Peacock subscribers grew by more than 60% or 22 million compared year-over-year. Comcast revealed that its revenue for the Peacock unit grew as much as 45% to $685 million. This growth was notably negated by the more than $700 million it printed in losses for the quarter.</p>
<p>&#8220;We delivered strong first quarter results as our team executed exceptionally well,&#8221; said Brian L. Roberts, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Comcast Corporation. &#8220;We grew Adjusted EBITDA and Adjusted EPS, and generated a significant amount of free cash flow. We accomplished all of this while continuing to invest in future growth initiatives. Also, importantly, we had solid revenue growth in our high-margin connectivity businesses, while increasing our Peacock subscribers more than 60% year-over-year.”</p>
<h2>Future Outlook</h2>
<p>While Comcast is not oblivious to the realities of the changing climes in some of its business segments, particularly broadband and cable TV, the company is still very optimistic about its prospects for the future.</p>
<p>Roberts noted that the company has great momentum and that it will look to capitalize on the growth of key units like Studios which re-introduced the Super Mario Bros game title.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Comcast shares are changing hands at a price of $37.93, up by 3.86%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/">Comcast Shares Up 3% after Impressive Q1 2023 Report</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/comcast-shares-q1-2023-report/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO CZ Is on Bloomberg’s ‘New Finance Rich List’</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/">Binance CEO CZ Is on Bloomberg’s &#8216;New Finance Rich List&#8217;</a></p>
<p>While Bloomberg says the Binance head is worth $28.2 billion, Forbes says Zhao’s net worth as of April 27 is $10.5 billion.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/">Binance CEO CZ Is on Bloomberg’s &#8216;New Finance Rich List&#8217;</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/">Binance CEO CZ Is on Bloomberg’s &#8216;New Finance Rich List&#8217;</a></p>
<p>According to Bloomberg, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> CEO Changpeng Zhao, also called <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>, is one of the “25 financial titans” that amassed their wealth through the business of lending, trading, or investing money. The <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2023-new-finance-rich-list/?ll_push_args=%7B%22utm_source%22:%22push%22,%22utm_medium%22:%22notification%22%7D&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> explains that computer-driven trading companies are the backers of the new generation of ultrarich, to which the Binance chief belongs.</p>
<h2>Binance CEO CZ Makes New Finance Rich List</h2>
<p>Bloomberg stated that CZ is worth $28.2 billion, and the CEO made the bulk of his wealth from Binance, which he founded in 2017. He worked on trading systems before he created the exchange. In Shanghai, he was introduced to the world’s first cryptocurrency by crypto entrepreneur and Bitcoin proponent Bobby Lee.</p>
<p>Since its inception, the crypto exchange has gathered more than 120 million users globally and has become the largest crypto company by trading volume. Binance controls more than half of the entire crypto market, and its estimated annual revenue is around $12 billion as of April 5. However, the largest exchange has been under intense regulatory scrutiny following the dramatic collapse of FTX last November. There is an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cftc-binance-legal-battle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ongoing legal battle</a> between the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) and Binance and its CEO, CZ. The Commission charged the exchange and its boss for allegedly helping clients mask their locations to evade trading restrictions. The regulator also accused the company of failing to implement effective compliance policies. However, Zhao responded that the company “does not agree with the characterization of many of the issues alleged in the complaint&#8221;.</p>
<p>While Bloomberg says the Binance head is worth $28.2 billion, Forbes says Zhao’s net worth as of April 27 is $10.5 billion. Apart from CZ, who made the list of Bloomberg’s richest men in finance, the CEO of hedge fund company Citadel was also mentioned. Ken Griffin was the highest ranked, with a net worth of $35 billion. He also launched Citadel Securities, which was valued at $22 billion after a funding round in January 2022 and handles around 40% of all US retail trading volume. On the other hand, the hedge fund had $59 billion in AUM as of last year December.</p>
<h2>Rich Men in Finance</h2>
<p>Other crypto entrepreneurs on the list, besides Binance CZ and Griffin, are Checkout.com CEO Guillaume Pousaz and Susquehanna founder Jeff Yass, whose valuation is estimated at $33.1 billion. On the other hand, Pousaz is worth $6.4 billion after its company reportedly lost its bet on the crypto industry due to the massive investor outflows following FTX’s demise.</p>
<p>More personalities in the rich men club include Uday Kotak of Kotak Mahindra Bank, Stan Druckenmiller, Chelsea football club chairman Todd Boehly and the co-founders of Two Sigma Investments, John Overdeck and David Siegel, etc.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/">Binance CEO CZ Is on Bloomberg’s &#8216;New Finance Rich List&#8217;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-finance-rich-list/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CoinList Set to List SUI as Mainnet Launch Date Approaches</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[casper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinlist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sui Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=252569</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/">CoinList Set to List SUI as Mainnet Launch Date Approaches</a></p>
<p>The Sui Network is adjudged to be a protocol that makes digital asset ownership fast, private, secure, and accessible to everyone.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/">CoinList Set to List SUI as Mainnet Launch Date Approaches</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/">CoinList Set to List SUI as Mainnet Launch Date Approaches</a></p>
<p>American token launchpad and trading platform CoinList is set to list SUI, the native token of the much anticipated Sui Blockchain network. As <a href="https://blog.coinlist.co/sui-network-sui-launching-soon-on-coinlist/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> by the trading platform, the listing will take place on May 3 which will coincide with the scheduled date that the Sui network will be launching its mainnet.</p>
<p>“Our mission at CoinList is to empower builders at any stage in their journey, and connect them with high quality early adopters of their products,” the CoinList announcement reads. “Today, we are excited to announce that CoinList will be listing SUI, the native token of the highly anticipated Sui Blockchain, on Day 1 of its launch.”</p>
<p>According to CoinList, it will be offering the trading of the token free for the first 48 hours after its listing on CoinList Pro. The trading platform also noted that the free trading will apply to all of the SUI token pairs and users staking SUI will also get a 1 month free to enable them to get more from their investment.</p>
<p>CoinList is known as one of the most functional token listing arenas in the industry. The launchpad has helped push out some of the most innovative blockchain protocols into the limelight. Some of its listed projects include but are not limited to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> (SOL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/filecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Filecoin</a> (FIL), Casper (CSPR) and Mina, recognized as the world’s lightest blockchain.</p>
<p>While the Sui protocol is designed to have a comprehensive embrace from users and developers in different jurisdictions, the token listing on CoinList is limited to users from specific countries. In its announcement, CoinList said users from the United States and Canada will not be able to participate in the trading and staking support it plans to give the Sui network.</p>
<p>This, it noted, is based on its own terms of service and is hinged on the regulatory provisions from these regions.</p>
<h2>Sui Network: Changing the Blockchain Functionality</h2>
<p>The Sui Blockchain is the brainchild of Mystem Labs, a Web 3.0 startup that is made up of mainly Meta Alumni. The protocol is based on the Move Programming Language that was designed by Mysten Labs and is known to power a highly functional and secure blockchain network.</p>
<p>In highlighting its features, the Sui Network is adjudged to be a protocol that makes digital asset ownership fast, private, secure, and accessible to everyone. With scalability and high cost still an issue for existing blockchain outfits, the Sui Network is aiming to claim a high market share owing to its ability to mitigate these common challenges.</p>
<p>Users will need the SUI coin for different utilities anchored on the Sui Network. For one, it will serve as the utility token for the blockchain network. Additionally, the token will aid in rewarding validators participating in storage of on-chain object related data while also serving as the de facto governance token in the network.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/">CoinList Set to List SUI as Mainnet Launch Date Approaches</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinlist-list-sui/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4934 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1359792 metric#prefetches=234 metric#store-reads=23 metric#store-writes=19 metric#store-hits=241 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=104.26 metric#ms-cache=7.34 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1791 metric#ms-cache-ratio=7.0 -->