<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:35:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance launches regulated crypto platform in Kazakhstan</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-launches-regulated-crypto-platform-in-kazakhstan/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-launches-regulated-crypto-platform-in-kazakhstan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kazakhstan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-launches-regulated-crypto-platform-in-kazakhstan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Kazakhstan was officially announced on June 20, 2023 with government and banking industry representatives present. The platform will allow users to buy and sell crypto with fiat, access spot trading, and conversions. Despite the local platform&#8217;s launch, users in Kazakhstan will still be able to use the global Binance.com. Binance has unveiled a regulated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-launches-regulated-crypto-platform-in-kazakhstan/">Binance launches regulated crypto platform in Kazakhstan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance Kazakhstan was officially announced on June 20, 2023 with government and banking industry representatives present.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The platform will allow users to buy and sell crypto with fiat, access spot trading, and conversions.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Despite the local platform&rsquo;s launch, users in Kazakhstan will still be able to use the global Binance.com.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> has unveiled a regulated digital asset platform in Kazakhstan, just days after the crypto behemoth <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/">exited</a> the Dutch market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">An <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-launches-a-regulated-digital-asset-platform-in-kazakhstan-7318383218004275432" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> on the Binance blog on Wednesday noted that the move into the Central Asia nation comes after the exchange secured a license from the AIFC Financial Services Authority (AFSA).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exchange secured the approval in October last year, which allowed it to offer crypto custodial services and operate a digital asset platform at the Astana International Financial Center (AIFC).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Binance Kazakhstan to offer custody and trading among other services</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The official launch of the Binance Kazakhstan platform was made on June 20, 2023, Binance noted in the blog post. Present during the unveiling were government officials and banking industry representatives from the country. Binance execs of the local digital asset platform were also present.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the news release, the new platform will provide several services, including exchange and conversion, fiat deposits and withdrawals, crypto custody, and exchange trading. Binance Kazakhstan supports deposits and withdrawals via bank cards and bank transfer, with these available through the Freedom Finance Bank.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Asset Turysov, Kazakhstan&rsquo;s Vice Minister of Digital Development, Innovation and Aerospace Industry, said the country was focused on promoting the interaction between second-tier banks, AIFC and crypto exchanges. As such, the National Bank of Kazakhstan, the Financial Monitoring Agency of the Republic of Kazakhstan, and the Agency for Regulation and Development of the Financial Market are all involved in this initiative.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Turysov also lauded Binance&rsquo;s role in the development of the country&rsquo;s crypto industry, including the development of a legislative framework for crypto regulation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-sec-sues-binance-and-coinbase-but-bitcoin-remains-above-26k/">recently sued</a> by the US Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) and announced its exit from the Canadian market citing regulatory constraints.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-launches-regulated-crypto-platform-in-kazakhstan/">Binance launches regulated crypto platform in Kazakhstan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-launches-regulated-crypto-platform-in-kazakhstan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fed Chair Powell: ‘we do see payment stablecoins as a form of money’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-chair-powell-stablecoins-form-of-money/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=143830</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Powell testified before the House Financial Services Committee today. He discussed a range of topics around digital assets on Wednesday. Bitcoin surpassed the $30,000 level today for the first in two months. Cryptocurrencies seem to have some &#8220;staying power&#8221; as an asset class, says Jerome Powell &#8211; Chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve. Fed should [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-chair-powell-stablecoins-form-of-money/">Fed Chair Powell: ‘we do see payment stablecoins as a form of money’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Powell testified before the House Financial Services Committee today.</li>
<li>He discussed a range of topics around digital assets on Wednesday.</li>
<li>Bitcoin surpassed the $30,000 level today for the first in two months.</li>
</ul>
<p>Cryptocurrencies seem to have some &ldquo;staying power&rdquo; as an asset class, says Jerome Powell &ndash; Chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve.</p>
<h2>Fed should have a role in crypto legislation</h2>
<p>On Wednesday, he also argued that the central bank should have a role to play in the regulatory framework being developed for stablecoins.</p>
<blockquote><p>We do see payment stablecoins as a form of money. The ultimate source of credibility in money is central bank. We believe it would be appropriate to have a robust federal role.</p></blockquote>
<p>Chair Powell made these remarks in his <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/06/21/feds-powell-on-crypto-would-be-a-mistake-to-leave-fed-with-weak-role-on-stablecoins.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">testimony</a> before the House Financial Services Committee today.</p>
<p>Interestingly, his statement signalled acceptance of crypto assets even though the SEC has recently filed a lawsuit against both <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sec-sues-binance-and-cz-for-breaking-us-securities-rules/">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-102" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a>.</p>
<h2>CBDC is not likely any time soon</h2>
<p>Chair Powell confirmed this morning that members of the Federal Reserve have held discussions with lawmakers on crypto legislation.</p>
<blockquote><p>Leaving us [U.S. Federal Reserve] with a weak role and allowing a lot of private money creation at the state level would be a mistake.</p></blockquote>
<p>In his testimony, he also said that a central bank digital currency or a &ldquo;CBDC&rdquo; is unlikely any time soon. His remarks arrive shortly after the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1fa66c1e-f485-4220-9ef5-fb2e391469f1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FOMC</a> skipped a rate hike for the first time since March of 2022.</p>
<p>Also on Wednesday, bitcoin surpassed the $30,000 level and technicals suggest it could go further up to $34,000, as per Glassnode &ndash; an on-chain data provider (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-technical-breakout-suggests-btc-rally-to-34k/">find out more</a>).</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fed-chair-powell-stablecoins-form-of-money/">Fed Chair Powell: ‘we do see payment stablecoins as a form of money’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance announces zero-fee for TrueUSD (TUSD) trading pairs</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-zero-fee-for-trueusd-tusd-trading-pairs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-zero-fee-for-trueusd-tusd-trading-pairs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Initially, Binance had announced zero-fee only for BTC-TUSD trading pair. Binance has now announced that the zero-fee will apply for all TUSD trading pairs. The move comes amid the regulatory backlash the exchange has received from regulatory authorities around the world. A new zero-fee promotion for TrueUSD (TUSD) trading pairs has been announced by Binance. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-zero-fee-for-trueusd-tusd-trading-pairs/">Binance announces zero-fee for TrueUSD (TUSD) trading pairs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Initially, Binance had announced zero-fee only for BTC-TUSD trading pair.</li>
<li>Binance has now announced that the zero-fee will apply for all TUSD trading pairs.</li>
<li>The move comes amid the regulatory backlash the exchange has received from regulatory authorities around the world.</li>
</ul>
<p>A new zero-fee promotion for TrueUSD (TUSD) trading pairs has been announced by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>. The tactical move, set to begin on June 30, 2023, is expected to stimulate the dynamics of the cryptocurrency market by opening up its fee-free trading opportunity to a larger audience.</p>
<p>This is an expansion of the prior promotion, which only applied to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> &ndash; TUSD pair, to introduce zero maker fees on all TUSD spot and margin trading pairs. Additionally, the exchange has also extended the BUSD zero-maker fee promotion for an additional six months until the end of 2023, Binance has shown its dedication to making trading more affordable.</p>
<h2>TrueUSD market activity and liquidity</h2>
<p>The bold move made by Binance is anticipated to have a significant effect. The expansion of TUSD&rsquo;s fee-free trading and its integration into Binance&rsquo;s platform is expected to increase market activity and liquidity, creating a more welcoming trading environment for the entire crypto community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The TUSD token, issued by the cryptocurrency company ArchBlock, formerly known as TrustToken, is currently the fifth-largest dollar-pegged stablecoin on the market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Binance navigating regulatory handles</h2>
<p>Regulatory scrutiny and legal issues have created turbulence for Binance&rsquo;s aggressive market expansion. Binance and its CEO, Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao, have recently been the target of several lawsuits, including ones from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>These difficulties have been made even more difficult by the fact that French authorities are looking into the company for possible &ldquo;aggravated money laundering.&rdquo; Binance also made the decision to leave the Netherlands after failing to obtain the necessary operating license and also revoked its operating permits in the UK. It has also chosen to cancel its registration with Cyprus&rsquo; securities regulator.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-announces-zero-fee-for-trueusd-tusd-trading-pairs/">Binance announces zero-fee for TrueUSD (TUSD) trading pairs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CleanSpark acquires two Bitcoin mining facilities for $9.3 million</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cleanspark-acquires-two-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3-million/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cleanspark-acquires-two-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3-million/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/cleanspark-acquires-two-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3-million/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CleanSpark will complete the $9.3 million all-cash deal for the two turnkey Bitcoin mining facilities this week. The facilities in Dalton, Georgia, will host 6,000 Antminer S19 XPs and S19J Pro+ rigs. CleanSpark CEO Zach Bradford says the deal puts the miner on track to reach its year-end hashrate target of 16 EH/s CleanSpark (NASDAQ: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cleanspark-acquires-two-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3-million/">CleanSpark acquires two Bitcoin mining facilities for $9.3 million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">CleanSpark will complete the $9.3 million all-cash deal for the two turnkey Bitcoin mining facilities this week.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The facilities in Dalton, Georgia, will host 6,000 Antminer S19 XPs and S19J Pro+ rigs.</li>
<li dir="ltr">CleanSpark CEO Zach Bradford says the deal puts the miner on track to reach its year-end hashrate target of 16 EH/s</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">CleanSpark (NASDAQ: CLSK), one of the largest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> mining firms in the world, has announced the acquisition of two BTC mining campuses in Dalton, Georgia.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company said in a <a href="https://www.cleanspark.com/blog/cleanspark-to-acquire-turnkey-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3m-in-all-cash-deal/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> that it had struck a definitive agreement to purchase the two turnkey facilities for $9.3 million, an all-cash deal expected to close later this week.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">CleanSpark targets 16 EH/s by end of year</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to the miner, the two campuses are set to host over 6,000 Antminer S19 XPs and S19J Pro+s, and will see the mining giant add just under 1 exahashes per second (EH/s) to its hashrate.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>This acquisition ensures that we have more than enough infrastructure to reach our year-end target of 16 EH/s. It also continues to position us as one of the most power-efficient miners on an energy-per-hashrate basis,</em>&rdquo; Zach Bradford, CEO of CleanSpark, said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CleanSpark&rsquo;s latest purchase adds to multiple previous buys and acquisitions secured over the past several months. After purchasing 20,000 Antminer S19j Pro+ machines for $43.6 million in February, the company added 45,000 Antminer S19 XP units worth $144.9 million in April. In May, it bought 12,500 Antminer S19 XP rigs.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CLSK traded at $4.86, up 10% on the day on Wednesday. The crypto stock has rallied more than 140% in 2023 and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-bitcoin-miner-stock-cleanspark-h-c-wainwright/">analysts</a> expect it to reach $12.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cleanspark-acquires-two-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3-million/">CleanSpark acquires two Bitcoin mining facilities for $9.3 million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cleanspark-acquires-two-bitcoin-mining-facilities-for-9-3-million/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Labs, CoinFund lead $10M round for Cosmos network Neutron</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-coinfund-lead-10m-round-for-cosmos-network-neutron/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-coinfund-lead-10m-round-for-cosmos-network-neutron/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-coinfund-lead-10m-round-for-cosmos-network-neutron/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Labs and CoinFund led several venture firms in raising a $10 million round for Neutron. Neutron is a Cosmos-based smart contracts platform that launched its mainnet in May. The platform will use the funds to further its development and adoption across the ecosystem. Crypto exchange Binance&#8217;s venture capital arm Binance Labs and Web3-focused venture [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-coinfund-lead-10m-round-for-cosmos-network-neutron/">Binance Labs, CoinFund lead $10M round for Cosmos network Neutron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance Labs and CoinFund led several venture firms in raising a $10 million round for Neutron.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Neutron is a Cosmos-based smart contracts platform that launched its mainnet in May.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The platform will use the funds to further its development and adoption across the ecosystem.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto exchange Binance&rsquo;s venture capital arm Binance Labs and Web3-focused venture firm CoinFund co-led a $10 million funding round for Cosmos-based smart contracts infrastructure Neutron.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The seed funding round also attracted the participation of Delphi Ventures, LongHash and Nomad, according to details of the funding round reported by <em>The Block</em>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Neutron is a cross-chain smart contract blockchain that uses CosmWasm, a computational feature in the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/cosmos/">Cosmos</a> ecosystem that allows for cost-effective creation and deployment of dApps. The platform, whose mainnet launch was in May this year, will use the funding to enhance its software development and promote further adoption as demand for layer-2 solutions and appchains grows.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With its Replicated Security layer, Neutron makes it easy for developers to build consumer chains, the first in the Cosmos ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Neutron Coin (NTRN), the blockchain&rsquo;s native token, traded at around $0.00088964.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-coinfund-lead-10m-round-for-cosmos-network-neutron/">Binance Labs, CoinFund lead $10M round for Cosmos network Neutron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-coinfund-lead-10m-round-for-cosmos-network-neutron/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>KAVA price spikes as USDT prepares to launch on Kava blockchain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-spikes-as-usdt-prepares-to-launch-on-kava-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-spikes-as-usdt-prepares-to-launch-on-kava-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos ATOM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-spikes-as-usdt-prepares-to-launch-on-kava-blockchain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At press time, KAVA was trading at $0.9214, up 13.27% over the last 24 hours. The first Kava-based USDT will be released on July 3, 2023. Since Kava is built on Cosmos, the move will also make USDT liquidity to be available to Cosmos users. USDT stablecoin is scheduled to go live on the Kava [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-spikes-as-usdt-prepares-to-launch-on-kava-blockchain/">KAVA price spikes as USDT prepares to launch on Kava blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>At press time, KAVA was trading at $0.9214, up 13.27% over the last 24 hours.</li>
<li>The first Kava-based USDT will be released on July 3, 2023.</li>
<li>Since Kava is built on Cosmos, the move will also make USDT liquidity to be available to Cosmos users.</li>
</ul>
<p>USDT stablecoin is scheduled to go live on the Kava blockchain in the coming month. This will make Kava the next blockchain supported by Tether Limited, the company that issues the biggest stablecoin USDT, according to an official announcement made by the company.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Tether USDt comes to the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cosmos?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Cosmos</a> ecosystem! We have chosen to deploy USDt on <a href="https://twitter.com/KAVA_CHAIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@KAVA_CHAIN</a>, the gateway to the Cosmos ecosystem. USDt on KAVA is launching on July 3rd.</p>
<p>Read more <a href="https://t.co/myCkHhHHud">https://t.co/myCkHhHHud</a> <a href="https://t.co/YQFgO5381m">pic.twitter.com/YQFgO5381m</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tether (@Tether_to) <a href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1671445095965499393?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The new release will allow the community of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cosmos/what-is-cosmos/">Cosmos (ATOM)</a>, a cutting-edge cross-chain ecosystem, to access USDT liquidity. Kava, Cosmos&rsquo; flagship network, recently underwent a significant upgrade.</p>
<h2>Kava and Tether collaboration</h2>
<p>Following the development, the Kava (KAVA) team emphasized that it combines the most impressive features of the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) with Cosmos SDK&rsquo;s speed, low transaction fees, and interoperability. Kava released the Kava 13 upgrade to increase throughput and speed.</p>
<p>The new release has Paolo Ardoino, CTO at <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether</a>, excited and he believes it will be crucial to USDT&rsquo;s development and adoption of different liquidity solutions. Paolo said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re thrilled to be launching USD&#8366; on Kava, offering its strong community access to the world&rsquo;s first, most stable, most trusted, and most widely used stablecoin. The Kava network is a unique and widely followed blockchain with a robust track record of four years with zero security issues, which is essential to protecting USD&#8366; users. Together, we aim to reshape the future of decentralized finance, fostering a robust and inclusive ecosystem that benefits users worldwide.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Besides Kava, USDT has been launched on several other blockchains including <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, Solana, Algorand, Tron, Eos, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/near-protocol/what-is-near-protocol/">Near Protocol</a>, and Avalanche blockchains as well as on Omni solutions and Liquid Network.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-spikes-as-usdt-prepares-to-launch-on-kava-blockchain/">KAVA price spikes as USDT prepares to launch on Kava blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kava-price-spikes-as-usdt-prepares-to-launch-on-kava-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX partners with LIV Golf League team Majesticks GC</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-liv-golf-league-team-majesticks-gc/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-liv-golf-league-team-majesticks-gc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-liv-golf-league-team-majesticks-gc/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OKX has become the first global sponsor and Web3 partner of Majesticks GC. The partnership will see OKX and the golf team collaborate on fan engagement projects meant to improve experiences. OKX has struck some key partnerships in the sports industry, including with the McLaren F1 Team and European soccer giants Manchester City. OKX, one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-liv-golf-league-team-majesticks-gc/">OKX partners with LIV Golf League team Majesticks GC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">OKX has become the first global sponsor and Web3 partner of Majesticks GC.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The partnership will see OKX and the golf team collaborate on fan engagement projects meant to improve experiences.</li>
<li dir="ltr">OKX has struck some key partnerships in the sports industry, including with the McLaren F1 Team and European soccer giants Manchester City.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-review-a-one-stop-platform-for-crypto-defi-dapps-nfts-and-gamefi/#:~:text=Final%20Verdict,services%20within%20the%20crypto%20industry.">OKX</a>, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the market and a leading Web3 company, has announced a sponsorship deal with Majesticks GC, one of the teams in the new LIV Golf League.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of the partnership, OKX becomes Majesticks GC&rsquo;s first global and Web3 sponsor. The crypto echange and the golf team will collaborate on efforts to increase fan engagement and experiences, according to a <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/okx-first-official-global-sponsor-of-Majesticks-GC-golf-team" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>press release</u></a> published on Wednesday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Having been an OKX Ambassador, I know that the company brings passion, technological expertise and creative thinking to everything it does. That&rsquo;s why I&rsquo;m so excited to welcome OKX as the first official global sponsor for Majesticks GC</em>,&rdquo; Majesticks Team co-captain Ian Poulter said in a statement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The partnership with the golf team adds to OKX&rsquo;s partnership forays into the sporting ecosystem. The crypto platform already boasts major deals with the McLaren F1 Team and Manchester City, the current EPL and Champions League winners.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Golf captivates people around the world</em>,&rdquo; Haider Rafique, Chief Marketing Officer at OKX, said. &ldquo;<em>However, its reach can be magnified if we dare to think big about fan engagement, inclusivity and truly unique partnership activations that use Web3 to amaze and inspire. This is what we&rsquo;re shooting for with Majesticks GC, a top-tier team in the LIV Golf League that exemplifies our values and ambitions</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">OKX will work with Majesticks on a number of exciting developments aimed at achieving the above goals, Rafique added.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-liv-golf-league-team-majesticks-gc/">OKX partners with LIV Golf League team Majesticks GC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-partners-with-liv-golf-league-team-majesticks-gc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price outlook: Technical breakout suggests BTC rally to $34k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-technical-breakout-suggests-btc-rally-to-34k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-technical-breakout-suggests-btc-rally-to-34k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s breakout to $29k comes after bulls established $26,190 as a key support zone. If bulls break to YTD highs, the next direct resistance per the Fibonacci model could be at the -50.0% retracement of $34,280. Bitcoin traded at around $29,030 on Monday morning after spot ETF news sparked by BlackRock&#8217;s filing aided bulls&#8217; upside [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-technical-breakout-suggests-btc-rally-to-34k/">Bitcoin price outlook: Technical breakout suggests BTC rally to $34k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s breakout to $29k comes after bulls established $26,190 as a key support zone.</li>
<li dir="ltr">If bulls break to YTD highs, the next direct resistance per the Fibonacci model could be at the -50.0% retracement of $34,280.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin traded at around $29,030 on Monday morning after spot ETF news sparked by BlackRock&rsquo;s filing aided bulls&rsquo; upside momentum.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> broke above a key downtrend line as it rose past the $28k level on Tuesday. In reaching the $29k area, BTC pushed well beyond the recent hurdle and now has a key support line of $26,190.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts have pointed Bitcoin&rsquo;s break of a multi-month downtrend as a bullish move that puts the top crypto asset on the verge of retesting the $30k level. Can it go higher than its year-to-date highs above $31k?&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The technical picture based on the Fibonacci model suggests it could pump beyond its YTD highs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin price to $34k next?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Bitcoin is clearly not in a bull market yet, the potential for a burst is looking likely as a confluence of positive factors align. Given, regulatory headwinds, including the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, continue to hover over the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the resilience shown over the past weeks and renewed optimism as major financial institutions embrace crypto has bulls poised and a break to $30k is very much on. Can it go to $34k next?</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Glassnode, an on-chain and financial metrics data provider, this robust support is at the -61.8% golden ratio Fibonacci retracement. If the price pushes higher and establishes a clear upward trend, it&rsquo;s likely bulls will retest the bears&rsquo; resolve around $34,280.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This would be the next direct resistance zone, Glassnode pointed out on Wednesday, putting this possible supply reload zone at the -50% Fibonacci retracement level.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 800px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/21/1687355028824-0a7e3b79-879c-4a64-90c8-1fb541e904f8.png" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="353"><span class="fr-inner">Chart showing Bitcoin Fibonacci retracement levels from its all-time. Source:<a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1671494336226250752/photo/1" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>Glassnode</u></a></span></span></span>Having survived the negative sentiment that surrounded the SEC&rsquo;s crackdown, the current wave of buy pressure could bring two other major resistance areas into play.
<p>Veteran trader Peter Brandt <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterLBrandt/status/1671211853895041038" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">believes</a> the breakout shifts the &ldquo;burden of proof&rdquo; to the bears as he suggests a rally to above $37k is possible. Meanwhile, Glassnode identifies the -38.2% and -23.6% Fibonacci retracement levels of $42,370 and $52,380 respectively as key hurdles.</p></div>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, BTC/USD is trading at $29,030, about 8% up in the past 24 hours and nearly 12% higher over the past week.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-outlook-technical-breakout-suggests-btc-rally-to-34k/">Bitcoin price outlook: Technical breakout suggests BTC rally to $34k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin mining stocks are far riskier than Bitcoin itself</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-far-riskier-than-bitcoin-itself/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-far-riskier-than-bitcoin-itself/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-far-riskier-than-bitcoin-itself/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Bitcoin mining stocks have underperformed Bitcoin heavily over the last year Greater competition among miners and higher amounts of energy required means margins are thinner Rising electricity costs and lower value of Bitcoin have also hurt miners immensely&#160; Greater number of variables beyond merely the price of Bitcoin means mining stocks have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-far-riskier-than-bitcoin-itself/">Bitcoin mining stocks are far riskier than Bitcoin itself</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin mining stocks have underperformed Bitcoin heavily over the last year</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Greater competition among miners and higher amounts of energy required means margins are thinner</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Rising electricity costs and lower value of Bitcoin have also hurt miners immensely&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Greater number of variables beyond merely the price of Bitcoin means mining stocks have been trading with greater volatility</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a tough time to be a Bitcoin miner. This piece will succinctly break down how and why, as well as delving into why I believe mining stocks are far riskier than just investing in Bitcoin itself. Let&rsquo;s get to it.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mining competition is higher than ever</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Firstly, the competition within mining is higher than ever before. The beauty of the blockchain is that we can see all sorts of statistics regarding the Bitcoin network in real-time. One of these is the difficulty adjustment. For the uninitiated, the difficulty adjustment is a mechanism by which the difficulty of mining changes to ensure the new supply of Bitcoin released via mining remains consistent (at approximately ten-minute intervals).</p>
<p dir="ltr">In other words, as more miners join the network, the difficulty increases so that Bitcoin is released at the same pace as prior. The same holds true the other way around &ndash; difficulty falls if miners stop operating.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As the below chart shows, Bitcoin mining difficulty recently <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-hits-all-time-high-above-50-trillion-hashes/"><u>smashed through</u></a> the 50 trillion hash mark for the first time ever. Only three years ago, that number sat at 14 trillion. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14013801">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">This is great for the Bitcoin network: the more miners, the more secure the network. For the miners themselves, however, that means greater energy amounts are needed to complete this now-more-difficult assignment of validating transactions on the network.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Oh, and there is a double whammy. As you may realise if you have turned on a light, charged your phone or boiled a kettle in the last year, the price of electricity has skyrocketed around the world. The next chart shows the rise in electricity costs in the US, which according to the Cambridge Electricity Consumption Index, has the highest amount of miners (the nation is responsible for 38% of the network&rsquo;s hash rate).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13976915">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">This means that higher amounts of energy are needed to mine, and the cost of that energy has also increased drastically.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">People are using Bitcoin less&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">So, we know costs have risen. But the bad news isn&rsquo;t over yet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s volumes have collapsed throughout the bear market. Perhaps the best barometer of this is to look at the trading volume on centralised exchanges, which fell 46% in 2022 compared to 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at Bitcoin fees shows a similar pattern, with fees far down on the heyday of the pandemic bull market. This was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-are-bitcoin-transaction-fees-rising-and-what-are-brc-20-tokens/"><u>briefly interrupted</u></a> in May when the Bitcoin Ordinals protocol sparked a revival in network activity. However, the below chart shows that fees have been falling for five consecutive weeks since (although they are still up significantly on the start of the year), giving up most of those gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14197342">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Much like the cost side, which saw an increase in inputs required (greater demands via the difficulty adjustment) as well as an increase in the per-unit costs of those inputs (rising electricity costs), the revenue side for miners is also suffering from a brutal double whammy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Not only is volume way down from the bull market and hence less fees (revenue) are recouped, but miners&rsquo; revenue (fees and the block subsidy award) is received in Bitcoin, which has also fallen in value. This means that, after earning Bitcoin by battling with the greater competition and toiling over increased costs, the value of that Bitcoin (revenue) on the market is substantially less &ndash; still 60% off its peak from November 2021.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Mining stocks are more volatile than Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">So let&rsquo;s think about these four variables:</p>
<ol>
<li dir="ltr">The amount of energy needed</li>
<li dir="ltr">The cost of that energy (electricity)</li>
<li dir="ltr">The fees and block rewards received (i.e. revenue)</li>
<li dir="ltr">The value of those fees and block rewards (the Bitcoin price)</li>
</ol>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, not only are mining companies dependent on the price of Bitcoin (variable number four), but it also depends on several other factors (admittedly variables 1 and 3 are heavily dependent on the price of Bitcoin too. In truth, economic incentives will drive mining to a certain price point, but I will discuss in another article).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, for the time being at least, the risk is greater with mining stocks than a direct investment in Bitcoin. As with all things, greater risk can mean greater reward, and there have been periods of mining stocks outperforming Bitcoin as a result.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, over the last year or so, mining investors are in an even worse state than Bitcoin investors (who themselves are licking their wounds). I&rsquo;ll let the below mining ETF, launched in February 2022, illustrate this:</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14199954">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">All this goes to show how tough mining has been. And that is without even mentioning the big bad wolf that is regulation. The regulatory crackdown in the US has been ferocious, and while Bitcoin has thus far been relatively unaffected, miners are more vulnerable (especially those that are publicly listed in North America) than Bitcoin itself, which is a decentralised asset theoretically immune to regulation (directly, at least).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is not meant to be a pro-Bitcoin or anti-mining piece. It is just comparing the two as investments and showing why mining stocks tend to be more volatile. And when you&rsquo;re more volatile than Bitcoin, that is really saying something. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-far-riskier-than-bitcoin-itself/">Bitcoin mining stocks are far riskier than Bitcoin itself</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-far-riskier-than-bitcoin-itself/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
