<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:23:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chancer presale accelerates as Binance CEO CZ makes a huge prediction on crypto</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-accelerates-as-binance-ceo-cz-makes-a-huge-prediction-on-crypto/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-accelerates-as-binance-ceo-cz-makes-a-huge-prediction-on-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-accelerates-as-binance-ceo-cz-makes-a-huge-prediction-on-crypto/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer seeks to introduce a P2P betting model. Chancer&#8217;s presale has accelerated, with over half of the tokens sold in the first stage. The token could hit three-digit or four-digit percentage price increases in 2023. When will cryptocurrencies resume a bullish trend after a down-beaten 2022 and 2023? Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) thinks 2025 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-accelerates-as-binance-ceo-cz-makes-a-huge-prediction-on-crypto/">Chancer presale accelerates as Binance CEO CZ makes a huge prediction on crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer seeks to introduce a P2P betting model.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale has accelerated, with over half of the tokens sold in the first stage.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token could hit three-digit or four-digit percentage price increases in 2023.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">When will cryptocurrencies resume a bullish trend after a down-beaten 2022 and 2023? Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) thinks 2025 could be the likely year. And while investors may feel this might be a little bit far after expecting the bull market later in 2023 and 2024, the interest in crypto keeps growing. Investors are banking on newly launched tokens that can defy the bear market. Chancer, a blockchain-based predictive markets application, has been attracting investors. Investors have bought at least $615,560 worth of tokens in less than a month since the&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=price_prediction" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> launched.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>CZ predicts a bull market in 2025</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a recent AMA Twitter session, CZ&nbsp;<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/746640" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>told</u></a> his followers that 2025 could be the probable year for a sustained Bitcoin bull market. According to CZ, the Bitcoin halving event in 2024 will likely catalyse the bullishness.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Binance CEO pointed out that historical bull price movements in Bitcoin have followed the halving cycles. If history is to repeat itself, Bitcoin is set for a bullish surge in 2025, with the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s price seen as a barometer for the rest of the sector. Notable halving events propelling Bitcoin&rsquo;s price were in 2012 and 2016, and CZ projects a repeat after the halving event in 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CZ&rsquo;s insights underline growing sentiments that Bitcoin is set for a bullish market after the price recently attempted to break above the $30,000 barrier. Investors have been hopeful of a likely bull run over the next couple of months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, macroeconomic concerns are yet to clear, meaning that a potential bull market could occur in or over a year. With this, investors could be looking for opportunities in newly launched projects to capture initial momentums before the bullish market. Chancer could be benefiting from this sentiment, given the fast-selling presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is Chancer, and how does it work?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is a blockchain-enabled peer-to-peer (P2P) betting platform. As the name suggests, the platform lets users bet with friends, colleagues, and other participants via custom markets. Chancer works quite simply.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users create P2P markets to predict the outcome of key events, processes, episodes, and many more. Unlike traditional betting, whose betting markets and odds are fixed by the bookmakers, Chancer allows users to determine what they want to bet on.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users also place odds and rules which guide the betting and claiming of winnings. All these are enabled via a secure decentralised platform powered by Binance Smart Chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER will be the token to run the Chancer project. Users earn CHANCER by winning on successful predictions, creating Chancer markets, or sharing the platform with others. The token will also be available for staking, allowing investors to earn passive income by committing their holdings to the growth of the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>CHANCER prediction in 2023</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is only starting, and a huge prediction for 2023 could be overambitious. However, the project is attracting global interest, which could propel it to higher value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the price of CHANCER at 0.01 BUSD in the first stage of the presale, the value could rise by triple digits before the end of 2023. The prediction is based on the fact that CHANCER will start listing in the third quarter of 2023, starting on Uniswap, giving it a chance to rise in value.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although tokens have risen by 10x after listing, which would also be realistic for CHANCER, such increases could be limited for 2023. That&rsquo;s because product development is still ongoing, with huge value increases possible in 2024.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is it the right time to buy CHANCER?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is no right time to buy Chancer. Nonetheless, investors are better off buying now when the price is low for a higher return-to-risk ratio. The token&rsquo;s price will rise in the next presales, meaning buying now could be the right idea for investors.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-accelerates-as-binance-ceo-cz-makes-a-huge-prediction-on-crypto/">Chancer presale accelerates as Binance CEO CZ makes a huge prediction on crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-accelerates-as-binance-ceo-cz-makes-a-huge-prediction-on-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu price prediction as presale rakes in over $215k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-price-prediction-as-presale-rakes-in-over-215k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-price-prediction-as-presale-rakes-in-over-215k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-price-prediction-as-presale-rakes-in-over-215k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Shiba Memu has generated more than $200k in its presale stage. The team increases SHMU&#8217;s price daily, with the presale event set to last for eight weeks.&#160; Bitcoin has maintained its value around the $30k level for the last two weeks. In addition to Bitcoin, other leading cryptocurrencies have performed well during that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-price-prediction-as-presale-rakes-in-over-215k/">Shiba Memu price prediction as presale rakes in over $215k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu has generated more than $200k in its presale stage.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The team increases SHMU&rsquo;s price daily, with the presale event set to last for eight weeks.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has maintained its value around the $30k level for the last two weeks. In addition to Bitcoin, other leading cryptocurrencies have performed well during that period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The positive performance saw the total cryptocurrency market cap reach the $1.2 trillion mark for the first time this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is currently in its presale stage and has raised more than $200k so far. The development team increases the token price daily, and it could rally higher once the token gets listed on cryptocurrency exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a cryptocurrency token combining AI and blockchain technology to create an unstoppable, entirely self-sufficient marketing powerhouse.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team claims that Shiba Memu can do the work of 100 marketing agencies. Unlike marketing agencies, Shiba Memu is always active. It is working all the time, finding the best work going on in creative advertising, eating it up and spitting it back out, but better.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The meme coin industry has experienced massive growth over the past three years. In 2020, meme coins were practically unknown in the crypto ecosystem but grew to a market cap of over $20 billion in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> seeks to be a leading meme coin and intends to achieve this, thanks to its utility. According to their whitepaper, Shiba Memu has self-sufficient marketing capabilities powered by AI technology, making it a unique and attractive investment.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team pointed out that Shiba Memu will create its own marketing strategies, write its own PR, and promote itself in relevant forums and social networks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu combines the powers of AI and blockchain technology, making it different from the plethora of meme coins currently available in the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, Shiba Memu operates on Ethereum and BNB Chain, the two leading DeFi blockchains in the cryptocurrency space.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale tops $215k</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is already gaining traction in the cryptocurrency space. The project&rsquo;s presale is already on, and the team has raised $215,000 so far. Shiba Memu will use the proceeds from the presale to develop some of its products.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, most of the funds would be used to develop Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI technology. In its whitepaper, the team explained that Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI technology lets it engage with users directly. There will be a robotastic dashboard to interact with the AI, provide feedback, make suggestions, and ask questions.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Click here</u></a> to find out more about Shiba Memu&rsquo;s presale event.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, it is impossible to accurately predict Shiba Memu&rsquo;s price since the meme token is still in its presale stage. At the moment, 1 SHMU = 0.011575 USDT.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the development team revealed that a major difference between this project and others is that Shiba Memu&rsquo;s price increases every day at 6 pm GMT.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHMU is set to trade at 0.011800 USDT tomorrow. The amount it increases varies, but it will over double in price throughout, with the presale starting at $0.011125 and ending at $0.0244. Users can purchase the SHMU token using Ethereum, USDT, BNB and BUSD</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Shiba Memu today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The decision to invest in a token depends on the investor. However,&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Shiba Memu</u></a> could be an interesting cryptocurrency project.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Combining AI and blockchain technology to ease marketing strategies for companies and organisations, Shiba Memu is one of the meme tokens with excellent use cases.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">SHMU, the native token of the Shiba Memu ecosystem, could record massive gains in the medium to long term if the team delivers on its products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, Shiba Memu could benefit from a market rally. The crypto market has been bullish since the start of the year, with the prices of most coins and tokens up by more than 40% during that period.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the fundamentals of the market continue to improve, SHMU could record excellent growth once it starts trading on cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-price-prediction-as-presale-rakes-in-over-215k/">Shiba Memu price prediction as presale rakes in over $215k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-price-prediction-as-presale-rakes-in-over-215k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash price prediction as Chancer presale hits new record</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-chancer-presale-hits-new-record/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-chancer-presale-hits-new-record/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-chancer-presale-hits-new-record/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin Cash could experience further pullback after its recent rally. Chancer&#8217;s presale surpasses $600k roughly a month after launch.&#160; Bitcoin Cash was the best-performing coin amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap over the past 30 days. After rallying by more than 200%, Bitcoin Cash has slightly retraced. Will Bitcoin Cash resume [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-chancer-presale-hits-new-record/">Bitcoin Cash price prediction as Chancer presale hits new record</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash could experience further pullback after its recent rally.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale surpasses $600k roughly a month after launch.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash was the best-performing coin amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap over the past 30 days. After rallying by more than 200%, Bitcoin Cash has slightly retraced.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Will Bitcoin Cash resume its upward trajectory soon, or will it shed off some of its gains in the near term?&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash rallies by more than 200% in 30 days</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash was the best performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap in recent weeks. BCH was trading around $110 at the start of June but rallied to the $320 mark by the end of last month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Since reaching $320, Bitcoin has slightly retraced, losing more than 10% of its value during that period. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin Cash</u></a> stands at $283 per coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Technical indicators show that Bitcoin Cash could embark on a bearish run in the near term. BCH could retreat after hitting the extreme greed zone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The pullback could see Bitcoin Cash test the next key support at $210, which is the 25-day moving average. However, Bitcoin Cash could continue its upward trajectory if Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market maintain upward momentum in the near term.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Chancer?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">One of the projects that could record excellent adoption in the cryptocurrency space is Chancer.&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is a unique Web3 peer-to-peer (P2P) custom betting platform designed to enable users to live stream betting events.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer operates differently from the other betting platforms due to its decentralised nature. It allows users to bet on numerous events, beyond the sporting and popular ones.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is currently in its presale stage, and the developers have earmarked the funds to build a P2P betting platform. The platform would allow users to enjoy betting markets in real time and based on user interests, social media connections, and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to their whitepaper, Chancer seeks to eliminate the challenges users experience due to bookmakers. With Chancer, users can set their own custom P2P betting markets using its decentralised platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the most important features of Chancer is that it supports betting far beyond the sporting and popular events users find on centralised betting platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to traditional sport betting activities, users can bet on any event they desire, whether mainstream or made-up. It doesn&rsquo;t matter the event, users can bet on them on Chancer.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale surpasses $600k</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> will hold 12 presale events, and the first one is coming to an end soon. The Chancer team has raised more than $600k so far, reaching more than 60% of the target.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer will use the funds to develop its suite of products. By the end of the 12 presale events, Chancer intends to raise $15 million in total.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, CHANCER, the native token of the Chancer ecosystem, is going for $0.01 BUSD per token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CHANCER will power various activities on the Chancer betting platform. Holders of the CHANCER token can create markets and invest in markets created by other users. In addition to that, the token could allow users to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Anyone can participate the in the presale event, as users only need to connect their wallets to the platform. The supported wallets include Trust Wallet, MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Rainbow.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Visit the&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer website</u></a> to get more information about the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should you invest in Chancer now?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and the broader crypto market have been performing well since the start of the year. The recent spot Bitcoin ETF filings by BlackRock, Fidelity, and Valkyrie, has increased optimism in the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With more institutional and retail investors entering the market, this might be a good time to invest in strong projects and unlock gems within the Web3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Chancer</u></a> is one of the projects that could become a hit in the market. Launching a decentralised betting platform could see Chancer gain massive adoption in the medium to long term.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The presale is still in its early stages, and CHANCER&rsquo;s price could soar once the token lists on numerous decentralised and centralised trading platforms.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-chancer-presale-hits-new-record/">Bitcoin Cash price prediction as Chancer presale hits new record</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-chancer-presale-hits-new-record/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin stabilises around $30k; can it rally to the $35k level soon?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stabilises-around-30k-can-it-rally-to-the-35k-level-soon/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stabilises-around-30k-can-it-rally-to-the-35k-level-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stabilises-around-30k-can-it-rally-to-the-35k-level-soon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Bitcoin has been trading around the $30k region in the last two weeks and could rally higher in the near term. AltSignals has entered stage two of its presale after raising more than $1 million in the first stage.&#160; The cryptocurrency market performed well in recent weeks, thanks to the spot Bitcoin ETF [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stabilises-around-30k-can-it-rally-to-the-35k-level-soon/">Bitcoin stabilises around $30k; can it rally to the $35k level soon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has been trading around the $30k region in the last two weeks and could rally higher in the near term.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has entered stage two of its presale after raising more than $1 million in the first stage.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market performed well in recent weeks, thanks to the spot Bitcoin ETF filings by BlackRock, Fidelity, and Valkyrie.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The events saw Bitcoin rally past the $31k level earlier this week before retracing to the $30k level.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin stays around $30k in recent weeks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency by market cap, has been trading around the $30k region for the last two weeks. The cryptocurrency has maintained its price around the region in recent weeks thanks to optimism from investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $30,117 per coin. Some cryptocurrency experts are now predicting a Bitcoin rally in the coming months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto services provider Matrixport believes that&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-services-provider-matrixport-predicts-bitcoin-to-125k-by-the-end-of-2024/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Bitcoin could rally as high as $125,000</u></a> by the end of 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bullish sentiment could positively affect other cryptocurrencies, including AltSignals, which recently concluded its first presale stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals will list on numerous cryptocurrency exchanges once it concludes its presale funding rounds, and its ASI token could experience a price surge if Bitcoin and the broader crypto market embark on a rally.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals commences the second stage of presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> concluded the first stage of its presale a few days ago, raising more than $1 million in the process. During the stage one presale, the ASI token was sold for $0.015 USDT.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The AltSignals team has raised the token price in the second stage, and ASI is now sold for $0.1875. With a target of over $2 million in the second stage, AltSignals has already raised more than $1 million so far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The team has already started working on releasing numerous products. AltSignals is a unique project that will use AI to make it easier for people to trade Bitcoin and a host of other cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Click here</u></a> to read more about the AltSignals presale.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is an exciting cryptocurrency project that could benefit crypto and forex traders. The products to be released by AltSignals could be beneficial to crypto traders, forex, stock, commodities, and indices traders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform makes it possible for crypto traders to access trading signals. AltSignals will also provide forex, stocks, commodities, and indices signals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The development team will use the funds raised from the presale to develop ActualizeAI, an AI solution that could make it easier for people to trade cryptos and other financial assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the team, ActualizeAI will be an automated solution that works 24/7. It will make it easier for traders to identify various patterns in the market, eliminating some of the pain points traders experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Holders of the ASI token would have access to the wide range of services provided by AltSignals.&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>AltSignals</u></a> will use other technologies, including natural language processing, machine learning, regression, and predictive modeling, to boost its services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI tokens would be listed on numerous exchanges, including Uniswap, once the presale stages are over.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the moment, ASI is yet to list on any cryptocurrency exchange. As such, it is hard to predict its price movement in the short term. However, the token price has increased from $0.015 to $0.1875 since the second presale stage began.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">ASI would be listed on cryptocurrency exchanges once the presale stages are concluded, and that could see ASI rally higher in the near to medium terms. If that happens, ASI could reach the $0.1 level over the next few months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market has seen an improved sentiment this year, with prices of most cryptocurrencies up by more than 50% year-to-date. If the fundamentals of the broader market improve in the near term, ASI could benefit once it starts trading on cryptocurrency exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Should I buy AltSignals in its presale?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Perhaps the best time to invest in a project is during its presale. Early investors in projects like Ethereum, Solana, and Dogecoin, recorded thousands of percentages in ROI.&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> could be a project that records excellent growth due to the fact that it is a unique project that is entering a multi-billion market with some exciting solutions. With the right level of adoption, ASI could become a big winner in the coming months and years.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stabilises-around-30k-can-it-rally-to-the-35k-level-soon/">Bitcoin stabilises around $30k; can it rally to the $35k level soon?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-stabilises-around-30k-can-it-rally-to-the-35k-level-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Solana, Zilliqa, Fantom (FTM)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-solana-zilliqa-fantom-ftm/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-solana-zilliqa-fantom-ftm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 12:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zilliqa News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-solana-zilliqa-fantom-ftm/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price remained slightly above $30,000 this week. There was no major cryptocurrency news during the week. We explain what to expect from Solana, Zilliqa, and Fantom. Cryptocurrencies had another muted week as volumes from the United States remained low because of the Independence Day celebrations. Also, there was no major crypto news&#160;during the week. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-solana-zilliqa-fantom-ftm/">Crypto price prediction: Solana, Zilliqa, Fantom (FTM)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price remained slightly above $30,000 this week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">There was no major cryptocurrency news during the week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">We explain what to expect from Solana, Zilliqa, and Fantom.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cryptocurrencies had another muted week as volumes from the United States remained low because of the Independence Day celebrations. Also, there was no major <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto news</a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>during the week. As a result, Bitcoin price remained at $30,000 while the total market cap of all coins dropped to $1.17 trillion.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Solana price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/solana/"><u>Solana</u></a> had a relatively strong performance this week. The coin jumped to a high of $21, the highest level since June 5th of this year. It has soared by more than 56% from the lowest level this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As the coin jumped, the coin managed to flip above the important resistance level at $16, the lowest level on March 10th. SOL price also flipped the crucial resistance level at $19.48 into support.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Solana price has jumped above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. The Average Directional Index (ADX) has moved to 26, signaling that the momentum is rising. At the same time, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved slightly below the overbought level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, Solana crypto price will likely continue rising as buyers target the next key resistance level to watch at $25. This price is about 22% above the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/07/1688733566935-443df67a-39aa-4654-8490-efd71fa534ba.png" style="width: 535px;height: 260.367px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="535" height="260.367"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Solana</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1MzIz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ1MzIz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SOL with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Zilliqa price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/zilliqa"><u>Zilliqa</u></a> price had a tough week as demand for the coin eased. After rising to a high of $0.0249 on Tuesday, the coin plunged by almost 20% to $0.020. The coin has dropped below the important support level at $0.0213, the lowest level on March 10th. This price was also the neckline of the double-top pattern.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Zilliqa has moved below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. The coin also formed a shooting star pattern, which is usually a bearish sign. Therefore, ZIL crypto price will likely continue falling as sellers target the next key support level at $0.018.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Zilliqa</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    OKX</h3>

    <p>OKX is a world-leading cryptocurrency exchange, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/okx-crypto?guid=MTQ1MzIz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ZIL with OKX today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Trading in digital assets is considered high risk. Digital assets are NOT backed by any government or central bank. The risk of loss in trading or holding digital assets can be substantial. You should carefully consider whether interacting, holding, or trading digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitvavo</h3>

    <p>The Bitvavo platform was launched in 2018, with the goal to bridge the gap between traditional currencies and digital assets. Bitvavo is making digital assets accessible to everyone, by offering transparent fees, a wide range of assets and an easy to use platform.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitvavo-crypto?guid=MTQ1MzIz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy ZIL with Bitvavo today            </a>
    </p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/07/1688733567948-eff17087-f90c-49b6-9f03-671d9013429b.png" style="width: 554px;height: 270.115px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="554" height="270.115"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Fantom price forecast</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/fantom"><u>Fantom</u></a> was also in the red this week as demand for crypto tokens waned. The token peaked at $0.3285 on June 25th and then retreated this week. It has moved below the important support level at $0.3050, the lowest point on March 10th.</p>
<p dir="ltr">FTM crypto price has dropped below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. At the same time, oscillators like MACD and the Relative Strength Index (RSI) have drifted downwards. Therefore, the outlook of the Fantom price is bearish, with the next key level to watch will be at $0.20, whic is about 20% below the current level.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Fantom</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ1MzIz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FTM with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQ1MzIz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy FTM with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/07/1688733568458-aaccf02f-df52-447d-8c5d-84010a7a2b2c.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-solana-zilliqa-fantom-ftm/">Crypto price prediction: Solana, Zilliqa, Fantom (FTM)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-solana-zilliqa-fantom-ftm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Department of Homeland Security returns stolen funds to Bitfinex</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-department-of-homeland-security-returns-stolen-funds-to-bitfinex/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-department-of-homeland-security-returns-stolen-funds-to-bitfinex/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitfinex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacked]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/us-department-of-homeland-security-returns-stolen-funds-to-bitfinex/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitfinex lost 119,756 bitcoins in a hack in August 2016. The hackers embarked on a plan to move the stolen tokens multiple times as they tried to launder them. In 2022, the US Department of Homeland Security arrested two people suspected of hacking Bitfinex. Cryptocurrency exchange Bitfinex has revealed that the US Department of Homeland [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-department-of-homeland-security-returns-stolen-funds-to-bitfinex/">US Department of Homeland Security returns stolen funds to Bitfinex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitfinex lost 119,756 bitcoins in a hack in August 2016.</li>
<li>The hackers embarked on a plan to move the stolen tokens multiple times as they tried to launder them.</li>
<li>In 2022, the US Department of Homeland Security arrested two people suspected of hacking Bitfinex.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/bitfinex/">Cryptocurrency exchange Bitfinex</a> has revealed that the US Department of Homeland Security has returned part of the funds stolen from the exchange after a hack that took place in August 2016. The US Department of Homeland Security intercepted the funds after arresting two people suspected of the hacking.</p>
<p>The funds returned by the US Department of Homeland Security included $312,219.71 in cash and 6.917 <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/what-is-bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash (BCH)</a>.</p>
<h2>The Bitfinex 2016 hack &nbsp;</h2>
<p>The hack was at the time one of the biggest in the cryptocurrency industry. A security flaw caused the exchange to lose almost 119,756 <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a>, at the time worth $71.8 million. At today&rsquo;s market price, the stolen BTC is worth more than 3 billion.</p>
<p>The Bitfinex hackers then started moving the stolen cryptocurrencies in an attempt to launder them.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/fbi-arrests-two-over-2016-bitfinex-hack-3-6b-in-bitcoin-seized/">two culprits identified as a married couple were arrested</a> by the US authorities in February 2022 and charged with conspiracy to commit money laundering. The arrest resulted in the recovery of stolen cryptocurrencies worth $3.6 billion, making the US government have the wealthiest BTC wallet.</p>
<h2>Distribution of the recovered funds</h2>
<p>Acknowledging the recovery of part of the stolen funds, Bitfinex&rsquo;s Chief of Technology Officer Paolo Ardoino said they:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;Look forward to recovering as much of the stolen bitcoin as we possibly can and redistributing that to holders of the tokens that were issued in response to the hack in 2016.&rdquo;&nbsp;</em></p>
<p>The victims of the Bitfinex hack had received Recovery Right Tokens (RTTs) that act as an IOU. The RTTs could be exchanged for cash or iFinex capital stock in future. There were a total of 30 million RRTs in circulation, and the crypto exchange has said that the funds it has recovered so far are not enough to meet all the redemptions.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-department-of-homeland-security-returns-stolen-funds-to-bitfinex/">US Department of Homeland Security returns stolen funds to Bitfinex</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/us-department-of-homeland-security-returns-stolen-funds-to-bitfinex/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink: crypto is digitalising gold in many ways</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-crypto-digitalising-gold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=145305</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink was all praise for BTC in a recent interview. The asset manager refiled for a Spot Bitcoin ETF earlier this week. Bitcoin is currently up close to 90% versus the start of the year. Bitcoin made a new 52-week high this morning after Larry Fink &#8211; the Chief Executive of BlackRock [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-crypto-digitalising-gold/">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink: crypto is digitalising gold in many ways</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink was all praise for BTC in a recent interview.</li>
<li>The asset manager refiled for a Spot Bitcoin ETF earlier this week.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up close to 90% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> made a new 52-week high this morning after Larry Fink &ndash; the Chief Executive of BlackRock Inc agreed that it was a valuable international asset.</p>
<h2>Fink is now constructive on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Fink had once dubbed the BTC an index of money laundering. But in a recent interview with <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/video/6330640643112" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fox Business</a>, he was all praise for the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</p>
<blockquote><p>I do believe the role of crypto is digitalising gold in many ways. Instead of investing in gold as a hedge against inflation or the onerous problem of any one country.</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this week, the asset manager <a href="https://decrypt.co/147177/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-filing-sec-coinbase-surveillance" target="_blank" rel="noopener">refiled</a> for a Spot Bitcoin ETF after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission asked for more clarity on its initial application.</p>
<p>BlackRock Inc currently has about $9.5 trillion worth of assets under management.</p>
<h2>Is a Spot Bitcoin ETF coming soon?</h2>
<p>Note that BlackRock has a history of getting regulatory approval for nearly every exchange-traded fund it has ever filed for.</p>
<p>That&rsquo;s important considering many experts forecast a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/anthony-pompliano-sec-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf/">Spot Bitcoin ETF</a> to unlock further upside in Bitcoin. The digital currency is already up close to 90% for the year at writing.</p>
<p>BlackRock has already made money investing in BTC and expects the crypto asset to grow further moving forward. According to CEO Larry Fink:</p>
<blockquote><p>The foundation of BlackRock is about hope. You have for retirement because you believe tomorrow is better than today.</p></blockquote>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-crypto-digitalising-gold/">BlackRock CEO Larry Fink: crypto is digitalising gold in many ways</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hashed Emergent to host the first multi-chain web3 conference in India</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-host-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 15:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-launch-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The conference will run from December 4 to December 10. The conference will include hackathons, side events, parties, a headline conference, and an ETHIndia hackathon. The conference is organized by Hashed Emergent, a subsidiary of Hashed, a prominent web3 venture fund from South Korea. Hashed Emergent has announced that it will host the first blockchain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-host-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/">Hashed Emergent to host the first multi-chain web3 conference in India</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The conference will run from December 4 to December 10.</li>
<li>The conference will include hackathons, side events, parties, a headline conference, and an ETHIndia hackathon.</li>
<li>The conference is organized by Hashed Emergent, a subsidiary of Hashed, a prominent web3 venture fund from South Korea.</li>
</ul>
<p>Hashed Emergent has announced that it will host the first <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> conference week in India in December. The week-long series of web3-focused events will be held in Bangalore, the heart of India&rsquo;s tech and startup scene, rightfully known as the &ldquo;Silicon Valley of the East.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The new conference dubbed India Blockchain Week (IBW) aims at becoming India&rsquo;s first world-class, multi-chain web3 conference with a pan-industry agenda. It will reflect India&rsquo;s increasing role in web3, expressed both in terms of crypto adoption and the exciting startups originating from the sub-continent.</p>
<p>Expressing his excitement about the upcoming event, Managing Partner of Hashed Emergent, Tak Lee, said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to bring the first world-class, pan-industry and multi-chain web3 conference to India, finally giving it the attention it has always deserved. Bangalore ranks among the most prolific startup hubs worldwide, and Indian startups in web3 have made a considerable impact on the industry, spearheaded by multiple hugely successful protocols and products. We believe that IBW will quickly become one of the most interesting and diverse gathering places for the crypto industry.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>The India Blockchain Week timetable</h2>
<p>The conference will have a week-long series of web3-focused events lasting from December 4-10.</p>
<p>It will start with a &ldquo;warm-up&rdquo; session on Monday and Tuesday, December 4-5. This will include hackathons, side events and parties.</p>
<p>The IBW headline conference will be held on December 6-7, or Wednesday and Thursday succeeded by the ETHIndia hackathon which set a record last year as one of the largest <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> hackathons with over 2,000 attendees and 450+ project submissions.</p>
<p>The main venue of the IBW conference will be the Sheraton Grand Hotel in Whitefield, a major IT and commercial hub of Bangalore.</p>
<h2>MarketAcross will be IBW&rsquo;s lead media</h2>
<p>MarketAcross, the world&rsquo;s leading web3 PR and marketing agency known for its work in the region with companies like Polygon and Hashed Emergent, will be joining the event as the global lead media.</p>
<p>MarketAcross has served as the official media partner in multiple web3 events including the Korea Blockchain Week, WebX, Paris Blockchain Week, and the IVS Kyoto.</p>
<p>India has rapidly emerged as one of the leading adopters of web3 despite the numerous regulatory hurdles seeing that the Indian government has been historically sceptical to crypto and is now positioning itself for globally harmonized regulation at the G20 Summit.</p>
<p>While the list of speakers at the IBW headline conference is yet to be revealed, Harsh Emergent has confirmed that it will include prominent local and global leaders within the blockchain industry.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hashed-emergent-to-host-the-first-multi-chain-web3-conference-in-india/">Hashed Emergent to host the first multi-chain web3 conference in India</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stay away from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust despite discount narrowing to 10-month low</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has persistently traded at a discount to its net asset value The discount has narrowed to its lowest mark since September off hope the fund is more likely to be converted to an ETF The entire GBTC debacle represents the mess that is the institutional regulatory climate in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/">Stay away from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust despite discount narrowing to 10-month low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) has persistently traded at a discount to its net asset value</li>
<li dir="ltr">The discount has narrowed to its lowest mark since September off hope the fund is more likely to be converted to an ETF</li>
<li dir="ltr">The entire GBTC debacle represents the mess that is the institutional regulatory climate in the US</li>
<li dir="ltr">Spot ETFs are a question of when rather than if, and such investment vehicles will then be a thing of the past</li>
<li dir="ltr">That won&rsquo;t assuage frustration of GBTC investors, who have been caught badly as alternative Bitcoin investment vehicles have come online and demand for the trust has dried up</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the interesting aspects of the fallout from the slew of recent spot Bitcoin ETF filings is how it affects the controversial Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The trust has been flying, up 56% in the three weeks since Blackrock&rsquo;s ETF filing was announced.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14353132">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Notably, this means it has significantly outpaced its underlying asset, Bitcoin. That sounds like a good thing, but it really summises the problem with this investment vehicle that has done nothing but frustrate investors in recent years, but we will get to that in a moment.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I have plotted the movement of the GBTC against Bitcoin itself in the next chart, highlighting the outperformance the Trust has had since the ETF filing, with Bitcoin itself up &ldquo;only&rdquo; 21%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14353266">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<h2 dir="ltr">Grayscale discount to net asset value narrowing but still enormous</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The trust&rsquo;s discount to net asset value has also narrowed to its smallest mark since September, now below 30%. This comes as investors bet the trust is now more likely to finally be allowed to convert to an ETF.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/06/1688650389110-2e2da1ba-ffda-469d-89b2-467982f18dd6.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="189"></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Should this conversion occur, the discount would narrow to near zero, as funds would then be allowed to flow in and out of the vehicle without affecting the underlying assets. For the time being, while it remains a trust, there is no way to get Bitcoin out of GBTC. This, coupled with steep fees (2% annually) means that a heavy discount has persisted.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In truth, the very existence of the Grayscale trust is a black mark on the sector. The discount it trades at is farcical &ndash; even following the recent narrowing, a 30% delta is an enormous chasm, one that is hurting investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The outsized assets under management &ndash; essentially trapped due to the closed-fund nature &ndash; feels like a throwback to the days when anyone and everyone wanted to get exposure to Bitcoin through whatever means necessary. Grayscale was the only shop in town, and such was the demand for Bitcoin, coupled with that monopolistic power, that it even traded at a premium for much of its early history.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, as more mediums through which Bitcoin exposure can be had have come online, the premium has flipped to a discount, and that discount has become <em>large.&nbsp;</em>It is probably fair to say that investors displayed a lack of due diligence for how the fund works, another throwback to the up-only bull market of days gone by.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Without donning a captain hindsight outfit, there was always going to be competitor firms coming online and the premium was bound to come under pressure. An investment in GBTC essentially amounted to two things: a bet on Bitcoin, and a bet that the trust would be converted into an ETF <em>quickly.&nbsp;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">But at that, perhaps sympathy can be shown to investors. Investment management firm Osprey Funds has a similar product, and earlier this year sued Grayscale, alleging that its competitor misled investors about how likely it was that GBTC would be converted into an ETF. This, they allege, is how they captured such a share of the market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Only because of its false and misleading advertising and promotion has Grayscale been able to maintain to date approximately 99.5% market share in a two-participant market despite charging more than four times the asset management fee that Osprey charges for its services&rdquo;, the suit alleges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Whether Grayscale knew of the regulatory difficulty it would face or not, it has tried and failed for years to convert the vehicle into an ETF. Last year, it sued the SEC itself, declaring the latest rejection &ldquo;arbitrary&rdquo;.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Institutional climate turning</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My thoughts on the trust overall remain the same. I believe it represents a terrible investment (obviously), and its mere existence is only a byproduct of the regulatory travails that the sector has struggled with. There is no reason to even consider buying this unless there is quite literally no other vehicle through which to gain Bitcoin exposure.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There will come a day when all this squabbling over trusts and ETFs will likely be nothing but a throwback of a more uncertain time. But time is a luxury that many investors don&rsquo;t have, and Grayscale has been a horrendous investment, typical in a lot of ways of the travails the space has had in bridging the gap to become a respected mainstream financial asset.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Not only is the discount jarring as it is, but it widened beyond 50% in the aftermath of the FTX collapse as it emerged that crypto broker Genesis was in deep trouble. Genesis&rsquo; parent company is Digital Currency Group (DCG), the same parent company of Grayscale. Genesis eventually filed for bankruptcy in January.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This sparked concern around the safety of Grayscale&rsquo;s reserves, something which they company did not exactly comfort investors about when it refused to provide on-chain proof of reserves, citing &ldquo;security concerns&rdquo;. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">6) Coinbase frequently performs on-chain validation. Due to security concerns, we do not make such on-chain wallet information and confirmation information publicly available through a cryptographic Proof-of-Reserve, or other advanced cryptographic accounting procedure.</p>
<p>&mdash; Grayscale (@Grayscale) <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale/status/1593737746413244417?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 18, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">While the furore over reserves has quietened down, the episode is yet another stark reminder of the oft-repeated (but perhaps not often enough) phrase: &ldquo;not your keys, not your coins&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The problem for institutions to date is that they have had trouble accessing Bitcoin directly for a variety of reasons, primarily regulatory-related. While spot ETFs will also technically violate the &ldquo;not your keys&rdquo; mantra, with prudent regulatory oversight and a strong custodian, this should be a safe way for institutions to gain exposure to Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That would end all this nonsense (and that really is the right word) such as trusts trading at 30% discounts, and give investors a secure avenue through which to put their views on Bitcoin into conviction. That may still be a long way off, but if demand for these products remains, it&rsquo;s only a matter of time.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/stay-away-from-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-despite-discount-narrowing-to-10-month-low/">Stay away from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust despite discount narrowing to 10-month low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
