<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:55:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blue origin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[richard branson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spacex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unity 25]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virgin galactic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256518</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
<p>American spaceflight company Virgin Galactic has announced preparation for a highly anticipated milestone as it prepares to launch its first spaceflight in nearly two years.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
<p>This crucial flight serves as the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/virgin-galactic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Virgin Galactic Holdings</a>&#8216; (NYSE: SPCE) final test before the company begins flying commercial passengers, marking a significant step forward in the realization of its space tourism vision.</p>
<p>The mission called ‘Unity 25’ represents the company&#8217;s fifth space voyage and is expected to launch from Spaceport America in New Mexico. According to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/25/virgin-galactic-unity-25-spaceflight-final-test-before-commercial-service.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, six Virgin Galactic staffers will be traveling on this mission for a brief voyage to the edge of space.</p>
<p>Notably, VSS Unity will be piloted by Virgin Galactic’s Mike Masucci and CJ Sturckow, while carrier aircraft VMS Eve will be flown by Jameel Janjua and Nicola Pecile. Notably, the firm has 600 bookings for tickets for upcoming flights, priced between $200,000 and $250,000 each.</p>
<p>Unlike its previous mission, which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/branson-space-virgin-galactic-flight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">carried</a> founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/richard-branson/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sir Richard Branson</a>, in July 2021, Virgin Galactic said it will not publicly broadcast the flight. Instead, the corporation intends to provide updates on Unity 25′s progress via social media platforms.</p>
<p>According to the details provided, the carrier aircraft VMS Eve is scheduled to take off at 10 a.m. ET. This significant flight will see the aircraft carrying Virgin Galactic&#8217;s VSS Unity spacecraft to an altitude of around 40,000 feet, before releasing the rocket-powered vehicle to continue its journey.</p>
<p>Once released from the carrier aircraft, the VSS Unity will ignite its engine, propelling itself further into the heavens. The aim of this flight is to surpass an altitude of 80 kilometers, which is the internationally recognized boundary of space in the United States.</p>
<p>At this altitude, passengers on board the VSS Unity will experience the incredible sensation of weightlessness and gaze upon the Earth from the awe-inspiring perspective of space. Depending on the results and data from Unity 25, the company hopes to fly its first commercial flight in &#8220;late June&#8221;.</p>
<p>By reaching the boundary of space, Virgin Galactic aims to push the boundaries of what is possible and inspire generations to come. This flight represents the culmination of years of meticulous planning, engineering advancements, and rigorous testing.</p>
<h2>Potential Impact of the Virgin Galactic Flight</h2>
<p>Virgin Galactic&#8217;s attempt to break through this barrier is both a show of its technological capabilities and a step toward its eventual aim of making space travel available to the general population. The lessons learned from these flights will be used to enhance and improve systems and processes, assuring the safety and comfort of future passengers.</p>
<p>The success of Virgin Galactic goes beyond tourism. The data and knowledge that will be gained during this flight will help to progress scientific research and technology. It will provide essential insights into the impacts of microgravity, spacecraft behavior, and prospective uses in a variety of sectors.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Virgin Galactic&#8217;s determination and dedication will serve as a key challenge to other firms including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/spacex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SpaceX</a> and Blue Origin that are working towards similar goals.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/">Virgin Galactic to Conduct Final Flight Test as It Eyes Full Space Travel Launch</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/virgin-galactic-final-flight-test-space-travel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &amp; Efficient Payment Systems</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ava labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Euro Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[euroc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jeremy allaire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
<p>USDC stablecoin issuer Circle recently launched Euro Coin on the Avalanche protocol to exploit the network’s blazing transaction speed. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a> has <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/circle-takes-euro-coin-multi-chain-with-launch-on-avalanche-301834001.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">launched</a> a euro-based stablecoin on the Avalanche blockchain to deliver prompt and efficient payments and financial services. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/euro-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Euro Coin</a> (EUROC) launch is the first of a series of anticipated multi-chain launches to aid developers and users. According to Circle’s team, Euro Coin availability on Avalanche increases liquidity and provides users an additional transactional option alongside USD Coin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDC</a>). Last year, Circle launched EUROC as a regulated stablecoin backed 100% by euro reserves. Each Euro Coin has an equivalent euro held in custody at financial institutions regulated by the US government.</p>
<h2>Execs Weigh In on Circle Euro Stablecoin</h2>
<p>VP of Product at Circle, Joao Reginatto, commented on benefits of the Euro stablecoin. According to Reginatto, Avalanche developers with apps that support USDC can easily integrate EUROC because both stablecoins have similar contract designs. The Circle senior executive also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“When we first introduced Euro Coin on Ethereum last year, we wanted anyone with an internet connection to have access to the euro across borders and time zones. By launching Euro Coin on Avalanche’s fast and efficient platform, we can help developers and their users experience near-instant, more cost-effective financial transactions and unlock new possibilities for payments, remittances, and 24/7 FX.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, John Nahas, Vice President of Business Development at Avalanche developer Ava Labs also discussed the possibilities of Euro Coin. Describing the arrival EUROC on Avalanche as a “pivotal moment” that unlocks “new possibilities for our developers and end users,” Nahas said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We continue to see great adoption and volume behind Circle’s USDC and expect great feedback and usage of Euro Coin on Avalanche.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the Ava Labs Business Development VP added that the “trusted and fully reserved” EUROC token would accelerate decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) adoption. Nahas opined that DeFi continues to make inroads into a “multi-currency, cross-border environment” via instant payments and remittances, and Euro Coin would be an additional boon.</p>
<p>Several popular wallets and apps would support Euro Coin on the Avalanche blockchain. These include Coinbase Wallet, Core, MetaMask, Curve, Dexalot, BENQI, Cables, GMX, NFT-TiX, Pangolin, Shift Markets, Trader Joe, and Platypus.</p>
<h2>Avalanche &#8211; The New Euro Stablecoin’s Host</h2>
<p>Avalanche is a decentralized open-source proof-of-stake network that can finalize transactions in less than a second. The blockchain uses smart contract functionality to aid Web3 development and has comprehensive toolkits to create robust, custom blockchain solutions. Avalanche’s native digital currency is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/avalanche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">AVAX</a>.</p>
<h2>Ava Labs</h2>
<p>Ava Labs is the developer behind Avalanche and seeks to facilitate the seamless digitization of disparate assets on a single open-source blockchain. Since its 2018 inception, the company has received funding from several established investors, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/a16z/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Andreessen Horowitz</a> (a16z) and Polychain Capital.</p>
<h2>Circle</h2>
<p>Founded in 2013 by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> and Sean Neville as a peer-to-peer payments technology company, Circle created and began issuing USDC. The Boston-based global fintech also assists various kinds of business scales in tapping into the power of digital currencies. In addition, Circle aids businesses in leveraging public blockchains for transactional, commercial, and financial applications.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/">Euro Coin: Circle Launches Stablecoin on Avalanche Blockchain to Facilitate Fast &#038; Efficient Payment Systems</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-euroc-stablecoin-avalanche-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
<p>The growth of BNB and the underlying chain is largely connected with the ongoing regulatory scrutiny, especially in the United States</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
<p>The BNB Smart Chain (BSC), a leading smart contract blockchain developed by the leading centralized exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> with about $4.45 billion in total value locked, is expected to have a hard fork on its mainnet at block height 29,020,050. Through the current block generation speed, Binance Chain core developers expect the Luban hard fork to take place on June 12, 2023. As a result, the BNB Smart Chain validators and full node operators have been advised to switch their software version to v1.2.4 before the hard fork takes place in seventeen days.</p>
<p>According to GitHub documentation, the Luban hard fork on the BNB Smart Chain is expected to introduce three BEPs. The first is called BEP-126 and is expected to introduce a fast finality mechanism. With BEP-126, the BNB Smart Chain can handle much more complicated transactions much faster without compromising security.</p>
<p>The second one is BEP-174, which is cross-chain-related management.</p>
<p>“This BEP introduces a new governance proposal type to manage the set of whitelisted Relayers…This BEP will improve the management of the relayer whitelist by introducing Relayer Managers, where a Relayer Manager can manage the registration of a single Relayer. Managers will be elected and ejected via governance,” the BSC core developers <a href="https://github.com/bnb-chain/bsc/releases/tag/v1.2.4" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>The third one is the BEP-221, which introduces a new precompiled contract to validate the CometBFT light blocks.</p>
<h2>BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The BNB Smart Chain has been developed over the years to compete with other smart contract-oriented blockchains like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tron/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tron</a>. According to on-chain data provided by BscScan, the BNB  chain had a market capitalization of about $7,413,623,726. Worth noting, the Smart Chain has a total voting power of about 22,447,545 BNB coins.</p>
<p>Moreover, the BNB chain was developed with the goal to embrace large-scale applications &#8211; including GameFi, SocialFi, and the metaverse. In this regard, BNB coin is expected to gain value as the underlying chain gets much-needed updates.</p>
<p>According to the latest market data provided by Coingecko and Tradingview, BNB coin traded around $306 on Thursday, up approximately 25 percent YTD. As a result, the BNB market has a market capitalization of about $48,315,168,651, with a circulating supply of 157,900,174 units. Nevertheless, BNB price has dropped approximately 55 percent from its ATH, around $686.</p>
<p>The growth of BNB and the underlying chain is largely connected with the ongoing regulatory scrutiny, especially in the United States. Notably, Binance has been losing significant ground in the United States since the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research late last year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/">BNB Chain Developers Schedule Hard Fork Dubbed Luban on June 12</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-chain-hard-fork-luban-june-12/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anne boden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goldman sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[starling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[starling bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
<p>Starling CEO Anne Boden agrees to step down from the role at the British neobank next month over 'conflict of interest' concerns. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
<p>According to reports, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/starling-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Starling Bank</a> co-founder and CEO Anne Boden <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/25/boss-of-goldman-backed-digital-bank-starling-to-step-down-next-month.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">will step down</a> at the end of next month. Chief operating officer John Mountain is replacing Boden at the helm of the British digital bank. The CFO has been with Starling since 2015.</p>
<p>Boden co-founded Starling in 2014 and grew the neobank&#8217;s profile and business visibility to become a leading UK financial player. The Starling CEO agreed to step down over concerns that her stake in the firm could create a conflict of interest. According to Boden, who owns 4% of the company, the initial decision to quit the CEO role was hers and not Starling&#8217;s board. In a statement released Thursday, the outgoing chief executive reflected on her time as leader of the digital bank and embraced the necessary shakeups. Boden wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I have spent almost a decade here as both the founder and CEO, a dual role which is unique in UK banking. It&#8217;s been all-consuming, and I&#8217;ve loved every minute of it. Now that we have grown from being an aspiring challenger to an established bank, it is clear the roles and priorities of a CEO and a large shareholder ultimately differ and require distinct approaches. As Starling continues to evolve and grow, separating my two roles is in the bank&#8217;s best interests.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As Starling&#8217;s CEO, Boden has been pivotal in making the digital banking platform an established fintech hub under the British government. The outspoken chief executive is also staunchly critical of social media facilitating online fraud and remains <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-anne-boden-dangerous/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">skeptical of digital currencies</a>.</p>
<h2>Starling CEO Announced Plans to Step Down &amp; Weighed in On Company&#8217;s IPO Outlook</h2>
<p>On Thursday, Boden touched on Starling&#8217;s operability, prospects, and mass market appeal. The CEO opined that the neobank was in a strong position and capable of raising capital today without sustaining a share price decrease. On how her exit could impact Starling&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-ipo-within-two-years-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">initial public offering (IPO) plans</a>, Boden suggested the company would address those concerns when due. According to her, the IPO market is closed, and Starling is in no immediate rush to pursue a public listing. Boden further added that there was no decision regarding a listing venue, but Starling could likely list domestically.</p>
<p>Boden said although options are open, the decision on a listing venue may not be a food one at this time. However, she mentioned that since Starling is a UK bank that has found success in the, the &#8220;default situation&#8221; would be that the company lists in the UK.</p>
<p>Starling <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/goldman-sachs-invests-starling-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enjoys the backing</a> of the US banking powerhouse <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> (NYSE: GS) and is one of the UK&#8217;s most prominent neobanks. The digital bank boasts a user base of 3.6 million customers and has raised a total of £946.5 billion to date from investors. Starling Bank&#8217;s last valuation in April 2022 was £2.5 billion.</p>
<p>The bank has its headquarters in London but operates offices in Southampton, Dublin, and Cardiff.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/">Starling Bank CEO to Step Down on June 30th after 10 Years in Charge</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/starling-bank-ceo-step-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[micron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia stock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
<p>Nvidia recently increased its quarterly earnings guidance on the back of solid demand, also sparking a rally in AI stocks. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
<p>The latest earnings outlook of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) has triggered a substantial rally in artificial intelligence (AI) stocks. Early Thursday, the chip maker&#8217;s stock soared, pulling other AI-exposed companies higher on a better-than-expected sales forecast. Nvidia&#8217;s bullish sales forecast originated from surging demand for its AI chips, which has also seen the company boost production.</p>
<p>Weighing in on increased production, Nvidia chief executive officer Jensen Huang explained in a <a href="http://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/nvidia-announces-financial-results-for-first-quarter-fiscal-2024" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The computer industry is going through two simultaneous transitions &#8211; accelerated computing and generative AI. Our entire data center family of products &#8211; H100, Grace CPU, Grace Hopper Superchip, NVLink, Quantum 400 InfiniBand, and BlueField-3 DPU &#8211; is in production. We are significantly increasing our supply to meet surging demand for them.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Nvidia Projected Earnings See AI Stocks Rally to Combined $300 Billion in Market Value Since Wednesday</h2>
<p>Since yesterday&#8217;s extended trading session, AI stocks have increased by a combined $300 billion in market capitalization from the Nvidia development. Furthermore, KeyBanc Capital Markets analysts described Nvidia&#8217;s earnings outlook as &#8220;[living] up to the generative hype.&#8221; The analysts increased their NVDA price target from $375 to $500, adding that the semiconductor player is in prime position to benefit from &#8220;AI/machine-learning secular data-center growth&#8221;.</p>
<p>Although Nvidia&#8217;s fiscal Q1 2023 earnings surpassed expectations, the firm&#8217;s Q2 outlook primarily stoked the AI rally. The Santa Clara-based multinational tech company expects a revenue haul of $11 billion for its fiscal second quarter. This figure is substantially higher than the $7.2 billion income that analysts expect.</p>
<p>Nvidia&#8217;s stock shot up 28% after the opening bell to trade at its highest-ever level of $391.50. This substantial upswing raised the company&#8217;s stock market value by roughly $200 billion to its current perch of $960 billion. Currently valued at almost a trillion dollars, Nvidia solidified its status as the world&#8217;s most valuable chipmaker. Additionally, the software and fabless computer component designer is currently Wall Street&#8217;s fifth most valuable company.</p>
<p>Nvidia&#8217;s good fortune boosted the valuation profile of several other tech-rooted entities in premarket trade. These include C3.ai Inc (NYSE: AI), Palantir Technologies (NYSE: PLTR), and Arista Networks (NYSE: ANET), which rose 9%, 7.5%, and 7%, respectively. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL) were also up 2%. Furthermore, Nvidia chip-manufacturing rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ: AMD) and Micron Technology (NASDAQ: MU), were 8.5% and 4.5% higher, respectively.</p>
<p>Synovus Trust senior portfolio manager Daniel Morgan commented on the Nvidia earnings-triggered AI rally, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With all the enthusiasm around AI and the fact Nvidia delivered a huge beat for first-quarter results and second-quarter estimates, this gives some actual evidence AI is for real.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Morgan also revealed that Synovus Trust owns shares in Nvidia.</p>
<h2>Will the Nvidia Rally Stand The Test of Time?</h2>
<p>With the Nvidia play in full swing, analysts ponder how long the AI rally would last and if the gains would hold. Although some analysts have faith in the staying power of AI, others point out that emerging technologies typically run in distinct cycles. These more pragmatically-inclined analysts reference blockchain, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> as recent examples of technologies that experienced a price slump soon after a rally. According to this group of analysts, the prices dropped when the news cycle &#8220;was played up&#8221;. By contrast, the same group stated that more established fields like streaming and e-commerce have more sustained lasting impacts on investments and the economy.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/">Nvidia Earnings Outlook for Current Quarter Induces AI Rally as Company Boosts Production</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-earnings-ai-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[esrb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
<p>The ESRB recommended restrictions on crypto firms' lending to clients, especially for leveraged bets, and suggested higher collateral requirements for distributed finance products and stablecoins.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, May 25, an EU watchdog &#8211; the European Systemic Risk Board &#8211; recommended that European authorities should curb leveraged bets on digital assets by introducing limits for investment funds and exchanges. Over the last few years, with the growing number of market participants, crypto trading is getting quite popular among retail investors. As a result of this, leveraged bets have been in high demand. The EU watchdog wants to prevent shocks in the crypto industry caused by leverage bets and prevent further jeopardy to financial stability.</p>
<p>The European Systemic Risk Board (ESRB) has made a few recommendations demanding regular reports from companies involved with the crypto sector along with introducing specific rules for some of the largest players in the space. In its <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/eu-watchdog-calls-curbing-leverage-crypto-trading-2023-05-25/#:~:text=FRANKFURT%2C%20May%2025%20(Reuters),EU%20watchdog%20said%20on%20Thursday." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> accessed by Reuters, the ESRB noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Systemic risks could arise quickly and suddenly. If the rapid growth trends observed in recent years were to continue, crypto-assets could pose risks to financial stability.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The development comes at a time when regulators across the world have been taking measures to protect investors&#8217; interest in the crypto space. The last 18 months have been absolutely tumultuous for the crypto industry and marred with high-profile scams and bankruptcies.</p>
<p>During the crypto winter of 2022, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> price tanked by more than 70% leaving investors dry of their money. Also, major incidents like the Terra ecosystem crash and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> exchange crash wiped out billions of dollars of investors&#8217; money.</p>
<h2>Making Tweaks to the MiCA Framework</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, in a landmark decision, the EU <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-parliament-passes-mica/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">passed</a> the much-awaited Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) legislation. The MiCA has been adopted by EU member states and the European Parliament. Under the MiCA legislative framework, cryptocurrency businesses must get EU authorization to serve customers in the EU. They must comply with protections against money laundering and financing extremist organizations.</p>
<p>Thus, the ESRB has recently proposed a change in the recently passed EU regulation for &#8220;introducing leverage limits for investment funds exposed to crypto-assets&#8221;. These recommendations from ESRB are not bindings but a proposal to consider in the EU&#8217;s future work and new versions of MiCA.</p>
<p>The ESRB recommended restrictions on crypto firms&#8217; lending to clients, especially for leveraged bets, and suggested higher collateral requirements for distributed finance products and stablecoins.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/">EU Regulator Proposes to Curb Leverage in Crypto Trading Activities</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eu-regulator-crypto-trading-activities/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Closes $175 Million Startup Investment Fund</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai ceo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai startup fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256420</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/">OpenAI Closes $175 Million Startup Investment Fund</a></p>
<p>Reputed for being a frontrunner when it comes to AI research and technology, OpenAI has been invested in helping AI-focused startups.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/">OpenAI Closes $175 Million Startup Investment Fund</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/">OpenAI Closes $175 Million Startup Investment Fund</a></p>
<p>American artificial intelligence (AI) company OpenAI may have just closed an investment fund. According to a Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) filing, the firm raised over $175 million.</p>
<p>Reputed for being a frontrunner when it comes to AI research and technology, OpenAI has been invested in helping AI-focused startups. To this end, the platform launched what it calls the OpenAI Startup Fund in May 2021.</p>
<p>As revealed by the SEC filing, the initial plan was to raise $100 million to support companies that share its artificial intelligence ambitions. However, the fund has now turned out to be significantly larger than was originally anticipated.</p>
<p>OpenAI believes that, together, they can push the boundaries of how “AI can positively impact the world and profoundly change people’s lives.”</p>
<p>The fund is managed by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and COO Brad Lightcap and was raised from 14 investors. Per the filing, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> is one of the notable brands that backed the fund.</p>
<h2>OpenAI Is Already Eyeing the Future of AI</h2>
<p>It might be worth mentioning how OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT and GPT-4 have recently become a worldwide sensation. That is not to mention that the platform also recently closed a share sale of over $300 million, bringing its valuation to around $29 billion.</p>
<p>But despite this level of success, Altman has continued to point out the need to be wary of the risks of AI technology. He also urges that the world needs forward thinking about the <a href="https://openai.com/blog/governance-of-superintelligence" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">governance of superintelligence</a>.</p>
<p>To this end, Altman has reportedly hinted that OpenAI may raise as much as another $100 billion in the coming years. According to reports, the fund will be used to develop &#8220;artificial general intelligence (AGI) that is advanced enough to improve its own capabilities&#8221;.</p>
<p>In one of the most recent events involving OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/solana-ai-chatgpt-plug-in/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> has integrated AI into its network.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/">OpenAI Closes $175 Million Startup Investment Fund</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-175m-startup-fund/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>High Court Denies Bail for Do Kwon Due to Lack of Concrete Evidence</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform labs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256456</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/">High Court Denies Bail for Do Kwon Due to Lack of Concrete Evidence</a></p>
<p>Kwon is currently expected to show up in court on June 16.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/">High Court Denies Bail for Do Kwon Due to Lack of Concrete Evidence</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/">High Court Denies Bail for Do Kwon Due to Lack of Concrete Evidence</a></p>
<p>The value of Kwon’s property was based on a statement alone, lacking concrete evidence. As a result, the high court has ruled against his bail. The requests to bail out Do Kwon, co-founder of the defunct Terra Labs, were rejected due to insufficient document verification. After a lower court reviewed the documents, a bail motion was made but was ultimately rejected by the high court due to improper property valuation. As a result, Do Kwon will remain in custody for a longer period.</p>
<h2>Do Kwon Arrested in Montenegro after Trying to Evade Capture</h2>
<p>It is important to remember that Do Kwon was accused of playing a significant role in the collapse of Terraform Labs’ Luna ecosystem. He was suspected of engaging in fraudulent activities involving stablecoin and other cryptocurrencies, resulting in billions of dollars in losses. Since the crash of Terraform Labs in May last year, the co-founder has tried to evade capture in many different ways.</p>
<p>Reportedly, he sought refuge in Singapore after South Korea issued an arrest warrant for violating the Capital Markets Act. By December 2022, rumors circulated that he was in Serbia, which was later confirmed by Korean investigative authorities. This led to international cooperation between South Korea and Serbia as they jointly worked towards locating him. Ultimately, Montenegro police arrested him in March 2023. Do Kwon’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-founder-do-kwon-arrested/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">arrest</a>, which occurred in Montenegro, marked the end of an extensive search.</p>
<h2>High Court Stresses Need for Concrete Evidences, Denies Do Kwon’s Bail</h2>
<p>He was charged <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-24/crypto-mogul-do-kwon-s-bail-is-revoked-in-montenegro" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">with falsifying his documents</a> using fake official documents. Even though the bail request from Do Kwon&#8217;s attorney was accepted by a basic court in Montenegro, it was later rejected by a high court in the same nation. The high court&#8217;s decision to reject the bail request was made in large part due to the absence of verifiable documentation of the defendant&#8217;s financial situation. The high court emphasized that rather than relying solely on statements in the case file that was presented, property assessments should be supported by strong evidence.</p>
<p>Reports have it that the basic court verified the high court’s decision and also made it known that it had received the payment of $428,000 from Kwon as per their agreement. The Court stated that:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In the renewed proceedings, the court will proceed according to the High Court&#8217;s grounds for termination and after that make a decision based on the proposal of the defense counsel for the defendants to accept bail.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Kwon is currently expected to show up in court on June 16. Additionally, the US and South Korea have asked that Kwon be returned to their respective nations so that he can be held accountable for Terraform Labs&#8217; collapse in May 2022. Their dedication to ensuring accountability in this prominent case is reflected in this request.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/">High Court Denies Bail for Do Kwon Due to Lack of Concrete Evidence</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/high-court-bail-do-kwon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fahrenheit Consortium Wins Bid to Acquire Celsius Network</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apollo global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celsius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fahrenheit LLC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[novawulf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voyager digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256436</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/">Fahrenheit Consortium Wins Bid to Acquire Celsius Network</a></p>
<p>The deal is yet to be finalized as an initial deposit is expected within the next ten days.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/">Fahrenheit Consortium Wins Bid to Acquire Celsius Network</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/">Fahrenheit Consortium Wins Bid to Acquire Celsius Network</a></p>
<p>It is a good day for the embattled crypto lender Celsius Network as crypto consortium Fahrenheit LLC has <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230525005382/en/Celsius-Announces-Fahrenheit-LLC-as-Winning-Bidder-to-Manage-New-Entity-to-Be-Owned-by-Celsius-Creditors" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">won</a> the bid to acquire the insolvent firm whose assets were previously valued at $2 billion. According to a May 25th <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174905252380000000034.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">court filing</a>, the Arrington Capital-backed group emerged as the successful bidder after beating NovaWulf Digital Management.</p>
<p>Markedly, Fahrenheit is a conglomerate of buyers which include venture capital firm Arrington Capital and miner US Bitcoin Corp. The Blockchain Recovery Investment Consortium (BRIC), another corporation that comprises VanEck Absolute Return Advisers Corp and GXD Labs, became the backup bidder.</p>
<p>The deal is yet to be finalized as an initial deposit is expected within the next ten days after which Fahrenheit will receive the insolvent exchange’s institutional loan portfolio, staked cryptocurrencies, mining unit, as well as other alternative investments. Specifically, the new company will receive between $450 and $500 million in liquid cryptocurrency while US Bitcoin Corp will construct crypto mining facilities including a befitting 100-megawatt plant.</p>
<p>If the deposit agreement is not fulfilled within the stipulated time frame, the bid will be transferred to BRIC as NovaWulf has lost out. Also, the bid still requires regulatory approval before the acquisition can be completed. Meanwhile, bankruptcy court Judge Martin Glenn had once mentioned possible regulatory obstacles that may hinder the acquisition of Celsius similar to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-voyager-digital-judge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">case</a> of Binance Exchange and Voyager Digital.</p>
<p>In the coming weeks, the Celsius Network would work on negotiating and publicly filing a plan sponsor agreement with Fahrenheit, and a backup plan sponsor agreement with BRIC. It would also draft a revised version of its Chapter 11 plan and a disclosure statement, but at the same time, all these are subject to bankruptcy court approval.</p>
<p>The auction of Celsius Network’s assets <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-auction-tuesday-coinbase-gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">attracted</a> several reputable crypto-related entities including American cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), and privately run crypto custodian Gemini Trust.</p>
<h2>NovaWulf Proposal to Celsius Precedes Fahrenheit LLC&#8217;s</h2>
<p>From the initial stage, it looked like NovaWulf had the most leverage owing to its outstanding promises to borrowers.</p>
<p>The digital asset investment manager <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/celsius-acquisition-agreement/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">promised</a> as much as 85% returns to borrowers who had collateral to Celsius Network for moving accounts to the NovaWulf platform, according to a proposal submitted earlier. However, the borrowers would have to hold the loan collateral on a new NovaWulf platform for an additional five years.</p>
<p>Other Celsius creditors were also billed to receive a refund via tokenized equity on the Provenance Blockchain. While it seemed like an interesting proposal, it is worth noting that it is quite an unpopular strategy within the crypto ecosystem. Consequently, some Celsius borrowers were not comfortable with the proposal. Most of them were concerned about whether the new venture will survive long enough to fully repay their collateral.</p>
<p>Private equity giant Apollo Global which also planned to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apollo-acquiring-celsius/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquire</a> the assets of the bankrupt crypto exchange in partnership with the same Provenance Blockchain turned out to be an investor in the bid submitted by NovaWulf.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/">Fahrenheit Consortium Wins Bid to Acquire Celsius Network</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fahrenheit-consortium-celsius-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Creator OpenAI Considers EU Departure Over Stringent Regulations</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/">ChatGPT Creator OpenAI Considers EU Departure Over Stringent Regulations</a></p>
<p>OpenAI CEO warns of potential exit from Europe if the firm fails to meet regulatory requirements for the forthcoming AI rules. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/">ChatGPT Creator OpenAI Considers EU Departure Over Stringent Regulations</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/">ChatGPT Creator OpenAI Considers EU Departure Over Stringent Regulations</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, the brains behind the famous and controversial artificial intelligence (AI) ChatGPT, said Wednesday that it might consider leaving Europe if it faces challenges complying with the upcoming AI regulations in the region. Based in the United States, OpenAI encountered a major legal snag in Italy last month when its Data Protection regulator <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/italy-ban-chatgpt-other-countries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">banned</a> it from processing user requests on suspicion of violating the European Union&#8217;s (EU) strict data privacy laws.</p>
<p>Although the data watchdog has since lifted the ban on ChatGPT, the firm is still not out of the loop as the EU is working to establish a comprehensive regulatory framework to police AI. If passed, the EU would be the first region in the world to introduce such rules.</p>
<p>Under the drafted law, software development companies creating generative AI tools such as ChatGPT and Adobe&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adobe-blizzard-generative-ai-tools/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">newly launched</a> Generative Fill are mandated to disclose copyrighted materials used in programming their systems.</p>
<h2>OpenAI to Try to Comply with the EU&#8217;s AI Act before Withdrawal</h2>
<p>The pending legislation has forced OpenAI into considering withdrawal from the region if it fails to meet the requirements for the drafted law. According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/openai-may-leave-eu-if-regulations-bite-ceo-2023-05-24/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the company&#8217;s CEO Sam Altman said during a conference in London that the firm would try to comply with the European regulations once the law is passed before deciding to leave.</p>
<p>Altman believes that the current draft of the EU AI Act is overly stringent in its regulations, but he anticipates that revisions will be made as discussions continue. He also believes there will be ample opportunity for improvement in the drafted law, particularly by reconsidering the definition of general-purpose AI systems.</p>
<p>&#8220;The current draft of the EU AI Act would be over-regulating, but we have heard it will get pulled back. There&#8217;s so much they can do, like changing the definition of general-purpose AI systems. There&#8217;s a lot of things that can be done,&#8221; Altman said.</p>
<p>EU lawmakers reached a consensus on the drafted act in April, marking a significant milestone for the proposed laws. However, further debates will be held among representatives from Parliament, the Council, and the Commission to finalize the specifics of the AI regulation.</p>
<h2>EU Policymakers Call on the US to Develop Global Governing Principles for AI</h2>
<p>The rapid rise in AI popularity has stirred a growing concern for the need to develop a global rulebook to regulate the development of such technologies worldwide.</p>
<p>Last month, some European Union parliamentarians signed a letter calling on US President <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/joe-biden/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Joe Biden</a> and EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen to host a global summit to discuss creating a &#8220;preliminary set of governing principles&#8221; for developing, controlling, and deploying AI tools.</p>
<p>The letter, signed by the same members of the EU charged with curating the forthcoming AI regulations, comes after a group of prominent figures such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> and Steve Wozniak <a href="https://futureoflife.org/open-letter/pause-giant-ai-experiments/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">signed</a> a Future of Life Institute letter asking OpenAI to suspend further development of its chatbot.</p>
<p>The letter seeks to place a six-month temporary ban on developing powerful generative AI tools such as ChatGPT.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-base-network-roadmap-mainnet/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/">ChatGPT Creator OpenAI Considers EU Departure Over Stringent Regulations</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-eu-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4678 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1291563 metric#prefetches=205 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=14 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=112.90 metric#ms-cache=6.31 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1856 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.6 -->