<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:26:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Xsolla and Crypto.com Partner to Integrate Payment Solutions</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LOS ANGELES, United States, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire Xsolla, a global video game commerce company, and global cryptocurrency platform Crypto.com have announced a partnership for the integration of Crypto.com&#8217;s checkout solution into Xsolla&#8217;s Pay Station platform. This transformative integration of Crypto.com Pay represents a significant advancement in the gaming industry and creates new possibilities for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/">Xsolla and Crypto.com Partner to Integrate Payment Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>LOS ANGELES, United States, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Xsolla, a global video game commerce company, and global cryptocurrency platform Crypto.com have announced a partnership for the integration of Crypto.com&rsquo;s checkout solution into Xsolla&rsquo;s Pay Station platform.</p>
<p>This transformative integration of Crypto.com Pay represents a significant advancement in the gaming industry and creates new possibilities for game developers and players, enabling them to accept cryptocurrency payments and streamline transactions in a user-friendly and secure manner for a universally enhanced experience. This pivotal update broadens the horizon for digital payment methods, offering players more diverse and preferred transaction options in digital and metaverse environments. This collaboration also marks a significant step for Crypto.com in building its presence and network across the gaming industry.</p>
<p>&ldquo;There is significant potential in the convergence of gaming and Web3,&rdquo; said Eric Anziani, President and Chief Operating Officer of Crypto.com. &ldquo;By partnering with a global gaming leader like Xsolla and leveraging our respective assets and expertise, we are helping make that potential a reality &ndash; giving developers, publishers, and players a seamless way to engage and create value in the crypto economy.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Xsolla&rsquo;s Pay Station, which facilitates in-game purchases across 200+ regions and countries using a variety of compliant payment providers, is enhancing its service with the integration of Crypto.com Pay. This forthcoming development promises to expand the reach of developers and publishers, enabling them to engage a more diverse player base and tap into new, dynamic markets and revenue streams.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled about this partnership with Crypto.com and the significant integration of Crypto.com Pay into our Pay Station platform. The gaming industry is rapidly evolving, and we must adapt to meet those changes. The integration of cryptocurrencies as a form of payment offers game developers and players an innovative payment solution that aligns with the global shift towards digital currencies,&rdquo; said Chris Hewish, CEO of Xsolla. &ldquo;Our collaboration with Crypto.com marks a pivotal moment for the gaming industry, paving the way for a more inclusive and secure gaming ecosystem.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are tremendously excited to take this first step with Xsolla as part of a broader collaboration initiative in Korea and on a global level,&rdquo; said Patrick Yoon, General Manager of Crypto.com Korea. &ldquo;We look forward to continuing to work with Xsolla in developing and advancing payment ecosystems and digital asset adoption.&rdquo;</p>
<p><strong>For more information about Crypto.com Pay and Pay Station, please visit: </strong><a href="https://xsolla.pro/cryptocom" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>xsolla.pro/cryptocom</strong></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong></p>
<h3>About Xsolla</h3>
<p>Xsolla is a global video game commerce company with a robust and powerful set of tools and services designed specifically for the industry. Since its founding in 2005, Xsolla has helped thousands of game developers and publishers of all sizes fund, market, launch, and monetize their games globally and across multiple platforms. As an innovative leader in game commerce, Xsolla&rsquo;s mission is to solve the inherent complexities of global distribution, marketing, and monetization to help our partners reach more geographies, generate more revenue and create relationships with gamers worldwide. Headquartered and incorporated in Los Angeles, California, with offices in Berlin, Seoul, Beijing, Kuala Lumpur, Tokyo, and cities around the world, Xsolla supports major gaming titles like Valve, Twitch, Roblox, Ubisoft, Epic Games, Take-Two, KRAFTON, Nexters, NetEase, Playstudios, Playrix, miHoYo, and more.</p>
<p>For additional information and to learn more, please visit: <a href="https://xsolla.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">xsolla.com</a></p>
<h3>About Crypto.com</h3>
<p>Founded in 2016,<a href="http://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Crypto.com</a> is trusted by more than 80 million customers worldwide and is the industry leader in regulatory compliance, security, and privacy. Our vision is simple: Cryptocurrency in Every Wallet&trade;.<a href="http://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Crypto.com</a> is committed to accelerating the adoption of cryptocurrency through innovation and empowering the next generation of builders, creators, and entrepreneurs to develop a fairer and more equitable digital ecosystem.</p>
<p>Learn more at<a href="https://crypto.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> crypto.com</a></p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Global Director of Public Relations, Derrick Stembridge, Xsolla, d.stembridge@xsolla.com, 919-971-7855</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/">Xsolla and Crypto.com Partner to Integrate Payment Solutions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/xsolla-and-crypto-com-partner-to-integrate-payment-solutions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood: SEC may ‘approve more than one Bitcoin ETFs at once’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-wood-sec-approve-more-than-one-bitcoin-etfs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148881</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC has to rule on ARK&#8217;s application for a Bitcoin ETF by August 13th. Cathie Wood expects the financial regulator to extend that deadline. A summary of what else she said in an interview with Bloomberg today. The U.S. SEC will likely delay ruling on application for a Spot Bitcoin ETF that Ark Invest registered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-wood-sec-approve-more-than-one-bitcoin-etfs/">Cathie Wood: SEC may ‘approve more than one Bitcoin ETFs at once’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>SEC has to rule on ARK&rsquo;s application for a Bitcoin ETF by August 13th.</li>
<li>Cathie Wood expects the financial regulator to extend that deadline.</li>
<li>A summary of what else she said in an interview with Bloomberg today.</li>
</ul>
<p>The U.S. SEC will likely delay ruling on application for a Spot Bitcoin ETF that Ark Invest registered on May 15<sup>th</sup>, says Cathie Wood.</p>
<h2>Highlights from Wood&rsquo;s interview with Bloomberg</h2>
<p>Current deadline for the financial regulator to announce its decision on the said filing is August 13<sup>th</sup>. But the famed investor anticipates that the Securities and Exchange Commission will extend that deadline.</p>
<p>Speaking with <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-08-07/wood-sec-could-approve-more-than-one-bitcoin-etf-video" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bloomberg</a> this morning, the Founder and Chief Executive of Ark Invest also alluded to the possibility that the U.S. SEC may approve a bunch of Bitcoin ETFs at once.</p>
<blockquote><p>I think SEC, if it&rsquo;s going to approve a Bitcoin ETF, will approve more than one at once. Most of these will be same, and it&rsquo;ll come down to marketing and communicating the message.</p></blockquote>
<p>Other than her investment management firm, eight others, including <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/should-exchanges-fear-a-blackrock-etf/">BlackRock Inc</a>, have so far filed for such an exchange-traded fund.</p>
<h2>Wood is significantly invested in Grayscale Bitcoin Trust</h2>
<p>A Bitcoin ETF has been the front and centre of all crypto-related debates in recent months.</p>
<p>In fact, the possibility of one that may make it more convenient to gain exposure to BTC has largely contributed to the 80% <a href="https://www.thenationalnews.com/business/cryptocurrencies/2023/06/23/bitcoin-surges-to-highest-level-since-june-last-year/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">year-to-date rally</a> in Bitcoin. Wood also said on Monday:</p>
<blockquote><p>We&rsquo;ve been putting out our Bitcoin monthly for the last year. We&rsquo;re now starting a Bitcoin brainstorming session. We&rsquo;re trying to get the word out there that our research is deep.</p></blockquote>
<p>Note that the third largest holding in her Ark Next Generation Internet ETF at writing is Grayscale Bitcoin Trust. Wood refrained from commenting, though, on what she plans on doing with her investment in GBTC if a Spot <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> ETF gets a nod from the financial regulator.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cathie-wood-sec-approve-more-than-one-bitcoin-etfs/">Cathie Wood: SEC may ‘approve more than one Bitcoin ETFs at once’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Shiba Memu, Bitcoin Cash, Algorand</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-shiba-memu-bitcoin-cash-algorand/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-shiba-memu-bitcoin-cash-algorand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-shiba-memu-bitcoin-cash-algorand/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu token has raised over $1.64 million from investors. It is one of the most popular upcoming crypto tokens in the world. It combines key industries like AI and meme coins. Cryptocurrency prices moved sideways even as American equities jumped. Bitcoin remained slightly above $29,000 while the total market cap dropped by 0.42% to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-shiba-memu-bitcoin-cash-algorand/">Crypto price prediction: Shiba Memu, Bitcoin Cash, Algorand</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu token has raised over $1.64 million from investors.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It is one of the most popular upcoming crypto tokens in the world.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It combines key industries like AI and meme coins.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/"><u>Cryptocurrency prices</u></a> moved sideways even as American equities jumped. Bitcoin remained slightly above $29,000 while the total market cap dropped by 0.42% to $1.16 trillin. The Dow Jones and the Nasdaq 100 indices jumped by over 0.65% as investors embraced a risk-on sentiment. This article will look at the forecast for key cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin Cash, Algorand, and Shiba Memu.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is an upcoming cryptocurrency that is aiming to combine key technologies like artificial intelligence and meme coins. Its goal is to take advantage of the most hyped industries this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In AI, some of the best-performing companies and cryptocurrencies have been in the industry. Some of these firms are Nvidia, Microsoft, and C3.ai while the most popular crypto AI platforms are SingularityNET and Fetch.Ai.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu aims to be a better alternative to other popular cryptocurrencies like Shiba Inu, Dogecoin, and Pepe. It is also taking advantage of AI technology by self-marketing. It will do that by self-responding to user inquiries and grow from their feedback.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu will have&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>several technologies</u></a>, including Natural Language Processing (NLP), Sentiment analysis, predictive analysis, and personalization among others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s token sale has gained traction in the past few weeks. It has already raised over $1.6 million from global investors. The price of the token is rising on a daily basis. You can buy the Shiba Memu token&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The 4H chart shows that the BCH price has moved sideways in the past few days. This price action has mirrored that of Bitcoin, which has also dropped from the year-to-date high of $31,388 to $29,000. BCH price has moved slightly above the 25-period and 50-period moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price was also slightly above the 38.2% Fibonacci Retracement level. At the same time, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved slightly above the neutral point at 60. Therefore, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a> price will likely remain in this range for a while. The key support and resistance levels to watch will be at $219 and $260.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/07/1691439162821-fc07e18d-c88a-426d-a892-03bee95bb33b.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Algorand price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/algorand/"><u>Algorand</u></a> has been under pressure in the past few months. This pressure intensified recently when AlgoFi, the biggest DeFi platform in the ecosystem collapsed. ALGO price is consolidating at the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) drifted upwards.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Average True Range (ATR) has drifted downwards while the price is above the key support level at $0.1043. Volume has been constrained in the past few weeks. Therefore, the token will likely remain in a tight range in the coming days. The key support and resistance levels to watch will be at $0.10 and $0.12.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/07/1691439162821-1fff4d45-71a8-44ff-b0fe-649757b12020.png" style="width: 649px;height: 315.847px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="649" height="315.847"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-shiba-memu-bitcoin-cash-algorand/">Crypto price prediction: Shiba Memu, Bitcoin Cash, Algorand</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-shiba-memu-bitcoin-cash-algorand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin revisits $28.8k as crypto sees huge outflows</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-revisits-28-8k-as-crypto-sees-huge-outflows/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-revisits-28-8k-as-crypto-sees-huge-outflows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutional investors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-revisits-28-8k-as-crypto-sees-huge-outflows/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price fell to $28,800 across major exchanges as Ethereum hit lows near $1,800. Equities also showed signs of uncertainty with mixed trading recorded. Crypto investment products saw outflows totaling $107 million, the primary focus being BTC. Bitcoin traded near the $28,800 early afternoon on Monday as caution dictated overall sentiment across the market. Stocks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-revisits-28-8k-as-crypto-sees-huge-outflows/">Bitcoin revisits $28.8k as crypto sees huge outflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price fell to $28,800 across major exchanges as Ethereum hit lows near $1,800.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Equities also showed signs of uncertainty with mixed trading recorded.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto investment products saw outflows totaling $107 million, the primary focus being BTC.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> traded near the $28,800 early afternoon on Monday as caution dictated overall sentiment across the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stocks/">Stocks</a> were mixed in midday trading on Monday as earnings season starts to wind down and investors brace for an inflation reading crucial to the Federal Reserve decision making.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the S&amp;P 500 and Dow Jones Industrial Average held slightly positive ground at 0.5% and 0.9% respectively, the tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite and Rusell 2000 were down 0.1% and 0.2% respectively.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BTC hovers at key level amid huge outflows</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On Monday, digital assets manager CoinShares released the latest <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-143-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6d46f78754c" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">weekly report</a> on digital asset investment products flows. According to an analysis by the firm, total outflows for last week was $107 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin saw total weekly outflows of $111 million. Although outflows into short bitcoin products reportedly stopped for the first time in 14 weeks, those from the flagship cryptocurrency were the largest since March.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Ethereum recorded outflows of $6 million, while Solana outpaced the top altcoin with $9.5 million in inflows. There were also inflows of $0.5 million for XRP and $0.46 million for Litecoin. Uniswap had $0.8 million in outflows and Cardano with $0.3 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">James Butterfill, Head of Research at CoinShares noted in the report that the outflows have come amid increased profit taking deals in recent weeks. Also notable was the decline in weekly trading volumes for digital asset investment products and on-exchange volumes &ndash; which stood at 36% and 62% year-to-date respectively.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-revisits-28-8k-as-crypto-sees-huge-outflows/">Bitcoin revisits $28.8k as crypto sees huge outflows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-revisits-28-8k-as-crypto-sees-huge-outflows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DODO price jumps after Binance makes major announcement</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dodo-price-jumps-after-binance-makes-major-announcement/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dodo-price-jumps-after-binance-makes-major-announcement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralised exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/dodo-price-jumps-after-binance-makes-major-announcement/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DODO price jumped 33% after Binance announced the DODO perpetual contract. Users will access the product with up to 20x starting August 8 at 08:00 (UTC). DODO, the governance token of the decentralized exchange (DEX) platform of the same name, spiked by more than 33% on Monday morning. Within hours of an announcement from leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dodo-price-jumps-after-binance-makes-major-announcement/">DODO price jumps after Binance makes major announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">DODO price jumped 33% after Binance announced the DODO perpetual contract.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Users will access the product with up to 20x starting August 8 at 08:00 (UTC).</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">DODO, the governance token of the decentralized exchange (DEX) platform of the same name, spiked by more than 33% on Monday morning. Within hours of an announcement from leading crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a>, the price of DODO rose to $0.13, quickly jumping to a two-month high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The last time DODO traded at that level was in early June this year. Before today&rsquo;s upside, the token had traded in a range between $0.09 and $0.10.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Trade DODO with up to 20x leverage</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Binance earlier today <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-futures-will-launch-usd%E2%93%A2-m-dodo-perpetual-contract-with-up-to-20x-leverage-a5d54915771e4ec58aa835cebc7e314f" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> a DODO perpetual contract with up to 20x leverage, notifying customers that the product will go live on August 8, 2023 at 08:00 (UTC). The DODO perpetual contract will trade under the ticker symbol DODOXUSDT.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Binance, the product supports multi-assets mode, which means customers can trade DODOXUSDT across multiple margin assets. It means when one activates the multi-assets mode, they can use Bitcoin (BTC) as margin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">DODO token price rose quickly after the Binance announcement, spiking more than 33% within an hour to top its two-month peak.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The DODO tokens, which offer much more than governance functionality to holders, is more than 39% up on the seven-day log. However, it remains more than 98% down on its all-time high of $8.38 reached in May 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Some of the utility DODO holders enjoy include crowdpooling, receiving IDO allocations and trading fee discounts.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dodo-price-jumps-after-binance-makes-major-announcement/">DODO price jumps after Binance makes major announcement</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dodo-price-jumps-after-binance-makes-major-announcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal launches a US Dollar stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Fintech firm PayPal has launched a stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain. The stablecoin is backed by the US Dollar and was launched in partnership with Paxos. PayPal joins the stablecoin train Silicon Valley-based payments firm PayPal announced on Monday, August 7th, that it had launched a US Dollar stablecoin. In a&#160;press release earlier [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/">PayPal launches a US Dollar stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fintech firm PayPal has launched a stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The stablecoin is backed by the US Dollar and was launched in partnership with Paxos.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">PayPal joins the stablecoin train</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Silicon Valley-based payments firm PayPal announced on Monday, August 7th, that it had launched a US Dollar stablecoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a&nbsp;<a href="https://newsroom.paypal-corp.com/2023-08-07-PayPal-Launches-U-S-Dollar-Stablecoin" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>press release</u></a> earlier today, PayPal said the stablecoin was launched in conjunction with Paxos.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The stablecoin will be pegged to the US Dollar and made available to PayPal&rsquo;s customers in the United States over the coming weeks and months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a>, Dan Schulman, president and CEO of PayPal, stated that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;The shift toward digital currencies requires a stable instrument that is both digitally native and easily connected to fiat currency like the U.S. dollar. Our commitment to responsible innovation and compliance, and our track record delivering new experiences to our customers, provides the foundation necessary to contribute to the growth of digital payments through PayPal USD.</em>&ldquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">PYUSD is an ERC-20 stablecoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The stablecoin, dubbed, &nbsp;PayPal USD, or PYUSD, will be issued on the Ethereum blockchain. The stablecoin will be fully backed by U.S. dollar deposits, short-term Treasuries and similar cash equivalents.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">PayPal has been expanding its efforts in the cryptocurrency space in recent years. In May last year, the company&rsquo;s Vice President Richard Nash revealed that the payment giant&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-plans-to-integrate-all-crypto-and-blockchain-services-the-firms-vp-says/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>plans to embrace</u></a> every possible service related to cryptocurrency and blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">PayPal planned to release its stablecoin earlier but reportedly faced a setback. Eligible customers can make transfers using the stablecoin and also make purchases.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, PayPal said it would allow users to convert supported cryptocurrencies into or from PYUSD. The company added that;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;PayPal USD is designed to reduce friction for in-experience payments in virtual environments, facilitate fast transfers of value to support friends and family, send remittances or conduct international payments, enable direct flows to developers and creators, and foster the continued expansion into digital assets by the largest brands in the world. Most of the current volume of stablecoins is used in web3-specific environments &ndash; PayPal USD will be compatible with that ecosystem from day one and will soon be available on Venmo.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">PayPal believes that issuing the stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain could become useful to the larger cryptocurrency community</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/">PayPal launches a US Dollar stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/paypal-launches-a-us-dollar-stablecoin-on-the-ethereum-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CryptoMinerBros Celebrates 5 Years of Building the Future in the Crypto Mining Community</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=148795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kowloon city, HongKong, August 7th, 2023, Chainwire Founded in August 2018 and headquartered in Hong Kong, Crypto Miner Bros has become one of the leading crypto mining hardware distributors within five years of its launch. With a dedicated team of blockchain experts, e-commerce specialists, and crypto mining professionals, Crypto Miner Bros has become a reputable [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/">CryptoMinerBros Celebrates 5 Years of Building the Future in the Crypto Mining Community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Kowloon city, HongKong, August 7th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Founded in August 2018 and headquartered in Hong Kong, <a href="https://www.cryptominerbros.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Crypto Miner Bros</a> has become one of the leading crypto mining hardware distributors within five years of its launch. With a dedicated team of blockchain experts, e-commerce specialists, and crypto mining professionals, Crypto Miner Bros has become a reputable name in the crypto mining industry.</p>
<p>Crypto Miner Bros has built an incredible mining community that wholeheartedly believes in the company&rsquo;s vision of making crypto mining accessible to everyone. The company&rsquo;s progress and achievements would not have been possible without the invaluable support of the clients. Crypto Miner Bros is committed to giving back to the community by offering the world&rsquo;s finest crypto mining tools and comprehensive end-to-end crypto mining solutions.</p>
<p>In August 2018, Crypto Miner Bros started as an E-commerce platform specializing in crypto mining hardware with a vision of providing miners with a positive crypto mining experience. Within one year of its launch, the company had already become one of the world&rsquo;s most trusted platforms for crypto mining hardware. Crypto Miner Bros is endorsed by globally recognized brands such as Nicehash, Asic Miner Value, Crypto Compare, Whattomine, and CoinWarz. The company&rsquo;s goal for the upcoming year is to continue making crypto mining accessible to everyone, spreading the benefits of this technology far and wide.</p>
<p>Buying crypto mining hardware from a reliable source has always been challenging for international buyers. Crypto Miner Bros provides an excellent platform for miners by joining hands with reputed mining hardware manufacturers in China and Hong Kong. Miners can find all the reputed mining hardware brands from Bitmain to Canaan Avalon Goldshell, Jasminer, MicroBT, Innosilicon, and more on the Crypto Miner Bros <a href="https://www.cryptominerbros.com/product-brands/innosilicon/?orderby=date" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">website</a>.</p>
<p>Entering its sixth year, Crypto Miner Bros focuses on bridging the gap between miners and manufacturers and getting quality crypto mining products to the global market. The company constantly strives to expand the mining community of Crypto Miner Bros in the coming year by introducing P2P (Peer-to-Peer) deals. Thus, miners can readily access advanced ASICs at better deals and enjoy hassle-free buying. The company also aids faster shipping to customers worldwide with its dedicated sales team. Though Crypto Miner Bros has an active international sales team, the organization plans to have dedicated technical support centers in every continent. Thus, the company can promptly ship the miners to any location and assist the customer with their queries. Besides, Crypto Miner Bros will continue to act as a reliable platform for all crypto miners with a rich source of information related to crypto mining, cryptocurrencies, blockchain, and other related topics. Moreover, the company&rsquo;s dedicated customer support team will assist the customers 24/7 in setting up the ASIC or any hiccups customers may face with crypto mining.</p>
<h3>About Crypto Miner Bros</h3>
<p>Crypto Miner Bros, a leading Asic hardware provider, continues delivering high-quality products and services worldwide to all crypto mining enthusiasts. The company partners with reputed mining hardware manufacturers and deals with high-quality mining equipment to provide a positive mining experience to its customers. For more information visit Crypto Miner&rsquo;s <a href="https://www.cryptominerbros.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official website</a>.</p>
<p>Crypto Miner Bros extends its heartfelt gratitude to its customers, stakeholders, and employees. Crypto Miner Bros promises to continue delivering excellent products and services in the years to come. Miners can look forward to Crypto Miner Bros for advanced mining equipment, informative videos, educational content, and, of course, 24/7 assistance.</p>
<h3>Contact Crypto Miner Bros</h3>
<p>Whatsapp / Wechat / Call : <a href="https://wa.me/8613530796464" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">+86-13530796464</a></p>
<p>USA Hotline: +1-806-305-324</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>COO, Han Su, Crypto Miner Bros, contact@cryptominerbros.com, +86-13530796464</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/">CryptoMinerBros Celebrates 5 Years of Building the Future in the Crypto Mining Community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong regulator warns crypto exchanges, Shiba Memu marches on</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-warns-crypto-exchanges-about-improper-practices/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 12:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-warns-crypto-exchanges-about-improper-practices/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong regulator the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) published the warning on August 7. Crypto exchanges yet to apply for licences but have gone ahead to publicise the same. Shiba Memu presale gathers speed with over $1.6 collected from early investors. Crypto exchanges looking to acquire virtual assets trading licences in Hong Kong have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-warns-crypto-exchanges-about-improper-practices/">Hong Kong regulator warns crypto exchanges, Shiba Memu marches on</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Hong Kong regulator the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) published the warning on August 7.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto exchanges yet to apply for licences but have gone ahead to publicise the same.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu presale gathers speed with over $1.6 collected from early investors.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">Crypto exchanges</a> looking to acquire virtual assets trading licences in Hong Kong have been warned that offering certain services and products are not allowed.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, one major <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">crypto news</a> headline today has been around Huobi, a crypto exchange looking to set up shop in Hong Kong. The exchange as well as Tron founder Justin Sun have termed insolvency rumours as more FUD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Quietly gaining fresh momentum despite these developments is the <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shiba Memu presale</a>. As seen on the new meme coin&rsquo;s website, investors eyeing new gems linked to artificial intelligence have poured nearly $1.64 million into the native SHMU token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hong Kong&rsquo;s warning to unlicensed exchanges</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Securities and Futures Commission, Hong Kong&rsquo;s securities regulator, today released a statement warning that some cryptocurrency exchanges are offering products for which they have no approval or license.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the agency, this translates to &ldquo;improper practices,&rdquo; by unlicensed virtual asset trading platforms (VATPs). &nbsp;Per the SFC, some unlicensed exchanges have falsely claimed to have applied for licenses from the regulator when they have taken no such step.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>These untrue and misleading claims give the public a false sense of assurance that the VATP is in compliance with the SFC&rsquo;s regulatory requirements</em>,&rdquo; the <a href="https://apps.sfc.hk/edistributionWeb/gateway/EN/news-and-announcements/news/doc?refNo=23PR87" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">statement</a> read.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Such claims amount to &ldquo;fraudulent or reckless misrepresentation&rdquo; aimed at inducing traders, the SFC warned and have likely been tailored to exploit the transitional arrangements in place as Hong Kong bring into effect new crypto rules relating to retail investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Some unlicensed VATPs set up new entities to provide virtual asset services in Hong Kong. They also publicly announced their intention to apply for licences for these new entities. However, the services and products offered by some of these new entities may not be in compliance with the legal and regulatory requirements under the new regime</em>,&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The SFC&rsquo;s warning also involved the launch of new products and services, including crypto derivatives and earn accounts &ndash; these are not allowed as per the new regulatory framework.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI-powered token like no other in meme coin-sphere</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a revolutionary meme token currently in the development phase. When it finally launches, it will boast of a self-sufficient marketing system powered by artificial intelligence (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a>).</p>
<p dir="ltr">AI and blockchain technology combine to give this token a unique pull compared to other meme coins. Unlike other meme coin projects, Shiba Memu is designed no to rely on human efforts for traction. Rather, Shiba Memu looks to deploy an AI dashboard that will drive the marketing strategies of the SHMU ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For this doge-inspired meme coin, AI promises to be the secret ingredient at the heart of its marketing genius.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Natural language processing, personalization and AI-powered image and video recognition technology are all integrated to give Shiba Memu the edge over competing tokens, including the likes of Dogecoin, Shiba Inu and Pepe.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Can Shiba Memu be a good long term investment?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Part of the expected success will come from the AI dashboard&rsquo;s capability to engage with ecosystem users directly. The AI robot dashboard, per the Shiba Memu whitepaper, will gather all there&rsquo;s in terms of industry news, hype and developments to bring more people to SHMU.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Users on the other hand will have an opportunity provide feedback or give suggestions aimed at creating more traction for SHMU, and in return receive rewards in the native token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">If the project delivers on its AI dashboard, it could potentially slalom towards the top of the meme coin charts. Long-term investors currently participating in its presale could thus be in position for significant returns.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Note that SHMU price increases every 24 hours while the presale is expected to run for just eight weeks &ndash; more than half of which is gone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Learn more about Shiba Memu on the project&rsquo;s website, or buy SHMU <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hong-kong-warns-crypto-exchanges-about-improper-practices/">Hong Kong regulator warns crypto exchanges, Shiba Memu marches on</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WorldCoin faces renewed headwinds as WLD price retreats</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-wld-price-retreats/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-wld-price-retreats/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 12:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-wld-price-retreats/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WorldCoin, the new blockchain project started by Sam Altman, is going through major headwinds as regulators remain concerned about data privacy. As a result, the WLD token price has plunged by more than 72% from the highest level this year. The total volume of the tokn traded in exchanges has dropped. Headwinds continue WorldCoin was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-wld-price-retreats/">WorldCoin faces renewed headwinds as WLD price retreats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">WorldCoin, the new blockchain project started by Sam Altman, is going through major headwinds as regulators remain concerned about data privacy. As a result, the WLD token price has plunged by more than 72% from the highest level this year. The total volume of the tokn traded in exchanges has dropped.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Headwinds continue</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-to-launch-its-wld-token-and-mainnet-today/"><u>WorldCoin was recently launched</u></a> with a lot of hype, mostly because of its founder, who was the creator of ChatGPT. The key challenge for the network is the data collection part of its operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of the strategy, the developers are collecting user data by scanning their iris using the Orb device. Many countries, especially in Europe, have warned the company against collecting its users data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Authorities in Kenya last week suspended the data collection as thousands of people participated in the process. These people were promised to receive tokens worth about $50. That was a high figure in a country where the youth unemployment rate stands at a record high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now, authorities in Kenya have raided a warehouse belonging to WorldCoin. A report by a Kenyan media company said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The officers backed by multi-agency officials went to the offices along Mombasa Road armed with a search warrant and broke in Saturday before leaving with machines they believe stores data gathered by the firm.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a recent statement, authorities in the UK warned that the company must work in line with the Data Protection Impact Assessment (DPIA) before collecting user data.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Organisations must conduct a Data Protection Impact Assessment (DPIA) before starting any processing that is likely to result in high risk, such as processing special category biometric data. Where they identify high risks that they cannot mitigate, they must consult the ICO.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">WLD price has lost steam</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/07/1691409714411-e62b7667-ead4-47fc-8056-94dd65005df1.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<p dir="ltr">WorldCoin&rsquo;s token, WLD, has been in a tight range in the past few days. On the 30-minute chart, we see that the token has formed a double-bottom pattern, which is usually a bullish sign. The token remains below the important resistance level at $2.20, the lowest point on August 1.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the token will likely remain in a consolidation phase in the coming days. A bullish breakout will likely see it rise to about $2.20. A break below the support at $2 will invalidate the bullish view.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-wld-price-retreats/">WorldCoin faces renewed headwinds as WLD price retreats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/worldcoin-faces-renewed-headwinds-as-wld-price-retreats/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
