<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: XDC Network, Polkadot, dYdX</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies remained in a tight range this week as Bitcoin continued to ping pong around the $30,000 support level. The crypto fear and greed index consolidated at the neutral point at 52 while volumes remained low. This article will provide predictions of some of the top performers during the week, including XDC Network, Polkadot, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/">Crypto price prediction: XDC Network, Polkadot, dYdX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/"><u>Cryptocurrencies</u></a> remained in a tight range this week as Bitcoin continued to ping pong around the $30,000 support level. The crypto fear and greed index consolidated at the neutral point at 52 while volumes remained low. This article will provide predictions of some of the top performers during the week, including XDC Network, Polkadot, and dYdX.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XDC Network price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">XDC Network is a small layer-1 and EVM-compatible network with enterprise grade features. It has higher transaction speeds and lower costs. Some of the players in its ecosystem are Copper, Vinter, Fireblocks, and Fluent, among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">XDC Network price has been in the green in the past five straight days and is now hovering at the highest level since April 2022. At its peak, the token was up by more than 41% from the lowest level this month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the daily chart, the coin has moved above the 50-day and 25-day moving averages, which is a bullish sign. Most importantly, XDC is hovering at an important resistance point since this price was the highest level on June 1st. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved to the overbought level.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, XDC network&rsquo;s rally will likely take a breather in the coming days. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.035.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689940841076-a5213bf7-9c77-40f4-af89-b78d23005b52.jpg" style="width: 623px;height: 282.427px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="623" height="282.427"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">DYDX price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The DYDX token price has done well in the past few days even as exchange volume has eased. This performance happened even as volume in the ecosystem dropped slightly. It also coincided with the strong performance of other DeFi tokens like&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/maker/"><u>Maker</u></a> and Compound.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The daily chart shows that the DYDX token rose from June&rsquo;s low of $1.3653 in June to $2.14. It has moved above the 50-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) rose above the neutral point. Volume has been a bit low. Therefore, the token will likely remain in this range during the weekend.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689940841274-cbb68339-a1a3-45f3-b7fb-4444970d18ab.jpg" style="width: 627px;height: 282.562px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="627" height="282.562"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Polkadot price forecast</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/polkadot"><u>Polkadot</u></a> has been in a tight range this week since there was no ecosystem news. It has remained above the support at $5.15, the important support point at $5.15, the lowest level on March 10th.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polkadot price has also remained slightly above the 50-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved above the neutral at 50. It is a few points below the support at $5.72, the highest point last week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the outlook for the coin is neutral, with the next level to watch being at $5.72. A move above that level in a high-volume environment will confirm a bullish breakout.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689940840751-711c7f7e-93be-45db-befe-9c897fe8b8bc.jpg" style="width: 668px;height: 302.314px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="668" height="302.314"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Polkadot</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQ3MTE3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    OKX</h3>

    <p>OKX is a world-leading cryptocurrency exchange, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/okx-crypto?guid=MTQ3MTE3&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy DOT with OKX today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Trading in digital assets is considered high risk. Digital assets are NOT backed by any government or central bank. The risk of loss in trading or holding digital assets can be substantial. You should carefully consider whether interacting, holding, or trading digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/">Crypto price prediction: XDC Network, Polkadot, dYdX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-xdc-network-polkadot-dydx/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Countdown to the 2nd phase of the Chancer presale amid strong demand for token</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer presale has seen strong demand as investors bet on blockchain-based betting. Less than 10% of Chancer tokens remain before the first stage presale concludes. The value of Chancer could rise strongly after listing on Uniswap in Q3 2023 and after the mainnet launch in early 2024. Chancer, a blockchain-based predictive markets application, opened the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/">Countdown to the 2nd phase of the Chancer presale amid strong demand for token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer presale has seen strong demand as investors bet on blockchain-based betting.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Less than 10% of Chancer tokens remain before the first stage presale concludes.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The value of Chancer could rise strongly after listing on Uniswap in Q3 2023 and after the mainnet launch in early 2024.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer, a blockchain-based predictive markets application, opened the presale on June 13th, 2023. Five weeks later, investors bought almost $905,000 in tokens in the first phase. The amount suggests that Chancer is imminently sold out at the current price of $0.01 since the first stage targets $1 million. Investors seeking to buy the token can do so via the company&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a> before the price rises in the second stage.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Why is Chancer in high demand?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Raising funds quickly through a presale suggests investors see value in Chancer. So, what does the token offer?</p>
<p dir="ltr">$CHANCER is the native token that will power a blockchain-enabled platform Chancer. It is the world&rsquo;s first blockchain betting platform that allows users to bet against each other through a peer-to-peer (P2P) model.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The opportunity lies in tapping into the fast-growing online gambling and bringing it to blockchain. According to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.acumenresearchandconsulting.com/online-gambling-market" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>market reports</u></a>, online gambling will grow by 11.6% CAGR in this decade to hit $172 billion by 2030. Investors are betting on Chancer to revolutionise betting, given the growing application of blockchain in several other sectors.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is the value proposition of Chancer and its P2P model?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer carries a value proposition in that it lets users bet on numerous events, outcomes, and situations. This happens as users create their own Chancer P2P markets and determine what to predict in those markets. They can then invite friends or join Chancer markets created by others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The exciting bit of P2P betting is that it allows flexibility. Users can bet on their preferred events, replacing the existing model where the bookmaker creates betting markets. Users can also determine the rules and odds for each bet via Chancer.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides rewards on successful bets, Chancer lets users earn from market-making activities or creating P2P markets. That makes Chancer more than just a betting platform. The Chancer token can also be staked, allowing investors to earn passive incomes and improve their bottom lines.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer roadmap and predictions in 2023, 2024</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is in the presale phase, but the demand for the project is already high. While the value of Chancer is increasing at each presale phase, the potential value of the token will be unlocked in the third and fourth quarters of 2023. This is when the token will be listed on exchanges. The token&rsquo;s roadmap points to the first listing on Uniswap in the third quarter. The team eyes at least two CEX listings in Q3.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the fourth quarter, product development will begin. It will start with the testnet, aiming to pave the way for the full mainnet launch in the first quarter of 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The launch of the mainnet will be influential for Chancer as it actualizes the dream of bringing forth P2P betting. While our prediction is that the value of the Chancer token could start to rise in the third quarter of 2023, 2024 will be the most influential. This is when sustainable gains could be realised, allowing Chancer to go mainstream and become more acceptable.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the above roadmap, the value of Chancer could rise initially by double or triple-digit percentages in 2023. In 2024, the value could skyrocket by more than 10x heading into the future, where Chancer&rsquo;s future acceptance will allow more gains.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy Chancer this week?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Only 10% of Chancer tokens remain before the first stage of the presale concludes. After that, the price will increase by 10% in the second phase.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With the demand for the token showing little signs of slowing down, chances are that the first phase will conclude in a few days. Thus, it could be the right time to grab the remaining tokens before the price increases to $0.011.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/">Countdown to the 2nd phase of the Chancer presale amid strong demand for token</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/countdown-to-the-2nd-phase-of-the-chancer-presale-amid-strong-demand-for-token/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer underscores future of online betting with epic presale</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer presale sees strong investor interest with over $835k raised just weeks into the token sale. Chancer could disrupt the online betting industry via a revolutionary P2P betting model. Early buyers of $CHANCER can now do so with ETH, USDT, BUSD and BNB. A recent&#160;report from K33 Research revealed that the global crypto industry currently [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/">Chancer underscores future of online betting with epic presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer presale sees strong investor interest with over $835k raised just weeks into the token sale.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Chancer could disrupt the online betting industry via a revolutionary P2P betting model.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Early buyers of $CHANCER can now do so with ETH, USDT, BUSD and BNB.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">A recent<a href="https://k33.com/research/articles/the-global-crypto-industry" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>report</u></a> from K33 Research revealed that the global crypto industry currently stands at $180 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the global online betting and gambling market is worth over $60 billion. Growth projections for these sectors point to an average of 11% CAGR to 2030. It is a scenario that alludes to the unprecedented growth investors anticipate for both crypto and online betting.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Tucked in between and out to underscore this future is <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Chancer</a>, one of the most exciting crypto project for the betting industry whose presale has seen incredible interest and investment.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s unique approach to the online betting</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to its<a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf">&nbsp;<u>whitepaper</u></a>, Chancer is building the &ldquo;<em>world&rsquo;s first decentralized social predictive markets platform</em>.&rdquo; The goal is to redefine the online betting market with a new peer-to-peer (P2P) model that puts control over market making into the hands of the user.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The project leverages blockchain technology to allow users be in charge of their markets, odds and rules &ndash; simply play your game at your own rules.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">No centralised power as is the case with current market where bookmaker have the biggest say in what bettors can access and how they do it. On Chancer, users can create a predictive market on any event, right from the local market&rsquo;s most mundane occurences, to the world&rsquo;s biggest sports and entertainment events.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is also not just another betting platform &ndash; it is designed to grow into a robust community spanning the global market. Its core features of blockchain and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a> support enhance the outlook of a project set to revolutionise the predictive markets space, likely attracting more and more users as all that is deficient with the traditional online betting platforms is essentially removed.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Powering Chancer&rsquo;s P2P betting model is its native token $CHANCER. Apart from handing control to the user, $CHANCER opens up the platform to true decentralisation. It also promises to democratise social betting with integration of bet sharing and livestreaming features.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">$CHANCER&rsquo;s blockbuster presale</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto space currently has numerous token presales for projects looking to raise funds from prospective early backers. At any given time, these projects see varying degrees of success, including reaching targeted amounts to support roadmap milestones.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale is proving to be one of the success stories already, less than six weeks into the event. After surpassing the $750k mark last week, the amount of $CHANCER sold has topped $835k and is poised to hit the landmark $1 million in record time.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total supply for $CHANCER is 1.5 billion tokens, 65% of which will be available throughout the 12 stage presale phase. Investors can buy tokens using ETH, USDT, BUSD and BNB, the first two buy options recently added in a step that could see more people easily buy $CHANCER.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Buy $CHANCER <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Will $CHANCER price reach $1 in 2024?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At present, the Chancer presale price is $0.01 and will jump to $0.011 in the next stage. The token&rsquo;s price at the end of the presale is set to be $0.021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto investors might view these prices as an ideal entry point, particularly for a project that&rsquo;s projected to take a big bite from a market expected to see significant growth all through to 2030.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With interest so high and crypto flying following Ripple&rsquo;s recent victory against the SEC, it&rsquo;s likely the token will sell out faster than anticipated. This even as investors eye a position in what could be the biggest investment opportunity of 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As for price, its difficult to pinpoint future performance due to the factors that can be at play during given market scenarios. A confluence of factors could help catapult Chancer price higher, including a raging bull market fueled by approval for first US spot Bitcoin ETF, regulatory clarity and the mainnet launch.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, while a token launching in a bull market phase &ndash; as $CHANCER is likely when it goes live in Q1, 2024 &ndash; opposite market conditions could hinder the would be price discovery. </p>
<p dir="ltr">Interested in buying $CHANCER? <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Join the presale</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-underscores-future-of-online-betting-with-epic-presale/">Chancer underscores future of online betting with epic presale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI market size prediction bodes well for AltSignals (ASI)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-market-size-prediction-bodes-well-for-altsignals-asi/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-market-size-prediction-bodes-well-for-altsignals-asi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 05:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-market-size-prediction-bodes-well-for-altsignals-asi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The AI industry is expected to grow to almost $2 trillion by 2030. AltSignals has raised more than $1.1 million in its second phase of the token sale The Artificial Intelligence (AI) market is expected to continue growing in the coming years as demand from individuals and corporations rises. The most recent intelligence report on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-market-size-prediction-bodes-well-for-altsignals-asi/">AI market size prediction bodes well for AltSignals (ASI)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The AI industry is expected to grow to almost $2 trillion by 2030.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has raised more than $1.1 million in its second phase of the token sale</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The Artificial Intelligence (AI) market is expected to continue growing in the coming years as demand from individuals and corporations rises. The most recent intelligence <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/1365145/artificial-intelligence-market-size/"><u>report</u></a> on the industry showed that the market size stood at $207 billion in 2023 and that it will soar to almost $2 trillion by 2030.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/21/1689916826814-3deb6567-09f0-4aa5-ab13-ad6562e58a88.jpg" style="width: 648px;height: 410.4px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="648" height="410.4"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AI market to grow</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The AI industry will continue growing as demand rises internationally. Analysts believe that AI models will disrupt all industries. For example, Hollywood actors and writers have gone on strike to protest the use of AI models in their work.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many news organizations are now implementing AI in their operations. Besides, a well-trained AI model can now do a better job than most individuals. Most importantly, AI models will likely replace many financial analysts. Some quant hedge funds have found a lot of success using these models.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result, many companies are now investing heavily in AI. Microsoft spent over $10 billion investing in ChatGPT while Google has launched a similar platform. Apple has also built its own ChatGPT rival and is testing it internally.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, Elon Musk has launched xAI, a company that will build AI tools. And Nvidia, the biggest semiconductor company in the world, is building technologies that will power the AI industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is unclear how the AI industry will affect the world in the future. While some analysts see it leading to job losses, others believe that it will create jobs in the long run.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals token sale continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, investors from around the world are still investing in&nbsp;<a href="https://www.altsignals.io/"><u>AltSignals</u></a>. The token sale has now raised over $1.19 million in its second stage. This means that the developers have sold over 53% of their $2.25 million target. Each ASI token is going for 0.01875 USDT and the price will rise by 12.05% in the next stage.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a financial services company that is seeking to incorporate artificial intelligence in its processes. The existing product, which is highly accurate and has thousands of customers, will be upgraded with a more advanced AI one.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to AltSignals&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the developers will use several advanced technologies like natural language processing (NLP) and machine learning to come up with predictions. The ecosystem will be powered by the ASI token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, customers with more ASI tokens will receive more features like ActualizeAI, AltScalpPro, and discounts on all AI products. In the future, they will also be able to vote on key details in the ecosystem. You can buy the AltSignals token&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is it safe to buy ASI?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are three main reasons why AltSignals will be the next big thing in the crypto industry. First, unlike meme coins that don&rsquo;t have a utility, ASI has a real use in that it powers the AltSignals ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, AltSignals is in industries that are growing fast: finance and AI. This year, we have seen many AI coins like SingularityNET and Fetch AI jump by more than 500%. Finally, AltSignals is a genuine company with thousands of customers and positive Trustpilot reviews.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Still, you should be cautious when investing in AltSignals and other token presales. One way to mitigate risks is to ensure that you are investing a small portion of your funds in it.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-market-size-prediction-bodes-well-for-altsignals-asi/">AI market size prediction bodes well for AltSignals (ASI)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ai-market-size-prediction-bodes-well-for-altsignals-asi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Galaxy Digital CEO: ‘I’m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/galaxy-digital-ceo-shares-view-on-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=147030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Novogratz puts Bitcoin and Gold in the same bucket. Wolfe Research strategist reiterated his bullish view on BTC. Bitcoin is currently up 80% versus the start of the year 2023. Owning Bitcoin today is nowhere as scary as it was about six months ago, says Michael Novogratz &#8211; the Chief Executive of Galaxy Digital. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/galaxy-digital-ceo-shares-view-on-bitcoin/">Galaxy Digital CEO: ‘I’m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Michael Novogratz puts Bitcoin and Gold in the same bucket.</li>
<li>Wolfe Research strategist reiterated his bullish view on BTC.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up 80% versus the start of the year 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>Owning <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> today is nowhere as scary as it was about six months ago, says Michael Novogratz &ndash; the Chief Executive of Galaxy Digital.</p>
<h2>Novogratz shares his view on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Interest rates continued to go up this year; FTX collapsed; the U.S. Securities &amp; Exchange Commission came down hard on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">bellwethers</a> of the crypto space.</p>
<p>And yet, Bitcoin has outperformed every other financial asset &ndash; now up 80% year-to-date.</p>
<p>What that establishes beyond doubt, as per Novogratz, is that the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency is here to stay. On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/20/im-more-comfortable-being-along-bitcoin-today-than-i-was-6-months-ago-galaxy-digital-ceo-novogratz.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk Box</a>&rdquo;, he said:</p>
<blockquote><p>The normalization of 5.0% budget deficit &hellip; is why Bitcoin, gold, silver trade great. I put them all in the same bucket. Bitcoin has got the additional adoption cycle.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Novogratz sees Bitcoin as digital gold</h2>
<p>Novogratz drives his optimism also from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-03/blackrock-s-bitcoin-etf-application-is-refiled-by-nasdaq-to-sec" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> that has recently filed with the regulator for a Spot Bitcoin ETF which could boost institutional interest in the digital asset.</p>
<blockquote><p>I&rsquo;m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today than I was six months ago. I like to think of BTC as digital gold to store value.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1d1de06a-a904-4db3-9017-4c061bd6854d" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jacobi Asset Management</a> is all set to debut its Bitcoin-focused exchange-traded fund in Europe by the end of this year.</p>
<p>Also on Thursday, Wolfe Research strategist Rob Ginsberg reiterated his bullish view on BTC. He agreed, though, that the cryptocurrency has to fight an uphill battle to reclaim its former highs.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/galaxy-digital-ceo-shares-view-on-bitcoin/">Galaxy Digital CEO: ‘I’m more comfortable being long Bitcoin today’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Reserve launches &#8216;FedNow&#8217; instant payment system</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The newly launched FedNow Service aims to empower banks and credit unions. FedNow will allow for the execution of transactions 24/7 365 days a year. 35 banks and credit unions, including the U Bureau of the Fiscal Service of the US Department of the Treasury, are already equipped to handle payments through the FedNow Service. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/">Federal Reserve launches &#8216;FedNow&#8217; instant payment system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The newly launched FedNow Service aims to empower banks and credit unions.</li>
<li>FedNow will allow for the execution of transactions 24/7 365 days a year.</li>
<li>35 banks and credit unions, including the U Bureau of the Fiscal Service of the US Department of the Treasury, are already equipped to handle payments through the FedNow Service.</li>
</ul>
<p>The FedNow&reg; Service, the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s instant payment platform, <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/other20230720a.htm?utm_source=dlvr.it&amp;utm_medium=twitter">went live</a> officially on Thursday morning. The service will allow banks and credit unions of all sizes instantly process the transactions of their clients.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve asserts that FedNow transactions can be carried out every day of the year, around the clock.</p>
<p>To begin with, 35 banks and credit unions and the Bureau of the Fiscal Service of the US Department of the Treasury are among those who are already prepared to handle payments through the FedNow Service. Furthermore, a group of 16 service providers is prepared to support banks and credit unions with payment processing.</p>
<h2>Prudent payments for individuals and companies via FedNow</h2>
<p>Explaining the benefits of the instant payment system, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;The Federal Reserve built the FedNow Service to help make everyday payments over the coming years faster and more convenient. Over time, as more banks choose to use this new tool, the benefits to individuals and businesses will include enabling a person to immediately receive a paycheck, or a company to instantly access funds when an invoice is paid.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p>Jerome Powell, however, clarified that the newly launched system is not attempting to replace fiat money. He said that FedNow is &ldquo;not related to a digital currency.&rdquo; He added that &ldquo;it is like other Federal Reserve payment services, such as Fedwire and FedACH. The FedNow Service is neither a form of currency nor a step toward eliminating any form of payment, including cash.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/federal-reserve-launches-fednow-instant-payment-system/">Federal Reserve launches &#8216;FedNow&#8217; instant payment system</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Labs invests $10 million in DeFi project Radiant</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Labs&#8217; strategic investment in Radiant Capital will help the DeFi protocol expands its product to more EVM chains. The price of Radiant&#8217;s native token RDNT rose 10% following the news. Binance Labs, the venture capital arm of world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange Binance, has invested $10 million in decentralised crypto lender Radiant Capital (RDNT). Radiant&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/">Binance Labs invests $10 million in DeFi project Radiant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance Labs&rsquo; strategic investment in Radiant Capital will help the DeFi protocol expands its product to more EVM chains.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of Radiant&rsquo;s native token RDNT rose 10% following the news.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Labs, the venture capital arm of world&rsquo;s leading crypto exchange <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/"><u>Binance</u></a>, has invested $10 million in decentralised crypto lender Radiant Capital (RDNT).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant&rsquo;s lending and borrowing protocol is built on top of LayerZero, one of Binance Labs&rsquo; portfolio companies.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Radiant to use funds to expand its DeFi product</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to an&nbsp;<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-labs-invests-%2410-million-in-radiant-to-support--its-mission-to-lead-the-next-era-of-defi-lending-1438479277678345894" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>announcement</u></a> from Binance, the strategic funding round continues Binance Labs&rsquo; commitment towards crypto innovation, including in supporting next-generation chain-agnostic DeFi projects.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant brings this goal to the market by taking on the fragmented liquidity that beleaguers the DeFi ecosystem. The platform promotes this by allowing users to tap into a bridging innovation to borrow and lend across any chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Binance Labs actively seeks out promising DeFi projects that not only advance the industry but also push the boundaries of innovation. Radiant Capital&rsquo;s commitment to facilitating seamless cross-chain transactions for DeFi, and performance on Arbitrum and BNB Chain demonstrates its potential for driving mass adoption</em>,&rdquo; Binance co-founder and head of Binance Labs Yi He said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-h1-2023/"><u>reported</u></a> today, Binance has released a mid-year report for the crypto industry in which the exchange highlights growth in the past six months. One of the areas to see significant growth is DeFi.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Radiant team says the funding comes at a crucial time as the platform looks to expand its product to more EVM chains. This will add to the traction seen on Arbitrum and BNB Chain, with the protocol looking to become of the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-defi-projects/"><u>best DeFi platforms</u></a> in the world.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Growth is expected to include expansion of oracle support, collateral, cross liquidations and abstract repayments. Also crucial in the product development is deployment on Ethereum mainnet and full integration with LayerZero&rsquo;s messaging support.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant believes the developments will see the next 100 million users come into and benefit from DeFi. Commenting on this milestone, Radiant Capital founder George Macallan said that the partnership with Binance Labs allows his platform to benefit from Binance&rsquo;s &ldquo;extensive expertise, resources, and strategic support.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Their investment will play a crucial role in propelling Radiant to new heights as the protocol expands to new chains, continues to scale, and drives utility back into the ecosystem</em>,&rdquo; he added.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Radiant&rsquo;s native token RDNT reacted positively to the news, with its value jumping 10% to near $0.32.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-announces-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/">Binance Labs invests $10 million in DeFi project Radiant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kuwait bans all crypto activities including mining</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After the July 19 circular, it is illegal to engage in any cryptocurrency activities in Kuwait. Kuwait has joined Thailand, Indonesia, and Turkey to ban crypto activities. Violators are to face penalties as stipulated in Kuwait&#8217;s AML and terrorist financing laws. Kuwait&#8217;s financial watchdog, the Central Markets Authority (CMA), issued a circular on July 19 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/">Kuwait bans all crypto activities including mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>After the July 19 circular, it is illegal to engage in any cryptocurrency activities in Kuwait.</li>
<li>Kuwait has joined Thailand, Indonesia, and Turkey to ban crypto activities.</li>
<li>Violators are to face penalties as stipulated in Kuwait&rsquo;s AML and terrorist financing laws.</li>
</ul>
<p>Kuwait&rsquo;s financial watchdog, the Central Markets Authority (CMA), issued a circular on July 19 declaring that all cryptocurrency activities including <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/invest/">crypto investment</a>, crypto payments, and crypto mining as described <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/mine/">here</a> were illegal in the Middle Eastern country.</p>
<p>The CMA also banned local regulators from granting licences to anyone attempting to &ldquo;provide cryptocurrency services as a commercial business.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>Tough penalties for violators</h2>
<p>The nation&rsquo;s anti-money laundering and terrorist financing laws carry harsh punishments, the financial regulator warned. The circular made it clear that &ldquo;securities regulated by the Central Bank of Kuwait and other securities and financial instruments regulated by the Capital Markets Authority&rdquo; are exempt from the prohibitions.</p>
<p>In addition to forbidding cryptocurrency-related activities within the nation, the Kuwaiti regulator informed clients of the dangers posed by cryptocurrencies. &ldquo;They do not carry a legal status and are not issued or supported,&rdquo; it declared.</p>
<p>Kuwait has joined the list of nations like Thailand, Indonesia, and Turkey that forbid accepting cryptocurrency payments.</p>
<p>Kuwait&rsquo;s move to ban cryptocurrencies comes after the National Committee for Combating Money Laundering and the Financing of Terrorism concluded its study that aimed at implementing Recommendation 15 of the International Requirements of the Financial Action Task Force (FATF). However, it is essential to note that the FATF does not mandate that nations outlaw cryptocurrency.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/">Kuwait bans all crypto activities including mining</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/kuwait-bans-all-crypto-activities-including-mining/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK&#8217;s FCA launches a permanent digital sandbox</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways FCA&#8217;s digital sandbox is set to launch on August 1st. The sandbox will serve as a testing environment for firms before rolling out their products. UK&#8217;s financial regulator launches a digital sandbox The U.K. Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) announced on Thursday, July 20th, that it will launch a digital sandbox. The regulator said [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/">UK&#8217;s FCA launches a permanent digital sandbox</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">FCA&rsquo;s digital sandbox is set to launch on August 1st.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The sandbox will serve as a testing environment for firms before rolling out their products.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">UK&rsquo;s financial regulator launches a digital sandbox</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The U.K. Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/news/news-stories/launch-permanent-digital-sandbox" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> on Thursday, July 20th, that it will launch a digital sandbox.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulator said the permanent digital sandbox will be made available on August 1st, 2023, opening up the platform to an even broader range of innovative businesses, start-ups and data providers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform will serve as a testing environment for firms to see how their products would perform at an early stage of development.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> comes nearly three years after the regulator launched the sandbox on a trial basis. The FCA said the sandbox would also be available to data providers and would offer firms access to data sets, application program interfaces (API) and data security protection.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The FCA said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Until now, the platform has only been available temporarily to those participating in pilots and TechSprints.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>The Digital Sandbox works to foster innovation and growth &ndash; more than half of the previous Small to Medium Enterprise participants in the pilots and TechSprints made positive developments, including launching new products, securing funding and partnerships, or receiving industry awards or recognitions.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The digital sandbox provides data security protection</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory agency pointed out that its digital sandbox has numerous features that would benefit developers. The sandbox&rsquo;s integrated development environment allows experimentation while safeguarding the data assets on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, developers would have access to over 200 synthetic, public or anonymised data sets and over 1000 APIs to enable testing and validation of technology solutions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The observation deck feature allows interested parties such as regulators, incumbents and others&#8239;to observe in-flight testing at a technical level.&#8239;Finally, the FCA believes that the sandbox could promote diversity of thought, share learnings and foster an ecosystem between teams, observers and mentors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Former Economic Secretary John Glen rolled out the plans for the sandbox in 2022 with the aim of making the UK a cryptocurrency innovation hub. Previously, the sandbox was available only during pilots and TechSprints, which brought people from the financial industry together to address industry challenges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/">UK&#8217;s FCA launches a permanent digital sandbox</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/uks-fca-launches-a-permanent-digital-sandbox/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
