<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin miner Hut 8 revenue declined by $18.3 million in Q2</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hut 8 posted revenue of $14.3 million (19.2 Canadian Dollars), which had fallen $18.3 million during the quarter compared to Q1, 2023. The company mined 399 Bitcoin (BTC) but sold a total of 396 BTC for $10.9 million (CAD 14.7 million) during the quarter. Hut 8 has announced its operating and financial results for Q2, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/">Bitcoin miner Hut 8 revenue declined by $18.3 million in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Hut 8 posted revenue of $14.3 million (19.2 Canadian Dollars), which had fallen $18.3 million during the quarter compared to Q1, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The company mined 399 Bitcoin (BTC) but sold a total of 396 BTC for $10.9 million (CAD 14.7 million) during the quarter.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8 has announced its operating and financial results for Q2, 2023. In details published on Monday August 14, the Bitcoin miner indicated its revenue fell $18.3 million (CAD 24.6 million) during the quarter ending June 30.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Hut 8 posted revenue of $14.3 million in Q2, 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Toronto-based cryptocurrency mining company highlighted revenue of $14.3 million (CAD 19.2 million) during the quarter, compared to $32.5 million (CAD 43.8 million) posted in Q2, 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the miner reported a loss of $12.4 million (CAD 16.7 million) for Q2, 2023 with per-share loss of 6 cents (8 Canadian cents).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8 also announced that it mined 399 Bitcoin (BTC) in the quarter, this being roughly 58% down on mined bitcoin for the same quarter in 2022. The company attributes the decrease to the increase in Bitcoin mining difficulty, impact of operations following issues at its North Bay Facility, as well as electrical issues encountered at the Drumheller facility.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>While we continued to face mining challenges during the second quarter at Drumheller, which are reflected in decreased revenue and fewer Bitcoin mined, we were successful in strategically managing our costs</em>,&rdquo; Shenif Visram, CFO at Hut 8, said in a <a href="https://hut8.io/2023/08/14/hut-8-reports-operating-and-financial-results-for-q2-2023/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8&rsquo;s financial results showed that the company&rsquo;s self-mined BTC balance as of June 30, 2023 &ndash; which it held in custody or had pledged as collateral &ndash; stood at 9,136 BTC. The holdings had a market value of $274 million (CAD 368.7 million). The miner sold a total of 396 BTC for $10.9 million (CAD 14.7 million) during the quarter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-mining/">Bitcoin mining</a> giant, which secured a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/">$50 million credit facility</a> from Coinbase in June, also reported on the progress of its highly anticipated merger with US Bitcoin (USBTC). A shareholder vote on the merger is expected on September 12, the company said in a separate <a href="https://twitter.com/Hut8Mining/status/1691046291122393088" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/">Bitcoin miner Hut 8 revenue declined by $18.3 million in Q2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-revenue-declined-by-18-3-million-in-q2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A price manipulation hack causes Zunami protocol to lose $2.1M</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-price-manipulation-hack-causes-zunami-protocol-to-lose-2-1m/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-price-manipulation-hack-causes-zunami-protocol-to-lose-2-1m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/a-price-manipulation-hack-causes-zunami-protocol-to-lose-2-1m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Zunami Protocol has lost $2.1 million due to a flash loan hack that manipulated prices. The hacker used a flash loan to inject liquidity. The attacker made 1,152 ETH in the process. Zunami Protocol, a leading player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) industry, has suffered a serious setback after a security breach resulted in a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-price-manipulation-hack-causes-zunami-protocol-to-lose-2-1m/">A price manipulation hack causes Zunami protocol to lose $2.1M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Zunami Protocol has lost $2.1 million due to a flash loan hack that manipulated prices.</li>
<li>The hacker used a flash loan to inject liquidity.</li>
<li>The attacker made 1,152 ETH in the process.</li>
</ul>
<p>Zunami Protocol, a leading player in the decentralized finance (DeFi) industry, has suffered a serious setback after a security breach resulted in a loss of more than $2.1 million.</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s Curve Finance-hosted liquidity pool was the target of the attack, which was disclosed by blockchain security companies PeckShield and Ironblocks.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Hi <a href="https://twitter.com/ZunamiProtocol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@zunamiprotocol</a>,  we have detected an ongoing attack. Users are strongly suggested to take necessary actions. </p>
<p>Here is the encrypted hash: 2638ae2969ce932d61c3ca66f9b8a4a6c01c4d89bb2b34ddcf2c4145960f41c4. Actual hash will be released once the situation is stable.</p>
<p>&mdash; PeckShield Inc. (@peckshield) <a href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1690857760412610560?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>How the Zunami hack was carried out</h2>
<p>The Zunami Protocol, which mostly operates through the &ldquo;zStables&rdquo; pool on the Curve network, enables decentralized exchange (DEX) services for stablecoins within the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> ecosystem. By enabling users to diversify their stablecoin holdings, the protocol attempts to lower the risk associated with the eventual demise of any given stablecoin.</p>
<p>According to Ironblocks, the attacker initiated the attack by leveraging a flash loan from the &ldquo;balancer.&rdquo;</p>
<p>This loan allowed the hacker(s) to inject liquidity into the system, allowing them to considerably manipulate the price. The attacker then went ahead to trade on the exchange with the newly created liquidity. Afterwards, they manipulated the price once more and withdrew the funds and returned the flash loan, making a profit of 1,152 ether (ETH) in the process.</p>
<h2>Effect on Zunami native assets</h2>
<p>The hack considerably impacted the prices of Zunami&rsquo;s native assets. Firstly, the Zunami USD stablecoin (UZD) declined by over 98%. Secondly, the Zunami Ether (zETH) dropped by over 85%, settling at $278.</p>
<p>Adding to the complexity of the hack, the stolen funds were channelled through Tornado Cash, a controversial crypto-mixing service platform.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/a-price-manipulation-hack-causes-zunami-protocol-to-lose-2-1m/">A price manipulation hack causes Zunami protocol to lose $2.1M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/a-price-manipulation-hack-causes-zunami-protocol-to-lose-2-1m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bald Network developer sends 7,000 ETH to Ethereum, deposits some on Kraken</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-network-developer-sends-7000-eth-to-ethereum-deposits-some-on-kraken/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-network-developer-sends-7000-eth-to-ethereum-deposits-some-on-kraken/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-network-developer-sends-7000-eth-to-ethereum-deposits-some-on-kraken/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After a spectacular mess up, Bald developer has transferred ether worth $12.9 million back to Ethereum Network. The developer deposited 2,100 ether on Kraken. In most cases, whales transfer cryptocurrencies to exchanges to sell them or trade them for other coins. After weeks of rapid growth, its mysterious creator of bald (BALD) yesterday transferred $12 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-network-developer-sends-7000-eth-to-ethereum-deposits-some-on-kraken/">Bald Network developer sends 7,000 ETH to Ethereum, deposits some on Kraken</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>After a spectacular mess up, Bald developer has transferred ether worth $12.9 million back to Ethereum Network.</li>
<li>The developer deposited 2,100 ether on Kraken.</li>
<li>In most cases, whales transfer cryptocurrencies to exchanges to sell them or trade them for other coins.</li>
</ul>
<p>After weeks of rapid growth, its mysterious creator of bald (BALD) yesterday transferred $12 million in ether (ETH) back to the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum&nbsp;</a>network. Bald had reached a market capitalization of $80 million before some events caused the token price to fall by 90%.</p>
<p>According to data published by analytics company Lookonchain, The bald token developer transferred 7,000 ether (worth about $12.9M) from the Base network back to Ethereum on Sunday. He then deposited 2,100 ether, worth $3.87 million at current prices, to the crypto exchange Kraken.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://dune.com/queries/2768158/4607762">Dune Analytics query</a>, this is the first time that more funds were sent out of the Base Network than deposited.</p>
<h2>The catastrophic fall of Bald</h2>
<p>Bald saw a surprisingly increased popularity in early August, when Base, a blockchain created by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase</a>, wasn&rsquo;t even formally open to the public. A popular tweet about a trader who turned $500 into hundreds of thousands of dollars caused Bald to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-token-records-astounding-40000-upside-after-launch-on-base/">soar 4,000,000% in a matter of days</a>, bringing in almost $66 million in ether (ETH) from investors looking to squeeze out profits from an otherwise stagnant larger crypto market.</p>
<p>At the time, Bald appeared to have it all: seemingly limitless liquidity, a thriving neighbourhood, an infusion of fresh traders, and, in some quarters, tenuous expectations that it may develop into the next SHIB. This exhilaration, however, did not endure more than a few days. After reaching a high of $0.02795, bald prices dropped by as much as 90% after the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-price-nosedives-90-as-deployer-removes-liquidity/">token&rsquo;s deployer removed millions of dollars worth of liquidity</a>, which swiftly affected sentiment as investors moved to remove their funds from the project.</p>
<p>The deployer had previously contributed up to $35 million worth of ether to a liquidity pool on the Base network-based exchange Leetswap, giving the appearance that the project was well-funded. Along with providing ether in exchange for BALD tokens and selling ether for BALD as prices increased, the deployer may have earned millions of dollars in fees.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-network-developer-sends-7000-eth-to-ethereum-deposits-some-on-kraken/">Bald Network developer sends 7,000 ETH to Ethereum, deposits some on Kraken</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bald-network-developer-sends-7000-eth-to-ethereum-deposits-some-on-kraken/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu nears $2M presale milestone – do you buy SHMU?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-2m-presale-milestone-do-you-buy-shmu/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-2m-presale-milestone-do-you-buy-shmu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-2m-presale-milestone-do-you-buy-shmu/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu presale is closing in on $2 million mark, with nearly $1.9 million already raised. Interest in the AI-powered crypto meme coin has soared in recent weeks. Early investors into the project could benefit from potential long term gains. Few crypto projects currently boost the amount of attention that Shiba Memu, a new meme [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-2m-presale-milestone-do-you-buy-shmu/">Shiba Memu nears $2M presale milestone – do you buy SHMU?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Shiba Memu presale is closing in on $2 million mark, with nearly $1.9 million already raised.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Interest in the AI-powered crypto meme coin has soared in recent weeks.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Early investors into the project could benefit from potential long term gains.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Few crypto projects currently boost the amount of attention that <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shiba Memu</a>, a new meme coin powered by artificial intelligence, is seeing in the market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> and major altcoins continue to stall at key levels, this crypto project&rsquo;s presale is attracting massive interest and is on the verge of clocking the $2 million raised milestone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But what&rsquo;s making Shiba Memu a likely gem for early investors? We assess below.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu and the meme coin hype</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Pepe (PEPE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Floki (FLOKI) have been some of the crypto meme projects to attract huge traction this year. Given how popular these tokens have become, it might be difficult for a new project taking a similar approach to steal some of the fervour and build a community to rival these meme coin leaders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Yet Shiba Memu is looking to achieve just that using a self-marketing strategy powered by <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a>. While the likes of PEPE and FLOKI need a significant input of human-driven hype to promote themselves to the community, Shiba Memu will leverage a cutting-edge AI dashboard to reach the global market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As such, what top meme coins have been able to achieve with traditional marketing strategies could be improved upon manifold by Shiba Memu&rsquo;s groundbreaking system. Does this mean the project has the capacity to challenge the likes of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/">Dogecoin</a>, Shiba Inu and Pepe?</p>
<p dir="ltr">Most probably, with all the buzz around the project as seen during the ongoing presale. It all suggests investors see Shiba Memu as having long term investment potential.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How Shiba Memu plans to tap into AI technology</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Artificial Intelligence is making waves across the tech industry, pulling in billions of dollars&rsquo; worth of investment from global giants Microsoft, Meta, Google and Apple among others. Companies such as Nvidia and Palantir have also bet big on the potential for AI to drive revenues and adoption.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a trend also seen across crypto, with crypto AI a new narrative that&rsquo;s driving applications in trading, decentralised cloud computing, and prediction markets. It&rsquo;s along these lines that Shiba Memu is looking to become the top AI-powered dog meme coin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, an automated marketing dashboard will use natural language processing, predictive analytics, sentiment learning and image and video recognition to intelligently target new markets for the native SHMU token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Akin to a puppy learning new tricks every day, AI is forecast to polish Shiba Memu into what could become the dominant meme coin.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is buying Shiba Memu today a good investment move?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Shiba Memu presale currently has SHMU priced at $0.020125. The project has so far raised nearly $1.9 million even as the token&rsquo;s value has increased from $0.011125 when the token sale launched a few weeks ago.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, and perhaps more appealing to investors is that the token&rsquo;s value is programmed to increase every day at 6 pm GMT. It will eventually hit $0.024400 for a total of 119% upside from that presale debut price. Going past key levels such as $0.1 and $0.5 on market debut could mean gains of between 310% and 1,950%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As with every other investment, the key is to acknowledge the risks involved versus the potential reward. This also applies to Shiba Memu, which as noted, is a new crypto project looking to revolutionise an industry that is very nascent.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, given the projections for both crypto and AI, the latter from tech giants such as Microsoft, suggests putting some money into Shiba Memu as part of an investment portfolio could be worth it down the road.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Learn more about Shiba Memu <a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-2m-presale-milestone-do-you-buy-shmu/">Shiba Memu nears $2M presale milestone – do you buy SHMU?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-nears-2m-presale-milestone-do-you-buy-shmu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer gains momentum as the English Premier League 2023-24 kicks off</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-gains-momentum-as-the-english-premier-league-2023-24-kicks-off/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-gains-momentum-as-the-english-premier-league-2023-24-kicks-off/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-gains-momentum-as-the-english-premier-league-2023-24-kicks-off/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Majority of EPL clubs played their opening matches over the weekend. The only teams that have not played are Manchester United and Wolves, which is scheduled for today at 22:00 GMT+3. The English Premier League has added some impetuous into the Chancer presale. The English Premier League (EPL) 2023-24, one of the most followed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-gains-momentum-as-the-english-premier-league-2023-24-kicks-off/">Chancer gains momentum as the English Premier League 2023-24 kicks off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>A Majority of EPL clubs played their opening matches over the weekend.</li>
<li>The only teams that have not played are Manchester United and Wolves, which is scheduled for today at 22:00 GMT+3.</li>
<li>The English Premier League has added some impetuous into the Chancer presale.</li>
</ul>
<p>The English Premier League (EPL) 2023-24, one of the most followed and watched games, just kicked off and the <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">presale of Chancer</a>, the world&rsquo;s first decentralized predictive market-making platform, is gaining momentum. At press time, 30,047,387 CHANCER tokens had been sold raising $1,331,800.21.</p>
<p>The Chancer presale saw increased activity over the weekend as EPL teams played their first matches over weekend and it is expected to gain momentum as the league progresses until its mainnet launch in Q1 2024.</p>
<h2>What is Chancer?</h2>
<p>Chancer is developing a cutting-edge prediction markets platform based on the principles of user empowerment and decentralization. It aims to primarily function as a peer-to-peer (P2P) betting facilitator rather than a typical betting establishment. It will allow individuals to create and control their own betting markets, a strategy that democratizes the betting market.</p>
<p>The appeal of Chancer, which Adam and Paul Kelbie co-founded, goes far beyond traditional sports betting. Users of the platform will be able to wager on any event they can think of, from the results of football matches including EPL matches and Champions League final to more specialized wagers between friends.</p>
<p>Chancer&rsquo;s value proposition heavily emphasizes its adaptability, which, along with the company&rsquo;s plans to become a DAO, distinguishes it from other cryptocurrencies and betting platforms and explains why so many investors are interested in finding out how to buy CHANCER.</p>
<p>At the heart of the Chancer ecosystem is the CHANCER token, which is the primary currency for transactions within the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The value of the CHANCER token is linked to the success of Chancer&rsquo;s P2P betting concept. As the project grows and widens its user base, the demand for CHANCER tokens is expected to also see an increased uptick leading to a potential price surge. That said, the value of CHANCER has also been rising throughout the presale with each presale stage.</p>
<p>Chancer also stands the chance of attracting users who are currently not attracted to the traditional online betting platforms which are centralized. One of the greatest Chancer prepositions is the ability for users to create their own wagers on anything including activities between friends.</p>
<h2>Why is the EPL causing so much excitement around CHANCER presale?</h2>
<p>A majority of Chancer investors see it as a great platform for creating betting markets and betting for the EPL matches besides other competitions. And it goes without saying that the EPL is the most followed football league in the world courtesy of the many top talents playing in the various teams.</p>
<p>Although the American Major League Soccer (MLS) has been seeing some traction since Lionel Messi moved to the Inter Miami club, the MLS is still far below the EPL in terms of popularity.</p>
<p>When Chancer officially launches in the first quarter of 2024, the EPL is likely to be one of the most betted competitions on the platform before the 2024 Olympics games begin later on in the year.</p>
<h2>Should you invest in Chancer now?</h2>
<p>Well, the decision to invest in any project is the prerogative of an investor and requires due diligence especially when it comes to cryptocurrency projects because of the volatile nature of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>So, far Chancer has shown its capability to revolutionize the betting industry which was valued at over $2B in 2022. If successful, the project will be a force to reckon with within the betting circles seeing it is introducing an opportunity for CHANCER token holders to create their own wagers on basically anything.</p>
<p>To purchase your CHANCER token, you can visit Chancer&rsquo;s official website <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-gains-momentum-as-the-english-premier-league-2023-24-kicks-off/">Chancer gains momentum as the English Premier League 2023-24 kicks off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-gains-momentum-as-the-english-premier-league-2023-24-kicks-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 technical reasons to buy Bitcoin (or sell the US dollar)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-bitcoin-or-sell-the-us-dollar/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-bitcoin-or-sell-the-us-dollar/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 10:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-bitcoin-or-sell-the-us-dollar/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>RSI stays above 50 in 2023 The weekly chart points out an ascending triangle pattern $45k is the next target, providing the Bitcoin price holds above $25k Bitcoin bulls must be frustrated by the slow price action in the last few months. After all, ever since it met resistance at the $30k level, Bitcoin moved [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-bitcoin-or-sell-the-us-dollar/">2 technical reasons to buy Bitcoin (or sell the US dollar)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>RSI stays above 50 in 2023</li>
<li>The weekly chart points out an ascending triangle pattern</li>
<li>$45k is the next target, providing the Bitcoin price holds above $25k</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin bulls must be frustrated by the slow price action in the last few months. After all, ever since it met resistance at the $30k level, Bitcoin moved in a very tight range compared to historical volatility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But the same happened to the FX market. Volatility remains subdued since the EUR/USD climbed over the pivotal 1.10 level, and now traders wonder what comes next &ndash; further upside or a reversal of the bullish trend.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The two are connected.&nbsp;</p>
<p>If one looks at the EUR/USD rally from 0.95 and compares it to the Bitcoin rally from $15,000, similarities can&rsquo;t be ignored. In other words, it is more of a US dollar&rsquo;s story than Bitcoin investors accumulating more coins.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Faced with this ambiguity, sometimes it helps to look at the bigger picture and interpret charts. In doing so, the bias for Bitcoin price is bullish.&nbsp;</p>
<p>So here are two technical reasons to buy Bitcoin (or sell the US dollar):&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>RSI stays above 50 in 2023</li>
<li>The weekly chart points out an ascending triangle pattern</li>
</ul>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/13/1691922492938-6ad0d9ef-f5d5-4615-a99d-55c97030cd8c.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="444"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>RSI holds above 50 in 2023</h2>
<p>The first technical bullish setup for Bitcoin comes from the Relative Strength Index (RSI). The RSI is an oscillator, typically displayed at the bottom of a chart.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The main theme of the weekly chart above is Bitcoin&rsquo;s rally from the 2022 lows. The move from $15k to above $30k resulted in the RSI crossing above 50.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The RSI &ldquo;oscillates&rdquo; between overbought and oversold levels, marked with 70, respectively 30. When in-between levels, technical traders focus on the 50 mark. More precisely, when the RSI crosses above 50, the price action is bullish, and when it crosses below, the price action is bearish. Of course, traders should be aware of false breakouts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But the timeframe above (i.e., weekly) suggests no such thing as a false breakout. Just the opposite, considering that the price action has held above 50 since the start of 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hence, the bias remains bullish while the RSI holds above 50, and the next move should be a climb into the overbought territory.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>An ascending triangle pattern hints at a move above $45k</h2>
<p>An ascending triangle is a bullish pattern characterized by the price action pushing against horizontal resistance. Its measured move equals the longest segment in the triangle formation and points to further advances toward the $45k area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there is one condition &ndash; the price action must hold above $25k. If it does so, the RSI will stay above 50, meaning Bitcoin&rsquo;s price will finally build energy to break above horizontal resistance.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-bitcoin-or-sell-the-us-dollar/">2 technical reasons to buy Bitcoin (or sell the US dollar)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/2-technical-reasons-to-buy-bitcoin-or-sell-the-us-dollar/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals price forecast 2023: How attractive is $ASI in the presale?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-forecast-2023-how-attractive-is-asi-in-the-presale/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-forecast-2023-how-attractive-is-asi-in-the-presale/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-forecast-2023-how-attractive-is-asi-in-the-presale/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals is a profitable trading service with more than 64% signal accuracy.&#160; AltSignals has raised $1.3 million in presale as investors show interest in AI trading $ASI token has been lauded as a 10x investment ahead of Uniswap listing in Q3 2023. 2023 has been a year of twists and turns in crypto. Major cryptos [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-forecast-2023-how-attractive-is-asi-in-the-presale/">AltSignals price forecast 2023: How attractive is $ASI in the presale?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a profitable trading service with more than 64% signal accuracy.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has raised $1.3 million in presale as investors show interest in AI trading</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI token has been lauded as a 10x investment ahead of Uniswap listing in Q3 2023.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">2023 has been a year of twists and turns in crypto. Major cryptos have underperformed, but newly launched projects have found a soft landing. This means Investors are looking for projects out of the ordinary. Cryptocurrencies with the potential to surge strongly in the next bull cycle have benefited. AltSignals ($ASI) has been one of them, with a fast-selling presale suggestion of high investor interest. $ASI has raised $1.3 million in&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>presale</u></a> amid a huge interest in its new AI-led trading platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>AltSignals&rsquo; AI application in trading</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Artificial intelligence is growing and finding applications in numerous sectors. Trading has been one of them, with Altsignals the latest to jump into the AI bandwagon. The company is creating an AI platform dubbed ActualizeAI. Investors will hold $ASI tokens to become a member of ActualizeAI.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals is a profitable trading signal provider in the UK with half a decade of existence. The company covers financial instruments ranging from forex, stock, and cryptocurrencies. Up to now, AltSignals has been using an algorithm indicator AltAlgo&trade; to generate trading signals. The company generates signals with an average accuracy rate of 64%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With AI, AltSignals expects to cover more trading instruments and increase the quality of its signals. In the trading world, AI has been used for generating quality signals. This is achieved through machine learning, natural language processing, and predictive modelling. AI is also devoid of human emotions, enabling traders to make better decisions in trading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The AltSignals team believes AI will supercharge earnings and give investors more value for money. $ASI, the token of the AI-powered platform, will be the unit of exchanging value. This includes allowing investors to participate in the governance of the platform. Members can earn more tokens by contributing ideas through an AI Members Club. There are also trading competitions where investors can improve their trading skills and earn $ASI.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>$ASI prediction and investment opportunity</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI has a huge opportunity to succeed, given that it powers an already successful trading platform. Success is illustrated by its over $52,000 followers on Telegram and 1,400 VIP members. That gives $ASI a headstart as it gears to list on Uniswap in the third quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But the future growth of AltSignals depends on how much it continues to attract users. With a blockchain and AI angle, the visibility of the platform could grow. As more members join to benefit from the trading signals, the value of $ASI could skyrocket.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">It means that AltSignals is an ideal investment for investors looking for a token with real-world utility. The token can deliver consistent returns and sustainable returns on increased use of ActualizeAI.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Predictably, analysts expect $ASI to close the year at $0.20. The current price for the token is $0.01875, implying an increase of nearly 1,000%. An increase of this magnitude happens quite often with newly launched tokens. This means $ASI has a real chance to rise by 10x, per analysts&rsquo; estimates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While this thesis finds $ASI with such a realistic potential, the increase could occur in the medium term. Potentially, the increase could occur over 2024 as the use of the platform grows. In 2023, a price increase of three-digit percentages would be more realistic.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Should you buy AltSignals in August?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals presale is happening first, while the token listing is fast approaching. $ASI&rsquo;s value could increase exponentially after listing. Investors might be forced to pay a premium buying a token on exchanges than on presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">An ideal investment decision is to buy $ASI when the price is still low on presale. This allows investors to benefit from a possible rise in value when the token is listed.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-forecast-2023-how-attractive-is-asi-in-the-presale/">AltSignals price forecast 2023: How attractive is $ASI in the presale?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-price-forecast-2023-how-attractive-is-asi-in-the-presale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huge predictions for SEI token ahead of debut, while Chancer token could be next</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/huge-predictions-for-sei-token-ahead-of-debut-while-chancer-token-could-be-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/huge-predictions-for-sei-token-ahead-of-debut-while-chancer-token-could-be-next/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The token of SEI Network debuts on Binance on August 15, with price estimates of $0.26 The token of the Chancer platform, a predictive markets application, will list in Q3 2023 Chancer token could rise by up to 10x after debuting with higher predictions in the future. Binance is set to debut the token of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huge-predictions-for-sei-token-ahead-of-debut-while-chancer-token-could-be-next/">Huge predictions for SEI token ahead of debut, while Chancer token could be next</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token of SEI Network debuts on Binance on August 15, with price estimates of $0.26</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The token of the Chancer platform, a predictive markets application, will list in Q3 2023</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Chancer token could rise by up to 10x after debuting with higher predictions in the future.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Binance is set to debut the token of Layer-1 blockchain SEI Network on August 15. Traders have huge expectations of the token, with its market expected to hit almost half a billion US dollars. Meanwhile, the robust presale of Chancer token continues, with over $1.32 million raised. The prospect of peer-to-peer betting by Chancer has accelerated the presale. Investors can&nbsp;<a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>buy</u></a> the token via ETH, USDT, BNB, and BUSD.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Upcoming SEI token debut and price predictions</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">SEI, the token of the SEI Network, will go live on Binance on August 15. The listing comes amid positive predictions, with price estimates of $0.26 immediately after going live. A&nbsp;<a href="https://app.aevo.xyz/perpetual/sei" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>pre-listing futures data</u></a> by Aevo shows at the estimated price, SEI will have a market cap of $486 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It means that SEI will enter the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap after listing. The token will have a circulating supply of 1.8 billion, equivalent to 18% of its 10 billion total supply. SEI&rsquo;s pre-listing futures contracts went live on Aevo on Wednesday. They allow traders and investors to speculate on the post-listing price of the token.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>About Chancer and the Chancer token</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer is the world&rsquo;s first blockchain-based predictive market application. The Chancer token will be the unit of exchanging value on the platform and claiming winnings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform enables betting in a P2P environment. What has made Chancer exciting is that it allows betting on multiple events. Users create P2P markets, decide what to bet on, determine rules and odds, and invite others.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Let&rsquo;s say you predict that it will rain in the evening. You can create a Chancer market and invite your friends to place bets for or against the outcome. Winners get rewarded with a Chancer token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer decentralises betting by taking betting to blockchain and allowing users to be in charge. This allows more users to join and benefit from the predictive market.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What value does the Chancer token carry?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Like any other cryptocurrency, Chancer carries value based on current and future price movements. Presently, the token is valued at $0.011, with the price increasing at each presale stage. In the future, the token&rsquo;s value could be higher when it is listed on exchanges. Investors buying the token will benefit from a potential price surge. With betting a popular sector, a high price potential remains.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer also carries value for investors for continued use of the platform. Users can join in on live betting games, create Chancer markets, and claim winnings on accurate predictions. Investors can also stake the token for passive income.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer presale and listing</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Chancer&rsquo;s presale will occur in 12 phases, targeting $15,000,000. The presale is in the second stage, with the selling occurring fast, barely two months since it was launched.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Chancer token will be listed in Q3 2023, starting with Uniswap. The aim is to get the token on at least two centralised exchanges in the third quarter. The listing will welcome more demand for the token, and the price could skyrocket.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Chancer token prediction</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Although predicting a new token is quite subjective, a price increase of up to 10x is not off the table. Newly-launched tokens have risen by similar margins a few weeks after listing. Given the huge expectation around the Chancer platform, high speculation is a plus for the token. Thus, a price of up to 10x is possible in 2024 and near similar margins in 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2025 and beyond, Chancer could be a 20x or more investment. The value could increase consistently into the future as blockchain-based betting gathers momentum. This means Chancer is a potential investment that can deliver sustainable returns over time.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/huge-predictions-for-sei-token-ahead-of-debut-while-chancer-token-could-be-next/">Huge predictions for SEI token ahead of debut, while Chancer token could be next</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BREAKING: Bankman-Fried sent to jail after judge revokes bail</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/breaking-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-after-judge-revokes-bail/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/breaking-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-after-judge-revokes-bail/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Judge Lewis Kaplan has revoked former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s bail. The judge has also denied the defence&#8217;s request to delay Bankman-Fried&#8217;s detention pending appeal. Bankman-Fried, whose criminal trial begins on October 2, will be jailed at Putnam. Judge Lewis Kaplan has revoked the bail granted to former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, and ordered his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/breaking-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-after-judge-revokes-bail/">BREAKING: Bankman-Fried sent to jail after judge revokes bail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Judge Lewis Kaplan has revoked former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s bail.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The judge has also denied the defence&rsquo;s request to delay Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s detention pending appeal.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bankman-Fried, whose criminal trial begins on October 2, will be jailed at Putnam.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Judge Lewis Kaplan has revoked the bail granted to former <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, and ordered his detention after a hearing over alleged witness tampering. CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/11/us-judge-sends-sam-bankman-fried-to-jail-over-witness-tampering.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">reported</a> the development on Friday.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Judge sands Bankman-Fried to jail</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Judge Kaplan on Friday ruled in favour of a motion filed by federal prosecutors after the government complained about Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s potential to tamper with both witnesses and the jury in his upcoming criminal trial.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In denying the defendant&rsquo;s plea for a delayed detention ahead of an appeal, Judge Kaplan said that SBF had tried to interfere with witnesses on at least two occasions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bankman-Fried is to be remanded at the Putnam jail pending his appeal and ahead of the October 2 trial. Prosecutors said the ex-FTX chief will have access to the internet at the facility as he prepares his defence, which would not be the case at MDC that is closest to the court but offers limited internet access.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Inner City Press has reported that defence lawyers already filed an appeal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">SBF appeal of remand to jail filed less than an hour after handcuffs, $505 filing fee paid &ndash; Inner City Press will follow the appeal in the Second Circuit, too <a href="https://t.co/YF01ftwGhX">https://t.co/YF01ftwGhX</a> <a href="https://t.co/aOsit518gR">pic.twitter.com/aOsit518gR</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Inner City Press (@innercitypress) <a href="https://twitter.com/innercitypress/status/1690098233790328832?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/us-justice-department-wants-bankman-fried-jailed/">highlighted</a> in July, prosecution had sought to have Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s bail revoked and he be jailed following instances of alleged witness tampering. The DOJ had <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/doj-accuses-bankman-fried-of-leaking-ellisons-diary-to-discredit-her/">allleged</a> that SBF leaked the private diary of his former colleague and now star federal witness Caroline Alison to a New York Times reporter.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the government, the disgraced ex-billionaire&rsquo;s goal was to discredit Alison and possibly affect the jurors. During the last hearing, Judge Kaplan had warned Bankman-Fried about his behaviour, noting the bail could be revoked.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/breaking-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-after-judge-revokes-bail/">BREAKING: Bankman-Fried sent to jail after judge revokes bail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
