<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:09:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US Inflation Rate Surge: Will Fed Stick to Its Aggressive Approach?</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco T. Lanz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/">US Inflation Rate Surge: Will Fed Stick to Its Aggressive Approach?</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, June 13, the markets reacted positively to the publication of inflation data.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/">US Inflation Rate Surge: Will Fed Stick to Its Aggressive Approach?</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/">US Inflation Rate Surge: Will Fed Stick to Its Aggressive Approach?</a></p>
<p>The inflation rate in the United States increased by 0.1% in May. This inflation figure represents a 4% increase over the past 12 months, which meets the economic expectations of the Fed. But will it be enough for the Federal Reserve to slow down its aggressive monetary policy?</p>
<p>According to the Consumer Price Index Summary <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/13/cpi-inflation-report-may-2023-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> for May, published by the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, inflation in the US reached its lowest annual level in the past two years.</p>
<p>However, excluding the volatile prices of food and energy, underlying inflation remains high. This could hinder the Fed&#8217;s decision to reduce interest rates.</p>
<h2>Will the Fed Change Its Aggressive Monetary Policy amid US Inflation Rate Surge?</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, the markets reacted positively to the publication of inflation data. However, the reaction has been as volatile as some analysts expected because many investors prefer to wait for the Fed&#8217;s announcements regarding interest rates, which will be published at its upcoming meeting scheduled for this Wednesday.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it is important to consider the upward trend in various indicators, including housing prices, used vehicle prices, transportation services, and more. While these indicators experienced relatively modest increases compared to April, their continuous growth should not be overlooked by the Fed.</p>
<p>However, some analysts like Jeffrey Roach, chief economist at LPL Financial, indicated that the &#8220;encouraging trend in consumer prices&#8221; could allow the Federal Reserve to keep rates unchanged, at least in the short term. He even stated that if a healthy trend continues, it is possible that the Fed will stop raising rates for the rest of the year.</p>
<h2>Volatility Takes Hold of the Cryptocurrency Market</h2>
<p>The report revealed a divergence among the different components of the index reflecting changes in commodity and service prices, which strongly influence the overall economic situation and the policies of the Federal Reserve.</p>
<p>For now, the cryptocurrency market is reacting with the same volatility it has typically shown in response to the publication of this data. BTC increased by almost 2%, from $25,900 to a peak of $26,433. However, at the time of writing this note, the price has experienced a 2.6% decline that has affected the majority of altcoins, which were experiencing a significant recovery.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a>, which also saw a 1.6% rise, is experiencing a 2.58% decline from its peak of $1,770 to a low of $1,724. Even <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>, which had achieved a 10% increase thanks to its victory against the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>, ended up declining along with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>.</p>
<div style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed-1.jpg" alt="US Inflation Rate Surge: Will Fed Stick to Its Aggressive Approach?" width="1024" height="614" /><p class="wp-caption-text">XRP Price drop 10%. Photo: TradingView</p></div>
<p>Therefore, it is premature to declare victory in the crypto market. The real test will come tomorrow, when the Fed announces whether it will persist with its aggressive policy or finally yield, thereby allowing the markets to recover.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/">US Inflation Rate Surge: Will Fed Stick to Its Aggressive Approach?</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-inflation-rate-surge-fed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Announces Maverick Protocol as 34th Project on Binance Launchpool</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance launchpad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance launcpool]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mav]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maverick protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sui]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258713</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/">Binance Announces Maverick Protocol as 34th Project on Binance Launchpool</a></p>
<p>The Maverick Protocol will be available on the Binance Launchpool as the newest project launched after the Sui blockchain in April.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/">Binance Announces Maverick Protocol as 34th Project on Binance Launchpool</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/">Binance Announces Maverick Protocol as 34th Project on Binance Launchpool</a></p>
<p>Binance has <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/introducing-maverick-protocol-mav-on-binance-launchpool-farm-mav-by-staking-bnb-and-tusd-a28d005ed545464cbb9a3661c26e6b38" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduced</a> the newest project on the Binance Launchpool, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ieo/maverick-protocol/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Maverick Protocol</a> (MAV). The Maverick Protocol, the 34th project on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> Launchpool, is a decentralized exchange (DEX) that helps liquidity producers hit their capital efficiency targets regardless of their liquidity providing (LP) strategy.</p>
<p>According to the official Binance announcement, interested users can farm Maverick Protocol (MAV) tokens by staking TUSD and BNB in different pools. Binance says following the farming period, it will list MAV as soon as the tokens meet the requirement for liquidity.</p>
<p>Available trading pairs upon initial listing will be MAV/BTC, MAV/TUSD, and MAV/USDT. The MAV/TUSD trading pair will allow users to enjoy zero maker fees. Binance will announce the date and timing as appropriate.</p>
<p>Farming for MAV tokens will begin on Wednesday, June 14th, at 00:00 (UTC), and end on Saturday, July 8th, at 23:59 (UTC).</p>
<h2>Maverick Protocol Details on Binance Launchpool</h2>
<p>The Maverick Protocol has a total token supply of 2,000,000,000 MAV, and will offer Binance Launchpool token rewards of 30,000,000. This is equal to 1.5% of the total token supply. The initial circulating supply at launch will be 12.5% of the total token supply, equal to 250,000,000 MAV. At the moment, there is no upper limit for staking. Therefore, users who have met the KYC requirement can stake as much as they like.</p>
<p>Binance will calculate user rewards using snapshots of users and total pool balances taken and updated every hour. Following the calculations, each user may then accumulate rewards or make multiple claims as calculated to receive their rewards at any time in their spot accounts. Nonetheless, any user who does not initiate claims will have their rewards automatically deposited in their spot account as each farming period ends.</p>
<p>Binance restricts users to staking tokens in one pool at a time. A user cannot stake the same tokens in multiple pools but can split their tokens into different pools concurrently. Also, Binance will continuously display each pool’s total balance and annual percentage yield (APY), updating both in real-time. Anyone can decide to unstake their funds from one pool and stake in another pool immediately.</p>
<p>Users who already have BNB staked in the BNB Vault automatically benefit from the Maverick Protocol launchpool. These users will receive calculated daily MAV rewards in their wallets.</p>
<h2>Binance Last Launched SUI</h2>
<p>In April, Binance launched Sui (SUI) as the 33rd project on the launchpool. Sui is a DPoS (delegated proof of stake) layer 1 blockchain that uses the Move programming language to write safe smart contracts. The Sui blockchain promises a high throughput and instant settlement for several next-gen decentralized applications. Sui had a much higher total token supply, at 10,000,000,000 SUI. Like Maverick, users also enjoyed zero maker fees on the SUI/TUSD trading pair at the time of its launch.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/">Binance Announces Maverick Protocol as 34th Project on Binance Launchpool</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-maverick-protocol-launchpool/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Politicized Crypto Regulatory Crackdown Could Deter Blockchain Decentralization in Future, Bernstein Analysts Says</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/">Politicized Crypto Regulatory Crackdown Could Deter Blockchain Decentralization in Future, Bernstein Analysts Says</a></p>
<p>The crypto market has turned bearish since the SEC charged Binance and Coinbase with listing unregistered securities last week.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/">Politicized Crypto Regulatory Crackdown Could Deter Blockchain Decentralization in Future, Bernstein Analysts Says</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/">Politicized Crypto Regulatory Crackdown Could Deter Blockchain Decentralization in Future, Bernstein Analysts Says</a></p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market is in a crucial growth phase that could significantly determine the winners of blockchain mainstream adoption. The fact that different countries are coming up with respective crypto policies is a true testament that there is a need for an update on the decades-old financial systems. Notably, Europe, Hong Kong, Middle East countries, El Salvador, and the Central African Republic have all adopted different friendly crypto policies. However, the United States and Nigeria, among other countries, have been divided on crypto regulations.</p>
<p>Last week, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission filed charges against <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN) for listing unregistered securities. Notably, SEC Chair Gary Gensler has argued that almost all crypto assets are unregistered securities with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> as an exception. Interestingly, the Hinman documents, which have been used against the SEC in the Ripple lawsuit, depict that <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> was considered not a security by former top officials.</p>
<h2>Bernstein Analysts on Crypto Regulatory Crackdown Dilemma</h2>
<p>According to analysts at a private wealth management adviser focused on high net worth clients, Bernstein, the view that all crypto tokens, other than Bitcoin, are unregistered securities does not leave any room for blockchain networks to attain decentralization over time. Additionally, Bernstein analysts led by Gautam Chhugani think the classification of crypto tokens as securities does not leave room for tokens to have functional utility within the underlying networks.</p>
<p>“The core issue is whether countries should use securities laws framed decades ago without realizing blockchain networks’ very aim is to transform the decades-old financial and securities market systems, with more transparency, instant settlement times, disintermediation of middlemen, automation and reduced costs, global liquidity and interoperability,” Bernstein report noted.</p>
<p>The move by the United States SEC seems to have influenced the Nigerian SEC to regulate the crypto market in a similar manner. Last week on Friday, the Nigerian SEC ordered Binance Nigeria to cease operations for issuing trade of unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Combined, the United States and Nigerian government controls about half a billion people, which is more than 25 percent of global economic activities. Consequently, blockchains other than Bitcoin will have a challenging time ahead implementing the decentralization of their ecosystems.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Bernstein analysts <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/13/classifying-crypto-tokens-as-securities-will-hamper-some-blockchains-decentralization-efforts-bernstein-says/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">concluded</a> that the different crypto regulatory scope is splitting both the blockchain industry and countries into jurisdictions. Arguably, crypto projects could be forced to provide services in respective jurisdictions according to the different regulations.</p>
<p>Eventually, the fiat system will win through the CBDCs if the regulations continue moving per different jurisdictions. Nevertheless, the regulations in the blockchain industry were imminent following increased scams and rug pulls. As a result, a faction of crypto enthusiasts has welcomed the crypto regulations as a means to mainstream adoption.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, blockchains will have a challenging time in the future rolling out their respective tokens as regulations get tighter.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/">Politicized Crypto Regulatory Crackdown Could Deter Blockchain Decentralization in Future, Bernstein Analysts Says</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-regulatory-crackdown-bernstein/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orbs Debuts Permissionless Beta Launch of DAO Solution – TON.Vote</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[orbs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON.Vote]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=257868</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/">Orbs Debuts Permissionless Beta Launch of DAO Solution &#8211; TON.Vote</a></p>
<p>As the permissionless beta launch of TON.Vote. goes live, Orbs' L3 Guardians technology will be required to boost security. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/">Orbs Debuts Permissionless Beta Launch of DAO Solution &#8211; TON.Vote</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/">Orbs Debuts Permissionless Beta Launch of DAO Solution &#8211; TON.Vote</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Layer-3 infrastructure network for Decentralized Applications (DApps) Orbs has announced the permissionless beta launch of TON.Vote. According to the Press Release shared with Coinspeaker, TON.Vote is the new Decentralized Autonomous Organization (DAO)-based governance solution for The Open Network (TON). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Orbs, any TON-based project focused on infusing DAO-based governance can leverage the TON.Vote as it is now available for use. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Already, the likes of STON.fi, EvAA, TON Punks and Fanzee have adopted the solution, thereby making them the official launch partners of the TON.Vote protocol. TON.Vote projects the possibility of all governance proposals and sites to happen on-chain. Precisely, the system generates a smart contract every time a user submits a proposal and this smart contract includes a reference to the Merkle tree of all votes. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Afterwards, the references are transparently stored on IPFS where they can be verified independently by any user. In the meantime, TON.Vote users can send a transaction to the smart contract with their vote which has three options; yes, no or abstain. It is then processed off-chain and final results are computed. While this model is very innovative, Orbs is considering a different approach for the future.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&#8220;In future, users will only need to sign a digital signature from their wallet, with their vote being secured in IPFS. Votes will then be validated via a wallet sign and be gassless, pending the adoption of a standard wallet signature across all dApps,&#8221; the press release reads.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Orbs had earlier bagged a partnership deal with TON Foundation, a non-profit association of developers and enthusiasts powering the development of TON. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Orbs was saddled with the responsibility of acting as the primary design partner for the development of the app. Thereafter, both worked together to build the TON.Vote while considering customers&#8217; requirements from both the TON and its ecosystem project. In 2022, Orbs </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-ton-verifier/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">launched</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> TON Verifier to help developers publish certified source code.</span></p>
<h2><b>Orbs Offers Extra Layer of Security to TON.Vote</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the permissionless beta launch of TON.Vote. goes live, Orbs&#8217; L3 Guardians technology will be required to boost security. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This technology will facilitate the verification of UI&#8217;s displayed votes&#8217; accuracy. At the same time, it will need to ascertain that the displayed votes are a complete match to those stored in the smart contract data by cross-checking the information presented on the front end. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Performing this action would enforce an additional layer of safety and assurance as the system already leverages other security avenues like independent validators and manual chain checks.  </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Noteworthy, two community votes have been facilitated by the TON.Vote with the first one being a “Proposal of TON Tokenomics Optimization” and the second, TON’s recent “Hack-a-TON” x DoraHacks contest. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For the first, community members were asked to vote for/against the freezing of Genesis mining wallets that had been inactive for more than four years. While the second time was to determine the prize ranking for the contest.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/">Orbs Debuts Permissionless Beta Launch of DAO Solution &#8211; TON.Vote</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/orbs-beta-launch-ton-vote/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Generative AI Video Platform Synthesia Raises $90 Million at $1 Billion Valuation </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[accel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[synthesia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/">Generative AI Video Platform Synthesia Raises $90 Million at $1 Billion Valuation </a></p>
<p>Through the latest funding, the firm aims to make video creation easy for everyone and has already served many businesses worldwide.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/">Generative AI Video Platform Synthesia Raises $90 Million at $1 Billion Valuation </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/">Generative AI Video Platform Synthesia Raises $90 Million at $1 Billion Valuation </a></p>
<p>Synthesia, a leading artificial intelligence (AI) company based in London, has successfully raised $90 million in a series C funding round, bringing its total valuation to $1 billion.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s groundbreaking AI technology, Synthesia, enables enterprise users, including HR professionals and marketers, to create high-quality video content in 15 minutes without needing traditional camera setups or professional studios.</p>
<p>On June 13, Synthesia officially <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230613913631/en/AI-Video-Creation-Pioneer-Synthesia-Raises-90-Million-Series-C-Led-by-Accel" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the completion of its latest financing round in a press release. The Series C funding was led by prominent venture capital firm Accel, with active participation from other notable companies such as NVentures and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia</a>&#8216;s venture capital arm.</p>
<p>Existing investors who contributed to its previous series B funding in 2021 also participated in the latest round. These include prominent entities and notable personalities like Leiner Perkins, GV, Firstmark Capital, Alex Wang, Olivier Pomel, and Amjad Massadr.</p>
<p>The AI video generation platform closed its first fundraising in April 2021 with $12.5 million led by FirstMark. The round was followed by another $50 million in December, although the firm did not disclose its valuation.</p>
<p>The company, founded in 2017, has experienced tremendous growth since then, with more users and videos being generated on the platform each year. According to the press release, Synthesia has user growth of 456% year-over-year, with over 12 million videos created on the platform.</p>
<h2>AI Company Synthesia Expansion Plans</h2>
<p>Through the latest funding, the firm aims to make video creation easy for everyone and has already served many businesses worldwide.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the new capital infusion will enable the company to fast-track its cutting-edge AI research initiatives, propelling innovation and advancement.</p>
<p>The AI generative firm said that since its establishment, it had dedicated its efforts to tackling complex AI challenges and developing its core technology internally.</p>
<p>Victor Riparbelli, Synthesia&#8217;s CEO and co-founder, expressed his pride in the team&#8217;s accomplishments in making video production easy for everyone. He further noted that while Synthesia was not actively seeking new investments, its new VC partners, Accel and Nvidia, share the company&#8217;s vision of transforming traditional video creation into a digital process.</p>
<p>&#8220;While we weren&#8217;t actively looking for new investments, Accel and Nvidia share our vision for transforming traditional video production into a digital workflow enabling creators to bring their ideas, from training videos to Hollywood films to life with only a Synthesia account. I&#8217;m delighted to have them on board as we accelerate our AI research efforts,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>Speaking on the matter, Philippe Botteri, a partner at Accel, noted that Synthesia stood out at its first meeting as one of the rare generative AI companies with unique technology and an exceptional team that delivers good returns on investment for enterprise customers.</p>
<p>In addition to the $100 million funding, the company has secured new <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gamestop-illuvium-d1sks-nft-sale/">partnerships</a> with strategic VC investors. These partners include Tiffany&#8217;s, IHG, and Moody&#8217;s Analytics.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/">Generative AI Video Platform Synthesia Raises $90 Million at $1 Billion Valuation </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ai-video-synthesia-90m-1b-valuation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Stabilizes in $26K Range Following Recent Regulatory-Induced Volatility</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 13:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[atom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[axs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance usd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[busd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decemtraland]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mtic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258651</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/">Bitcoin Price Stabilizes in $26K Range Following Recent Regulatory-Induced Volatility</a></p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin is now experiencing some stability after heavy volatility following last week's events in the crypto sector.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/">Bitcoin Price Stabilizes in $26K Range Following Recent Regulatory-Induced Volatility</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/">Bitcoin Price Stabilizes in $26K Range Following Recent Regulatory-Induced Volatility</a></p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) seems to have stabilized as the world’s largest cryptocurrency by market cap recovers from recent volatility. Throughout last week, Bitcoin was unstable following regulatory issues that plagued the crypto industry and caused uncertainty and doubt.</p>
<p>According to CoinMarketCap data, Bitcoin is trading at $26,147 after climbing less than 2% over the last 7 days. Last week, the king coin shed more than $1,500 after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-binance-matic-sol-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> Binance for malpractice. Binance also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">went after Coinbase</a>, accusing the company of operating as an unregistered national securities exchange.</p>
<p>The Coinbase indictment gave way to a Bitcoin price pump of $2,000, increasing the asset’s volatility. However, this pump was shortlived as Bitcoin retraced to $26,500, maintaining this price for much longer.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the king coin’s volatile spree wasn’t over, as BTC lost another $1,000 towards the weekend. As the weekend progressed, Bitcoin began to climb again but could not hit $26,500.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Bitcoin’s dominance tells a different story. The dominance has nearly hit 50% as investors continuously flock to the asset. Dominance is the percentage of the entire crypto market a particular asset controls.</p>
<p>Regardless of the problems in the crypto market, the king coin’s dominance is reaching levels not seen since April 2021. When dominance is high, investors are likely to buy more.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Bitcoin sees more dominance in a bear market. This is largely because investors prefer to buy BTC at such downtimes to hedge against volatility in the market. Most crypto investors and community members believe that even in a bear market, Bitcoin offers more stability than altcoins.</p>
<h2>Price of Altcoins Also Suffered Volatility but Are Recovering Along with Bitcoin</h2>
<p>As Bitcoin bled, the altcoin market was essentially no different regarding volatility. In addition to the SEC’s lawsuits, altcoins also suffered following the SEC’s decision to designate a few more as securities. <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/litigation/complaints/2023/comp-pr2023-101.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">According to the SEC</a>, altcoins like BNB, MATIC, BUSD, SAND, ADA, SOL, MANA, ATOM, and AXS are also securities.</p>
<p>Binance’s native BNB was trading at more than $315 last week. However, it crashed to $222 yesterday and has only recovered to about $243 since then. While many other altcoins also fell, the coins are starting to recover. For instance, ETH, DOGE, ADA, MATIC, and SOL all saw gains. In the last day, XRP has also climbed nearly 8%. Others like LTC, TRX, AVAX, and DOT have all seen gains of up to 4%.</p>
<p>SUI is one of the largest climbers, pulling in up to 6% in the last 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>It is unclear whether the near future would augur well for Bitcoin. Over the last few weeks, BTC suffered through selling pressure and is still some distance from its 2023 high of over $31,000. The recent suspension of the US debt ceiling could also have a yet-to-be-known effect on Bitcoin as investors patiently await the outcome of the scheduled June 14 Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/">Bitcoin Price Stabilizes in $26K Range Following Recent Regulatory-Induced Volatility</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-price-26k-volatility/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fortune Ranks Ripple as One of Best Places to Work in Bay Area</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Temitope Olatunji]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258634</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/">Fortune Ranks Ripple as One of Best Places to Work in Bay Area</a></p>
<p>After the analysis of thousands of feedback from employees across various workplaces in the Bay Area, Ripple was named among the top 10 in the Fortune Magazine ranking of the best workplaces in 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/">Fortune Ranks Ripple as One of Best Places to Work in Bay Area</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/">Fortune Ranks Ripple as One of Best Places to Work in Bay Area</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.greatplacetowork.com/best-workplaces/bay-area/2023?category=small-and-medium" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Great Place to Work ranking</a> is based on employees’ experiences and general feedback about their workplaces. The data is usually gathered to see how companies can improve based on the information derived about specific needs. In conducting the analysis, they use a Trust Index survey to get qualitative and quantitative information about what is expected of good workplaces. This way, employees can share their feedback about their employers.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> expressed their appreciation for the recognition in a recent tweet on its official Twitter page.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We’re honored to be recognized by <a href="https://twitter.com/FortuneMagazine?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FortuneMagazine</a> in their roundup of the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BestWorkplaces?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BestWorkplaces</a> in the Bay Area. Thank you for the recognition!<a href="https://t.co/UNix5fbmtW">https://t.co/UNix5fbmtW</a> <a href="https://t.co/je3mcxXCBJ">pic.twitter.com/je3mcxXCBJ</a></p>
<p>— Ripple (@Ripple) <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple/status/1668296767828381696?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The information gathered for the survey includes how accessible and trustworthy the company’s leaders are, how employees are treated and appreciated, how they see their pay in relation to the workload, the structure, and pattern for promotions if the company has an opportunity for growth if they are proud of the work they do, and if they enjoy it, among many other yardsticks.</p>
<p>The employees’ feedback was then thoroughly analyzed using various criteria to form the ranking. After getting 1.3 million responses from companies with more than 7 million employees in 2022, the agency garnered close to 100,000 replies, from which they chose companies that should rank as Fortune’s Best Workplaces in the Bay Area in 2023.</p>
<h2>95% of Ripple’s Employees Have a Conducive Work Environment</h2>
<p>Most of the employees at Ripple, amounting to about 95% of the company’s workforce, agree that Ripple provides a conducive work environment. The high percentage is also a big deal compared to the responses from a typical workplace in the United States, which are usually around 57%.</p>
<p>Some of the comments made by Ripple&#8217;s employees include being able to take time off work when necessary, the freedom and independence the company grants them, the facilities provided by the company to create a comfortable workplace, and honesty and positive ethics among the management.</p>
<p>Ripple’s ranking of 8 out of 75 companies reveals a lot about its culture. First, it is an improvement over <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last year’s ranking of 34 out of 100 medium-scale</a> best companies to work with. The company also boasts of creating a work environment that enables employees to be the best versions of themselves while also being a ground for learning and career development. The blockchain payment provider sells itself as a workplace that values its employees and has the facilities to help them bring out their real selves as they carry out innovative tasks.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/">Fortune Ranks Ripple as One of Best Places to Work in Bay Area</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fortune-ripple-best-places-bay-area/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler Refers to Bitcoin and Ethereum as Non-Securities in Newly Revealed Video</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ltc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[near]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nera]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/">SEC Chair Gary Gensler Refers to Bitcoin and Ethereum as Non-Securities in Newly Revealed Video</a></p>
<p>The SEC chair previously indicated that all cryptocurrencies apart from BTC are securities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/">SEC Chair Gary Gensler Refers to Bitcoin and Ethereum as Non-Securities in Newly Revealed Video</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/">SEC Chair Gary Gensler Refers to Bitcoin and Ethereum as Non-Securities in Newly Revealed Video</a></p>
<p>In a recently unearthed video from a 2018 crypto-themed event hosted by Bloomberg and Fidelity, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gary Gensler</a>, the current chairman of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), made statements that contradict his current position on digital assets regulations in the country.</p>
<p>The video, which started circulating on Twitter on June 12, shows Gensler addressing institutional investors at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, where he worked as a professor before joining the SEC in 2021 after he was nominated by President Joe Biden, asserting that four major cryptocurrencies, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (Ether), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Litecoin</a> (LTC) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin-cash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Cash</a> (BCH) are not securities.</p>
<p>At the time, the SEC chairman highlighted that these four digital assets accounted for approximately 75% of the market, emphasizing their exclusion from the securities category.</p>
<p>&#8220;Over 70% of the crypto market is Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and Bitcoin Cash. Why did I name those four? They&#8217;re not security. Three-quarters of this [digital asset] market are not securities,&#8221; the SEC chair said in the video.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Chair Gensler in 2018 at a Bloomberg conference in NYC:</p>
<p>“Bitcoin. Ether. Litecoin. Bitcoin Cash. Why did I name those four? They’re not securities.”</p>
<p>What’s Goldman Gary going to say about this one? Deep fake? <a href="https://t.co/p7DJlYkJIt">pic.twitter.com/p7DJlYkJIt</a></p>
<p>— Ryan Selkis 🪳 (@twobitidiot) <a href="https://twitter.com/twobitidiot/status/1668328519334780928?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Gensler&#8217;s 2018 Comments Come from a Personal View</h2>
<p>Gensler&#8217;s remarks in the video have sparked controversy, as the comments contradict his recent suggestions that most cryptocurrencies, aside from BTC, may be considered securities.</p>
<p>Although legal experts such as crypto lawyer Preston Byrne have <a href="https://decrypt.co/138334/gary-gensler-sec-ethereum-not-security-mit-2018" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">clarified</a> that Gensler&#8217;s 2018 comments were made in a personal capacity, the remarks have raised concerns within the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Critics argue that his lack of clear guidance on the legality of specific tokens before initiating a &#8220;regulation by enforcement strategy&#8221; without a clear path for compliance has created uncertainty and frustration among the crypto community.</p>
<p>Last week, the market regulator <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-crypto-market-tokens-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">labeled 19 more crypto assets</a> as securities, including Solana (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a>), Polygon (MATIC), Flow (FLOW), and Near (NEAR), making it a total of 68 digital currencies the Commission has identified as security under Gensler&#8217;s leadership. However, none of the crypto assets mentioned in the 2018 video have yet made it to the SEC&#8217;s list.</p>
<h2>Is Ethereum a Security or Not?</h2>
<p>The SEC chair previously indicated that all cryptocurrencies apart from BTC are securities. On that note, the Commission has sued many crypto companies, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-enforcement-action-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase</a>, Ripple Labs, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance,</a> Gemini, and Genesis, for violating federal securities laws by selling unregistered securities in America.</p>
<p>In April, Patrick McHenry, chairman of the US House Financial Services Committee, requested that Gensler provide a clear answer as to whether Ethereum is a security. Still, the SEC chair failed to answer the question definitively.</p>
<p>That same month, another <a href="https://youtu.be/2D3SbYzzJLc" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">video</a> of Gensler from 2019 emerged before his time at the SEC. In the video, he praised the smart contract platform Algorand for its underlying technology before declaring its native token ALGO security in a lawsuit against the crypto exchange Bittrex.</p>
<p>Earlier in March, the SEC chairman disclosed that Ether could be a security after the Ethereum Merge,  referring to the protocol&#8217;s transmission to a proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism last year.</p>
<p>At the time, Gensler argued that all PoS tokens could be classified as a security under the Howey Test, used to measure assets that meet the security requirements.</p>
<p>According to him, users&#8217; profits from staking on such protocols indicate that the tokens are securities and should be regulated under the SEC purview.</p>
<p>&#8220;Whatever they&#8217;re promoting and putting into a protocol, and locking up their tokens in a protocol, a protocol that&#8217;s often a small group of entrepreneurs and developers are developing, I would just suggest that each of these token operators seek to come into compliance, and the same with the intermediaries,&#8221; he said.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/">SEC Chair Gary Gensler Refers to Bitcoin and Ethereum as Non-Securities in Newly Revealed Video</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-chair-gensler-bitcoin-ethereum/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manchester United (MANU) Shares Price Surges as Qatar Media Hints Takeover Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[manchester united]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[manchester united stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[manu stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[qater media]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/">Manchester United (MANU) Shares Price Surges as Qatar Media Hints Takeover Plans</a></p>
<p>MANU stock price surged by a staggering 30% as the news emerged of Sheikh Jassim being the preferred bidder of the Premier League soccer club. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/">Manchester United (MANU) Shares Price Surges as Qatar Media Hints Takeover Plans</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/">Manchester United (MANU) Shares Price Surges as Qatar Media Hints Takeover Plans</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, June 13, the shares price of Manchester United (NYSE: MANU) popped up by a massive 30% in the pre-market hours on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nyse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New York Stock Exchange</a>. The recent surge happened after Qatari media suggested Sheikh Jassim bin Hamad al-Thani is likely to succeed with his takeover bid.</p>
<p>On Tuesday, Qatar&#8217;s local news publication Al-Watan reported that Sheikh Jassim will soon emerge as the preferred bidder of the Premier League soccer club. However, Machester United has not confirmed this takeover so far. But the news was enough to put fuel to MANU shares.</p>
<p>The development happens after seven long months of negotiations that happened between the concerned parties. British petrochemicals billionaire Jim Ratcliffe was also one of the interested parties in buying the Manchester United Club.</p>
<p>The Al-Watan newspaper also shared the same news on their social media Twitter handle stating that “the success of Sheikh Jassim bin Hamad bin Jassim’s acquisition” would be announced soon. Fahad al-Emadi, editor of Al Watan newspaper also shared a similar message. He <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/13/soccer-man-utd-shares-pop-after-qatar-hints-at-takeover-bid-success.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“All the news received indicates the success of Sheikh Jassim bin Hamad bin Jassim’s acquisition of Manchester United, and the announcement of the deal will be very soon.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>With the current surge in the stock, MANU stock price has now moved close to $25. However, it still trades in negative since the beginning of the year 2023.</p>
<h2>Events that Influence MANU Shares Price</h2>
<p>The American owners of Manchester United i.e. the Glazer family announced the formal sale process of the club last year in November 2022. Back then, the company&#8217;s board of directors spoke about exploring “strategic alternatives” for the club.</p>
<p>Last year in August 2022, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> also made a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/buying-manchester-united-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">joking comment</a> that he was buying Manchester United which sparked a major reaction in the global football community.</p>
<p>In recent days, Sheikh Jassim submitted an enhanced bid of approximately £5 billion, accompanied by a pledge of £1 billion in investment. This offer aims to acquire complete ownership of Old Trafford. Meanwhile, Ratcliffe&#8217;s proposal is believed to be for a 60% stake in the club, with the possibility of involvement from members of the Glazer Family.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/">Manchester United (MANU) Shares Price Surges as Qatar Media Hints Takeover Plans</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-manu-shares-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taiwan Mobile Open to Potential Alliance with Local Crypto Firms</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taiwan Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XREX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258655</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/">Taiwan Mobile Open to Potential Alliance with Local Crypto Firms</a></p>
<p>Taiwan Mobile's decision demonstrates the growing interest of conventional sectors in capitalizing on the possibilities of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/">Taiwan Mobile Open to Potential Alliance with Local Crypto Firms</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/">Taiwan Mobile Open to Potential Alliance with Local Crypto Firms</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan Mobile </span>Co Ltd (TPE: 3045), one of Taiwan&#8217;s prominent telecommunications companies, has expressed its openness to potential alliance opportunities with Taiwanese firms specializing in crypto.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As </span><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/taiwan-mobile-in-early-talks-on-possible-investment-in-local-crypto-platform-1.1932321" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by Bloomberg, the company is reportedly engaging in discussions with various Taiwanese firms that specialize in digital currencies. This includes the fintech blockchain company XREX. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to sources familiar with the matter, the talks aim to assess potential alliance opportunities and explore potential investments. However, no decisions have been made, and a deal may not be reached, according to the sources.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">XREX, a fintech and blockchain company, is known for its expertise in providing a secure and efficient platform for cryptocurrency transactions. The specific benefits and objectives of a potential alliance between Taiwan Mobile and crypto-focused companies remain undisclosed.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, such collaborations may provide mutual benefits. Collaboration with crypto enterprises could enable Taiwan Mobile to explore new business models, services, and revenue sources inside the digital asset ecosystem. Additionally, these collaborations may make it easier to integrate blockchain technology into telecoms infrastructure, improving efficiency, security, and customer services.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In response to inquiries about alleged talks between Taiwan Mobile and XREX, TaiwanMobile claimed that it is “open to any potential opportunities.” However, the corporation made no further remarks or provided any additional information on the situation. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Similarly, Wayne Huang, co-founder of XREX, refused to clarify whether his company is currently in talks with Taiwan Mobile. However, the co-founder highlighted that there are significant synergies between established institutions like telecom companies and blockchain firms like XREX.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Huang points out that organizations such as telecommunications corporations already have a large user base that has gone through the appropriate Know-Your-Customer (KYC) requirements. On the other hand, XREX </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrex-17-million-funding-dollar-liquidity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">brings</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> its resources, and domain expertise in blockchain technology and cybersecurity to the table. </span></p>
<h2><b>Collaborations Between the Telecom and Crypto Firms</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Notably, Taiwan Mobile&#8217;s decision demonstrates the growing interest of conventional sectors in capitalizing on the possibilities of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The growing popularity and usage of crypto have driven established firms from a variety of industries to seek collaborations and investments in the blockchain and crypto sectors. By demonstrating a willingness to engage with crypto-based firms, Taiwan Mobile acknowledges the potential for innovation and growth within this emerging industry.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a significant move, NTT Docomo, the largest mobile telephone operator in Japan, </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ntt-docomo-web3-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> last year its intention to partner with Irish-American IT company Accenture, on Web3 implementation. According to the agreement, NTT Docomo would invest up to 600 billion yen ($4 billion) in Web3 infrastructure in the East Asian corporation. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This initiative is part of a larger plan by the largest Japanese mobile telecom provider to use the Web3 space with its existing capabilities. Meanwhile, Japan has </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/japan-web3-white-paper-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">adopted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a Web3 white paper, which could propel the East Asian country to the forefront of global crypto development. </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/toyota-shares-electric-vehicles/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/">Taiwan Mobile Open to Potential Alliance with Local Crypto Firms</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/taiwan-mobile-local-crypto-firms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4470 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1085030 metric#prefetches=217 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=224 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=101.51 metric#ms-cache=5.25 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2502 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.2 -->