<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 20:49:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>NFTNYC 2023 Recap: Safeguarding NFTs &#8211; 
Insights from CEO of My Neighbor Alice Lenny Pettersson</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nftnyc-2023-recap-safeguarding-nfts-insights-from-ceo-of-my-neighbor-alice-lenny-pettersson/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/nftnyc-2023-recap-safeguarding-nfts-insights-from-ceo-of-my-neighbor-alice-lenny-pettersson/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 20:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nftnyc-2023-recap-safeguarding-nfts-insights-from-ceo-of-my-neighbor-alice-lenny-pettersson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>My Neighbor Alice CEO, Lenny Pettersson, spoke at the three-day NFTNYC conference, which happened between April 12th and 14th, alongside other NFT projects and creators&#8212;sharing his insights with calmer than usual audiences to highlight the shifts in NFT for games, metaverse, as well as the importance to protect NFTs from falling in price. Speaking on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nftnyc-2023-recap-safeguarding-nfts-insights-from-ceo-of-my-neighbor-alice-lenny-pettersson/">NFTNYC 2023 Recap: Safeguarding NFTs &#8211;<br />
Insights from CEO of My Neighbor Alice Lenny Pettersson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">My Neighbor Alice CEO, Lenny Pettersson, spoke at the three-day NFTNYC conference, which happened between April 12th and 14th, alongside other NFT projects and creators&mdash;sharing his insights with calmer than usual audiences to highlight the shifts in NFT for games, metaverse, as well as the importance to protect NFTs from falling in price.</p>
<p>Speaking on the recent uptrend in investing in collectibles and gaming assets, Lenny has highlighted how blockchain games are now at the forefront and equivalent to the mainstream gaming industry. The younger investors are now looking to invest in blockchain games with reliable and credible development teams, with a much lesser interest in the token ecosystem of a project than in previous years.</p>
<p>Another spotlight moment for Lenny was the moderation of a panel discussion on &ldquo;NFTs: Placing More Power in Players&rsquo; Hands&rdquo;, Lenny discusses the potential of a significant IP that offers interoperability through NFTs and the importance of keeping a healthy relationship between developers and players.</p>
<p>He closes off his topic by addressing the issues of falling NFT prices. Although there is no guaranteed way to protect an NFT from falling in price from various factors, which includes market sentiment, supply and demand, and broader economic trends.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lenny advises NFT collectors to take additional steps to help mitigate the risk of their NFTs losing value by doing a thorough research and due diligence before buying an NFT. Look into the artist or creator, the rarity and uniqueness of the NFT, and the historical sales data for similar NFTs. Information on credible news channels to help investors make informed decisions and avoid overpaying for an NFT.</p>
<p>In most cases, diversifying the NFT holdings by investing in various assets with different creators and themes can help spread the risk and reduce the impact of any individual NFT losing value. NFT collectors were advised to take a long-term approach to NFT investing and focus on assets with long-term potential value, such as those with strong community support, unique functionality, or historical significance.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>About My Neighbor Alice</h2>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice</a> is a social online multiplayer builder game built on the Chromia blockchain platform. The project is designed to promote an end-to-end blockchain game ecosystem that allows for an easy transactions within the NFT and gaming community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The technology behind My Neighbor Alice is based on a staking and renting system. The system is being developed and will debut next year, allowing users to rent their NFTs for even more significant earnings potential. Ultimately sets them apart from other play-to-earn games. My Neighbor Alice aims to become a dominant entity in the blockchain gaming space and seeks to maintain and develop a vibrant community for diverse players.</p>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Media Contact: pr@myneighboralice.com</p>
<p dir="ltr">Contact Name: Fati Hakim</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nftnyc-2023-recap-safeguarding-nfts-insights-from-ceo-of-my-neighbor-alice-lenny-pettersson/">NFTNYC 2023 Recap: Safeguarding NFTs &#8211;<br />
Insights from CEO of My Neighbor Alice Lenny Pettersson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/nftnyc-2023-recap-safeguarding-nfts-insights-from-ceo-of-my-neighbor-alice-lenny-pettersson/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals is 63% sold out as the hunt for new tokens takes SUI tokens to new heights</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-is-63-sold-out-as-the-hunt-for-new-tokens-takes-sui-tokens-to-new-heights/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-is-63-sold-out-as-the-hunt-for-new-tokens-takes-sui-tokens-to-new-heights/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Motiur Rahman]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-is-63-sold-out-as-the-hunt-for-new-tokens-takes-sui-tokens-to-new-heights/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals presale is now 63% complete as investors camp on new tokens $ASI, the native token, will power ActualizeAI, an AI-based signal service $ASI could rise by 1,000% after listing on exchanges as more investors access the token AltSignals upcoming token $ASI, currently in the first phase of the presale, is 63.85% sold out. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-is-63-sold-out-as-the-hunt-for-new-tokens-takes-sui-tokens-to-new-heights/">AltSignals is 63% sold out as the hunt for new tokens takes SUI tokens to new heights</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals presale is now 63% complete as investors camp on new tokens</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI, the native token, will power ActualizeAI, an AI-based signal service</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">$ASI could rise by 1,000% after listing on exchanges as more investors access the token</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals upcoming token $ASI, currently in the first phase of the presale, is 63.85% sold out. The quick sell-off of the token that will power an AI trading signal service by AltSignals underlines investors&rsquo; growing appetite for new tokens. $ASI will be the first of its own for a reputable trading service provider, explaining why investors are anxious. Investors can join the presale here.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>SUI token surges 1,000% amid strong demand&nbsp;</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">SUI, the token of the highly anticipated Sui Network, went up 1,000% on May 03, shortly after it went live. The price increase underlined investors&rsquo; demand for newly launched tokens powering novel use cases.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Sui is a Layer-1 blockchain network that operates similarly to established protocols like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, unlike its peers, Sui facilitates instant transactions through Move, a native programming language. Sui also enables parallel transaction processing by scaling horizontally. Enthusiasts see this feature as crucial in the overall scalability and throughput of the network. As such, SUI is expected to be powerful in retail payments as well as gaming.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The case for SUI is a testament that investors are always searching for the next big thing in crypto, despite the prolonged bear market. AltSignals token $ASI is in no way different. $ASI is unique, and its success is pegged on investors&rsquo; belief that it caters to an unmet need in the market &ndash; AI-enabled trading. So far, as the presale has shown, investors are highly optimistic.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>What is AltSignals and $ASI</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.altsignals.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>AltSignals</u></a> is a UK-based signal service company that was launched in 2017. Since then, it has grown popular for providing quality trading signals to its over 50,000 members on Telegram. The trading signal service has earned a 4.8/5 star rating on Trustpilot.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The AltSignals team wants to upgrade its signal-generating service after its early success. It seeks to integrate artificial intelligence, natural language processing, machine learning, and advanced sentiment analysis in signal generation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The new AI-powered trading platform, dubbed ActualizeAI, will be powered by $ASI crypto tokens. The tokens will be the unit of membership in ActualizeAI, which holders will use to vote on governance. The idea of fully automated trading, available 24/7, makes ActualizeAI a step higher and why investors are buying $ASI.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Is $ASI a good investment?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Looking at AltSignals in general, $ASI could be a good investment for investors looking to grow earnings through trading digital assets, shares, and forex. The good thing about the signal service is that it has earned a reputation for the past years. Investors know they are dipping their fingers into an already trusted service and company.</p>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI is starting, and its price could skyrocket as more investors join ActualizeAI. It then makes sense to expect huge returns once the token completes the presale and starts to get listed on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apart from speculating on the price of $ASI, investors can earn by staking the token and participating in trading tournaments. Investors also get early access to exclusive opportunities on the platform. As such, the token could be a good investment for investors seeking passive income.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Will $ASI reach $1 in 2023?</strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">$ASI is valued at $0.015 presently. To get to $1, the token must rise by over 6,500%. This could be an over-ambitious prediction for 2023, although we can&rsquo;t rule out the price in the future.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Our conservative prediction is $0.15 when the token is listed on major exchanges, which is expected to occur in the second quarter. As we already saw with SUI, newly launched tokens easily rise by over 1,000% when demand is strong. Thus, if $ASI rises by similar margins, given the current and expected demand, a 10x price is most likely.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-is-63-sold-out-as-the-hunt-for-new-tokens-takes-sui-tokens-to-new-heights/">AltSignals is 63% sold out as the hunt for new tokens takes SUI tokens to new heights</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-is-63-sold-out-as-the-hunt-for-new-tokens-takes-sui-tokens-to-new-heights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin and DigiToads leading the charge as meme coins disrupt the crypto market</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-and-digitoads-leading-the-charge-as-meme-coins-disrupt-the-crypto-market/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-and-digitoads-leading-the-charge-as-meme-coins-disrupt-the-crypto-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-and-digitoads-leading-the-charge-as-meme-coins-disrupt-the-crypto-market/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiToads is currently conducting a presale of its native token, TOADS. At press time, the current presale stage Lilypad 5 was 83.84% sold out. A single TOADS token is currently going for $0.024. Meme coins might have taken their sweet time to enter the crypto hall of fame, but there&#8217;s no denying that they still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-and-digitoads-leading-the-charge-as-meme-coins-disrupt-the-crypto-market/">Dogecoin and DigiToads leading the charge as meme coins disrupt the crypto market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>DigiToads is currently conducting a presale of its native token, TOADS.</li>
<li>At press time, the current presale stage Lilypad 5 was 83.84% sold out.</li>
<li>A single TOADS token is currently going for $0.024.</li>
</ul>
<p>Meme coins might have taken their sweet time to enter the crypto hall of fame, but there&rsquo;s no denying that they still have a long way to go. Inspired by viral internet memes, meme coins are edging ahead to establish themselves as a quality mainstream financial instrument.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Take the example of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin&nbsp;</a>or even <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl">DigiToads</a>, which has raised more than $2.2 million in just four presale stages.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Built on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum&nbsp;</a>network, DigiToads has been garnering a lot of attention with its next-generation features that combine the utility of different cryptocurrencies. The hybrid model enables users to earn a passive income.</p>
<h2>DigiToads: Unravelling the full potential of DeFi</h2>
<p>DigiToads is an upcoming meme coin that offers stake-to-earn and play-to-earn features on its platform. Its native token is TOADs which can be used to access all its features. DigiToads&rsquo; unique DeFi model makes it an ideal option for those interested in learning all about cryptocurrency trading for beginners.</p>
<p>You can stake tokens or trade them, participate in Web 3.0 games to win rewards, enter giveaways worth $150,000, and even stand a chance to win daily and weekly prizes. For those interested, the TOADS token has been released on presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With 10 stages in all, the presale process is currently in its fifth phase &lsquo;Lillypad 5&rsquo;. You can participate in the presale <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl">here</a>.</p>
<h2>DigiToads game</h2>
<p>DigiToads game is based in a metaverse swamp where players have to show their skills by defeating their competitors with the help of DigiToads. These digital creatures have unusual abilities like strength or a special trait that can up a player&rsquo;s game. Players can use TOADS tokens to acquire food, potions, and exercise equipment for their DigiToads.</p>
<p>When the season ends, the players occupying the top 25% of the positions on the scoreboard are rewarded with TOADS tokens. As far as staking goes, there are ample opportunities to stake NFTs on DigiToads. The longer the period of staking, the higher the rewards that you will earn. The staking pool comprises 2% of the annual profits rakes by the project.</p>
<p>The DigiToads team has laid out a community-centric roadmap for its future growth. These plans include donating 2.5% of the annual profits to organizations involved in the preservation of rainforests and replanting trees.</p>
<p>The organizations that would get these donations would be picked out by the community members. Moreover, the team would be launching an online learning facility to offer sessions on cryptocurrencies and the DigiToads network. To access these sessions, one would have to own at least three TOADS NFTs.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin has a new patron: Sean Ono Lennon</h2>
<p>Dogecoin is one of the most-traded meme coins and its symbol briefly replaced Twitter&rsquo;s iconic blue bird symbol. It draws inspiration from a Japanese dog breed and its meme coin&rsquo;s native token is DOGE.</p>
<p>Dogecoin was initially rolled out as a hard fork of Litecoin and the meme coin recently made waves internationally after former Beatles singer John Lennon&rsquo;s son Sean Ono Lennon announced that he is now following Dogecoin founder Billy Markus on Twitter. He had earlier also extended his support to Bitcoin in a tweet.</p>
<h2>What are analysts saying about DigiToads?</h2>
<p>DigiToads has become a sensation within the crypto space and especially among the meme coins. If it continues on the same track, DigiToads could be among the meme coins that are going to shine in 2023.</p>
<p>The major reasons behind TOADS&rsquo; popularity include its higher growth potential and the diversity it offers users when it comes to earning passive income. By choosing between various opportunities, users can look forward to building a respectable means of residual income.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-and-digitoads-leading-the-charge-as-meme-coins-disrupt-the-crypto-market/">Dogecoin and DigiToads leading the charge as meme coins disrupt the crypto market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dogecoin-and-digitoads-leading-the-charge-as-meme-coins-disrupt-the-crypto-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flare’s API Portal launches on the Google Cloud Marketplace</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways Flare has integrated its API Portal on the Google Cloud Marketplace. The integration grants developers access to a wide range of blockchain APIs. Flare partnered with Uppercent earlier this year to launch an NFT marketplace for e-learning.&#160; Flare integrates its API Portal on Google Cloud Marketplace Flare, a Layer 1 blockchain that gives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/">Flare’s API Portal launches on the Google Cloud Marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Flare has integrated its API Portal on the Google Cloud Marketplace.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The integration grants developers access to a wide range of blockchain APIs.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Flare partnered with Uppercent earlier this year to launch an NFT marketplace for e-learning.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Flare integrates its API Portal on Google Cloud Marketplace</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Flare, a Layer 1 blockchain that gives developers decentralized access to high-integrity data from other chains and the internet, has announced the integration of its API Portal on Google Cloud Marketplace.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a press release shared with Coinjournal, the team said it is launching some of the first blockchain APIs on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>latest cryptocurrency news</u></a> means that blockchain data from Flare&rsquo;s nodes and Connected Chain nodes can be accessed by developers using Google Cloud Marketplace to perform easy blockchain transactions and read up-to-date states.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Thanks to this integration, Google Cloud&rsquo;s built-in Cloud Marketplace now supports blockchain APIs for Algorand, BNB Smart Chain, Bitcoin, Dogecoin, Ethereum, Flare, Litecoin, Songbird, and XRP.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, the Flare team said all of the blockchain APIs that are added to its API Portal in the future would be made available to Google Cloud developers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With blockchain APIs, developers can create applications that carry out transactions and query on-chain data pertaining to the chain&rsquo;s latest state.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By accessing APIs, developers no longer need to run their own nodes for the blockchains they wish to interact with. This is a useful feature for developers, especially when creating cross-chain applications that must query multiple data sources.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Developers can access Flare APIs using their existing Google Cloud account</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Flare team informed developers that they can access all of Flare&rsquo;s current APIs via their existing Google Cloud account.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While commenting on this latest development, Josh Edwards, Flare&rsquo;s VP of Engineering, said;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Greater availability of leading blockchain APIs on platforms such as Google Cloud Marketplace reduces the barriers to Web3 participation. It makes it easier for developers to experiment with blockchain technology and its many use cases without being burdened by onerous hardware costs and ongoing maintenance. It also opens up the possibility for larger organizations and partners to experiment with a safe, secure, and approved set of Web3 APIs. As a result, developer teams have the flexibility to create applications without any infrastructure headache, which allows them to focus on creating and shipping great products.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">James Tromans, Head of Web3 Engineering at Google Cloud, also said;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to support and promote the ambitions of our Web3 partners in our ecosystem, with the integration of Flare&rsquo;s high-performance APIs into our Marketplace.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Flare has been busy creating despite the bear market. In February,&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/flare-and-uppercent-collaborate-to-create-an-e-learning-nft-marketplace/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Flare partnered with Uppercent</u></a> to launch the first NFT marketplace for e-learning</p>
<p dir="ltr">Flare is an EVM-based Layer 1 blockchain that gives developers decentralized access to high-integrity data from other chains and the internet.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/">Flare’s API Portal launches on the Google Cloud Marketplace</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/flares-api-portal-launches-on-the-google-cloud-marketplace/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimistic Tone Lifts Cryptocurrency Market. Metacade, Post Presale, Holds Strong as It Lists on Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/optimistic-tone-lifts-cryptocurrency-market-metacade-post-presale-holds-strong-as-it-lists-on-exchanges/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/optimistic-tone-lifts-cryptocurrency-market-metacade-post-presale-holds-strong-as-it-lists-on-exchanges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/optimistic-tone-lifts-cryptocurrency-market-metacade-post-presale-holds-strong-as-it-lists-on-exchanges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While crypto investing can produce significant percentage gains over a long-term timeframe, investors seeking quick gains at the top of prolonged rallies often see negative returns. The cryptocurrency market tends to fluctuate between maximum fear and maximum greed, with widespread bullish sentiment occasionally producing the inverse effect on the market. Crypto investing has been rewarding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/optimistic-tone-lifts-cryptocurrency-market-metacade-post-presale-holds-strong-as-it-lists-on-exchanges/">Optimistic Tone Lifts Cryptocurrency Market. Metacade, Post Presale, Holds Strong as It Lists on Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">While crypto investing can produce significant percentage gains over a long-term timeframe, investors seeking quick gains at the top of prolonged rallies often see negative returns. The cryptocurrency market tends to fluctuate between maximum fear and maximum greed, with widespread bullish sentiment occasionally producing the inverse effect on the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto investing has been rewarding recently, with new projects such as <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=63" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> seeing major success during their early stages. Many participating in crypto investing are wondering whether prices will continue to rise or whether a correction is imminent, and what this might mean for promising new projects such as Metacade.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto investing becomes overbearingly bullish. What could this mean for Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sentiment has remained bullish in the cryptocurrency market as Bitcoin (BTC) <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/bitcoin-pushes-past-30000-investors-eye-end-rate-rises-2023-04-11/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>recently broke through</u></a> a critical psychological resistance level at $30,000. Shortly after, Ethereum (ETH) broke $2,000 and kickstarted calls for an alt season following a multi-month Bitcoin rally.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Alt seasons can be prime times to buy as crypto investing often produces significant returns during this period. However, it remains to be seen whether 2023 will have a fully-fledged alt season, as some leading tokens in the cryptocurrency market have yet to retest support.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market is filled with new altcoin opportunities, including the emergence of Metacade &ndash; a comprehensive GameFi platform that brings <a href="https://sensoriumxr.com/articles/what-is-play-to-earn-gaming" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>extensive earning capabilities</u></a> to its community. The MCADE token has just been launched on UniSwap and Bitmart, which has generated excitement among the Web3 community.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The MCADE token presale was a major success, raising $16.4 million worth of investment to develop the blockchain arcade</strong>. Metacade has been one of the most exciting new platforms in the cryptocurrency GameFi market during 2023, as investors have strongly backed its expansive, community-based and futuristic Game-Fi vision.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Could MCADE reach $4 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto investing during a bear market can potentially produce major long-term returns, especially when purchasing promising new tokens such as MCADE. Whether or not the recent rally in the cryptocurrency markets continues, the MCADE token is widely considered to have vast potential for the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE is fresh from a successful presale and two popular exchange listings in April 2023. The token can now be purchased on both Uniswap and Bitmart, which could boost overall demand for the project in the coming months and years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto price analysts have highlighted MCADE&rsquo;s innate utility and deflationary tokenomics as reasons to be bullish. Some put the 2025 MCADE price prediction at $3.50 &ndash; a significant price increase from its current price of $0.039.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=63" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> will become the largest on-chain arcade in <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/web3/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Web3</u></a>, offering a vast selection of different play-to-earn (P2E) arcade games that each has integrated earning potential for players. The project is a community-driven initiative built by gamers for gamers, which can help usher in a new era of gaming on the blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A core aim of the Metacade project is to create a central hub for blockchain gamers to enjoy. To do this, the platform brings several variations of the classic P2E mechanic. Metacade&rsquo;s earning capabilities go beyond gaming to include Create2Earn, Compete2Earn, and Work2Earn.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does MCADE work?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token is used to pay rewards in the metaverse arcade. As well as this, Metacade is developing various DeFi services for crypto investing, including staking to earn a passive yield and voting privileges for the project&rsquo;s governance proposals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The metaverse arcade will contain the most extensive collection of Play2Earn arcade games on the blockchain. Gamers can play solo while progressing through infinite levels and trying to beat their high score while earning MCADE token rewards for their in-game achievements.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Competitive gamers can join paid entry tournaments through the Compete2Earn feature. These tournaments will have major prize pools paid in MCADE, which allows players to go head-to-head and test their skills for the chance to gain ultimate victory.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The community hub will reward content creators through Create2Earn. Community members can contribute to the platform in several ways, including posting game reviews, sharing crypto investing alpha, and interacting with other users&rsquo; posts. In return, MCADE tokens will be paid out to encourage continued participation.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, Metacade will help crypto enthusiasts kickstart a career in blockchain through the Work2Earn mechanic. One element of Work2Earn is the crypto jobs board, which will advertise open positions at some of the hottest start-ups in Web3. Another is beta testing, where gamers can play brand new P2E games and earn rewards for providing feedback.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade could help drive progress for play to earn gaming</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The project aims to usher in a new era for the gaming cryptocurrency market by helping support new projects during the early stages of development. The Metagrants program will involve a voting process from the Metacade community, where the most in-demand titles are provided with early stage funding to help bring the game into the Metaverse arcade when it&rsquo;s built.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade supports developers and community members directly and unlocks the true power of decentralization. <strong>With generous rewards for gamers, a variety of additional earning mechanics, and supporting innovation in the space, Metacade could be a true gamechanger for play to earn</strong>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Is MCADE worth buying?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Price analysts have highlighted Metacade&rsquo;s fundamental solid characteristics as a good reason to be bullish for the future. GameFi has vast disruptive potential for the wider gaming industry, which is why GameFi crypto investing has produced over 100x gains for several of the leading projects in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade combines the best elements of play-to-earn gaming with a sprawling, decentralized community. To learn more about how to buy MCADE, head over to the project&rsquo;s <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=63" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>website</u></a>. The MCADE token is currently valued at $0.039 and may be the ideal addition to a long-term GameFi portfolio.</p>
<p><strong>You can find more information, including how to buy MCADE,&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=63" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/optimistic-tone-lifts-cryptocurrency-market-metacade-post-presale-holds-strong-as-it-lists-on-exchanges/">Optimistic Tone Lifts Cryptocurrency Market. Metacade, Post Presale, Holds Strong as It Lists on Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/optimistic-tone-lifts-cryptocurrency-market-metacade-post-presale-holds-strong-as-it-lists-on-exchanges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EX Ankr and Blockdaemon executives launch Liquid Staking Derivatives L1 chain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-executives-launch-liquid-staking-derivatives-l1-chain/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-executives-launch-liquid-staking-derivatives-l1-chain/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-executives-launch-liquid-staking-derivatives-l1-chain/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Liquid Staking Derivatives layer 1 blockchain is called Tenet. The blockchain will create a hub for Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSDs). Tenet&#8217;s testnet went live today allowing developers to interact and experiment with the platform. Former Ankr&#160;and Blockdaemon executives have joined hands to create Tenet, the first Layer 1 blockchain built to create a hub for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-executives-launch-liquid-staking-derivatives-l1-chain/">EX Ankr and Blockdaemon executives launch Liquid Staking Derivatives L1 chain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Liquid Staking Derivatives layer 1 blockchain is called Tenet.</li>
<li>The blockchain will create a hub for Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSDs).</li>
<li>Tenet&rsquo;s testnet went live today allowing developers to interact and experiment with the platform.</li>
</ul>
<p>Former <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ark/what-is-ark/">Ankr&nbsp;</a>and Blockdaemon executives have joined hands to create <a href="https://tenet.org/">Tenet</a>, the first Layer 1 blockchain built to create a hub for Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSDs).</p>
<p>The Tenet Testnet has been launched today, allowing developers to interact and experiment with the platform.</p>
<h2>Tenet protocol features</h2>
<p>Tenet is an <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum </a>Virtual Machine (EVM) compatible Layer 1 protocol. It is designed to bring additional liquidity and yield opportunities to LSDs by allowing users to re-stake their assets in the network and participate in the network&rsquo;s DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>Different from other Cosmos chains that rely on their own native tokens for PoS security, Tenet validators can make use of a unique mechanism called Diversified Proof of Stake (DiPoS). DiPoS allows validation by re-staking LSDs from other L1 ecosystems supported by Tenet, such as <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, BNB Chain, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cosmos/what-is-cosmos/">Cosmos</a>, Solana, and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/what-is-polygon/">Polygon</a>.</p>
<p>Re-staking LSDs from other blockchains ensures the long-term security of the Tenet chain by leveraging the joint security of each of the Layer 1 ecosystems it services.</p>
<p>Commenting on the launch of Tenet&rsquo;s Testnet, the co-founder of Tenet, Greg Gopman, said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;At Ankr, we helped bring Liquid Staking Tokens to eight Blockchains and built out some of the best LSD infrastructure in the industry, but no one used it. Tenet was really a golden opportunity for being first to market in utilizing best-in-class technology with almost $20B in untapped liquidity. We analyzed what other projects like Berachain and Eigen Layer were doing and realized that there was a better way to position ourselves to best address the market. We&rsquo;ve chosen to take a user-centric path, making the staking and LSD experience simpler and more secure for the average user.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Using LSDs on Tenet</h2>
<p>The re-staked LSDs on Tenet are usable just like LSDs or LLSDs to take advantage of DeFi opportunities on the Testnet ecosystem.</p>
<p>Besides taking advantage of lending pools and DEXs, Tenet users will also be able to mint the Universal Stablecoin interest-free, allowing them to receive an &ldquo;advance&rdquo; on their future LSD yields.</p>
<p>Tenet also offers the first L1 ecosystem with native gauges, which allow veTenet token holders to earn direct rewards to the pools they choose.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-executives-launch-liquid-staking-derivatives-l1-chain/">EX Ankr and Blockdaemon executives launch Liquid Staking Derivatives L1 chain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-executives-launch-liquid-staking-derivatives-l1-chain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor on bitcoin: ‘hold on to it and stomach the volatility’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/michael-saylor-view-on-bitcoin-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=138361</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy Inc narrowed its bitcoin-related loss in the first quarter. Its executive chairman Michael Saylor remains bullish as ever on bitcoin. Bitcoin is currently up roughly 70% versus the start of the year 2023. Bitcoin has lost about 7.0% in recent weeks but Michael Saylor &#8211; the Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy Inc remains convinced as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/michael-saylor-view-on-bitcoin-price/">Michael Saylor on bitcoin: ‘hold on to it and stomach the volatility’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>MicroStrategy Inc narrowed its bitcoin-related loss in the first quarter.</li>
<li>Its executive chairman Michael Saylor remains bullish as ever on bitcoin.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up roughly 70% versus the start of the year 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> has lost about 7.0% in recent weeks but Michael Saylor &ndash; the Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy Inc remains convinced as ever in its long-term potential.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor on MicroStrategy&rsquo;s Q1 results</h2>
<p>Earlier this week, the Nasdaq-listed firm said impairment loss related to its bitcoin holdings narrowed more than 90% sequentially to $18.9 million in the <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/en/investor-relations/press/microstrategy-announces-first-quarter-2023-financial-results_05-01-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first quarter</a>. According to Saylor:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is the ultimate digital scarcity network. It&rsquo;s moved up about 50% on average over the last three years. The key with bitcoin is to be able to hold on to it and stomach the volatility.</p></blockquote>
<p>MicroStrategy now owns a total of about 140,000 bitcoins. Naturally, therefore, the recent surge in BTC that&rsquo;s still up some 70% for the year has been a meaningful tailwind for the company.</p>
<p>&ldquo;MSTR&rdquo; has more than doubled since the start of 2023.</p>
<h2>Why is bitcoin price on the rise this year?</h2>
<p>Saylor attributes strength in the price of bitcoin this year partially to <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/04/12/economy/cpi-inflation-march/index.html">inflation</a> that&rsquo;s still running at an annualised rate of 5.0% in the United States &ndash; well above the Fed&rsquo;s 2.0% target.</p>
<p>The recent bank failures, he added, have also hurt confidence in the fiat currencies. On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/05/02/microstrategys-michael-saylor-says-hold-onto-bitcoin-and-stomach-the-volatility.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Closing Bell: Overtime</a>&rdquo;, Saylor said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin is a bank in cyberspace run by incorruptible software. So, the phase be your own bank has emerged as an investment idea in the United States.</p></blockquote>
<p>Interestingly, he dubbed the ongoing <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tylerroush/2023/03/29/crypto-crackdown-here-are-all-the-major-crypto-firms-facing-charges-from-regulators-this-year/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">crypto crackdown</a> a benefit for bitcoin as well since it has established a reputation as the safe-haven asset.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/michael-saylor-view-on-bitcoin-price/">Michael Saylor on bitcoin: ‘hold on to it and stomach the volatility’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash price remains calm ahead of the Fed decision</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-remains-calm-ahead-of-the-fed-decision/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-remains-calm-ahead-of-the-fed-decision/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 12:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-remains-calm-ahead-of-the-fed-decision/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash price has remained in a consolidation phase in the past few weeks. It remains significantly below the year-to-date high of $153. The Fed is expected to hike interest rates by 0.25% and point to a strategic pause.&#160; Bitcoin Cash price has moved sideways in May as the recent bullish momentum faded. The BCH [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-remains-calm-ahead-of-the-fed-decision/">Bitcoin Cash price remains calm ahead of the Fed decision</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price has remained in a consolidation phase in the past few weeks.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">It remains significantly below the year-to-date high of $153.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The Fed is expected to hike interest rates by 0.25% and point to a strategic pause.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a> price has moved sideways in May as the recent bullish momentum faded. The BCH coin was trading at $120, where it has been in the past few days. This price is below the year-to-date high of $152.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Fed interest rate decision</h2>
<p dir="ltr">BCH price continued consolidating as investors waited for the upcoming interest rate decision by the Federal Reserve. This will be an important decision because of the current state of the American economy.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the unemployment rate sits at a 50-year low, inflation remains stubbornly high while the manufacturing output has contracted for several straight months. Similarly, data published last week showed that the economic slowdown continued in Q1.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other risk is that the commercial real estate industry is on the verge of collapse as interest rates rise and maturities near. Further, because of hybrid work and white-collar layoffs, many houses have high vacancy rates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a possibility that the Federal Reserve will have a balancing act in its decision later today. Analysts believe that the bank will hike rates by 0.25% and then hint of a strategic pause. In a note, an analyst told Coindesk:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;As the market is expecting a pause after this hike, we&rsquo;ll be looking for the sentence on &lsquo;additional policy firming may be appropriate&rsquo; to be removed from the statement, replaced by more open-ended language leaving the door open for either more rate hikes or a pause.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A dovish tone will be positive for Bitcoin Cash and other cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Cardano, and Solana. Historically, these coins tend to do well when the Fed has abandoned its hawkish tone.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The other catalyst for Bitcoin Cash is the performance of regional bank stocks on Wednesday. Of companies like Western Alliance and PacWest continue crashing, it could incentivize more people to buy cryptocurrencies like BCH.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price prediction&nbsp;</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/03/1683117173343-223ed11b-1581-4ae1-a292-ccb0a8e35915.png" style="width: 622px;height: 303.141px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="622" height="303.141"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Is it safe to invest in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/invest/"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a>? The daily chart shows that the BCH price has been in a tight range in the past few weeks. It is consolidating at the 25-day and 50-day moving averages. The Awesome Oscillator has moved below the neutral point while the price is below the key resistance point at $153. Volume remains low.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the next price action of Bitcoin Cash will depend on the performance of regional bank stocks and the outcome of the Fed decision. The next key support and resistance levels to watch will be at $110 and $125.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin Cash</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM4MzUz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BCH with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTM4MzUz&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy BCH with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-remains-calm-ahead-of-the-fed-decision/">Bitcoin Cash price remains calm ahead of the Fed decision</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-remains-calm-ahead-of-the-fed-decision/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin still trading like a risk asset, despite claims of decoupling amid banking crisis</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways First Republic has become the latest bank to collapse in the US Bitcoin has bounced this week, as it did in March when SVB fell and the banking crisis was triggered Our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore, contends that Bitcoin remains a risk asset, despite claims from enthusiasts that a decoupling is occuring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/">Bitcoin still trading like a risk asset, despite claims of decoupling amid banking crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">First Republic has become the latest bank to collapse in the US</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin has bounced this week, as it did in March when SVB fell and the banking crisis was triggered</li>
<li dir="ltr">Our Head of Research, Dan Ashmore, contends that Bitcoin remains a risk asset, despite claims from enthusiasts that a decoupling is occuring</li>
<li dir="ltr">Correlation with stock market is still high, he writes, pointing to altered expectations around interest rate policy as the reason Bitcoin has moved upward</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">There has been chatter amid the market recently (again) that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> is decoupling from stocks. Something about Bitcoin offering an alternate store of value outside the realm of the fiat world, a proposition that has suddenly become a lot more valuable as the banking turmoil striking the US rages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Let me start by saying that I don&rsquo;t think my opinion is very valid here. I can&rsquo;t predict the future. But I want to look at the numbers because I believe they prove that this theory, that Bitcoin has decoupled, is objectively false.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I wrote a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-bitcoin-is-still-as-correlated-as-ever-with-the-stock-market-a-deep-dive/"><u>deep dive</u></a> on Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with stocks in March, when this theory originally surfaced as Silicon Valley Bank collapsed, while Bitcoin raced upwards. The same logic applies now, so let me try summarise it by refreshing the same numbers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">And a quick note &ndash; this article is nothing about my beliefs around Bitcoin&rsquo;s trajectory in the long-term. Whether Bitcoin decouples in future and establishes itself as a store of value akin to gold, uncorrelated to other risk assets, is a debate for another time and not one I will delve into here. I&rsquo;m purely looking at the price action <em>today&nbsp;</em>and saying that, as of May 2023, Bitcoin is trading like an extreme-risk asset, completely removed from this uncorrelated vision.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with the Nasdaq</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The natural place to look is tech stocks, being one of the riskier subsectors of the equity universe. The Nasdaq, being a tech-heavy index, is often seen as the benchmark for this sector. So let us chart Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with the Nasdaq over the past couple of years.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13627095">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Using a 60-Day Pearson measure, the chart shows that the correlation has bounced around a lot over the past couple of years. For the most part, however, it has shown a relatively strong relationship, frequently residing above 0.5.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There were a couple of dips. The first is clearly May/June 2021, when Bitcoin cratered from $63,000 to $31,000 for no apparent reason, before climbing back up into the high sixties later that year.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The second large dip in correlation is in November 2022. This was none other than the FTX collapse, the staggering implosion sending shockwaves through the crypto industry. At the same time, stocks actually advanced significantly as softer inflation data cropped up and optimism increased around the future path of interest rates. Cue the big dip in correlation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there have been two periods of notable, and very large, decorrelations. Both of these occurred as crypto melted down, independently of the stock market. If you look closely over the last year &ndash; I have shown the correlation over the last year below &ndash; you will see another big deviation in the summer of 2022 when crypto &ldquo;bank&rdquo; Celsius shut withdrawals.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13627258">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">And most importantly, the correlation has come back up swiftly every time. Including in March, when Bitcoin outperformed in the aftermath of the banking crisis.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But, did it really outperform in March? The correlation above remained relatively high, certainly nowhere near previous episodes of decorrelation &ndash; and a lot more brief. Sure, Bitcoin raced upward further than the Nasdaq post-SVB, but it also fell further prior to the guarantee that deposits backing the second largest stablecoin, USD Coin, were safe. In reality, Bitcoin did what it has been doing &ndash; sold off more aggressively and then bounced back stronger. Because, well, it is riskier. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Besides, the elephant in the room is the Federal Reserve. Markets have been moving off expectations of Fed policy all year long, and this was the true cause of the movement in March, as well as this week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With SVB&rsquo;s collapse, the market reacted to the announcement of a large liquidity injection by the Fed, as well as the expectation that rates could not be hiked as much in future as a result of the creaking banking system. These are both good things for risk assets and so Bitcoin rose. Again, not because of any potential downfall of the fiat system.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Not to mention, these banking problems were borne out of duration risk management, completely distinct to the banking issues of the GFC in 2008, which were a full-blown insolvency crisis built upon terrible underlying assets (subprime mortgages). Today, the banking crisis is still a crisis, but a regional one borne out of the most aggressive hiking cycle in recent memory, which has seen bank assets dropping in value and deposits pulled to take advantage of those higher rates elsewhere, leading to an unsustainable bank run as confidence evaporates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13627363">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">We have seen similar developments again this time around, as First Republic Bank fell last week after revealing it saw over $1 billion of withdrawal requests last quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Again, the market reacted to these things breaking by saying: <em>&ldquo;OK, the Fed cannot hike much more. This is good for risk assets&rdquo;.&nbsp;</em>Looking at Fed fund probabilities, there is the expectation of a 25 bps hike today (May 3rd) and then&hellip;.nothing. The market is viewing this as the final hike.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, it is important to keep track of lurking variables (interest rate policy) when assessing correlations and trying to garner why Bitcoin is moving. For the time being, the numbers are pretty clear, and the conclusion is unequivocal: Bitcoin is trading like a risk asset. Perhaps we don&rsquo;t even need to look at correlation. Take a glance at the below chart plotting Bitcoin&rsquo;s returns since the start of 2022 against the Nasdaq. Do you really want to argue that these assets are uncorrelated?</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13627437">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The numbers speak for themselves. Again, this is not speculating about what will happen in future. Tomorrow, Bitcoin could go to $1 million and the Nasdaq could go to zero for all I care. Bitcoin may one day reach that uncorrelated store of value status. But for now, the numbers are clear: it is trading like a risk asset.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/">Bitcoin still trading like a risk asset, despite claims of decoupling amid banking crisis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-still-trading-like-a-risk-asset-despite-claims-of-decoupling-amid-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
