<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why is the crypto market down today? BTC briefly slips below $27k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today-btc-briefly-slips-below-27k/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today-btc-briefly-slips-below-27k/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today-btc-briefly-slips-below-27k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways The cryptocurrency market is down by roughly 1% over the past 24 hours. Bitcoin briefly dropped to $26,990 earlier today before recovering to now trade above $27,500. The dump came due to reports that there was a transaction with the United States government&#8217;s BTC wallet. Why the crypto market is down today The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today-btc-briefly-slips-below-27k/">Why is the crypto market down today? BTC briefly slips below $27k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market is down by roughly 1% over the past 24 hours.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin briefly dropped to $26,990 earlier today before recovering to now trade above $27,500.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The dump came due to reports that there was a transaction with the United States government&rsquo;s BTC wallet.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why the crypto market is down today</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The cryptocurrency market recorded a sharp spike in movement a few hours ago. Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, was trading just above $28k earlier today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, BTC fell below the $27k level for the first time in more than a week, briefly touching the $26,990 mark before retracing its movement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to market experts, the sharp decline in Bitcoin&rsquo;s price came as a result of a transaction from the United States government&rsquo;s BTC wallet.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: US Gov BTC Wallet is moving<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> dumps hard. Lot of longs rekt. <a href="https://t.co/kyw8QIhAnR">pic.twitter.com/kyw8QIhAnR</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Woetoe (@cryptowoetoe) <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptowoetoe/status/1656348619455201283?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://blockstream.info/tx/0d3873d4a9e5b31156605143f27b84a503d69f70df46b31576bc26f7a6c947ae" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Data obtained from Blockstream</u></a> showed that 9819.01814463 bitcoins were on the move from the wallet. This large transaction was reflected in the market, with Bitcoin dropping below the $27k mark for the first time in a month.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin recovers to trade above $27,500</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The dump didn&rsquo;t last long, as Bitcoin is now trading above the $27k level once again. At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>price of Bitcoin</u></a> stands at $27,502, down by more than 2% in the last hour.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is not the only cryptocurrency that recorded losses. Ether, the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, also dropped below the $1,800 mark earlier today before retracing to now trade at $18,36 per coin.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today-btc-briefly-slips-below-27k/">Why is the crypto market down today? BTC briefly slips below $27k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today-btc-briefly-slips-below-27k/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price prediction: Bitcoin, Ethereum and KAVA after CPI data</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-bitcoin-ethereum-and-kava-after-cpi-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-bitcoin-ethereum-and-kava-after-cpi-data/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price broke to $28,200 while Ethereum hovered above $1,800 as stocks climbed on US CPI data. KAVA price also rose, jumping 11% amid the positive sentiment and increased network activity. BTC, ETH and KAVA are trading near key technical levels. The global cryptocurrency market rose 1.8% on Wednesday to $1.2 trillion as investors reacted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-bitcoin-ethereum-and-kava-after-cpi-data/">Crypto price prediction: Bitcoin, Ethereum and KAVA after CPI data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price broke to $28,200 while Ethereum hovered above $1,800 as stocks climbed on US CPI data.</li>
<li dir="ltr">KAVA price also rose, jumping 11% amid the positive sentiment and increased network activity.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC, ETH and KAVA are trading near key technical levels.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The global cryptocurrency market rose 1.8% on Wednesday to $1.2 trillion as investors reacted to the latest US inflation data. The price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> was up 3% to $28,270 while Ethereum retested levels above $1,800 following recent dumps for the top two coins by market cap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Elsewhere, US <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/stocks/">stocks</a> turned green as Consumer Price Index (CPI) data showed inflation continued to cool, with the annual rate now at its slowest pace in two years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Gains across equities and in the crypto major caps were also replicated in the medium and small cap altcoins. A notable upside was with the price of Kava (KAVA), which was up more than 11% as of 12:20 ET.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BTC, ETH, KAVA price prediction: what next after CPI bump?</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">BTC/USD</h3>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin price had fallen below $28k this week following the large transaction volumes that hit the network and saw fees skyrocket. The congestion, attributable to the rise in BTC-20 tokens, forced crypto exchange Binance to halt BTC withdrawals on two occasions. The ensuing FUD pushed Bitcoin price lower.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although prices are above $28k again, market experts and analysts suggest bulls are not in control yet. This is because the price remains below the key technical level of $30,000. Crypto analyst Rekt Capital noted via a<a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1656264559483846658">&nbsp;<u>tweet</u></a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BTC?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BTC</a> relief rally into $28,200 followed by a strong rejection from there would likely precede bearish continuation for price<a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Rekt Capital (@rektcapital) <a href="https://twitter.com/rektcapital/status/1656264559483846658?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">ETH/USD</h3>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> is hovering above a key support level after this week&rsquo;s weakness. The ETH/USD pair fell to lows of $1,800 on Monday and saw four consecutive red candles on the daily timeframe before today&rsquo;s uptick.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The RSI and MACD suggest bears are still strong and bulls are likely to struggle for support at current prices. This means the $2,000 remains a key technical level and moving further off it could spell more bloodbath for ETH price. Here&rsquo;s an analyst&rsquo;s Ethereum price prediction?</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Ethereum</a> breached a key demand wall at $1,850-$1,905.</p>
<p>Failure to regain this critical support zone may trigger a correction, potentially leading <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> to the next significant demand area at $1,570-$1,630. <a href="https://t.co/7s7q1LlF06">pic.twitter.com/7s7q1LlF06</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1655900952644272129?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">KAVA/USD</h3>
<p dir="ltr">KAVA is the native token of layer-1 blockchain Kava, which ranks as the 98th&nbsp;largest cryptocurrency by market. The price of KAVA hit the all-time high of $9.12 in August 2021. At current prices, its value is more than 90% down.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, increased ecosystem activity around DeFi on the Kava blockchain has aided the double digit gains seen in the past 24 hours. It&rsquo;s what pushed KAVA/USD towards the psychological $1.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The main barrier for KAVA remains the $1.12 zone, while bears could enjoy some bloodbath to $0.52.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 700px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/10/1683739070003-c4401ade-5953-4bb7-8639-5c0d42007f08.png" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="270"><span class="fr-inner">Kava price daily chart outlook. Source:<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/Jg2v27FK/">&nbsp;<u>TradingView</u></a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-prediction-bitcoin-ethereum-and-kava-after-cpi-data/">Crypto price prediction: Bitcoin, Ethereum and KAVA after CPI data</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HCW analyst raises price target on Coinbase stock after its strong Q1 report</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-coinbase-stock-on-q1-earnings-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=139135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase reported strong results for its first financial quarter last week. HCW analyst Mike Colonnese now sees upside in &#8220;COIN&#8221; to $77. Coinbase stock is already up about 85% versus the start of the year. Coinbase Global Inc is trading up this morning after an H.C. Wainwright analyst raised his price objective on the largest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-coinbase-stock-on-q1-earnings-report/">HCW analyst raises price target on Coinbase stock after its strong Q1 report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Coinbase reported strong results for its first financial quarter last week.</li>
<li>HCW analyst Mike Colonnese now sees upside in &ldquo;COIN&rdquo; to $77.</li>
<li>Coinbase stock is already up about 85% versus the start of the year.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> is trading up this morning after an H.C. Wainwright analyst raised his price objective on the largest U.S. based crypto exchange.</p>
<h2>Coinbase stock has upside to $77</h2>
<p>Mike Colonnese now sees upside in the Coinbase stock to $77 that suggests it could climb another 25% from here.</p>
<p>The bullish call arrives only days after the crypto company reported solid results for its <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coinbase-global-inc-coin-q1-231511193.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first financial quarter</a>. What thrilled this analyst in particular was improvement in terms of the retail take rate.</p>
<blockquote><p>Coinbase increased spreads to drive over a 13-bps sequential increase in blended average retail take rate to 1.68%. So, we view its pricing power as very encouraging.</p></blockquote>
<p>Colonnese is bullish on <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/prime" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Prime</a> as well that saw record volumes in the first quarter. Shares of Coinbase Global Inc are already up 85% for the year at writing.</p>
<h2>Coinbase shares have positive risk-reward</h2>
<p>The H.C. Wainwright analyst now expects the Nasdaq-listed firm to generate $3.04 billion in revenue this year.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Coinbase received a &ldquo;<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-03-22/coinbase-coin-gets-sec-wells-notice-over-crypto-offerings" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wells Notice</a>&rdquo; from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. But Colonnese remains constructive based on what executives said on the earnings call.</p>
<blockquote><p>Management said the company is 100% committed to U.S. and is optimistic on U.S. getting crypto regulation right, citing strong bipartisan support to introduce new legislation.</p></blockquote>
<p>All in all, he sees positive risk-reward in the Coinbase stock especially considering the ongoing recovery in crypto prices at large and the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/02/coinbase-sets-up-shop-in-bermuda-as-it-battles-sec-at-home/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">international exchange</a> this company launched earlier this month in Bermuda.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/buy-coinbase-stock-on-q1-earnings-report/">HCW analyst raises price target on Coinbase stock after its strong Q1 report</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AltSignals (ASI) price prediction as token sale hits $723k</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-prediction-as-token-sale-hits-723k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-prediction-as-token-sale-hits-723k/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals&#8217; token sale has already raised $723k or 67% of the initial target. The success is mostly because of the artificial intelligence hype in the industry. The artificial intelligence (AI) hype continued this week as more companies announced their plans about the industry. For example, Palantir stock price surged after the company announced strong earnings [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-prediction-as-token-sale-hits-723k/">AltSignals (ASI) price prediction as token sale hits $723k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals&rsquo; token sale has already raised $723k or 67% of the initial target.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The success is mostly because of the artificial intelligence hype in the industry.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The artificial intelligence (AI) hype continued this week as more companies announced their plans about the industry. For example, Palantir stock price surged after the company announced strong earnings and demand for its AI products.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, IBM decided to relaunch Watson as an AI development studio. WatsonX will be a platform that will help companies launch their AI projects. IBM will offer the service as well as consultations on the same.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals token sale continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Analysts believe that artificial intelligence is the most disruptive technology in modern era. Some analysts see it as the iPhone moment that disrupted the mobility industry forever. That&rsquo;s because AI will disrupt specific industries like health, education, and even journalism. For example, doctors are now using AI models to diagnose diseases while journalists are using AI to write content. </p>
<p dir="ltr">The ongoing AI hype explains why the&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=investment_opportunity"><u>AltSignals</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>token sale is going on so well. The developers have already raised $723k from investors from around the world. This means that the developers are approaching the 70% mark since the first phase seeks to raise $1 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">An ASI token is going for just $0.015, making it highly affordable to most people. Like in other token sales, the developers are expected to hike the price in the next stage of the sale.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is AltSignals?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, AltSignals is a company that has been in existence for a while. It is a profitable company that provides trading signals for traders in the forex and cryptocurrency industry. These signals, which are highly accurate, are sent to thousands of traders every day. They are developed using technical indicators like moving averages and the Relative Strength Index.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of its growth, the developers have announced plans to leverage artificial intelligence in its process. This AI will leverage other technologies like natural language processing, machine learning, regression, and predictive modeling among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to trading signals, the AI layer of the network will have more features including an AI members club, trading tournaments, and community governance among others.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to its&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the second quarter will have several events in the ecosystem. The most important one will be the token launch and listing it on Uniswap and other exchanges. The developers will also expand the team, secure OTC partnerships, and introduce the sentiment analysis engine.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals (ASI) price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It is hard to make a precise ASI price prediction since the token is yet to be launched in exchanges. However, judging by history, there are several reasons why the AltSignals price will rise after being listed. First, in most periods, tokens tend to rally after being listed in exchanges. This happens mostly because of the overall hype.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, AltSignals is in industry that is expected to grow rapidly in the coming years. We have seen this with the success of other AI tokens and companies that are betting on the industry. Further, AltSignal will likely rise ahead of the AI layer launch.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, like other cryptocurrencies, ASI will always have its ups and downs. As such, it makes sense to only allocate funds you can easily afford to lose. You can buy the AltSignals ASI token&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/altsignals-asi-price-prediction-as-token-sale-hits-723k/">AltSignals (ASI) price prediction as token sale hits $723k</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDC market cap below $30 billion, struggles signify crypto turmoil</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-market-cap-below-30-billion-struggles-signify-crypto-turmoil/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-market-cap-below-30-billion-struggles-signify-crypto-turmoil/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-market-cap-below-30-billion-struggles-signify-crypto-turmoil/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways USDC&#8217;s market cap has dipped from $54 billion to $30 billion in the last eight months The stablecoin has lost market share since March, falling from 32% to 23% Regulatory concerns and the fallout from the SVB collapse have plagued the stablecoin, whose struggles signify the capital flight out of the crypto industry [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-market-cap-below-30-billion-struggles-signify-crypto-turmoil/">USDC market cap below $30 billion, struggles signify crypto turmoil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">USDC&rsquo;s market cap has dipped from $54 billion to $30 billion in the last eight months</li>
<li dir="ltr">The stablecoin has lost market share since March, falling from 32% to 23%</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory concerns and the fallout from the SVB collapse have plagued the stablecoin, whose struggles signify the capital flight out of the crypto industry as a whole</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto prices have been on the rise over the past couple of months, but that is not to say that all is well in the sector. As I have analysed before, capital has flooded out of the space at a scarcely believable pace, with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/22-billion-of-stablecoins-has-fled-exchanges-in-5-months-a-report-into-cryptos-capital-flight/"><u>$22 billion</u></a> in stablecoins alone leaving exchanges in the last five months.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">USD Coin, the world&rsquo;s second largest stablecoin, illustrates the struggle well. The Coinbase-backed cryptocurrency held a market cap of $54 billion last August. Today, it is below $30 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13705670">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The coin has had its fair share of battles. The first is, well, it is a cryptocurency, and that means it operates in an industry that has been ravaged. Last year&rsquo;s scandals hurt the space deeply, none more so than FTX&rsquo;s startling collapse in November. Since the exchange went under, liquidity has poured out of the industry. Plotting USDC&rsquo;s fall against the total market cap of all stablecoins shows that, while USDC has been worse, the entire sector has been hit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13705767">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">However, USDC has faced other battles, too. In March, Silicon Valley Bank failed in the US, guilty of mismanaging its risk in the face of rising interest rates, ultimately succumbing to mismatched duration as its bonds sold off fiercely amid the swiftest interest rate hiking cycle in modern times.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The problem for USDC was that part of its reserves were held in this bank, throwing panic into the market. Later revealed as only 8.25% in SVB, the market went into a flurry, selling off the stablecoin in masse. The peg dipped down to 88 cents.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the US administration stepped into guarantee all deposits at SVB a few days later, and the peg hence restored shortly thereafter, the dip in market cap didn&rsquo;t fully recover. Prior to the SVB collapse, its market share among stablecoins was 32%. Two weeks later, it was 25%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/13705882">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    &nbsp;
<p dir="ltr">Today, the market share sits at 23%, and it continues to fall.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Regulation tightens on crypto</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The other big factor in this is regulation. In February, the SEC announced it was <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-busd-shutting-down-mean-for-the-crypto-industry-a-deep-dive/"><u>suing Paxos</u></a>, the issuer of the Binance-branded stablecoin, BUSD, for violating securities laws. The result was no more BUSD, minting of the stablecoin halted and the circulating supply slated to gradually dwindle towards zero.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the surface of things, this sounds promising for USDC. The fall of a competitor and more room to suck up extra supply. However, the problem is that USDC&rsquo;s parent company is Circle, which like Paxos, is also US-domiciled.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That means a fear that USDC could be next in line to get a knock on the door from SEC. The market has hence looked elsewhere, most notably Tether, which <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tethers-market-share-grows-to-61-a-two-year-high-as-crypto-centralisation-grows-a-report/"><u>seized extra market share</u></a> with aplomb, grinning smugly in the cosy confines of Europe, far away from the SEC. The world&rsquo;s largest stablecoin has advanced to a 61% market share, its highest mark in two years.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory fears were exacerbated by parent company Coinbase being issued with a Wells notice, which typically precedes legal action. A Wells notice is a formal warning from the SEC that evidence of proof of lawbreaking has been found. Typically, legal action will follow. The claims surround (you guessed it) a violation of securities laws, and while it is not directly to do with USDC, it has not exactly helped its image in the market, as the market cap continues to head south.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Whether USDC can wrestle back market share in future remains to be seen. But its plight, and the overall state of stablecoins in crypto, highlight that while prices have recently been on the up, the state of industry is still very much a concern.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-market-cap-below-30-billion-struggles-signify-crypto-turmoil/">USDC market cap below $30 billion, struggles signify crypto turmoil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/usdc-market-cap-below-30-billion-struggles-signify-crypto-turmoil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the year of the meme coins will DOGEs growth be eclipsed by TOADS?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DigiToads (TOADS) is a play to earn full utility meme coin. DigiToads (TOADS) is currently ongoing. 2023 has seen new meme coins like PEPE overtake former meme coin stars like DOGE. Dogecoin (DOGE) became arguably the most famous meme coin buoyed by social media hype over the past few years. Millionaires were created out of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/">In the year of the meme coins will DOGEs growth be eclipsed by TOADS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>DigiToads (TOADS) is a play to earn full utility meme coin.</li>
<li>DigiToads (TOADS) is currently ongoing.</li>
<li>2023 has seen new meme coins like PEPE overtake former meme coin stars like DOGE.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/dogecoin/what-is-dogecoin/">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> became arguably the most famous meme coin buoyed by social media hype over the past few years. Millionaires were created out of nowhere, and thousands of other meme coins sprung up to try and capitalize on increased demand for the &ldquo;next big thing&rdquo; in the crypto world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, only some of these meme coins have succeeded. This, combined with wider economic pressures and a general slowdown in the entire crypto market, has led some investors to look elsewhere.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But the meme coin boom isn&rsquo;t over. It&rsquo;s just getting started following the launch of new trending meme crypto projects like&nbsp;<a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DigiToads (TOADS)</a>.</p>
<h2>What is DigiToads (TOADS)?</h2>
<p>Savvy investors think that DigiToads (TOADS) is a win-win proposition. Unlike many other meme coin success stories, it&rsquo;s actually got a ton of solid fundamentals built-in to an incredibly innovative ecosystem that&rsquo;s rewarding, fun, and primed for growth. Memecoin hype can only get you so far, but TOADs has both the fun marketing appeal and the long-term profit potential investors have been crying out for.</p>
<p>DigiToads leads the charge as one of the hottest P2E cryptos in the crypto space, thanks to its extremely enjoyable swamp battle arena that lets users train and battle with a range of TOAD companions. The best-placed competitors will receive regular rewards in the form of TOADS tokens, which can then be used to buy food, train, and customize your companions to take them to the next level.</p>
<p>The TOADS ecosystem has been built from the ground up with a community-focused ethos at the core of everything it does. &nbsp;It is currently conducting its presale which provides early investors with long-term gains thanks to heavily discounted prices and sustainable passive income potential thanks to top NFT staking capabilities. You can participate in the <a href="https://digitoads.me/cjl" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DigiToads presale here</a>.</p>
<p>With prices already soaring during TOADS&rsquo; presale phase, the token price is locked in to go even higher before its official launch thanks to staggered increases. With the increased popularity and number of investors flocking to purchase the new TOADS token, DigiToads could surpass well-known meme coins like Dogecoin (DOGE) and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a>.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin (DOGE) market performance</h2>
<p>Dogecoin hype and price performance over the years have certainly shown what sort of gains are possible in the meme coin world. It also showed other crypto projects how much marketing power a few tweets from famous followers can get you.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However,&nbsp;<u><a href="https://dogecoin.com/">DOGE</a></u> could not solidify those huge gains, and its long-term journey has been slightly less appealing to investors. Analysts have suggested that this comes down to fundamentals: social media hype can only get you so far, and credible investors need credible crypto options.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>While DOGE remains a viable option for your crypto portfolio since it could still surge back to its former highs, experts think that TOADS also has everything needed to become the next meme coin.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/in-the-year-of-the-meme-coins-will-doges-growth-be-eclipsed-by-toads/">In the year of the meme coins will DOGEs growth be eclipsed by TOADS?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venom Foundation announces strategic partnership with the Government of Kenya</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-strategic-partnership-with-the-government-of-kenya/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-strategic-partnership-with-the-government-of-kenya/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The partnership is through Venom Africa. Venom seeks to establish a &#8220;blockchain hub&#8221; in Africa. The hub will focus on the development of Web3 and blockchain technology applications. Just over fifteen days after launching the public testnet of its L1 blockchain, Venom Foundation has announced a strategic partnership with the Government of Kenya through Venom [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-strategic-partnership-with-the-government-of-kenya/">Venom Foundation announces strategic partnership with the Government of Kenya</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The partnership is through Venom Africa.</li>
<li>Venom seeks to establish a &ldquo;blockchain hub&rdquo; in Africa.</li>
<li>The hub will focus on the development of Web3 and blockchain technology applications.</li>
</ul>
<p>Just over fifteen days after launching the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-public-testnet-of-its-l1-blockchain/">public testnet of its L1 blockchain</a>, Venom Foundation has announced a strategic partnership with the Government of Kenya through Venom Africa. The partnership is a great step towards establishing a &ldquo;blockchain hub&rdquo; in Africa focusing on the development of Web3 and blockchain technology applications.</p>
<p>Expressing enthusiasm for the partnership, the Cabinet Secretary for Investments, Trade and Industry, in Kenya, Moses Kuria said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We are excited to work together with the Venom Foundation. This collaboration signifies the stance that we are taking towards next-generation technology and financial and technological developments in the world. We believe that the establishment of this blockchain hub will catalyze further innovations in various industries, benefitting our people both nationally and globally.&rdquo;</em></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This partnership with <a href="https://twitter.com/VenomFoundation?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@VenomFoundation</a> through <a href="https://twitter.com/VenomAfrica?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@venomafrica</a> signifies Kenya's stance towards next-gen technology, financial and technological developments, and will catalyze further innovations in various industries, benefitting people both nationally and globally.</p>
<p>&mdash; CS Moses Kuria (@HonMoses_Kuria) <a href="https://twitter.com/HonMoses_Kuria/status/1656085322269356033?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>This partnership is aimed at driving innovation in key sectors like financial infrastructure, supply chain, agriculture, SMEs, and cross-border trade, in Kenya and the entire African continent.</p>
<h2>Impact on financial services</h2>
<p>Currently, more than 84% of the Kenyan population has access to financial services through banks and fintech.</p>
<p>The implementation of blockchain infrastructure will increase value for the population, create more opportunities for the Kenyan domestic economy, create new international trade routes and add efficiency to intra-African trade lines.</p>
<p>By advocating for the adoption of blockchain technology, Venom Foundation is seeking to endow African communities and create a bridge between traditional finance and trade with the web3 world. It also wants to stimulate regional economic growth by enabling seamless cross-border trade and transactions.</p>
<p>The population will benefit from:</p>
<ul>
<li>Minimized transaction costs</li>
<li>Enhanced security and transparency</li>
<li>Increased access to financial services</li>
<li>Expedited settlement times for cross-border transactions</li>
<li>Creation of new investment opportunities through asset tokenization.</li>
<li>Economic development and financial inclusion across the continent.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Venom&rsquo;s blockchain hub in Africa</h2>
<p>The blockchain hub will be a central platform for building partnerships with innovative companies in Africa.</p>
<p>Venom will also supply crucial resources and tools to support African countries in developing a solid foundation for digital transformation including blockchain-based solutions for land registry, voting systems, and supply chain management among other areas. Venom will primarily be seeking to promote efficiency, transparency and trust across various sectors in Africa.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/venom-foundation-announces-strategic-partnership-with-the-government-of-kenya/">Venom Foundation announces strategic partnership with the Government of Kenya</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu price lags as Pepe, Keke, Ben volume and traction jumps</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-lags-as-pepe-keke-ben-volume-and-traction-jumps/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-lags-as-pepe-keke-ben-volume-and-traction-jumps/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-lags-as-pepe-keke-ben-volume-and-traction-jumps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu price performance has lagged that of new meme tokens like Keke, Ben, and Pepe.&#160; The volume of Shiba Inu in the past 24 hours stands at $120M compared to Pepe&#8217;s $500M. Many novice crypto traders are buying meme tokens that are clearly scams.&#160; Shiba inu price has recoiled recently as focus remains on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-lags-as-pepe-keke-ben-volume-and-traction-jumps/">Shiba Inu price lags as Pepe, Keke, Ben volume and traction jumps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu price performance has lagged that of new meme tokens like Keke, Ben, and Pepe.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The volume of Shiba Inu in the past 24 hours stands at $120M compared to Pepe&rsquo;s $500M.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Many novice crypto traders are buying meme tokens that are clearly scams.&nbsp;</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu"><u>Shiba inu</u></a> price has recoiled recently as focus remains on the upcoming alternatives like Keke, Ben, Pepe, and Bambi. SHIB was trading at $0.0000090, which was the lowest level since January 13. It has dropped by more than 42% from the highest point in March.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Meme coin season continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A major&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>news theme in the cryptocurrency</u></a> industry is the meme coin season. In the past few days, we have seen many new meme coins move from obscurity to become some of the biggest coins in the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu, the second-biggest meme coin in the world after Dogecoin, has been abandoned as investors focus on these new tokens. For example, data by CoinMarketCap shows that the volume of Shiba Inu traded in the past 24 hours stands at just $120 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the other hand, the volume of Pepe traded in the same period stands at about $508 million. This makes it the fourth coin after Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Sui. BEN, another meme coin, has seen the volume jump to $79 million, which is a substantial figure considering that it is a relatively new token.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other smaller meme coins like Keke, FourCoin, and Bambi have seen their volumes jump.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the risk is that many crypto traders are buying tokens that are being pumped and dumped. As we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pepe-price-dives-after-whale-transfers-trillions-of-tokens-to-binance/"><u>here</u></a>, some whales have started to move their Pepe tokens. Indeed, the prices of most of these new meme coins have dropped sharply from their all-time high. Since they lack a clear utility, I suspect that most of these tokens will drop sharply in the near term.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Inu price prediction&nbsp;</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/10/1683727736243-cb6cfc87-9ece-4cba-81ff-73f0e015e785.png" style="width: 692px;height: 336.773px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="692" height="336.773"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Turning to the daily chart, we see that the SHIB price has been in a strong bearish trend in the past few weeks as attention shifts to the new meme coins. The token managed to move below the key support level at $0.0000096, the lowest level on March 10.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Inu remains below the 25-day and 50-day moving averages while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved to the oversold level. Therefore, the outlook of the token is still bearish, with the next level to watch being at $0.0000080. A move above the resistance level at $0.000010 will invalidate the bearish view.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Shiba Inu</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTM5MTAy&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SHIB with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTM5MTAy&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy SHIB with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-lags-as-pepe-keke-ben-volume-and-traction-jumps/">Shiba Inu price lags as Pepe, Keke, Ben volume and traction jumps</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-inu-price-lags-as-pepe-keke-ben-volume-and-traction-jumps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Stacks (STX) going down: Can it stay above $0.6?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-stacks-stx-going-down-can-it-stay-above-0-6/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-stacks-stx-going-down-can-it-stay-above-0-6/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Maishera]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 12:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-stacks-stx-going-down-can-it-stay-above-0-6/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key takeaways STX is the worst performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap so far today. Stacks has lost more than 9% of its value today and could record further losses in the near term. The broader market is stagnant ahead of today&#8217;s CPI readings. STX dips by more than 9% today STX, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-stacks-stx-going-down-can-it-stay-above-0-6/">Why is Stacks (STX) going down: Can it stay above $0.6?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Key takeaways</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">STX is the worst performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap so far today.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Stacks has lost more than 9% of its value today and could record further losses in the near term.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The broader market is stagnant ahead of today&rsquo;s CPI readings.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 dir="ltr">STX dips by more than 9% today</h2>
<p dir="ltr">STX, the native token of the Stacks ecosystem, is the worst performer amongst the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap so far today. The coin has lost more than 9% of its value over the last 24 hours and could experience further bearish trend continues.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There is no catalyst behind STX&rsquo;s ongoing poor performance. The cryptocurrency is correcting after rallying to its weekly high of $0.81. Over the past month, STX has lost more than 20% of its value after reaching a high of $0.9819.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At press time, the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/stacks/"><u>price of Stacks</u></a> stands at $0.6442. If the bearish trend continues, STX could drop below the $0.6 psychological level in the near term.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto investors await the CPI readings</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Consumer Price Index (CPI) readings in the United States will be revealed later today. Cryptocurrency investors are awaiting the figures before making their moves, with volatility in the market currently low.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The CPI will give investors insight into the current inflation situation in the United States. If the inflation figures increase, the Federal Reserve could continue its interest rate hike.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this month, the Fed increased interest rates by 25 basis points, taking interest rates in the US to a 16-year high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, a lower inflation figure could see the Federal Reserve cool down its rate hike.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s leading cryptocurrency by market cap, continues to trade just below the $28k level. The total cryptocurrency market cap stands at $1.14 trillion, down by less than 1% today.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-stacks-stx-going-down-can-it-stay-above-0-6/">Why is Stacks (STX) going down: Can it stay above $0.6?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-stacks-stx-going-down-can-it-stay-above-0-6/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
