<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:25:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Former PBoC Official Slams e-CNY as Being Underutilized</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[e-cny]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pboc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/">Former PBoC Official Slams e-CNY as Being Underutilized</a></p>
<p>The Chinese government designed the e-CNY as a digital payment instrument that can serve as a substitute for the fiat yuan in regular day-to-day activities.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/">Former PBoC Official Slams e-CNY as Being Underutilized</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/">Former PBoC Official Slams e-CNY as Being Underutilized</a></p>
<p>Xie Ping, the former Director General of Research at the People’s Bank of China (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/peoples-bank-of-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PBoC</a>) has expressed dissatisfaction about the progress made thus far by the country’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Central Bank Digital Currency</a> (CBDC) dubbed e-CNY or Digital Renminbi. According to a <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/former-pboc-official-says-chinas-digital-yuan-is-little-used-caixin-2022-12-29/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by a local news channel, Caixin, Ping faults the distribution of the e-CNY which he said is limited to just a few billion dollars.</p>
<p>&#8220;The cumulative circulation of the digital yuan in the two years of the trial has been only 100 billion yuan ($14 billion),&#8221; he said while speaking at a conference organized by Tsinghua University. He added that the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/e-cny-13-68b-transactions-261m-users/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported figure</a> showed that the Digital Renminbi’s &#8220;usage has been low, highly inactive.&#8221;</p>
<p>China remained at the forefront of the Central Bank Digital Currency race and was the first major advanced economy to launch retail trials involving the new form of money. Over the past 2 years, pilot tests have been conducted in its main cities including Beijing, Shanghai, Shenzhen, and Suzhou and this has featured both state-owned banks as well as private companies in the country.</p>
<p>To the world, the embrace of the e-CNY was impressive and the PBoC even <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-plans-digital-yuan-olympics-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">extended the pilot test to the 2022 Winter Olympics</a> hosted in Beijing earlier in the year. Beyond the media frenzy, Xie Ping believes the new form of money is not meeting the goals for which it was created and that the results from the pilot tests are not ideal.</p>
<p>The Chinese government designed the e-CNY as a digital payment instrument that can serve as a substitute for the fiat Yuan in regular day-to-day activities. To Ping, the limited functions of the e-CNY are exactly the reasons why its adoption will be limited if not urgently addressed.</p>
<h2>PBoC Advised Expanding the Utility of the e-CNY</h2>
<p>Ping highlighted that the dominance of existing fintech firms such as Alibaba-backed Alipay and Tencent-backed WeChat Pay will make it difficult for the Chinese masses to adjust to the e-CNY. He said the existing payment models currently satisfy the daily need of the citizens and as such, finds no new challenges that the CBDC was introduced to solve.</p>
<p>&#8220;Cash, bank cards, and China&#8217;s third-party payment mechanisms have formed a payment market structure that has met needs for daily consumption,&#8221; he said. &#8220;The common people are used to it, and changing it is difficult.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;What needs to change is the digital yuan acting only as a substitute for cash and only for consumption,&#8221; Ping added.</p>
<p>He advised the PBoC to expand the utility of the e-CNY such that it can be used to purchase other financial instruments, and deployed in investments as much as Alipay and other independent players.</p>
<p>While it is unlikely that the PBoC heed the advice from Ping with respect to the e-CNY, the apex bank is optimistic that the narrative will change when the CBDC is finally launched for the public to use.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/">Former PBoC Official Slams e-CNY as Being Underutilized</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/pboc-official-e-cny-underutilized/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Market Slip Reflects Investor Caution Heading into 2023</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf global]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stoxx 600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/">European Market Slip Reflects Investor Caution Heading into 2023</a></p>
<p>The recent European market slip indicates that investors remain cautious about the potential macroeconomic headwinds next year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/">European Market Slip Reflects Investor Caution Heading into 2023</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/">European Market Slip Reflects Investor Caution Heading into 2023</a></p>
<p>The pan-European Stoxx 600 index closed marginally lower than the flatline on Wednesday amid a broader market slip. As 2022 winds to a close, the Stoxx 600 is trading down more than 12% year-to-date (YTD). Furthermore, caution abounds throughout the European capital markets, with investors remaining wary of incessantly high inflation and central banks&#8217; fiscal policy tightening. Lastly, investors also assess the impact of a global recession on likely headwinds in 2023.</p>
<p>The European Stoxx 600 began Thursday&#8217;s session down 0.5% in early trade. In addition, food and beverage stocks dipped 1% to lead losses as virtually all sectors were trading in the red.</p>
<h2>European Market Slip Follows Asia-Pacific Decline</h2>
<p>The European market slip appears set to extend the weak sentiment from the Asia-Pacific markets. Conversely, there was a slight gain among US stock futures to begin Thursday&#8217;s gain. Overall, global markets are hours away from rounding out a turbulent year characterized by disparate macroeconomic factors. These include the selloff of tech shares, soaring inflation from the fallout of Russia&#8217;s war in Ukraine, and persistent Chinese Covid restrictions. The fact that China recently relaxed its remaining zero-Covid measures did little to improve investor confidence. According to a recent assertion by an economist, the global economy heads into a decade of low growth. However, Tressis Gestion author and chief economist Daniel Lacalle, also stated that the full reopening of the Chinese economy remained the silver lining. In a media session, Lacalle <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/28/global-economy-is-heading-into-a-decade-of-low-growth-economist-says.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The reopening of the Chinese economy is certainly going to give a significant boost to growth all over the world, but also &#8211; and I think it is a very important factor &#8211; German exporters, French exporters have felt the pinch of the lockdown and the weakening of the profit environment in China, and this is certainly going to help a lot.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Lacalle further noted that the projected Chinese boost would be different from the pre-pandemic growth levels for a while. As he put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I think that we are probably going to move into a decade of very, very poor growth in which developed economies are going to find themselves lucky with 1% growth per annum, if they are able to achieve it…&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>IMF Global GDP &amp; Inflation Projections</h2>
<p>According to International Monetary Fund <a href="https://www.imf.org/en/Publications/WEO/Issues/2022/10/11/world-economic-outlook-october-2022#:~:text=Press%20Briefing%3A%20World%20Economic%20Outlook%2C%20October%202022,-October%2011%2C%202022&amp;amp;text=The%20IMF%20forecasts%20global%20growth,acute%20phase%20of%20the%20pandemic." target="_blank" rel="noopener">projections</a>, there will be a progressive slowdown in global GDP growth between 2021 and 2023. The IMF puts these figures at 6% in 2021, 3.2% in the current year, and a lower 2.7% in 2023. The Fund also described this growth trajectory as the weakest since 2001, barring the financial meltdown and early Covid phase.</p>
<p>Projections also state that global inflation could rise from 4.7% last year to 8.8% in 2022 before tapering off to 6.5% in 2023. Furthermore, global inflation is projected to drop even further to 4.1% in 2024. These figures remain above the target levels for several major central banks.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/">European Market Slip Reflects Investor Caution Heading into 2023</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-market-slip-caution-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3Commas Finally Admits Latest API Keys Leak Was Its Fault</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3commas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[API Keys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kucoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230859</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/">3Commas Finally Admits Latest API Keys Leak Was Its Fault</a></p>
<p>The company's CEO has not confirmed whether or not he will be making a refund to the affected victims but said as an immediate course of action, the platform has requested all partner exchanges to disable their API keys linking to its systems.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/">3Commas Finally Admits Latest API Keys Leak Was Its Fault</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/">3Commas Finally Admits Latest API Keys Leak Was Its Fault</a></p>
<p>For the past few weeks, crypto Twitter has been calling out 3Commas, an automated trading platform with respect to the leak of its Application Programming Interface (API) that has caused the loss of funds for users. After much denials and blame shifting, the platform’s Chief Executive Officer, Yuriy Sorokin has <a href="https://twitter.com/YS_3Commas/status/1608202390121111552" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">come out to admit</a> the leak was from the platform.</p>
<p>As a protocol, 3Commas helps users to connect to third-party exchanges like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kucoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">KuCoin</a>, and the like where highly functional codes can be used to place trades in an automated manner. The connections to these centralized exchanges are through its APIs of which hundreds of users’ keys were compromised.</p>
<p>Popular on-chain Sleuth, ZachXBT said he verified as many as 44 3Commas users who lost a cumulative of $14.8 million through the API keys that were stolen from the platform. When the report first made the rounds, Sorokin argued that any form of leak meant that users themselves had given up their API keys through a targeted phishing attack.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">It&#39;s not about the terminology, it&#39;s about the roof of the problem. Which is &#8211; API keys issues by exchanges were leaked. Has nothing to do with 3Commas API, period. We are trying to help as much as we can &#8211; push people to work with the exchanges and law enforcement.</p>
<p>&mdash; Yuriy Sorokin (@YS_3Commas) <a href="https://twitter.com/YS_3Commas/status/1606206842547277824?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 23, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Considering the fact that 3Commas is used by millions of traders, he posited that a hack on its database will involve a relatively larger number of victims than are being reported on Twitter.</p>
<p>“If you are a victim &#8211; then it means that somehow your keys were leaked. Not from 3Commas, as otherwise, you would&#8217;ve seen millions of cases, not a hundred. browser extensions, stealers, and all kinds of malware are out there.”</p>
<p>In a dramatic twist of events, Sorokin finally admitted that the leak originated from its platform and that he was sorry for how things have shaped out so far.</p>
<h2>3Commas API Leak: Next Course of Action</h2>
<p>Following the admittance of its role, Sorokin and the 3Commas team have been receiving more intense backlash from the community, especially with the fact that the trading outfit is known for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-api-keys-3commas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">related exploits</a> in the past.</p>
<p>A Twitter user, CoinMamba who also doubles as a 3Commas customer demanded a refund for all affected victims.</p>
<p>“You kept lying and saying this was our fault instead of taking responsibility and preventing further exploits. Are you going to refund the users now?” he demanded.</p>
<p>Sorokin has not confirmed whether or not he will be making a refund to the affected victims but said as an immediate course of action, the platform has requested all partner exchanges to disable their API keys linking to its systems.</p>
<p>“We saw the hacker’s message and can confirm that the data in the files is true. As an immediate action, we have asked that Binance, Kucoin, and other supported exchanges revoke all the keys that were connected to 3Commas,” he tweeted.</p>
<p>He said in its investigations, evidence that the hack was an inside job was not found and that it will continue to coordinate with law enforcement agents as it launches a full investigation into the incident.</p>
<p>Unlike how he has handled the situation prior to this time, Sorokin said he will be more forthcoming in its communications moving forward.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/">3Commas Finally Admits Latest API Keys Leak Was Its Fault</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/3commas-api-keys-leak-fault/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Dollar Will Eventually Make Its Way into Market</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital doolar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital euro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital yuan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230880</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/">Digital Dollar Will Eventually Make Its Way into Market</a></p>
<p>The policy research director at the Digital Dollar Project said that the Federal Reserve is waiting for Congress to initiate legislation on CBDC, for them to proceed further. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/">Digital Dollar Will Eventually Make Its Way into Market</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/">Digital Dollar Will Eventually Make Its Way into Market</a></p>
<p>A number of central banks across the world have been working on central bank digital currencies (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDCs</a>), however, the US Federal Reserve has been a bit slow in this regard. While there&#8217;s been no major news with respect to the Digital Dollar recently, things do seem to be moving ahead.</p>
<p>Michael Greco, policy research director at the Digital Dollar Project recently said that there&#8217;s not a question of &#8216;if&#8217; but &#8216;when&#8217; regarding the establishment of the Digital Dollar in the United States. Greco&#8217;s comments came during his <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/12/28/digital-dollar-will-come-eventually-lobbyist-says/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with CoinDesk TV&#8217;s &#8220;First Mover&#8221; show on Tuesday, December 27.</p>
<p>He said that the Digital Dollar might see the day of the light in the next few years without mentioning the actual timeline. But Greco said that the Federal Reserve is waiting for Congress to enact legislation before it can move ahead. Although he doesn&#8217;t expect Congress to pass such a law next year, Greco believes that the conversation to advance on Capitol Hill, especially in regard to privacy&#8221; in 2023.</p>
<p>The soaring inflation in the US has kept the Fed on the edge and busy focusing on other key macro factors. Once things look under control, probably the Fed might have a serious consideration over the Digital Dollar project.</p>
<p>Nearly 87 countries across the globe have initiated some talks or pilot projects over CBDCs. Countries like The Bahamas and Nigeria have rather made quick moves to push the use of digital money and reduce the influence of cash in their economies.</p>
<p>Not to forget, China has been the major economy that has been steadfast in the launch of its Digital Yuan. The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/peoples-bank-of-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PBoC</a> has been devising several ways to push the use of CBDCs among merchants and consumers.</p>
<h2>US vs Other Major Economies</h2>
<p>Although the United States has been a bit slow in the CBDC developments, its competing democracies are making a move. Josh Lipsky, senior director of the Atlantic Council’s GeoEconomic Center, recently said that CBDCs are making &#8220;huge leaps&#8221; in other parts of the world such as Europe and South Korea.</p>
<p>In 2023, the European Central Bank is likely to move ahead with the pilot phase of the Digital Euro from its development phase. This could be a major step given the size of the European Union. He further noted that the US authorities would wait to see how the ECB tackles privacy concerns with CBDCs and how they can interact efficiently with the existing banking systems.</p>
<p>Lipsky also sees greater potential in a wholesale CBDC suitable for transactions between banks instead of retail CBDCs.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/">Digital Dollar Will Eventually Make Its Way into Market</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/digital-dollar-make-its-way-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Faces Class-Action Lawsuit from Customers Who Claim Right Over Exchange’s Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230825</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/">FTX Faces Class-Action Lawsuit from Customers Who Claim Right Over Exchange&#8217;s Assets</a></p>
<p>The plaintiffs have argued that the customers of FTX have the first right over the exchange's frozen funds, in an attempt to get their money back. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/">FTX Faces Class-Action Lawsuit from Customers Who Claim Right Over Exchange&#8217;s Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/">FTX Faces Class-Action Lawsuit from Customers Who Claim Right Over Exchange&#8217;s Assets</a></p>
<p>The collapse of the crypto exchange FTX-led to more than a million active customers losing their digital asset holdings. These customers have now come forward filing a class-action lawsuit against the exchange in an effort to their money back first.</p>
<h2>Class-Action Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Four individuals have filed a class action lawsuit demanding priority access to the frozen funds. They are now seeking a declaration that the company&#8217;s holding of digital assets belongs to its customers. The four plaintiffs filed the lawsuit earlier this week on December 27 in the United States Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware.</p>
<p>They are representing the whole class of former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> customers, which are a total of 1 million individuals. The plaintiffs have argued that the FTX User Agreement didn&#8217;t permit the exchange to use customer funds for its own purposes. This includes either using them for operational expenses or borrowing them.</p>
<p>Also, the class action lawsuit adds that any removal of customer funds from accounts was an “impermissible co-mingling, misappropriation, misuse, or conversion of customer property&#8221;. The lawsuit thus adds that any funds frozen by FTX and traceable as customer property cannot be used for non-customer expenses. It further <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/ftx-customers-file-class-action-lay-claim-dwindling-assets-2022-12-28/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">adds</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Customer class members should not have to stand in line along with secured or general unsecured creditors in these bankruptcy proceedings just to share in the diminished estate assets of the FTX Group and Alameda.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto exchange FTX has yet to respond on this matter.</p>
<h2>FTX Reportedly Facing DoJ Investigation</h2>
<p>Last month, crypto exchange FTX faced a massive liquidity crisis amid heavy withdrawals and had to soon file for bankruptcy. However, a day after its filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy, the crypto exchange faced a massive $400 million hack.</p>
<p>As per the latest details, the US Department of Justice has launched an investigation into this matter about the whereabouts of the missing funds from FTX. Many have started raising fingers over FTX&#8217;s disgraced founder <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> considering his criminal past.</p>
<p>In another such development, another foul play has been suspected as crypto wallets linked to FTX&#8217;s sister concern and bankrupt trading firm Alameda Research, started transferring funds just days after SBF&#8217;s $250 million bailout.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/">FTX Faces Class-Action Lawsuit from Customers Who Claim Right Over Exchange&#8217;s Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-action-lawsuit-exchange-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manchester United and Tezos Foundation Accused of NFT Copyright Infringement</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chiliz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[socios]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/">Manchester United and Tezos Foundation Accused of NFT Copyright Infringement</a></p>
<p>The $3.77 billion valued football club has been expanding its revenue collection avenues since the onset of the coronavirus, which significantly slashed the company’s profits.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/">Manchester United and Tezos Foundation Accused of NFT Copyright Infringement</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/">Manchester United and Tezos Foundation Accused of NFT Copyright Infringement</a></p>
<p>After debuting its NFT collectibles earlier this month, popular football club Manchester United Ltd Cl A (NYSE: MANU)  and its official blockchain provider Tezos Foundation have been accused of copying monsters’ NFT traits belonging to Lucrece. The 7,777 digital collectibles announced by Manchester United are said to share most of their unique traits with Lucrece’s monster artwork.</p>
<p>In response to this, Lucrece announced that he is in contact with Manchester United to amicably resolve the existing issues for the betterment of the Tezos community.</p>
<p>“It’s important to note that Arthur and I both share sentiments that art and artists on Tezos are something we both want to protect. I think the resolution here should be beneficial for everyone involved,” Lucrece <a href="https://twitter.com/deslucrece/status/1608125414496690178?s=46&amp;t=F3XMSdUSVtEMFH1XgcxlRg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>.</p>
<p>The Manchester United NFT collection costs £30 including VAT and gives the holder a chance to unlock rare devils. Nonetheless, their closeness with Lucrece’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> may significantly downgrade their floor prices.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A final note&#8230;.I figured out who the artist was for the <a href="https://twitter.com/ManUtd?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ManUtd</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/TezosFoundation?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@TezosFoundation</a> rip-off of <a href="https://twitter.com/DesLucrece?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@DesLucrece</a> </p>
<p>I&#39;m not going to share their identity publicly, but check out their OpenSea favorites&#8230;.</p>
<p>case closed.</p>
<p>Looking forward to the resolution by <a href="https://twitter.com/ArthurB?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ArthurB</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/EdwardsMason?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@EdwardsMason</a>, etc. <a href="https://t.co/sC5VD3f6tW">pic.twitter.com/sC5VD3f6tW</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ClownVamp (@ClownVamp) <a href="https://twitter.com/ClownVamp/status/1608133423826092037?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 28, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Closer Look at Manchester United and NFT Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The $3.77 billion valued football club has been expanding its revenue collection avenues since the onset of the coronavirus, which significantly slashed the company’s profits. Notably, Manchester United has been looking into Web 3.0 to enhance fan engagement around the world. Moreover, blockchain technology has proved to be a unique way of fan engagement in the past two years, as evident with Socios and Chiliz (CHZ).</p>
<p>The football club is looking to venture into the metaverse industry through its official blockchain technology, Tezos. The low cost of minting and transfers on the Tezos blockchain has enabled United to reach out to global fans seamlessly.</p>
<p>Notably, the United NFTs come in three types Classic Key, Rare Key, and Ultra Rare Key. The Classic Key ensures fans have a chance to win giveaways, drops, and also secret channels on the club’s Discord community.</p>
<p>The Rare Key, on the other hand, is a step up and any fan getting one of these will get special discounts and discussions with United legends. The Ultra Rare Key NFT holders will get all the benefits of the Classic and Rare Keys but also get an invite to Old Trafford.</p>
<p>The rarity of the United NFTs has, however, been disputed following claims of copyright infringement. Nonetheless, the involved parties have announced that they are working on a solution to ensure Lucrece NFT fans are not compromised by United collectibles.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Man United NFT collectibles are not regulated by the UK financial authorities.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/">Manchester United and Tezos Foundation Accused of NFT Copyright Infringement</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/manchester-united-tezos-nft-copyright/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US-Listed Chinese Tech Companies No Longer See Hong Kong Listing as Vital Hedge Strategy Following PCAOB Development</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pcaob]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pinduoduo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/">US-Listed Chinese Tech Companies No Longer See Hong Kong Listing as Vital Hedge Strategy Following PCAOB Development</a></p>
<p>As US listing prospects improve, several US-listed Chinese tech players have halted their Hong Kong listing plans. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/">US-Listed Chinese Tech Companies No Longer See Hong Kong Listing as Vital Hedge Strategy Following PCAOB Development</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/">US-Listed Chinese Tech Companies No Longer See Hong Kong Listing as Vital Hedge Strategy Following PCAOB Development</a></p>
<p>A number of US-listed Chinese companies have <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-listed-chinese-tech-companies-cancel-hk-listing-plans-the-information-2022-12-28/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> suspended plans for a potential Hong Kong listing. According to <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/pinduoduo-and-other-u-s-listed-chinese-tech-stocks-cancel-plans-to-list-in-hong-kong" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">The Information</a>, these Chinese tech companies include agricultural tech giant Pinduoduo Inc (NASDAQ: PDD) and Full Truck Alliance Co (NYSE: YMM).</p>
<p>Although Pinduoduo merely paused discussions regarding a potential Hong Kong listing, Full Truck Alliance scrapped its plans altogether. Meanwhile, tech heavyweights such as<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> Alibaba</a> and JD.com have also made significant strides toward a Hong Kong listing over the years. The primary motivating factor for this agenda is to hedge the risk of a potential US delisting amid socio-political disputes with China. The US and the influential East Asian nation (two of the world’s largest economies), are locked in a tense trade and tech war.</p>
<h2>US-Listed Chinese Companies Abandon Hong Kong Listing Following Reduced Fears of US Delisting</h2>
<p>The development regarding Chinese companies with US listings halting Hong Kong plans follows news of a possible investigation. About two weeks ago, the US accounting watchdog Public Company Accounting Oversight Board (PCAOB) announced that it had unrestricted access to inspect and investigate Chinese companies. This is the first time the PCAOB would have such oversight.</p>
<p>In addition, the announcement also negated the risk of having up to 200 Chinese firms booted off US bourses amid fractured relationships between both countries. On December 15th, PCAOB Chair Erica Williams explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“For the first time in history, we are able to perform full and thorough inspections and investigations to root out potential problems and hold firms accountable to fix them.”</p></blockquote>
<p>B. Riley Financial chief market strategist Art Hogan also pointed out the relief experienced by Chinese firms like Alibaba. As Hogan put it:</p>
<blockquote><p>“[The PCAOB announcement] falls into the category of a game changing view of Chinese companies because the threat of their delisting seems to have been eliminated.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite the welcome news at the time, Chinese companies’ US-listed shares gave up gains and ended sharply lower. For instance, on Friday, December 16th, Alibaba, JD.com, and Baidu were all trading down between 3-5%. In addition, the shares of prominent music streaming provider Tencent Music were down 3.5%. The decline in these Chinese US-listed shares was steeper than the broader market decline. For instance, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> was down 2.5%, while the iShares MSCI China ETF sank 2.2%.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Q2 2023 Earnings</h2>
<p>In November, Alibaba’s Q2 2023 financial report <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-misses-q2-2023-revenue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fell short</a> of revenue expectations. According to reports, factors that caused the miss included slow spending and Covid restrictions. Weighing in on the subpar earnings release at the time, Alibaba CEO Daniel Zhang stated that the company remains undeterred. As he put it, “the uncertainties of the global landscape have only reinforced our resolve to focus on building capacity that will yield sustainable, high-quality growth for our customers and our own business over the long term.”</p>
<p>Zhang also noted that the trust shown by Alibaba’s shareholders over the years is responsible for the company’s continuous growth. In addition, the CEO stated that Alibaba plans to improve shareholder returns looking forward.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/">US-Listed Chinese Tech Companies No Longer See Hong Kong Listing as Vital Hedge Strategy Following PCAOB Development</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-listed-chinese-listing-hong-kong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2022 Auto Stocks: Top &amp; Bottom Performers, Ferrari Takes Lead</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ferrari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[general motors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[morgan stanley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nissan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[toyota]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volkswagen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230836</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/">2022 Auto Stocks: Top &#038; Bottom Performers, Ferrari Takes Lead</a></p>
<p>Traditional automaker Ferrari surprisingly came out at the top of auto stocks for 2022, beating out EV companies. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/">2022 Auto Stocks: Top &#038; Bottom Performers, Ferrari Takes Lead</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/">2022 Auto Stocks: Top &#038; Bottom Performers, Ferrari Takes Lead</a></p>
<p>Amid the selling pressure in the tech space that characterized much of 2022, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/28/top-2022-auto-stocks-ferrari-outshines-ev-makers-tesla.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">top-performing auto stocks</a> were those with the lowest decline. Some auto stocks outperformed others this year because they escaped the worst of 2022’s selling pressure. However, the best-performing auto stock for the year was not from the emerging EV industry but rather the fossil-fueled <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ferrari/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ferrari</a>.</p>
<p>Several once-promising EV startups constituted the biggest losers of 2022 due to capital hurdles or production scale limitations. According to reports, companies such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nikola-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nikola</a> (NASDAQ: NKLA), Canoo (NASDAQ: GOEV), Lucid (NASDAQ: LCID), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/rivian/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rivian</a> (NASDAQ: RIVN) all experienced massive 76% drawdowns year-to-date (YTD). Meanwhile, traditional auto manufacturers were able to moderate their stock declines better than the EV platforms. For instance, Italian luxury automaker Ferrari sat at the summit of the top-performing auto stocks for 2022. The company achieved this feat by sustaining a relatively smaller 18% decline YTD amid more significant drawdowns by its contemporaries.</p>
<h2>Ferrari Leverages Product Exclusivity to Top 2022 Auto Stocks</h2>
<p>Ferrari was also able to better manage losses by limiting annual production to preserve exclusivity and pricing power. Although the company’s cars are high-end and expensive, Ferrari projects to sell far less than other traditional manufacturers and EV makers. This approach gives Ferrari excellent profit margins and ensures that its production plants run at a balanced capacity.</p>
<p>According to Ferrari CEO Benedetto Vigna, the car manufacturer has a long waiting list, even though its products are pricey. In addition, at Ferrari’s Q3 earnings call, Vigna also forecasted <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ferrari-4-door-suv-purosangue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">healthy demand</a> for the company’s high-performance cars in 2023. The Ferrari CEO stressed the Italian maker would not see any shortage in demand regardless of how global economies fare.</p>
<p>Other traditional automakers managed declines much more extensive than Ferrari’s 18% but relatively more minor than EV setbacks. For example, prominent American auto manufacturers <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/general-motors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">General Motors</a> (NYSE: GM) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ford/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ford Motor</a> (NYSE: F) sank 40% in the year. Beyond the US, automotive companies such as Stellantis, Nissan, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/toyota/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Toyota</a>, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/volkswagen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Volkswagen</a> experienced declines of around 25%.</p>
<h2>The Tesla Way</h2>
<p>Although <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) featured prominently in 2021 and this year, the famous EV maker was not among 2022’s best-performing auto stocks. Tesla’s shares have plunged 68% YTD, with much of the decline coming since CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> acquired <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>. Oppenheimer analyst Colin Rusch commented on the Tesla situation, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We believe increasing negative sentiment on Twitter could linger long term, limiting its financial performance and become an ongoing overhang on TSLA.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Since the Twitter deal closed on October 27th, Tesla stock is trading down more than 50%.</p>
<p>The EV industry experienced significant stock growth last year but ran into micro and macroeconomic constraints in 2022. These constraints include low vehicle inventories, surging interest rates, and pervasive fears of a recession. Although several leading automakers performed reasonably well this year, they could not replicate 2021’s profitability. In an investor note from earlier in the month, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/morgan-stanley/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Morgan Stanley</a> analyst Adam Jonas observed:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are preparing for a challenging FY23 outlook for auto earnings on demand decline (higher rates), deflation (lower price/mix) and unfavorable changes in the supply/demand balance for EVs.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Wall Street analysts also anticipate that automotive stocks will experience choppiness in 2023.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/">2022 Auto Stocks: Top &#038; Bottom Performers, Ferrari Takes Lead</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-auto-stocks-top-ferrari/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy to Launch Enterprise Plugins on Lightning Network</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/">MicroStrategy to Launch Enterprise Plugins on Lightning Network</a></p>
<p>Citing the speed of transactions on the Lightning network, Saylor noted the delays associated with using credit cards for such a transaction would not affect the Lightning network.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/">MicroStrategy to Launch Enterprise Plugins on Lightning Network</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/">MicroStrategy to Launch Enterprise Plugins on Lightning Network</a></p>

<p>Co-founder and former CEO of MicroStrategy <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/michael-saylor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Michael Saylor</a> has revealed the firm’s plans to release enterprise plugins on Lightning Network in 2023. Saylor made this disclosure while speaking at a Twitter Spaces event.</p>
<p>At the event, Saylor noted the company was working to introduce cybersecurity, e-commerce, and marketing solutions for enterprise users. The company is hoping to leverage its experience in developing mass-deployable plugins.</p>
<p>The announcement is not surprising given that MicroStrategy recently announced it was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-bitcoin-lightning-engineer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hiring</a> a Bitcoin Lightning Software engineer to build a SaaS platform using the Lightning network.</p>
<p>According to Mr. Saylor, the firm has teams working on different products concurrently. The company will unveil the products in the first quarter of 2023 and launch them later that year.</p>
<h2>Potential Use Cases of Lightning Network Enterprise Plugins</h2>
<p>Saylor spoke extensively on the company’s idea during the Twitter Spaces event, citing varying use cases of the proposed enterprise plugins.</p>
<p>He talked about the possibility of creating a Lightning wallet as a paywall that requires micropayments before accessing private content.  If the wallet is non-custodial, Saylor believes its reach could extend to 100 million people. “We want to make it possible for any enterprise to spin up a Lightning wallet and a Lightning wallet architecture in the matter of an afternoon,” he concluded.</p>
<p>Again, the former CEO noted that it could be used as a corporate security wall. With that, it could protect enterprise websites from <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/63ea94fa-c6fc-449f-b2b8-ea29cc83637d">cyber attacks</a> since visitors will be asked to make a crypto deposit. Once complete, the assets will be returned to the website visited immediately.</p>
<p>Citing the speed of transactions on the Lightning network, Saylor noted the delays associated with using credit cards for such a transaction would not affect the Lightning network. Asides from this, Saylor noted that marketing officers could use the plugins to reward customers and incentivize them for specific activities like posting good reviews or completing surveys.</p>
<h2>Will MicroStrategy’s Bitcoin Buying Spree Backfire?</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, MicroStrategy <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-bitcoin-holdings-selling-units/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">has increased its Bitcoin holdings</a>, acquiring about 0.6% of the world’s total Bitcoin supply. Between 1st November and 24th December, the company purchased 3,205 BTC to bring its total Bitcoin supply to 132500 BTC. Consequently, the company has an unrealized loss of about $1.8 billion.</p>
<p>Will the decision to keep buying Bitcoin backfire or reward the company? The next few months will tell.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/">MicroStrategy to Launch Enterprise Plugins on Lightning Network</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-plugins-lightning-network/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alameda Research Wallets Became Active as Over $1M Worth of Coins Were Liquidated</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alameda research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[curve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam bankman-fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=230839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/">Alameda Research Wallets Became Active as Over $1M Worth of Coins Were Liquidated</a></p>
<p>As the bankruptcy proceedings take shape, chances are that these current withdrawals will be investigated and thanks to on-chain data, the flow of funds can easily be tracked.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/">Alameda Research Wallets Became Active as Over $1M Worth of Coins Were Liquidated</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/">Alameda Research Wallets Became Active as Over $1M Worth of Coins Were Liquidated</a></p>
<p>Alameda Research, the defunct trading firm belonging to the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, the founder and former Chief Executive Officer of bankrupt cryptocurrency trading platform, FTX Derivatives Exchange came alive a few nights ago as several assets were consolidated and liquidated.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1608204990581202946" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">updates posted</a> by Arkham Intelligence, the wallets belonging to Alameda Research had not been used to post any transaction in over 4 weeks until the latest flagged transactions.</p>
<p>“Sharp-eyed users may have noticed a number of interesting movements from Alameda wallets in the past 24 hours. These wallets had been inactive for multiple weeks before they &#8216;woke up&#8217; last night. Over $1M has been sent through crypto-mixers by Alameda wallets,” Arkham Intelligence said in a tweet on Wednesday, adding that “The final transactions made by tagged Alameda Research wallets occurred on December 1st, almost 4 weeks ago. Since then the wallets were silent, until ~24 hours ago. At which point, multiple Alameda addresses began to swap tokens for ETH/USDT, sending them to crypto mixers.”</p>
<p>As pointed out by the outfit, Ethereum-based digital currencies including DAI, Curve (CRV), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH), and USDC were sent from several of the company’s wallets to the 0x64e wallet. From here, the funds were moved to active crypto mixers including ChangeNow and Fixedfloat.</p>
<p>To Arkham Intelligence, the extensive nature of the liquidations perhaps showed that someone order than a regular employee might be involved in the liquidations. Whether or not the person is a hacker remains unknown but in total, as many as 30 wallets have been identified in the asset consolidation.</p>
<p>The crypto intelligence provider noted that Altogether, there has been more than “270.5Eth through ChangeNOW (~$325k)..800k USDT through Fixedfloat…200k through Curve SynthSwap (to native BTC)&#8230;200k through Airswap…200k through other crypto-mixing services,” all reaching a total of $1.7 million.</p>
<h2>Are the Alameda Research Liquidations Sanctioned by SBF?</h2>
<p>With the assets of Alameda Research also embroiled in bankruptcy proceedings with the rest of the entities linked to FTX Exchange, chances are that this current liquidation is sanctioned by Sam Bankman-Fried who has been on house arrest in the United States since he was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-be-released-on-250-million-bail/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">granted</a> a $250 million bail bond.</p>
<p>Though he is free in his parent’s house, for the time being, his freedom is limited, and consolidating funds from multiple wallets in a highly monitored firm does not seem likely.</p>
<p>FTX is not alien to cyberattacks as more than $370 million were <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ftx-hacker-339m-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">allegedly hacked</a> from the firm at the time it filed for bankruptcy. The suspicion of a cyberattack hinged on this current liquidation of funds from the exchange is the most tenable explanation as both SBF and Caroline Ellison, the CEO who managed Alameda Research prior to its collapse are also under the authority’s radar.</p>
<p>As the bankruptcy proceedings take shape, chances are that these current withdrawals will be investigated and thanks to on-chain data, the flow of funds can easily be tracked.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/china-state-owned-nft-marketplace/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/">Alameda Research Wallets Became Active as Over $1M Worth of Coins Were Liquidated</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alameda-research-wallets-coins-liquidated/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>