<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
>

<channel>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coincu.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<description>Coin and Crypto Infomation Update</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 16:45:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-Screen-Shot-2022-05-31-at-14.56.39-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinCu News</title>
	<link>https://coincu.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Liquid Staking Solution &#8211; Groundbreaking Generation Method In PoS</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205147-liquid-staking-solution-groundbreaking-generation-method-in-pos/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 16:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liquid Staking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LST]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PoS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205147</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Liquid staking is an innovative solution that addresses the limitations of traditional cryptocurrency staking, providing users with enhanced liquidity and flexibility.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205147-liquid-staking-solution-groundbreaking-generation-method-in-pos/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Liquid staking is an innovative solution that addresses the limitations of traditional cryptocurrency staking, providing users with enhanced liquidity and flexibility.</em></li>



<li><em>Users receive liquid staking tokens (LST) when staking their cryptocurrencies, allowing them to trade, lend, or use their staked assets as collateral while still earning staking rewards.</em></li>



<li><em>The method democratizes the staking process and aligns with the principles of DeFi, offering users a user-centric approach to growing their assets in the dynamic decentralized finance ecosystem.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>With the increasing popularity of cryptocurrency staking as a means of earning rewards and among networks, concerns surrounding illiquidity, complexity, and centralization have arisen among investors. However, a groundbreaking alternative known as &#8220;Liquid Staking&#8221; has emerged as an innovative solution to address these limitations.</strong></h5>



<p>Cryptocurrency staking involves locking up funds to support blockchain networks and validate transactions, thereby earning rewards in return. Traditional staking methods like self-staking and exchange staking have their drawbacks, including the inability to access locked assets for a specific period, complexity in managing staking operations, and concerns about centralized custody of staked assets.</p>



<p>In contrast, Liquid Staking introduces a novel approach that seeks to sidestep these risks. By tokenizing staked assets, users can maintain liquidity while participating in staking activities. This newfound liquidity allows investors to trade, lend, or use their staked assets as collateral, providing flexibility that was previously unavailable in conventional staking models. Let&#8217;s learn about this staking method with <a href="https://twitter.com/Coincuofficial" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coincu</a>.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604.png"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="424" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604-1024x424.png" alt="Liquid Staking Solution - Groundbreaking Generation Method In PoS" class="wp-image-205162" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604-1024x424.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604-300x124.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604-768x318.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604-750x311.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604-1140x472.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1604.png 1340w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Liquid Staking Solution - Groundbreaking Generation Method In PoS 1"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">What is liquid staking?</h2>



<p>At its core, liquid staking is a software-based innovation that facilitates direct staking on proof of stake (PoS) networks. When users stake their cryptocurrencies, they receive a liquid staking token (LST) that is programmatically minted by the protocol. This LST serves as evidence of ownership for the staked tokens and any associated network rewards.</p>



<p>The primary advantage of liquid staking lies in its ability to address the liquidity constraints imposed by traditional staking methods. Unlike the latter, which require users to endure bonding and unbonding periods lasting several days to weeks, liquid staking empowers token holders with enhanced liquidity and capital efficiency. The LSTs they receive can be transferred, stored, traded, or utilized in various DeFi applications without compromising their staking rewards.</p>



<p>One of the pioneering platforms in the liquid staking landscape is Lido. This platform enables users to stake any amount of Ethereum and receive stETH (a tokenized representation of their staked funds) in return. The stETH can be utilized for lending, used as collateral, or traded in other DeFi activities, all while the user continues to earn daily staking rewards. Additionally, Lido&#8217;s approach enables users to unstake at any time through stETH-ETH liquidity pools.</p>



<p>In the context of liquid staking, the process is akin to depositing ETH into a third-party application, which then deposits the user&#8217;s ETH into the Ethereum deposit contract through their own validators. In exchange, the app mints a representative ETH token (e.g., stETH) for the user. This representative token grants users the flexibility to transfer their ETH while still earning Ethereum staking rewards.</p>



<p>However, it is crucial to acknowledge that liquid staking comes with its own set of risks. While it offers increased liquidity, it also exposes users to potential security vulnerabilities or network-related issues. As with any financial venture, cautious research and risk assessment are vital when considering participation in liquid staking activities.</p>



<p>The year 2022 witnessed significant adoption of liquid staking, riding on the wave of DeFi opportunities. As more crypto enthusiasts explore innovative ways to earn rewards and optimize their assets, liquid staking is anticipated to play a prominent role in shaping the future of staking and contributing to the continuous growth of the DeFi ecosystem.</p>



<p>In conclusion, liquid staking represents a paradigm shift in the world of staking and DeFi. It empowers users to unlock the potential of their staked assets while participating in securing PoS networks. As the demand for DeFi opportunities continues to surge, liquid staking is poised to become an integral component of the evolving decentralized finance landscape. However, prudent consideration of the risks and benefits associated with liquid staking is essential for users seeking to make the most of this groundbreaking innovation.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="621" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-1024x621.png" alt="Liquid Staking Solution - Groundbreaking Generation Method In PoS" class="wp-image-205164" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-1024x621.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-300x182.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-768x466.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-1536x932.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-750x455.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606-1140x692.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1606.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Liquid Staking Solution - Groundbreaking Generation Method In PoS 2"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">How does it work?</h2>



<p>While bearing some resemblance to traditional staking options, the execution methods of liquid staking stand apart as a distinct and game-changing approach.</p>



<p>Liquid staking protocols represent a new generation of opportunities that enable users to stake any desired amount of an asset and easily withdraw them without impacting their initial deposit. This process involves depositing assets into specialized platforms, where users are then issued tokenized versions of their staked crypto assets. These derivative tokens carry an equivalent value and operate on a one-to-one basis with the original asset, albeit usually distinguished with a unique emblem.</p>



<p>For instance, if a user decides to stake 1 ETH into one of the liquid staking services, they would receive one stETH, with the &#8220;st&#8221; signifying staked ETH.</p>



<p>One of the key benefits of liquid staking is the fluidity it offers to users. The newly issued tokens can be freely transferred, traded, stored elsewhere, or even used for transactions without interfering with the initial deposit. This enhanced accessibility sets liquid staking apart from conventional staking methods. Additionally, users can earn staking rewards on their initial deposits while simultaneously generating more funds from their derivative tokens, creating a win-win situation.</p>



<p>Should a user choose to withdraw their initial deposit, they must return an equivalent deposit value to regain access to their funds. It is worth noting that certain liquid staking protocols may charge fees for the use of their platforms, though the fee structures can vary.</p>



<p>In contrast to conventional staking, where locked-up assets remain inaccessible for a set period, liquid staking empowers users to grow their crypto holdings while retaining the flexibility to capitalize on other investment opportunities or navigate volatile market conditions.</p>



<p>Liquid staking operates through a process of users delegating their crypto assets to a validator node on a delegated Proof-of-Stake (DPoS) network by pooling tokens in a staking pool via a third-party liquid staking service provider or native projects within the network. In return for locking their tokens in the network, users are issued derivative tokens representing their underlying assets, granting them access to liquid funds while their crypto remains staked. Liquid staking protocols typically utilize two primary mechanisms: rebasable and exchange rate-based tokens.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Rebasable Liquid Staking Derivatives</strong></h3>



<p>Under the rebasable LSD model, the value of the underlying asset and the derivative token remains consistently pegged at a 1:1 ratio. The balance of the derivative token is recalculated daily through updates from an oracle, reporting changes in the balance of the underlying token. For example, staking 1 Ether (ETH) on platforms like Lido would yield users 1 stETH, and upon withdrawal, users can redeem their ETH by burning stETH at the same 1:1 ratio established during minting.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Exchange Rate-Based Liquid Staking Derivatives</strong></h3>



<p>Exchange rate-based LSDs differ by experiencing fluctuations in value over time to reflect accrued rewards and fees while maintaining an unaltered balance. This results in a constant change in the exchange rate between the LSD and its underlying asset, usually updated on a 24-hour basis, depending on the specific protocol. For instance, staking 1 ETH on Rocket Pool would grant users 1 rETH, with the rETH/ETH exchange rate updated daily based on rewards earned by Rocket Pool&#8217;s Beacon Chain node operators, leading to an increase in the value of rETH over time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Advantages and Disadvantages</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Advantages</strong></h3>



<ol>
<li>Mobility: Liquid staking offers the flexibility to withdraw tokenized assets, allowing users to move their funds and react to market changes swiftly. This prevents users from being locked into long-term staking commitments during volatile market conditions, reducing the risk of potential losses.</li>



<li>Multiple Income Streams: Liquid staking enables users to leverage their staked assets as collateral for crypto-backed loans, creating additional income streams. By depositing these loans into higher-yield accounts, users can optimize their returns and take advantage of various DeFi opportunities.</li>



<li>Barrier-Free Entry: The concept of liquid staking aims to address the barriers associated with traditional staking, such as illiquidity, immobility, and inaccessibility. By converting locked capital into liquid assets through Receipt Tokens, users gain immediate access to liquidity, fostering a more accessible and inclusive staking ecosystem.</li>



<li>Composability of Yield Strategies: Liquid staking tokens can be utilized as collateral on centralized or decentralized platforms, allowing stakers to earn interest on top of their staking rewards. This opens up a wide array of yield strategies in the DeFi space, enhancing the overall profitability of staked assets.</li>



<li>Enhanced Technical Features: Unlike traditional staking, which delegates funds to a single validator, liquid staking offers more technical sophistication. Users can interact with smart contracts to manage their staked assets, granting them greater control and diversification options.</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disadvantages</strong></h3>



<ol>
<li>Depegging Risk: One significant risk of liquid staking lies in the possibility of tokenized assets depegging from the original staked tokens. If the tokenized version&#8217;s value deviates significantly from the underlying asset, users may experience losses when trading or redeeming their assets.</li>



<li>Loss of Access to Deposited Funds: Users face the risk of losing access to their deposited funds if they lose their tokenized assets in a trade. Retrieving the original deposit then requires making an equivalent deposit, which could be problematic for users facing financial constraints.</li>



<li>Smart Contract Vulnerabilities: Liquid staking relies on smart contracts to manage the tokenization process. While smart contracts are efficient, they are not immune to bugs or vulnerabilities. If a smart contract is exploited, it could lead to the loss of users&#8217; funds, with no recourse for recovery.</li>
</ol>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-1024x536.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="536" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-1024x536.png" alt="image 1607" class="wp-image-205165" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-1024x536.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-300x157.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-768x402.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-750x393.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607-1140x597.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1607.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Liquid Staking Solution - Groundbreaking Generation Method In PoS 3"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Liquid staking, a groundbreaking new-generation system, has emerged as a game-changer in the world of decentralized finance (DeFi), offering users unprecedented opportunities to grow their assets. Unlike traditional staking, which often locks funds, it provides a flexible and accessible approach, enabling users to make the most of their assets while reaping the benefits of staking.</p>



<p>Led by prominent platforms like Lido, liquid staking empowers users to utilize a liquid version of their staked assets on various other platforms. This newfound liquidity has quickly made liquid staking a favorite among users who seek greater control over their funds, allowing them to redeem their assets at any time without the usual restrictions.</p>



<p>One of the main attractions of liquid staking is that it eliminates the risks and complexities associated with self-staking while still providing the same benefits. Users can now enjoy the rewards of staking without the need to navigate intricate processes or depend on centralized exchanges.</p>



<p>In the realm of Ethereum, liquid staking stands out as a viable alternative to both self and exchange staking. By skillfully balancing risk, reward, and convenience, liquid staking opens doors for traders to exchange staked tokens without facing the stringent requirements often imposed on stakers in the Ethereum network.</p>



<p>Furthermore, liquid staking democratizes the staking process, catering to holders of all ETH amounts. For those with smaller wallets, the system allows staking any desired amount of Ethereum while retaining the flexibility to unstake at any moment. On the other hand, larger ETH holders can leverage liquid staking services to hedge their funds against the volatility of ETH prices, enjoying the benefits without the burden of maintaining a complex staking infrastructure.</p>



<p>As the greater DeFi movement continues to gather momentum, liquid staking aligns perfectly with its core values of decentralization and accessibility. Enabling users to earn staking rewards while actively participating in the dynamic DeFi ecosystem, liquid staking represents the epitome of decentralized finance in action.</p>



<p>With its user-centric approach and revolutionary features, liquid staking is poised to disrupt the traditional staking landscape, unlocking a wealth of opportunities for users and fostering the growth of the DeFi space as a whole. As the popularity of liquid staking continues to surge, the future of decentralized finance looks brighter than ever.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205147-liquid-staking-solution-groundbreaking-generation-method-in-pos/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1605-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Large Shiba Inu Holders Witness Jaw-Dropping 923% Surge in SHIB Outflows Overnight</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205154-shiba-inu-holders-dropping-923-surge-in-shib/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 15:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205154</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a surprising turn of events, large holders of Shiba Inu (SHIB) tokens experienced a remarkable 923% surge in outflows within a span of 24 hours.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205154-shiba-inu-holders-dropping-923-surge-in-shib/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Large Shiba Inu holders experience a massive 923% surge in outflows of SHIB tokens in 24 hours, raising questions about potential coordinated efforts.</em></li>



<li><em>Concentration of SHIB supply in a few wallets sparks concerns about the impact of major holders on the token&#8217;s market and prompts discussions on transparency and decentralization in the crypto space.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a surprising turn of events, large holders of Shiba Inu (SHIB) tokens experienced a remarkable 923% surge in outflows within a span of 24 hours.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2021-09-10-20.28.19.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1000" height="667" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2021-09-10-20.28.19.jpeg" alt="Large Shiba Inu Holders Witness Jaw-Dropping 923% Surge in SHIB Outflows Overnight" class="wp-image-205155" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2021-09-10-20.28.19.jpeg 1000w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2021-09-10-20.28.19-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2021-09-10-20.28.19-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2021-09-10-20.28.19-750x500.jpeg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" title="Large Shiba Inu Holders Witness Jaw-Dropping 923% Surge in SHIB Outflows Overnight 4"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>On-chain data revealed that the SHIB tokens moved from 268 million to a staggering 2.47 trillion, leaving experts puzzled over the sudden spike. Notably, this surge occurred despite the <a href="https://coincu.com/202984-shiba-inu-shib-burning-rate-surges-by-2000/">Shiba Inu</a> token&#8217;s price showing no extraordinary fluctuations during the same period.</p>



<p>While some tokens were flowing back into the wallets, the incoming amounts were relatively smaller in comparison to the massive outflows. The most intriguing aspect of this development is the fact that the majority of the Shiba Inu token supply, an astounding 636.42 trillion SHIB (including the burn address), is concentrated in whale wallets. Many of these large wallets belong to centralized exchanges&#8217; hot wallets, which has led to speculation about orchestrated efforts by centralized entities.</p>



<p>The coordinated movement of tokens between these wallets raises questions about potential motives and actions taken by these entities. The lack of clear reasons for such large-scale outflows has left the crypto community guessing about the intentions behind these transactions. Additionally, the apparent resilience of these large holders in the face of significant outflows has further fueled discussions about their potential influence on the Shiba Inu token market.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="582" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-1024x582.jpeg" alt="Large Shiba Inu Holders Witness Jaw-Dropping 923% Surge in SHIB Outflows Overnight" class="wp-image-205156" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-1024x582.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-300x170.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-768x436.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-750x426.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-1140x648.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SHIB_7D_graph_coinmarketcap.jpeg 1394w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Large Shiba Inu Holders Witness Jaw-Dropping 923% Surge in SHIB Outflows Overnight 5"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The concentration of such a substantial portion of the SHIB supply in a few wallets raises concerns about the impact these holders could have on the overall token market. With such a significant stake in their possession, these large holders could potentially influence token prices and market sentiment through their actions.</p>



<p>While the Shiba Inu community is still trying to make sense of this sudden surge in outflows, analysts and investors are keeping a close eye on any further developments. The dynamics of large holders and their activities continue to be a topic of interest, prompting discussions about the need for transparency and decentralization within the crypto space.</p>



<p>As the situation unfolds, the crypto market will closely monitor the movements and actions of these major SHIB holders to gain a better understanding of their impact on the token&#8217;s performance and overall market stability.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205154-shiba-inu-holders-dropping-923-surge-in-shib/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Copy-of-Final-Thumb-7-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alphapo Hot Wallet Breach: $23 Million Stolen Due To Compromised Private Key</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205148-alphapo-23-million-stolen-private-key/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 15:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alphapo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a recent and concerning security breach, Alphapo's hot wallet experienced a devastating attack resulting in the theft of $23 million in funds. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205148-alphapo-23-million-stolen-private-key/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Alphapo&#8217;s hot wallet breached, resulting in a $23 million theft.</em></li>



<li><em>Compromised private key believed to be the cause; users advised to take precautionary measures.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In a recent and concerning security breach, Alphapo&#8217;s hot wallet experienced a devastating attack resulting in the theft of $23 million in funds.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Loses-23-Million-in-Multi-Platform-Attack-1024x527-1.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="527" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Loses-23-Million-in-Multi-Platform-Attack-1024x527-1.png" alt="Alphapo Hot Wallet Breach: $23 Million Stolen Due To Compromised Private Key" class="wp-image-205150" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Loses-23-Million-in-Multi-Platform-Attack-1024x527-1.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Loses-23-Million-in-Multi-Platform-Attack-1024x527-1-300x154.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Loses-23-Million-in-Multi-Platform-Attack-1024x527-1-768x395.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alphapo-Loses-23-Million-in-Multi-Platform-Attack-1024x527-1-750x386.png 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Alphapo Hot Wallet Breach: $23 Million Stolen Due To Compromised Private Key 6"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>According to CertiK monitoring, the breach occurred on July 23, raising alarms within the cryptocurrency community. The stolen funds included 5,700 ETH, which were subsequently bridged to BTC, and a substantial amount of 118.3 million TRX, traced to a wallet address beginning with &#8220;TJF7m.&#8221;</p>



<p>The primary cause of the breach appears to be a compromised private key, a sensitive cryptographic code used to access and secure the wallet&#8217;s contents. This incident is part of a growing trend of losses due to compromised private keys in 2023, contributing to a staggering total of $214 million in losses.</p>



<p>The security firm ZachXBT also reported on the incident, confirming the gravity of the situation. Following the breach, Alphapo&#8217;s client HypeDrop swiftly implemented precautionary measures, temporarily disabling withdrawals to prevent further unauthorized access and safeguard users&#8217; assets.</p>



<p>The stolen funds were cleverly laundered through multiple cross-chains, attempting to obscure the digital footprint of the attackers. The first step involved transferring the stolen assets to the Ethereum network, followed by intricate cross-chaining to the Avalanche and BTC networks, making it more challenging to track and recover the stolen funds.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC-1024x512.png" alt="Alphapo Hot Wallet Breach: $23 Million Stolen Due To Compromised Private Key" class="wp-image-205151" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/GDAC.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Alphapo Hot Wallet Breach: $23 Million Stolen Due To Compromised Private Key 7"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The incident has raised concerns within the cryptocurrency community, highlighting the critical importance of securing private keys and employing robust security measures. Users are urged to exercise caution, verify security protocols, and utilize multi-factor authentication to protect their assets from potential breaches.</p>



<p><a href="https://coincu.com/205076-alphapo-loses-23-million-multi-platform-attack/">Alphapo</a>&#8216;s security team is actively investigating the breach and working to bolster their security infrastructure to prevent future attacks. Additionally, the broader cryptocurrency industry may also use this incident as a valuable learning opportunity to enhance security practices across the board.</p>



<p>As the investigation unfolds, users are advised to stay informed and follow updates from Alphapo and HypeDrop to ensure the safety of their holdings. Cybersecurity remains a top priority in the crypto space, and industry stakeholders must continue to collaborate and innovate to create a safer environment for all participants.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205148-alphapo-23-million-stolen-private-key/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Copy-of-Final-Thumb-6-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>OP Stack vs. ZK Stack &#8211; The Battle For Ethereum&#8217;s Future Unleashed</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205141-op-stack-vs-zk-stack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer-2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OP Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Garden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimism Collective]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZK Stack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zksync]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkSync Era]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205141</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The race to scale Layer-2 solutions is heating up, and two prominent contenders, OP Stack and ZK Stack, are leading the charge in addressing Ethereum's scalability challenges.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205141-op-stack-vs-zk-stack/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>OP Stack and ZK Stack are leading contenders in the race to address Ethereum&#8217;s scalability challenges through Layer 2 solutions.</em></li>



<li><em>OP Stack focuses on creating a high-quality open-source platform for launching optimistic rollup networks, aiming to achieve a unified Superchain in the future.</em></li>



<li><em>ZK Stack, based on zkSync Era code, empowers developers with unparalleled sovereignty and seamless connectivity to build custom ZK-driven Layer 2 and Layer 3 chains, known as Hyperchains, offering hyperscalability and a trustless liquidity network.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In the dynamic world of blockchain technology, the race to scale Layer-2 solutions is heating up, and two prominent contenders, <a href="https://stack.optimism.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OP Stack</a> and ZK Stack, are leading the charge in addressing Ethereum&#8217;s scalability challenges.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-1024x512.png" alt="OP Stack vs. ZK Stack - The Battle For Ethereum&#039;s Future Unleashed" class="wp-image-205143" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1601.png 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="OP Stack vs. ZK Stack - The Battle For Ethereum&#039;s Future Unleashed 8"></a></figure></div>


<p>OP Stack and ZK Stack are both innovative products that aim to enhance Layer-2 scaling on the Ethereum network. While their ultimate goal is the same, they employ distinct approaches to achieve this feat, making the competition between the two projects particularly intriguing.</p>



<p>The competition between OP Stack and ZK Stack is fierce, with both projects attracting attention from developers and the blockchain community. The winner of this race will have a profound impact on Ethereum&#8217;s future scalability, enabling faster and more cost-effective transactions on the network. Let&#8217;s Coincu compare the difference between these 2 structures.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">OP Stack</h2>



<p>Developed and maintained by the dedicated Optimism Collective, OP Stack (Over Powered Stack) stack is designed with key principles in mind: utility, simplicity, and extensibility, enabling a shared, open-source system for deploying new rollup networks.</p>



<p>The primary focus of the OP Stack is to create a high-quality, fully open-source platform for launching optimistic rollup networks. This becomes increasingly vital as the concept of the Superchain gains traction, necessitating the secure establishment of new networks that can seamlessly interoperate within the proposed Superchain ecosystem. By adhering to shared standards, the Optimism Collective aims to foster collaboration and avoid redundancy in software development, thus streamlining the deployment of layer 2 blockchains.</p>



<p>Presently in its Bedrock iteration, the OP Stack provides developers with the necessary tools to launch optimistic rollup networks. It has been meticulously designed to support the Optimism Superchain, which is a network of interconnected layer 2 solutions sharing security, communication layers, and the common development stack &#8211; the OP Stack itself. Bedrock empowers developers to rapidly create and deploy custom rollup networks that are fully compatible with the Superchain ecosystem. However, it&#8217;s important to note that the current Bedrock release lacks the flexibility for easy modifications, which is essential for accommodating future iterations of the OP Stack.</p>



<p>One of the most notable aspects of the OP Stack is the groundbreaking concept it introduced &#8211; the &#8220;Open Garden.&#8221; This concept allows OP chains to achieve atomic cross-chain combinations, provided they voluntarily choose to enter the same shared sequencer set. In essence, it enables seamless collaboration among different chains within the ecosystem. For those OP chains that prefer not to operate their own sequencer, they have the option to utilize the Optimism shared sequencer for a certain fee, presenting a profit model for Optimism.</p>



<p>Looking ahead, the vision for the OP Stack revolves around the concept of a unified Superchain, where all OP chains are fully interoperable within the Optimism platform. Thanks to the sharing of modules within the OP Stack, developers can recycle and reuse code, making the entire system more robust and resistant to vulnerabilities and bugs.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-1024x514.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="514" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-1024x514.png" alt="OP Stack vs. ZK Stack - The Battle For Ethereum&#039;s Future Unleashed" class="wp-image-205144" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-1024x514.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-768x385.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-1536x770.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-750x376.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602-1140x572.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1602.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="OP Stack vs. ZK Stack - The Battle For Ethereum&#039;s Future Unleashed 9"></a></figure></div>


<p>Shortly after its launch, the OP Stack received overwhelming support from prominent players in the Web3 space. Coinbase, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, announced its collaboration with the OP Stack to create a multi-chain Layer 2 (L2) platform. The partnership aims to upgrade the Optimism mainnet, Base, and other L2s to establish an initial superchain structure, enabling seamless bridging and sorting of transactions. As part of this collaboration, Base, built on the OP Stack, provides enhanced security and scalability to support decentralized applications, while offering full compatibility with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) at minimal cost, thereby boosting developer platform growth.</p>



<p>At the core of the OP Stack, Ethereum serves as the dedicated Data Availability (DA) layer, responsible for storing and securing data. Ethereum&#8217;s Proof of Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism ensures the integrity and security of the data on which the OP Stack relies.</p>



<p>The OP Stack&#8217;s layered architecture includes the execution layer, which leverages the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) to process transactions and execute state changes. The derivation layer is responsible for deriving data inputs from the DA layer for state writes, ensuring smooth operations and interoperability.</p>



<p>As the ecosystem expands, the OP Stack is committed to continuous improvement. The team plans to introduce a modular sequencer set to prepare for multiple rollup networks to be built using the OP Stack, enhancing interoperability and scalability. The governance layer, consisting of governance tokens and multi-signature smart contracts, manages the OP Stack, including system configurations, upgrades, and decision-making processes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">ZK Stack</h2>



<p>In an exciting leap for decentralized technology, the ZK Stack has emerged as a revolutionary modular open-source framework designed to create custom ZK-driven Layer 2 (L2) and Layer 3 (L3) chains, known as Hyperchains. Based on zkSync Era code, this cutting-edge platform offers unparalleled sovereignty, seamless connectivity, and hyperscalability, redefining the landscape of blockchain solutions.</p>



<p>At the heart of the ZK Stack lies its key features, empowering creators with absolute autonomy to customize and shape every aspect of their chains. This framework operates under a fully permissive MIT/Apache open-source license, ensuring that developers can freely contribute and utilize its capabilities as they see fit.</p>



<p>A central characteristic of the ZK Stack is its focus on sovereignty and seamless connectivity. Hyperchains built using this framework maintain their independence while relying on Ethereum L1 for security and liveness. Interconnecting these Hyperchains is facilitated through a network of Hyperbridges, enabling trustless, low-latency, and cost-effective interoperability.</p>



<p>Pioneering this hyperscalable unified liquidity network is zkSync Era, serving as the flagship Hyperchain. For developers seeking synchronous composability with existing protocols within the ecosystem, deploying their projects on zkSync Era proves to be a straightforward choice, with added features like flash-loans becoming readily accessible.</p>



<p>However, the ZK Stack offers a compelling alternative under specific circumstances. Developers seeking tailored customization for their chains or those comfortable with asynchronous connectivity to the broader ecosystem can fully leverage the capabilities of this framework. It caters to diverse use-cases, from lightweight sequencers for games and social networks to low-latency sequencing for exchange appchains like dYdX, and even private chains for enterprises seeking interconnectedness with the ecosystem while maintaining privacy.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-1024x500.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="500" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-1024x500.png" alt="OP Stack vs. ZK Stack - The Battle For Ethereum&#039;s Future Unleashed" class="wp-image-205145" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-1024x500.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-300x147.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-768x375.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-1536x750.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-750x366.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603-1140x557.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1603.png 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="OP Stack vs. ZK Stack - The Battle For Ethereum&#039;s Future Unleashed 10"></a></figure></div>


<p>The decision to build on the ZK Stack stems from its future-proof nature. Zero-knowledge technology unlocks unique superpowers that go beyond what traditional non-ZK solutions can offer. The framework&#8217;s design capitalizes on gas-less calldata in its ZK-enabled architecture, ensuring an exceptional user experience through native Account Abstraction.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the ZK Stack achieves remarkable compression through ZK proofs, making specific transaction types, such as oracle updates, up to 1,000 times cheaper compared to other rollup platforms. In addition, the framework offers an optional ultra-low-cost extension through zkPorter accounts, catering to specific use-cases with budget constraints.</p>



<p>The core philosophy of hyperscalability sets the ZK Stack apart. By allowing developers to create sovereign Hyperchains without compromising on interoperability and composability, the framework fosters an unfragmented liquidity network. Hyperchains within this ecosystem can seamlessly transfer assets across one another within minutes, all in a trustless manner and without incurring extra costs, thanks to Hyperbridges.</p>



<p>Smart contracts calling each other asynchronously cross-chain further enhance the seamless experience for users, contributing to the overall fluidity of the decentralized ecosystem.</p>



<p>To foster knowledge-sharing and in-depth discussions, the ZK Stack team has initiated a series of technical deep-dives, delving into the framework&#8217;s architecture and principles. This approach ensures transparency and strengthens the community&#8217;s understanding of the ZK Stack, particularly its Hyperscalability.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Conclusion</h2>



<p>The Ethereum community has been abuzz with excitement following the announcement of the ZK Stack, a groundbreaking advancement in the realm of Layer 2 (L2) scaling solutions. In response, the community wasted no time in conducting an in-depth technical comparison between the newly introduced ZK Stack and the existing OP Stack.</p>



<p>ZK Stack, developed by a consortium of leading researchers and developers, has emerged as a strong contender in the race for L2 scaling supremacy. One of its key differentiators lies in its approach to handling state and consensus. Unlike OP Stack, which requires the maintenance of state and consensus, ZK Stack can directly rely on the security of Ethereum, streamlining the process and enhancing overall efficiency.</p>



<p>The innovative use of ZKPs sets ZK Stack apart from its competitors. Instead of waiting for underlying state changes on the Ethereum blockchain, ZK Stack can employ ZK proofs to directly verify state changes between chains. This revolutionary method significantly improves the efficiency of inter-chain interactions, reducing the delays associated with asynchronous cross-chain calls.</p>



<p>On the other hand, the OP Stack, boasting the advantage of being an early entrant in the L2 scaling arena, has established its presence within the Ethereum ecosystem. However, it is not without limitations. Asynchronous cross-chain calls in OP Stack necessitate waiting for the underlying verification of Ethereum, potentially impeding the scalability and speed of interactions.</p>



<p>The clash between the two scaling solutions reflects the broader narrative of multi-chain scaling surrounding Ethereum, which has emerged as a crucial driving force in the ongoing cryptocurrency market cycle. As the battle intensifies, the industry eagerly awaits to see which solution will emerge as the preferred choice.</p>



<p>For the team behind ZK Stack, this paradigm shift represents a strategic move from technology-centric development to a community-oriented focus. Earlier this year, they unveiled the EVM-compatible ZK Rollup, zkSync Era, which showcased their commitment to building mature ZK technology. With the release of additional Hyperchains, the team aims to encourage a surge in core contributors to the zkSync ecosystem, empowering the community to take ownership of the network.</p>



<p>The competition between ZK Stack and OP Stack is not just a battle for technological supremacy; it represents a defining moment in the evolution of L2 scaling solutions for Ethereum and the broader cryptocurrency landscape. With both solutions vying for dominance, the future of scalable and efficient blockchain networks lies in the hands of innovation and community support. As the race continues, the cryptocurrency community watches closely, anticipating a new era of secure and scalable decentralized applications.</p>



<p>In conclusion, the OP Stack is spearheading a new era of blockchain interoperability and scalability. With its innovative approach and commitment to openness and collaboration, the OP Stack is paving the way for a decentralized future with powerful rollup networks integrated within a seamless and interconnected ecosystem.</p>



<p>The ZK Stack emerges as a trailblazing solution in the decentralized technology landscape. Offering unmatched customization options, seamless connectivity, and hyperscalability, it empowers developers to create future-proof Hyperchains that can shape the decentralized future. As this technology continues to evolve, the possibilities for the decentralized tech frontier seem limitless, and the ZK Stack stands at the forefront, guiding the way to a more inclusive and innovative decentralized world.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205141-op-stack-vs-zk-stack/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1600-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205130-zero-knowledge-proof-projects-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 09:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immutable X]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mina protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Scroll]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[StarkWare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zero-knowledge proof]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZK-rollup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zkEVM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZKP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zksync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With zero-knowledge proof, a party can prove the truth of a statement to another party without divulging any additional information, making it a game-changer for the blockchain space.
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205130-zero-knowledge-proof-projects-in-2023/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>In the fast-evolving world of blockchain technology, one of the most critical challenges is striking a balance between data verification and privacy. Fortunately, zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) cryptography has emerged as a powerful solution to address this dilemma. With ZKP, a party can prove the truth of a statement to another party without divulging any additional information, making it a game-changer for the blockchain space.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1598.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="700" height="394" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1598.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205138" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1598.png 700w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1598-300x169.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 11"></a></figure></div>


<p>As we gear up for the year 2023, several ZKP projects have garnered significant attention for their potential to revolutionize the industry. These six projects, in particular, are worth keeping a close eye on:</p>



<ul>
<li><strong>zkSync</strong>: zkSync stands out as an L2 scaling solution on Ethereum, powered by ZK-Rollup technology. It excels in providing exceptional transaction processing capacity, reduced gas costs, and ensuring the same security levels as Ethereum Layer 1.</li>



<li><strong>Polygon</strong>: Previously known as Matic Network, Polygon has established itself as a robust infrastructure and scaling solution on Ethereum. Its integration of ZK-Rollup through Polygon zkEVM boosts compatibility with EVM and enhances layer 2 composability.</li>



<li><strong>Mina Protocol</strong>: Mina takes a unique approach by introducing a special private blockchain with a remarkably small size of about 22KB. By utilizing ZK-SNARKs, Mina can maintain fast synchronization of nodes and offer a high level of security.</li>



<li><strong>StarkWare</strong>: StarkWare, founded by Eli Ben Sasson in January 2018, is at the forefront of leveraging ZKP to enhance blockchain scalability and privacy. Its StarkEx framework allows protocols to build specific rollups, facilitating simple transactions, AMM, spot trading, NFT minting, and more.</li>



<li><strong>Immutable X</strong>: Focused on NFT and gaming on Ethereum, Immutable X utilizes Validium StarkEx solution developed by StarkWare. It enables minting, trading, and integrating crypto assets into games, making it more accessible and cost-effective for game developers.</li>



<li><strong>Scroll</strong>: Scroll is making strides with zkEVM Equivalence technology, a fully compatible ZK-Rollup solution with EVM. By providing code consistency and seamless dApp migration between layers 1 and 2, Scroll aims to simplify blockchain development for developers.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">zkSync</h2>



<p><a href="https://zksync.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zkSync</a>, an innovative Layer 2 protocol built on ZK Rollup technology, is revolutionizing asset transfers between Ethereum&#8217;s Layer 1 and Layer 2 networks. By harnessing the capabilities of Zero-Knowledge proofs and on-chain data accessibility, zkSync ensures seamless and efficient transactions while significantly enhancing scalability on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>



<p>Currently, Ethereum employs two different types of rollups: ZK rollups and Optimistic rollups. In the case of ZK rollups, the transaction batch is meticulously verified for accuracy on the Ethereum network. Once the verification process is successfully completed, the transaction batch is treated as final, akin to any other Ethereum transaction.</p>



<p>The magic behind ZK rollups lies in Zero-Knowledge proofs. The zkSync operator generates proof of validity for a batch of offline transactions. These proofs are then transmitted to Ethereum for the final execution of the transaction batch using a cryptographic technique called SNARK.</p>



<p>The fundamental concept of zkSync is to provide an open and sacrifice-free Layer 2 solution to boost Ethereum&#8217;s scalability. Users can now transfer assets via zkSync without encountering tiering issues, the need for new addresses, or any other barriers that might hinder their experience.</p>



<p>zkSync&#8217;s benefits extend to both users and developers alike. By significantly lowering transaction fees and enhancing the user experience of crypto wallets and services, zkSync paves the way for exploring new DeFi innovations. This protocol eliminates the reliance on third-party intermediaries, ensures instant transaction confirmation, and reduces fees by up to 99%. Additionally, zkSync enables seamless payments to existing Ethereum addresses and smart contracts.</p>



<p>With zkSync leading the charge in adopting Zero Knowledge rollups, the Ethereum community is poised for a new era of smooth and scalable asset transfers, opening up exciting possibilities for the future of decentralized finance.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="513" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-1024x513.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205132" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-1024x513.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-768x385.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-750x376.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592-1140x571.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1592.png 1300w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 12"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Polygon</h2>



<p>Polygon, a leading infrastructure and scaling solutions project, has been making significant strides in the DeFi market with its array of products designed to address Ethereum&#8217;s congestion and high transaction fees. With a market capitalization among the largest and a popular Layer 1 blockchain, Polygon has become a force to be reckoned with in the crypto space.</p>



<p>The introduction of Polygon zkEVM, a Layer 2 scaling solution employing Zero Knowledge Rollup technology and the zkEVM programming language, further showcases Polygon&#8217;s commitment to revolutionizing the DeFi landscape. Vitalik&#8217;s classification designates Polygon zkEVM as type 2, offering full compatibility with EVM, with minor modifications needed for execution. Though currently in type 3, Polygon zkEVM is steadily progressing toward the planned type 2 status.</p>



<p>The inception of Polygon zkEVM is the result of strategic acquisitions of Mir and Hermez Network, both ZK technology development projects, making Polygon a prominent player in the ZK space.</p>



<p>The ZK rollup technology integrated into Polygon&#8217;s ecosystem provides a scalable solution by aggregating multiple off-chain transactions into a single on-chain transaction. This eliminates the need for miners to verify each transaction on the Ethereum Mainnet and ensures the trustless verification of batched transactions through zero-knowledge proofs. The enhanced security and immediate transaction confirmation make Polygon&#8217;s rollups an efficient and user-friendly option compared to Optimistic rollups that impose waiting periods for fund withdrawals.</p>



<p>Polygon&#8217;s strong commitment to scaling Ethereum through ZK rollups is evident in its substantial investment of over $1 billion in zero-knowledge technology. Among its products, four, namely Zero, Hermez, Miden, and Nightfall are based on ZK rollups, highlighting Polygon&#8217;s dedication to fostering DeFi development and revolutionizing the future of decentralized finance.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-1024x577.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="577" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-1024x577.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205133" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-1024x577.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-1536x865.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593-1140x642.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1593.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 13"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Mina Protocol</h2>



<p>Mina Protocol, the world&#8217;s first crypto protocol with a unique private blockchain, is leading the charge in addressing the growing challenges faced by traditional blockchains like Bitcoin and Ethereum. With data sizes reaching thousands of GB, Mina aims to provide users with a fast and efficient blockchain solution while also serving as a global payment system in the future.</p>



<p>At the heart of Mina&#8217;s innovation is its Proof-of-Stake blockchain, which stores transactions in a compact and efficient form. Unlike traditional blockchains that continuously grow with usage, Mina&#8217;s blockchain remains a fixed size of about 22KB, ensuring fast synchronization of nodes.</p>



<p>This breakthrough is made possible by zk-SNARKs, a concise cryptographic proof that verifies the validity of each block created by the Mina node. These proofs are much smaller than the entire chain, allowing nodes to store and process data more easily, thus achieving decentralization on a large scale.</p>



<p>The Mina Protocol&#8217;s implementation of zk-SNARKs ensures the accuracy and security of transactions without revealing unnecessary information. Each block produced includes a zk-SNARKs proof that validates the integrity of all previous blocks, allowing nodes to move forward without storing the entire transaction history from the beginning.</p>



<p>zk-SNARKs act as irreplaceable certificates, proving the correctness of calculations without the need for full disclosure. This allows for the verification of every transaction in a block, significantly reducing the block size to just 1 single SNARK, approximately 1KB in size.</p>



<p>By leveraging zk-SNARKs and its Proof-of-Stake consensus mechanism, Mina Protocol sets a new standard in blockchain efficiency, speed, and decentralization. As it continues to push the boundaries of blockchain technology, Mina Protocol emerges as a game-changer in the crypto world, paving the way for a more convenient and sustainable global payment system.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594-1024x576.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205134" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1594.png 1120w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 14"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Starknet</h2>



<p>Starknet, a pioneering Layer 2 solution, has emerged as a game-changing technology to address the crucial issue of scalability in the Ethereum network. In the past, Ethereum has faced challenges in handling large transaction volumes, resulting in congestion and high gas fees. Starknet&#8217;s innovative approach aims to overcome these limitations by utilizing zero-knowledge (ZK) rollups, revolutionizing the way transactions are processed, and enhancing the overall efficiency and security of the Ethereum blockchain.</p>



<p>To understand the significance of Starknet&#8217;s impact, let&#8217;s delve into the technology behind it. The term &#8220;ZK-rollups&#8221; comprises two crucial components: &#8220;ZK&#8221; stands for zero-knowledge proofs, and &#8220;rollups&#8221; refer to the bundling of transactions into a single, aggregated batch.</p>



<p>Zero-knowledge proofs are cryptographic protocols that allow one party (the prover) to prove the validity of a statement to another party (the verifier) without revealing any specific information about the statement itself. In the context of Starknet, zero-knowledge proofs enable the network to verify the validity of transactions without disclosing the underlying sensitive data. This ensures that transactions are secure and private, a vital aspect for users in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space.</p>



<p>Starknet achieves scalability by employing STARK (Scalable Transparent Argument of Knowledge) technology, a highly secure and efficient cryptographic proof system. With STARK, the prover generates proofs for transactions off-chain, and the verifier checks these proofs on-chain without the need to execute the actual transactions. This process significantly reduces computational overhead, making it more cost-effective and scalable compared to traditional on-chain computations.</p>



<p>The beauty of this approach lies in its ability to create a one-time event for complex calculations. Instead of repeating these calculations across the entire network, Starknet generates a proof once and allows others to verify it, thereby saving considerable time and computational resources. This optimization is pivotal in enhancing Ethereum&#8217;s throughput, reducing congestion, and mitigating high gas fees.</p>



<p>Through the integration of ZK-rollups, Starknet enables the bundling of multiple transactions into a single transaction sent to the Ethereum mainnet. By consolidating multiple operations into one, Starknet drastically reduces the number of transactions processed on-chain, leading to faster and more efficient transaction processing.</p>



<p>Furthermore, Starknet embraces account abstraction (AA), which enables greater flexibility in the management of user accounts. AA allows users to interact with the blockchain using a broader range of assets, making it easier to utilize various tokens and assets within the network.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-1024x538.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-1024x538.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205135" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-300x158.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595-1140x599.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1595.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 15"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Immutable X</h2>



<p>Immutable X, a layer 2 scaling solution, is making significant strides in revolutionizing the NFT and gaming sectors on the Ethereum blockchain. Founded in 2018 by James Ferguson, Robbie Ferguson, and Alex Connolly, the project aims to provide game developers with the necessary infrastructure and software development tools to seamlessly integrate crypto assets into games, thereby streamlining the process and reducing barriers to entry into the web3 gaming world.</p>



<p>Central to Immutable X&#8217;s success is its implementation of the Validium StarkEx solution, a cutting-edge Zk rollup technology developed by StarkWare. StarkWare Industries, co-founded by Eli Ben Sasson, an influential figure in the development of STARK and ZCash, focuses on leveraging SNARK proof technology to enhance blockchain scalability and privacy.</p>



<p>The StarkEx framework within Immutable X facilitates the creation of specific rollups, enabling applications such as AMM, Spot Trading, Payments, NFT minting, and trading. Dapps can be deployed in two primary modes: ZK Rollup, which stores transaction data on Ethereum via calldata, and Validium, where transaction data is stored off-chain.</p>



<p>When users conduct operations that modify the network&#8217;s state, such as minting or trading NFTs, transactions are generated and processed within the Immutable X chain. The Operator role aggregates and issues transaction batches, sending them to Ethereum with Merkle roots before and after processing the new transactions. In contrast to Optimistic Rollups, which require Verifiers to recalculate and verify the state, Immutable X leverages STARK Proofs, providing a more efficient and timely approach to validating the state of new transactions on Ethereum.</p>



<p>Transaction data on Immutable X is stored off-chain by the Data Availability Committee (DAC), a network of nodes responsible for storing relevant data. In case of disputes, the DAC supplies the necessary data, and each batch of transactions is accompanied by attestations, confirming the availability of data when needed. This approach significantly reduces costs compared to posting full transaction data to Ethereum as calldata.</p>



<p>With its focus on NFT and gaming applications, Immutable X is poised to make a significant impact on Ethereum&#8217;s scalability, driving innovation and fostering growth within the web3 gaming ecosystem. As the platform continues to expand its capabilities and integration, it is expected to attract further attention from developers and users alike.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-1024x576.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-1024x576.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205136" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-1024x576.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-300x169.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-768x432.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-750x422.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596-1140x641.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1596.png 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 16"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Scroll</h2>



<p>Scroll is making waves in the blockchain space as a layer 2 solution built on zkEVM Equivalence technology, an innovative ZK-Rollup technology fully compatible with EVM. Developed in early 2021, zkEVM addresses the limitations of existing Zk-Rollup solutions, which often lack code consistency and hinder the seamless movement of DApps between layers 1 and 2.</p>



<p>Traditional zk-Rollup implementations have posed challenges for developers, leading to difficulty in building DApps and limited functionality. Scroll recognized the need for a user-friendly and more versatile solution, prompting the adoption of zkEVM to enhance the product development experience for developers.</p>



<p>By integrating zkEVM, Scroll strengthens layer 2 composability, unifying programming methods and facilitating the smooth migration of Ethereum DApps to the zk-Rollup chain without the need for extensive source code modifications.</p>



<p>The structure of Scroll revolves around three key components:</p>



<ul>
<li>Scroll Node: Responsible for transmitting transactions from L2 to L1, ensuring seamless communication between the layers.</li>



<li>Roller Network: Empowered with the capability to generate valid zkEVM proofs, ensuring the proper execution of transactions.</li>



<li>Rollup and Bridge Contracts: These essential components serve as data sources for Scroll transactions, verifying zkEVM validity, and enabling smooth asset transfers between Ethereum and Scroll.</li>
</ul>



<p>Scroll&#8217;s workflow involves the creation, validation, and completion of information blocks in chronological order on L2. Sequencers within the Scroll Node work diligently to establish contiguous blockchains.</p>



<p>The crucial information and proof of authenticity are subsequently sent to smart contracts for approval, undergoing the stages of Precommitted, Committed, and Finalized before being officially recorded on the Scroll blockchain.</p>



<p>By leveraging zkEVM Equivalence technology, Scroll aims to provide developers with a seamless and efficient environment for building DApps, fostering layer 2 composability, and enhancing the overall user experience. With its user-centric approach and compatibility with Ethereum, Scroll is well-positioned to drive innovation and growth in the blockchain industry.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-1024x512.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-1024x512.png" alt="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023" class="wp-image-205137" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-2048x1024.png 2048w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1597-1140x570.png 1140w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Top 6 Outstanding Zero-knowledge Proof Projects In 2023 17"></a></figure></div>


<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em>`</p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205130-zero-knowledge-proof-projects-in-2023/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1599-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weekly Top Crypto News (July 17 – July 23)</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205099-weekly-top-crypto-news-july-17-july-23/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Recap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EthCC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[highlight]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mantle Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The past week witnessed a thrilling wave of innovations across the crypto market, leaving many enthusiasts astir with excitement.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205099-weekly-top-crypto-news-july-17-july-23/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The past week witnessed a thrilling wave of innovations across the crypto market, leaving many enthusiasts astir with excitement. Amid this surge of developments, the Ethereum community&#8217;s EthCC conference stood out as a focal point for major players to reveal groundbreaking updates in the realms of DeFi and layer-2 initiatives.</strong> <strong>Here, let&#8217;s review this week&#8217;s top crypto news with <a href="https://twitter.com/Coincuofficial" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coincu</a>!</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="512" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-1024x512.png" alt="Weekly Top Crypto News (July 17 – July 23)" class="wp-image-205127" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-1024x512.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-300x150.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-768x384.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-1536x768.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-360x180.png 360w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-750x375.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590-1140x570.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1590.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Weekly Top Crypto News (July 17 – July 23) 18"></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">SEC Adds BlackRock, Fidelity &amp; 6 Other Spot Bitcoin ETF Applicants To The Federal Register</h2>



<p>SEC now registers BlackRock, Fidelity, and six other companies&#8217; Bitcoin ETF applications. Countdown begins for the SEC decision on approving or rejecting these applications. Market surveillance and investor protection standards key factors in SEC&#8217;s evaluation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="vBPFCk7R5K"><a href="https://coincu.com/204120-sec-adds-spot-bitcoin-etf-to-federal-register/">SEC Adds BlackRock, Fidelity &amp; 6 Other Spot Bitcoin ETF Applicants To The Federal Register</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;SEC Adds BlackRock, Fidelity &amp; 6 Other Spot Bitcoin ETF Applicants To The Federal Register&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204120-sec-adds-spot-bitcoin-etf-to-federal-register/embed/#?secret=LABNa9LLeY#?secret=vBPFCk7R5K" data-secret="vBPFCk7R5K" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Binance’s Arkham Launchpad Trials Price Limit To Protect Users From Volatility</h2>



<p>Binance Launchpad is releasing a new token called Arkham (ARKM). The token sale will last for 24 hours starting from July 17, 2023, 06:00 (UTC). Users can subscribe to BNB at any time during these 24 hours and commit their BNB based on their past six-day average BNB holdings.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="6fp6Nr7bR0"><a href="https://coincu.com/203289-binances-arkham-launchpad-trials-price-limit/">Binance&#8217;s Arkham Launchpad Trials Price Limit To Protect Users From Volatility</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Binance&#8217;s Arkham Launchpad Trials Price Limit To Protect Users From Volatility&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203289-binances-arkham-launchpad-trials-price-limit/embed/#?secret=MAlsD0040h#?secret=6fp6Nr7bR0" data-secret="6fp6Nr7bR0" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Vitalik Buterin Envisions Future of Crypto Wallets: Account Abstraction Revolution</h2>



<p>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin envisions a shift from traditional wallets to smart contract-based wallets for simplified management of digital assets. Smart contract wallets offer enhanced security and user experience with customizable access controls and advanced security features like multi-factor authentication. Buterin highlights the importance of community collaboration and continuous research to address scalability and security concerns for widespread adoption.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="i998Nmunpz"><a href="https://coincu.com/203815-vitalik-buterin-envisions-future-crypto-wallets/">Vitalik Buterin Envisions Future of Crypto Wallets: Account Abstraction Revolution</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Vitalik Buterin Envisions Future of Crypto Wallets: Account Abstraction Revolution&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203815-vitalik-buterin-envisions-future-crypto-wallets/embed/#?secret=GGB7dNT1fS#?secret=i998Nmunpz" data-secret="i998Nmunpz" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Layer 2 Mantle Network Officially Launched Its Mainnet Alpha</h2>



<p>Mantle Network launches mainnet alpha, an Ethereum Layer 2 solution. Modular architecture and Optimistic Rollup design enable high performance and low costs. Backed by BitDAO, Mantle supports dApp development on Ethereum Layer 2.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="c0N85UFgfZ"><a href="https://coincu.com/203354-mantle-network-launched-its-mainnet-alpha/">Layer 2 Mantle Network Officially Launched Its Mainnet Alpha</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Layer 2 Mantle Network Officially Launched Its Mainnet Alpha&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203354-mantle-network-launched-its-mainnet-alpha/embed/#?secret=rOETU5LaYJ#?secret=c0N85UFgfZ" data-secret="c0N85UFgfZ" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Lens Protocol Announces V2 Release With Web3 Experience Supports</h2>



<p>Lens Protocol introduces V2 release, bringing greater control and flexibility to developers and integrators. Open Actions enable external smart contract actions on Lens publications, including cross-chain actions with oracle support. V2 features enhanced composability, improved profile security and introduces native Quoted Publications for increased engagement.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="AYayV9UvFa"><a href="https://coincu.com/203388-lens-protocol-announces-v2-release/">Lens Protocol Announces V2 Release With Web3 Experience Supports</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Lens Protocol Announces V2 Release With Web3 Experience Supports&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203388-lens-protocol-announces-v2-release/embed/#?secret=ZfzvpPntnD#?secret=AYayV9UvFa" data-secret="AYayV9UvFa" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">UniswapX Launches: Empowering Traders with Next-Level Cross-AMM Capabilities</h2>



<p>Uniswap launches “UniswapX” – a new blockchain protocol for trading across automated market makers and liquidity sources. Features include “better prices” by aggregating liquidity sources, gas-free swapping, protection against MEV, and no cost for failed transactions. UniswapX will expand to gas-free cross-chain swaps in the coming months. Fillers cover gas fees, fostering a competitive environment for achieving the most favorable price.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="PFKmYbNeAO"><a href="https://coincu.com/203440-uniswapx-launches-empowering-traders/">UniswapX Launches: Empowering Traders with Next-Level Cross-AMM Capabilities</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;UniswapX Launches: Empowering Traders with Next-Level Cross-AMM Capabilities&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203440-uniswapx-launches-empowering-traders/embed/#?secret=UggR6t4PUH#?secret=PFKmYbNeAO" data-secret="PFKmYbNeAO" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Chainlink&#8217;s New Protocol Is Now Live For Seamless Blockchain Interaction</h2>



<p>Chainlink&#8217;s Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP) goes live on multiple blockchains. CCIP enables decentralized finance protocols and SWIFT connectivity for international transfers. The protocol also offers simplified token transfers and an ARM Network for added security.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="fYSL2vaM59"><a href="https://coincu.com/203471-chainlink-new-protocol-is-now-live/">Chainlink&#8217;s New Protocol Is Now Live For Seamless Blockchain Interaction</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Chainlink&#8217;s New Protocol Is Now Live For Seamless Blockchain Interaction&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203471-chainlink-new-protocol-is-now-live/embed/#?secret=UBIpBTxSJt#?secret=fYSL2vaM59" data-secret="fYSL2vaM59" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Neon EVM Now Supports Ethereum Applications On Solana Blockchain</h2>



<p>Neon Labs has launched the Neon EVM, allowing developers to write Ethereum applications on the Solana blockchain. Neon EVM enables the deployment of Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) code on Solana, bridging the gap between Ethereum and Solana&#8217;s computing models. This integration offers cost-effectiveness and efficiency by leveraging Solana&#8217;s high throughput capabilities, reducing transaction costs for Ethereum dApps.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="u9E7NDkgxe"><a href="https://coincu.com/203512-neon-evm-now-supports-ethereum-on-solana/">Neon EVM Now Supports Ethereum Applications On Solana Blockchain</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Neon EVM Now Supports Ethereum Applications On Solana Blockchain&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/203512-neon-evm-now-supports-ethereum-on-solana/embed/#?secret=r0NCOvTarJ#?secret=u9E7NDkgxe" data-secret="u9E7NDkgxe" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Starknet Unveils Starknet Appchains: Enhanced Performance And Customizability For Developers</h2>



<p>Starknet launches Starknet Appchains, enabling developers to leverage the performance and customization benefits of the Starknet Stack, resulting in enhanced throughput and a tailored user experience. The use of the decentralized rollup stack and the Cairo programming language empowers developers on Starknet to create secure and scalable applications, attracting top talent and opening up new possibilities for innovation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="KYzBwNvHx1"><a href="https://coincu.com/204036-starknet-starknet-appchains-performance/">Starknet Unveils Starknet Appchains: Enhanced Performance And Customizability For Developers</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Starknet Unveils Starknet Appchains: Enhanced Performance And Customizability For Developers&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204036-starknet-starknet-appchains-performance/embed/#?secret=Q75alDUX1Y#?secret=KYzBwNvHx1" data-secret="KYzBwNvHx1" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Coinbase&#8217;s Layer 2 Base To Embrace Decentralization With Optimism&#8217;s Drive</h2>



<p>Coinbase&#8217;s Base to adopt Optimism&#8217;s open neutrality framework for decentralization. Framework principles focus on maintaining decentralization in networks. Base&#8217;s main network launch in August, grants for builders, and participation in a virtual hackathon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="rXJcnylFOl"><a href="https://coincu.com/204074-coinbases-base-optimisms-drive/">Coinbase&#8217;s Layer 2 Base To Embrace Decentralization With Optimism&#8217;s Drive</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Coinbase&#8217;s Layer 2 Base To Embrace Decentralization With Optimism&#8217;s Drive&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204074-coinbases-base-optimisms-drive/embed/#?secret=8VOFoR9orP#?secret=rXJcnylFOl" data-secret="rXJcnylFOl" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Wormhole Launches Groundbreaking Gateway For Seamless Cosmos Application Chain Integration</h2>



<p>Wormhole launches the first bridge connecting over 20 blockchains to any Cosmos application chain, promoting liquidity growth in the Cosmos ecosystem. The Wormhole Gateway allows easy token integration and fee-free fund bridging, enhancing blockchain interoperability and user experience within the Cosmos network.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="rqPWtU7y36"><a href="https://coincu.com/204736-wormhole-gateway-seamless-cosmos-chain/">Wormhole Launches Groundbreaking Gateway For Seamless Cosmos Application Chain Integration</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Wormhole Launches Groundbreaking Gateway For Seamless Cosmos Application Chain Integration&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204736-wormhole-gateway-seamless-cosmos-chain/embed/#?secret=XLcP9IbFDb#?secret=rqPWtU7y36" data-secret="rqPWtU7y36" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Optimism To Launch ZKPs To Boost Cross-Chain Communication</h2>



<p>Optimism is adding zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) to enable secure and efficient cross-chain communication between its Layer 2 solution and Ethereum. The ZKPs will be provided by O(1) Labs and RISC Zero, enhancing security and reducing latency in the network. Optimism aims to improve its ecosystem&#8217;s performance and compatibility with existing systems, paving the way for more accessible development using Solidity and EVM.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="MwJ9IDcGjW"><a href="https://coincu.com/204801-optimism-to-launch-zkps/">Optimism To Launch ZKPs To Boost Cross-Chain Communication</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Optimism To Launch ZKPs To Boost Cross-Chain Communication&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204801-optimism-to-launch-zkps/embed/#?secret=Bi6ErNZD1u#?secret=MwJ9IDcGjW" data-secret="MwJ9IDcGjW" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Polygon Introduces Exclusive NFTs To Celebrate The Launch Of Polygon 2.0</h2>



<p>Polygon and Suku release exclusive NFT to celebrate Polygon 2.0 launch. The upgrade aims to enhance network functionality and governance. This move highlights Polygon&#8217;s significant growth and development.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="kCKcsyKB3y"><a href="https://coincu.com/204206-polygon-introduces-open-edition-nft/">Polygon Introduces Exclusive NFTs To Celebrate The Launch Of Polygon 2.0</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Polygon Introduces Exclusive NFTs To Celebrate The Launch Of Polygon 2.0&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204206-polygon-introduces-open-edition-nft/embed/#?secret=JASoHIqbHZ#?secret=kCKcsyKB3y" data-secret="kCKcsyKB3y" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-luminous-vivid-orange-color has-text-color">Worldcoin Makes Strides In Scaling Web3 On The Optimism Superchain</h2>



<p>Worldcoin has completed the migration of its World ID and World App technology stack to the OP Mainnet, enabling inclusive and open identity primitives for anyone on the Superchain and beyond. The migration has strengthened the capabilities of Optimism’s Citizens’ House and AttestationStation, enabling a robust web of trust on any OP Chain in the Superchain.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-wp-embed is-provider-coincu-news wp-block-embed-coincu-news"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="gQT13eUyeJ"><a href="https://coincu.com/204461-worldcoin-makes-strides-in-scaling-web3-optimism/">Worldcoin Makes Strides In Scaling Web3 On The Optimism Superchain</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" title="&#8220;Worldcoin Makes Strides In Scaling Web3 On The Optimism Superchain&#8221; &#8212; CoinCu News" src="https://coincu.com/204461-worldcoin-makes-strides-in-scaling-web3-optimism/embed/#?secret=MDo1p0i85j#?secret=gQT13eUyeJ" data-secret="gQT13eUyeJ" width="500" height="282" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205099-weekly-top-crypto-news-july-17-july-23/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1591-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Empowers Users with Enhanced STMX Contract Features Amid Volatility</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205110-binance-stmx-contract-features-amid-volatility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205110</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On July 23, leading cryptocurrency exchange Binance made significant updates to its STMXUSDT U-margined perpetual contract leverage and margin ladder, aiming to bolster risk management and user protection. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205110-binance-stmx-contract-features-amid-volatility/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Binance temporarily adjusts STMX U-margined perpetual contract features for enhanced risk management, following significant price fluctuations of the STMX digital asset.</em></li>



<li><em>Changes include updates to leverage, margin ladder, and funding rate settlement frequency to provide users with greater control and protection during volatile market conditions.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>On July 23, leading cryptocurrency exchange Binance made significant updates to its STMXUSDT U-margined perpetual contract leverage and margin ladder, aiming to bolster risk management and user protection.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-1-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="315" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-1-1.jpeg" alt="Binance Empowers Users with Enhanced STMX Contract Features Amid Volatility" class="wp-image-205112" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-1-1.jpeg 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-1-1-300x158.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="Binance Empowers Users with Enhanced STMX Contract Features Amid Volatility 19"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The changes, which took effect at 15:15 on July 23 (Eastern Eighth District Time), will impact users&#8217; existing positions, prompting them to review the updated leverage and margin ladder to ensure their margins align with the new settings and avoid potential forced liquidation.</p>



<p>The move comes after STMX, a digital asset, experienced volatile price fluctuations, with a staggering 30% drop within a mere half-hour and an overall decline of approximately 45% from its recent peak. These abrupt price changes raised concerns as some users faced challenges closing their positions at market prices during contract transactions amidst the STMX price swings.</p>



<p>To address such concerns and protect traders from sudden market movements, Binance took proactive measures to adjust the STMX U-margined perpetual contract features. By optimizing the leverage and margin ladder, the exchange aims to offer users greater flexibility and control over their positions, enabling them to make informed decisions aligned with their risk appetite.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-1024x576.jpeg" alt="Binance Empowers Users with Enhanced STMX Contract Features Amid Volatility" class="wp-image-205113" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-1536x864.jpeg 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-750x422.jpeg 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd-1140x641.jpeg 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin-44000-dolari-asarken-binance-coktu-iste-son-durum-Kmub4ugd.jpeg 1590w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Binance Empowers Users with Enhanced STMX Contract Features Amid Volatility 20"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>In addition to the leverage and margin adjustments, <a href="https://coincu.com/204647-binances-h1-2023-report-crypto-market/">Binance</a> Futures also modified the settlement frequency of the STMX U-margined perpetual contract funding rate. The funding rate settlement frequency, which was previously every eight hours, has been increased to every two hours. This alteration ensures more frequent updates and real-time adjustments, enabling traders to respond more effectively to changes in market conditions and funding rates.</p>



<p>By fine-tuning the STMX U-margined perpetual contract and introducing these updates, Binance seeks to provide a safer and more stable trading environment for its users. The exchange acknowledges the importance of risk management and strives to enhance user experience, particularly during periods of heightened market volatility.</p>



<p>Traders and investors using Binance&#8217;s platform are encouraged to stay informed about such updates and adjust their trading strategies accordingly. The exchange remains committed to ensuring transparency and open communication with its users, fostering a thriving and secure cryptocurrency trading ecosystem.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205110-binance-stmx-contract-features-amid-volatility/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Copy-of-Final-Thumb-5-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-XRP Lawyer Assures That SEC&#8217;s Appeal Won&#8217;t Affect XRP Holders</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205100-pro-xrp-secs-appeal-wont-affect-xrp-holders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chubbi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 07:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[# Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Securities and Exchange Commission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Attorney John Deaton, who represents over 75,000 XRP token holders, has clarified that even if the SEC decides to appeal, it would not have a significant impact on XRP holders. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205100-pro-xrp-secs-appeal-wont-affect-xrp-holders/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Pro-XRP lawyer assures XRP holders that SEC&#8217;s potential appeal won&#8217;t significantly impact them.</em></li>



<li><em>Judge Torres&#8217; ruling clarifies XRP&#8217;s non-security classification, prompting discussions on regulatory status for institutional sales.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Attorney John Deaton, who represents over 75,000 XRP token holders, has clarified that even if the SEC decides to appeal, it would not have a significant impact on XRP holders.&nbsp;</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SEC-Ripple-XRP-Lawsuit-Could-Change-Crypto-1024x576-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SEC-Ripple-XRP-Lawsuit-Could-Change-Crypto-1024x576-1.jpeg" alt="Pro-XRP Lawyer Assures That SEC&#039;s Appeal Won&#039;t Affect XRP Holders" class="wp-image-205102" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SEC-Ripple-XRP-Lawsuit-Could-Change-Crypto-1024x576-1.jpeg 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SEC-Ripple-XRP-Lawsuit-Could-Change-Crypto-1024x576-1-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SEC-Ripple-XRP-Lawsuit-Could-Change-Crypto-1024x576-1-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/SEC-Ripple-XRP-Lawsuit-Could-Change-Crypto-1024x576-1-750x422.jpeg 750w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Pro-XRP Lawyer Assures That SEC&#039;s Appeal Won&#039;t Affect XRP Holders 21"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>This comes amid widespread rumors that an SEC appeal could have a negative influence on the cryptocurrency market. The judge&#8217;s finding that XRP should not be classified as a security raises issues about the possible legal ramifications that could follow if the SEC decides to appeal. Deaton provides additional information regarding the various possibilities and estimates that the decision regarding the appeal might take up to two years, with the Summary Judgment continuing to be in place during this time.</p>



<p>Following Terraform Labs CEO Do Kwon&#8217;s aim to use it as a precedent to argue against the classification of digital assets as securities, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has indicated in its filing that they intend to reconsider the decision that was made in the Ripple dispute. Despite the fact that the outcome of the appeal is still undetermined, Deaton&#8217;s positive comments highlight the significance of the victory for XRP and those who possess it.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-3.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="600" height="315" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-3.jpeg" alt="Pro-XRP Lawyer Assures That SEC&#039;s Appeal Won&#039;t Affect XRP Holders" class="wp-image-205103" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-3.jpeg 600w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/timthumb-3-300x158.jpeg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" title="Pro-XRP Lawyer Assures That SEC&#039;s Appeal Won&#039;t Affect XRP Holders 22"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Ripple&#8217;s chief legal officer, Stuart Alderoty, has weighed in on the SEC&#8217;s jurisdiction, saying that the agency&#8217;s authority is restricted to matters pertaining to securities. Tokens that are not securities, like <a href="https://coincu.com/204894-us-sec-signals-appeal-court-ripple-xrp-case/">XRP</a>, should not be subject to regulation by the SEC. Claiming jurisdiction where it does not exist is nothing more than a political power play that will have negative repercussions for everyone concerned.</p>



<p>The decision made by Judge Torres makes it quite clear that the only type of sale of the token that does not involve securities is the retail sale. This opens the door for further debate on the regulatory status of institutional sales. Deaton is still optimistic, despite the possibility of an appeal, that it will not alter the beneficial conclusion for those who possess XRP and for Ripple.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The Information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>



<p>Join us to keep track of news: <a href="https://linktr.ee/coincu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://linktr.ee/coincu</a></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Chubbi</strong></p>



<p class="has-text-align-right"><strong>Coincu News</strong></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205100-pro-xrp-secs-appeal-wont-affect-xrp-holders/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Copy-of-Final-Thumb-4-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ParaSpace Navigates Asset Liquidation Crisis And Compensation To Users</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205075-paraspace-swift-action-on-asset/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Harold]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft lending]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ParaSpace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205075</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ParaSpace addressed asset liquidations that affected some users between July 3 and July 4.<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205075-paraspace-swift-action-on-asset/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>ParaSpace addressed asset liquidations that affected some users between July 3 and July 4.</em></li>



<li><em>The platform promptly reimbursed the affected users for the price difference resulting from the liquidations.</em></li>



<li><em>ParaSpace plans to host an event for affected users to provide clarity and remains committed to improving the platform for a user-friendly ecosystem.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ParaSpace, a decentralized NFT lending protocol, recently <a href="https://twitter.com/ParaSpace_NFT/status/1682957087196975104" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">addressed</a> an issue related to asset liquidations that <a href="https://coincu.com/199951-paraspace-temporarily-suspend-azukis-pool/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">occurred</a> between July 3 and July 4.</strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="538" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-1024x538.png" alt="ParaSpace: Swift Action on Asset Liquidation, Users Reimbursed" class="wp-image-205091" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-1024x538.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-300x157.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-768x403.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-1536x806.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-750x394.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587-1140x598.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1587.png 1686w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ParaSpace Navigates Asset Liquidation Crisis And Compensation To Users 23"></a></figure></div>


<p>A small number of users were affected when their assets were liquidated at prices below the floor price. The incident was a result of dutch auctions running on the backend without displaying the auctioned assets on the front end. ParaSpace promptly took action to rectify the situation and reimburse the affected users.</p>



<p>In response to the incident, ParaSpace&#8217;s team contacted each of the affected users to ensure open communication and resolve the matter promptly. The platform successfully reimbursed them for the price difference resulting from the liquidations.</p>



<p>The unexpected liquidations occurred as a consequence of successful purchases of NFTs during the dutch auctions. These successful purchases terminated the ongoing auctions, leading to prices dropping to the lower end of the auction range. Consequently, some purchases were made under the floor price, resulting in a discrepancy between the sale price and the actual floor price.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-1024x1024.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="1024" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-1024x1024.png" alt="ParaSpace: Swift Action on Asset Liquidation, Users Reimbursed" class="wp-image-205092" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-1024x1024.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-300x300.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-150x150.png 150w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-768x768.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-75x75.png 75w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-350x350.png 350w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-750x750.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588-1140x1140.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1588.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="ParaSpace Navigates Asset Liquidation Crisis And Compensation To Users 24"></a></figure></div>


<p><a href="https://coincu.com/200128-paraspace-azuki-airdrop-elementals-on-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ParaSpace</a> acknowledged the impact this event had on the affected users and prioritized their compensation. With transparency and accountability as core principles, ParaSpace demonstrated its commitment to its community members.</p>



<p>To further address the situation and provide clarity, ParaSpace will be hosting a space on Monday where some of the affected users will have the opportunity to share their experiences and receive more information about the incident. During the space event, ParaSpace&#8217;s team will also shed light on their mission for the platform and outline their future plans.</p>



<p>ParaSpace is dedicated to creating a secure and user-friendly ecosystem for its users. The incident served as a valuable learning experience for the platform, prompting further improvements in its smart contract mechanisms and auction processes to prevent similar occurrences in the future.</p>



<p>The platform is gearing up to <a href="https://coincu.com/202259-paraspace-upcoming-critical-upgrade-2-0/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">launch</a> Version 2.0, bringing significant upgrades to the future of lending. This user-friendly platform aims to empower the web3 community with seamless and powerful borrowing options. Excitement is building as the launch date approaches, marking a new milestone in decentralized finance.</p>



<p><strong><em>DISCLAIMER: </em></strong><em>The information on this website is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205075-paraspace-swift-action-on-asset/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1589-1024x731.png" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/png" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App</title>
		<link>https://coincu.com/205085-aptos-active-accounts-surge-to-182000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Annie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 06:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[APT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media App]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coincu.com/?p=205085</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Aptos, a blockchain-based platform, experienced a remarkable surge in active accounts, reaching a record-high of 182,000 since the APT airdrop. <p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205085-aptos-active-accounts-surge-to-182000/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li><em>Aptos, a blockchain-based platform, experienced a remarkable surge in active accounts, reaching a record-high of 182,000 since the APT airdrop.</em></li>



<li><em>The integration with Chingari, a popular social media app in India, has added virtual gifting capabilities within the Aptos ecosystem, incentivizing active participation and driving interest in the crypto community.</em></li>



<li><em>Virtual gifting has emerged as a powerful and rewarding method for content creators and influencers to monetize their online presence, with blockchain technology ensuring transparency and traceability in the process.</em></li>
</ul>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Aptos, a blockchain-based platform, experienced a remarkable surge in active accounts, reaching a record-high of 182,000 since the APT airdrop. </strong></h5>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="248" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-1024x248.png" alt="Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App" class="wp-image-205087" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-1024x248.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-300x73.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-768x186.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-1536x373.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-750x182.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583-1140x277.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1583.png 1880w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App 25"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>The surge in users coincides with the recent integration of <a href="https://analytics.aptscan.ai/public/dashboards/ie5Gu6NerkaezgQiImQ01AL6cc9DGiDbRKaQUbxp?org_slug=default" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://analytics.aptscan.ai/public/dashboards/ie5Gu6NerkaezgQiImQ01AL6cc9DGiDbRKaQUbxp?org_slug=default" rel="noreferrer noopener">Chingari</a>, a popular social media app in India, which now offers exciting new functionalities like virtual gifting within the Aptos ecosystem.</p>



<p>The integration with Chingari has been a game-changer for Aptos, attracting a staggering number of new users in the past two days, with over 94,000 new accounts created. The addition of virtual gifting capabilities within the platform has added a novel and engaging dimension to the user experience, incentivizing active participation and driving interest in the crypto community.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="317" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-1024x317.png" alt="Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App" class="wp-image-205088" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-1024x317.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-300x93.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-768x238.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-1536x475.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-750x232.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584-1140x353.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1584.png 1851w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App 26"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Chingari, known for its unique features and widespread popularity in the Indian social media landscape, has significantly contributed to Aptos&#8217; recent growth. By joining forces with the blockchain-based platform, Chingari users now have access to a seamless and secure way of exchanging virtual gifts using Aptos&#8217; native token, APT.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><a href="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585.png"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="477" src="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-1024x477.png" alt="Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App" class="wp-image-205089" srcset="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-1024x477.png 1024w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-300x140.png 300w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-768x358.png 768w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-1536x716.png 1536w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-750x350.png 750w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585-1140x531.png 1140w, https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image-1585.png 1884w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" title="Aptos Active Accounts Surge to 182,000 Following Integration with Chingari Social Media App 27"></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"> </figcaption></figure></div>


<p>Virtual gifting has emerged as a powerful and rewarding method for content creators and influencers to monetize their online presence, as fans and followers can now support their favorite creators directly through the gifting feature. With blockchain technology underlying the entire process, transparency and traceability are ensured, adding a layer of trust and accountability to the virtual gifting ecosystem.</p>



<p>The success of Aptos&#8217; integration with Chingari underscores the potential of blockchain technology to revolutionize social media and digital content platforms. By leveraging the power of cryptocurrencies, platforms like Aptos can foster vibrant communities while empowering creators to monetize their content and interact more meaningfully with their audiences.</p>



<p id="block-643c4ba8-b40b-4525-9a96-f280dbfbeb9d"><strong><em>DISCLAIMER:&nbsp;</em></strong><em>The Information on this&nbsp;website&nbsp;is provided as general market commentary and does not constitute investment advice. We encourage you to do your own research before investing.</em></p>
<p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com/205085-aptos-active-accounts-surge-to-182000/" target="_blank">Read more...</a></p><p class="has-text-align-right"><a href="https://coincu.com"><strong>Coincu News</strong></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://coincu.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Aptos-Active-Accounts-Surge-to-182000-1024x731.jpg" width="1024" height="731" medium="image" type="image/jpeg" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
