<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:45:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canadian RCMP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[тае]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266657</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
<p>While the primary focus is on cryptocurrencies, the RCMP acknowledges the importance of including NFTs in its approach.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
<p>In Canada, the Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) and Shared Services Canada (SSC) are collaborating to develop a groundbreaking digital asset solution aimed at streamlining the seizure and storage of crypto and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Tokens</a> (NFTs) from multiple public blockchains.</p>
<p>On August 10, the RCMP <a href="https://ised-isde.canada.ca/site/innovative-solutions-canada/en/digital-asset-repository" target="_blank" rel="noopener">opened</a> a tender inviting applications from technology providers capable of developing a centralized repository solution. This move marks a significant stride in adapting law enforcement methods to the evolving digital era.</p>
<h2>The Essential Features of the Crypto Storage Solution</h2>
<p>The tender released by the RCMP outlines a comprehensive list of seventeen key features they seek from the future repository solution. Among these requirements is the capability to process transactions for the top 20 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization.</p>
<p>This demonstrates a forward-thinking approach, ensuring that the RCMP’s solution remains relevant as the crypto landscape evolves. Recognizing the ever-evolving nature of the digital asset landscape, the RCMP said the solution must not only onboard existing blockchains but also accommodate new ones that may emerge over time.</p>
<p>An equally significant aspect of this initiative is accessibility. The RCMP intends to grant authorized users access to the repository&#8217;s data, enabling efficient collaboration between law enforcement agencies and other stakeholders. Such accessibility could potentially enhance the effectiveness of investigations and asset recovery processes.</p>
<p>While the primary focus is on cryptocurrencies, the RCMP acknowledges the importance of including NFTs in its approach. Consequently, the repository is expected to handle NFTs created on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH), Solana (SOL), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Polygon</a> (MATIC). This emphasizes the adaptability of the system under consideration and its ability to accommodate various digital asset types.</p>
<p>Other features in the repository include transaction logging, robust security measures, automated verification, and a Web interface.</p>
<h2>The Changing Landscape in Crypto Fraud</h2>
<p>The RCMP’s recent pursuit of a secure digital asset solution is a proactive response to the surge in criminal activities involving cryptocurrencies and NFTs. The rise of cryptocurrencies has ushered in a new paradigm of financial transactions, with both legitimate and illicit applications being recorded.</p>
<p>While cryptocurrencies provide greater privacy and protection for legitimate users, it have also become a favorite way for criminals to participate in activities such as ransomware attacks, internet scams, money laundering, and fraud.</p>
<p>This not only poses a threat to individual financial security but also undermines the integrity of financial systems and erodes public trust in digital assets. Recognizing the urgency of tackling this emerging challenge, the RCMP’s decision to seek an advanced digital asset solution marks a pivotal moment in law enforcement&#8217;s adaptation to the digital age.</p>
<p>Recently, Canadian law enforcement began employing specialist tools from Chainalysis to trace crypto while investigating cybercrime. Local police may now trace blockchain transactions, identify suspects, and discover where funds have been put.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/">Canada to Create Solutions for Storing Seized Crypto Assets</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/canada-storage-crypto-assets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
<p>Visa's solution revolves around Ethereum's ERC-4337 account abstraction standard and the utilization of a "paymaster" smart contract feature which allows off-chain settlements of gas fees. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, August 10, payments giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/visa-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Visa Inc</a> made an important announcement allowing users to pay the on-chain Ethereum gas fees directly in fiat currencies, either using a credit or debit card.</p>
<p>Visa said that it first conducted the test on the Ethereum Goerli testnet by using a paymaster contract in order to sponsor gas fees on behalf of users. Thus, users can send blockchain transactions without having to worry about maintaining an ETH balance. As per Visa, the contracts would make transactions accessible to a wide range of users. Commenting on the development, Visa’s technical team <a href="https://usa.visa.com/solutions/crypto/paying-blockchain-gas-fees-with-card.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our experiment aims to offer a promising approach to substantially addressing the challenges of blockchain-based transactions. By leveraging the innovative concept of a paymaster, in conjunction with account abstraction and the ERC-4337 standard, we explored the potential for a process that could redefine blockchain-based transactions.”</p></blockquote>
<p>A paymaster contract is a specialized variant of a smart contract in the blockchain ecosystem, intended for overseeing the settlement of gas fees.</p>
<p>The company has proposed that merchants or decentralized applications (Dapps) have the option to implement their own paymaster solution. Alternatively, established wallet and paymaster service providers could present a gas fee payment option using cards in conjunction with their existing paymaster services.</p>
<p>This initiative is a continuation of Visa&#8217;s ongoing efforts in the field. The company has been actively exploring methods to enhance the user-friendliness and accessibility of blockchain-based payments. At the beginning of 2023, Visa started converting digital assets into fiat payments on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<h2>Using Visa Card Payment for Gas Fee</h2>
<p>In the usual Ethereum usage process, individuals acquire <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETH</a> through exchanges or on-ramp services. Then, they transfer the acquired ETH to their wallets to ensure they have enough to cover fluctuating gas fees. However, this dynamic gas pricing often leads to situations of overpayment or insufficient ETH supply, introducing complexity and challenges.</p>
<p>Visa&#8217;s solution revolves around Ethereum&#8217;s ERC-4337 account abstraction standard and the utilization of a &#8220;paymaster&#8221; smart contract feature. This approach enables off-chain settlements of gas fees. The five-step sequence is as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>A user initiates an Ethereum transaction using their wallet, which forwards the transaction details to the paymaster web service.</li>
<li>The web service calculates the gas fee&#8217;s cost and charges the user&#8217;s Visa card using Visa&#8217;s Cybersource system for payment processing.</li>
<li>Once completed, the web service sends a digital signature back to the wallet, validating the payment. This validation is effective within a specified timeframe.</li>
<li>The wallet attaches this signature to the transaction and submits it to the Ethereum network.</li>
<li>The paymaster smart contract then verifies the signature&#8217;s authenticity and covers the gas fee, facilitating the transaction processing.</li>
</ol>
<p>This series of actions enables users to pay gas fees using their Visa card off-chain. It also eliminates the necessity to hold ETH solely for fee payments. This approach greatly streamlines the user experience, enhancing the convenience of transactions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/">VISA Allows Users to Pay Ethereum Gas Fees via Credit Card</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/visa-ethereum-gas-fees/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Commodities & Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
<p>Analysts and stakeholders expect gold prices to rise as the year runs out because of macroeconomic factors and recession risks.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
<p>There is a general bullishness around gold prices as the yellow metal is on course to an all-time high in 2024. Analysts believe that the new record is likely because of economic uncertainty which indicates a possible recession, and a potential reduction in interest rates.</p>
<p>According to TD Securities’ managing director and global head of commodity strategy Bart Melek, gold will likely hit $2,100 as 2023 ends or early in 2024. Melek believes that a softened stance towards continuously increasing interest rates would be bullish for the yellow metal. Melek is also bullish because gold has performed better than most other assets over the last 12 months.</p>
<p>Generally, many people consider gold a safe haven asset and are likely to buy more in times of economic instability. According to a CME Group <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/openmarkets/metals/2023/How-Does-Gold-Perform-with-Inflation-Stagflation-and-Recession.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, gold performed about 37% better than the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a> in six of the last eight recessions. This suggests that gold is likely to soar higher in the event of an official recession.</p>
<p>Another stakeholder believes gold will hit $2,500 in a “couple of years”. According to Randy Smallwood, the CEO of Canadian company Wheaten Precious Metals, a recession would be good for gold. Smallwood is bullish because he expects some drawbacks in the economies of both the US and China.</p>
<p>More bullish predictions continue to pour in for gold. One indicator of a rise in spot prices is the inverse relationship between gold and interest rates. When interest rates increase, people tend to move away from gold to other more attractive investment assets like bonds. This eventually reduces the demand for gold.</p>
<p>Gold is trading at $1,916 as of writing time.</p>
<h2>More Predictions for Gold Prices</h2>
<p>Singaporean banking giant UOB is also bullish on gold prices. According to the head of markets strategy, global economics, and markets research, Heng Koon How, the Fed will likely stop increasing interest rates soon:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Key driver in our positive outlook for gold is anticipated peak in Fed rate hiking cycle as well as upcoming topping out of US Dollar strength.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The UOB exec also predicted higher prices and that a strong demand for gold would come as people regain their economic spending power. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We also see a return of physical gold jewelry demand from China and India as both economies stabilize and retail spending returns.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent report, Citi noted that retail demand for gold from China has been buoyant especially compared to other goods. According to Citi&#8217;s head of commodities strategy Aakash Doshi in a report, gold demand from China was only slightly lower than 200 tons. Doshi notes that this the “strongest seasonal” seen since 2015. The report expects the demand to hit 700 tons by the end of the year. This project would confirm a 22% increase year on year.</p>
<p>Wheaton CEO Smallwood also stated that there is an increase in demand. According to him, customers are getting more gold in all forms, including coins, jewelry, and bars.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/">Gold Prices Expected to Hit $2,500 as Recession Fears Continue</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gold-prices-hit-2500-recession/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meme stock trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266636</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
<p>Robinhood had earlier motioned for the arguments against it to be completely dismissed.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
<p>The federal appeals court of the United States has yet again dismissed a class-action lawsuit against online brokerage firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Robinhood Markets</a>. This follows after 16 investors alleged that the platform did not allow them to buy 13 “meme stocks” during a January 2021 social media frenzy that sent prices to the moon.</p>
<p>According to the complainants, the restriction meant that they could not enjoy any profits. The decision also ended up causing the share prices of these stocks to plunge, they added.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the suit, which began in September 2021, only lasted for so long. By January 2022, Robinhood motioned for the complaint to be dismissed, and the court granted that request. In its motion at the time, the firm noted that the plaintiffs failed to state any claim.</p>
<p>Still doubtful about the earlier ruling in the Robinhood case, the plaintiffs then proceeded to the US appeals court in March 2023 to seek redress.</p>
<p>As it turns out, the investors may just have hit another setback. US Appellate Court Judge Britt Grant has <a href="https://www.courthousenews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Juncadelia-v-Robinhood-order-11th-circuit.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">upheld</a> the earlier ruling, claiming that the case lacks legal merit.</p>
<p>Judge Grant clarified that Robinhood, according to its customer agreement, is permitted to restrict any transaction. That is, the platform may decide whether or not to accept a trade offer.</p>
<h2>Is Robinhood Finally in the Clear?</h2>
<p>The court may have established that Robinhood had no hand in the arguments against it. But that is only for the time being.</p>
<p>The investors may decide to take the case up a notch by heading to the US Supreme Court, in what would be a final showdown. To do that, however, they must first file a petition for a “writ of certiorari”, which is a document asking the Supreme Court to review the case.</p>
<p>But out of over 7,000 cases that the Supreme Court reviews, it only takes up about 100-150 cases. Therefore, it is not very likely that the investors will have one more day in court over this case.</p>
<p>As of publication, lawyers from both ends – Robinhood and the plaintiffs, have yet to comment on the development.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/">Robinhood Beats Investors Again as Appeal Court Upholds Earlier Rule in Meme Stock Trading Suit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-investors-appeals-court/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huawei Reports 3% Revenue Growth and Widened Profit Margin in H1 2023 amidst Sanctions Challenges</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[donald trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huawei]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[huawei cloud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ict]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266624</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/">Huawei Reports 3% Revenue Growth and Widened Profit Margin in H1 2023 amidst Sanctions Challenges</a></p>
<p>Despite the US sanctions and the current economic situation in China, Huawei has continued to innovate and diversify.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/">Huawei Reports 3% Revenue Growth and Widened Profit Margin in H1 2023 amidst Sanctions Challenges</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/">Huawei Reports 3% Revenue Growth and Widened Profit Margin in H1 2023 amidst Sanctions Challenges</a></p>
<p>Chinese tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/huawei/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Huawei Technologies</a> has released its financial earnings report for the first half (H1) of 2023. The company announced a 3.1% rise in revenue, reaching 310.9 billion yuan ($43.1 billion) for the quarter. The revenue growth comes despite challenges posed by sanctions that have limited access to US processor chips and other technologies. In response to the restrictions severely impacting its smartphone business, Huawei has strategically shifted its focus towards supplying network gear to industries like hospitals, ports, and electric car manufacturers. The move is aimed at reducing vulnerability to sanctions.</p>
<p>The company revealed that its profit margin expanded to 15%, equivalent to approximately 45 billion yuan ($6.5 billion). The figure marks a notable increase from the 4.3% margin reported in the first quarter of the year.</p>
<h2>Huawei Gained $23.2B Revenue from Its Infrastructure Unit in H1 2023</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.huawei.com/en/news/2023/8/h1-business-results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the revenue generated by its ICT infrastructure business stood at 167.2 billion yuan ($23.2 billion), and its consumer sales reached 103.5 billion yuan ($14.3 billion).</p>
<p>Similarly, Huawei&#8217;s cloud <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-cloud-metaverse-web3-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">unit</a> saw a profit of CNY 24.1 billion, while its digital power business stood at CNY 24.2 billion. The firm&#8217;s fledgling automotive unit, responsible for supplying technology for electric cars, generated sales of 1 billion yuan ($138.6 billion).</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s chairwoman Sabrina Meng said the Chinese tech giant has been investing in foundational technology to provide value for customers.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;d like to thank our customers and partners for their ongoing support. I&#8217;d also like to thank the Huawei team for their solidarity and dedication. Huawei has been investing heavily in foundational technologies to harness trends in digitalization, intelligence, and decarbonization, focusing on creating value for our customers and partners,&#8221; said Meng.</p>
<p>Over the past few years, Huawei&#8217;s journey has been marked by resilience and adaptation. The company faced significant challenges after former US President <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/donald-trump/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Donald Trump</a> imposed sanctions restricting its access to US processor chips in 2019. Authorities cited security concerns and the company&#8217;s potential for facilitating Chinese espionage as reasons for the sanctions, which Huawei has consistently denied.</p>
<h2>Huawei Demonstrates Resilience Despite Economic Challenges in China</h2>
<p>Despite the US sanctions and the current economic situation in China, Huawei has continued to innovate and diversify. The company remains a dominant global player in the network equipment sector, serving as a significant supplier to phone and internet companies worldwide. While the firm sold its Honor smartphone brand in 2020, it continues to operate within the smartphone market, focusing primarily on its home market in China.</p>
<p>In 2022, the company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2022-huawei-biggest-annual-profit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> a 70% decline in profits to 35.6 billion yuan ($5.2 billion) but achieved a 0.9% increase in sales, reaching 642.3 billion yuan ($93.5 billion).</p>
<p>It is important to note that half of Huawei&#8217;s vast employee base of 207,000 individuals is dedicated to research and development. This emphasis on innovation has enabled the company to develop alternatives to US components, including breakthroughs in designing its processor chips.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/">Huawei Reports 3% Revenue Growth and Widened Profit Margin in H1 2023 amidst Sanctions Challenges</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/huawei-revenue-h1-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Currency Group (DCG) Files Motion to Dismiss Lawsuit by Gemini</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266613</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) Files Motion to Dismiss Lawsuit by Gemini</a></p>
<p>The DCG filing notes that Silbert and the company "played an insignificant role in the Gemini Earn program", and Gemini's allegations of fraudulent behavior don't hold merit.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) Files Motion to Dismiss Lawsuit by Gemini</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) Files Motion to Dismiss Lawsuit by Gemini</a></p>
<p>Venture capital giant Digital Currency Group (DCG) has recently filed a motion for dismissing a lawsuit from crypto exchange Gemini, alleging fraud to the users of its Earn program.</p>
<p>The Digital Currency Group (DCG) submitted its filing to the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York, on Thursday, August 10. In the motion, DCG CEO Barry Silbert and lawyers note that Gemini&#8217;s lawsuit filing last month was a “continuation of [a] public relations campaign” targeting the firm on social media with “personal, vicious, and false” claims.</p>
<p>Last month, crypto exchange Gemini complained that they are seeking to recover funds as a result of “DCG’s and Silbert’s false, misleading, and incomplete representations and omissions to Gemini” and their role “in encouraging and facilitating Genesis’s fraud against Gemini”.</p>
<p>Genesis, a subsidiary of DCG, managed a cryptocurrency lending initiative known as the Earn program, which was introduced in collaboration with Gemini in 2021. The program offered Gemini users the opportunity to lend their crypto to Genesis, with the commitment of receiving it back along with interest. Regrettably, Gemini suspended withdrawals in November 2022, attributed to &#8220;unprecedented market turmoil&#8221;. Later, the situation ultimately led to the company seeking Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in January 2023.</p>
<h2>DCG Blames the Gemini&#8217;s Winklevoss Twins</h2>
<p>As per the DCG submission, Silbert and the company &#8220;played an insignificant role in the Gemini Earn program&#8221;, and Gemini&#8217;s allegations of fraudulent behavior don&#8217;t hold merit. The filing highlights that the claims made in the Complaint against non-defendant Genesis lack supporting evidence. DCG also pointed out Gemini&#8217;s failure to present these claims during the Genesis bankruptcy, which contradicts their sensational nature. The Digital Currency Group <a href="https://twitter.com/DCGco/status/1689670266752823296" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The lawsuit is a baseless continuation of Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss’ year-long Twitter-based character assassination and public relations campaign to deflect blame from their own mismanagement. DCG looks forward to moving past this ridiculous lawsuit as we continue working towards our mission of accelerating the development of a better financial system.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2022, the downfall of Three Arrows Capital led to a reported $1.2 billion in unsettled funds for Genesis due to bankruptcy issues. Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, the founders of Gemini, allege that both Genesis and DCG owe the exchange&#8217;s customers $900 million.</p>
<p>Gemini and Genesis are confronting a legal suit from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>), filed in January regarding their Earn program. The SEC noted that the program involved the sale of unregistered securities. New York State&#8217;s Department of Financial Services is also investigating the exchange on similar grounds.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) Files Motion to Dismiss Lawsuit by Gemini</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-motion-gemini/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266619</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
<p>Besides the criticism of its method and storage of data collection, the project has also been subject to scrutiny over its onboarding of early adopters.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Argentina joins Germany, France, and Kenya on the list of governments to investigate the cryptocurrency project <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/worldcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Worldcoin</a> over privacy concerns. The country’s Agency for Access to Public Information (AAIP) <a href="https://www.argentina.gob.ar/noticias/la-aaip-investiga-el-tratamiento-de-datos-personales-de-worldcoin-en-argentina" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> on August 8 that it was looking into the collection, storage, and use of user data at Worldcoin to ensure that it is handled in line with privacy regulations. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Worldcoin started as a way to distinguish people from bots online and uses retinal scans to verify users, a method that has raised privacy concerns.  The project&#8217;s WRLD token was launched on July 24 with over 2 million accounts already signed up.   </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The AAIP stated that the project has garnered “public notoriety in recent weeks due to the procedure of scanning the faces and irises of numerous individuals in exchange for financial compensation at different locations in Buenos Aires City and the provinces of Buenos Aires, Córdoba, Mendoza, and Río Negro.” It stated that Argentinians “have the right, whenever personal data is provided, to have clear and accessible information in relation to the assignment, use and purpose for which the data is collected and processed, especially with regard to sensitive data, such as biometric data.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Expressing similar sentiments, Kenya’s government, through its minister of internal security, announced on August 2 that it was suspending Worldoin operations pending an investigation into the potential risk to citizens. Local media reports state that Kenyan law enforcement raided a Worldcoin office and seized equipment suspected to contain user data. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Germany, the Bavarian State Office for Data Protection Supervision revealed that it was investigating the project over privacy concerns. The French National Commission on Informatics and Liberty has also described Worldcoin’s data collection methods as “questionable.” The United Kingdom’s Information Commissioner’s Office has also expressed similar concerns, stating that it would examine the project to ensure compliance with data laws. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, in a </span><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/08/10/worldcoin-regulatory-scrutiny-grows-as-argentina-opens-investigation/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">statement to CoinDesk</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Worldcoin stated that “the project complies with all laws and regulations governing the processing of personal data in the markets where Worldcoin is available, including but not limited to Argentina&#8217;s Personal Data Protection Act 25.326.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Worldcoin was co-founded by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and raised $115 million in funding in May from Andreessen Horowitz, Bain Capital Crypto, and Distributed Global.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Besides the criticism of its method and storage of data collection, the project has also been subject to scrutiny over its onboarding of early adopters. A </span><a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/04/06/1048981/worldcoin-cryptocurrency-biometrics-web3/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">study</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> conducted by MIT Technology asserts that Worldcoin’s first 1 million users were obtained by “deception, cash handouts and exploiting workers” in developing countries. </span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/">Argentina Launches Investigation into Worldcoin over Privacy Concerns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/argentina-investigation-worldcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Commodities & Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia gas strikes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chevron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dutch title transfer facility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[europe gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gas Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[natural gas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woodside energy group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
<p>Prices on the Dutch Title Transfer Facility, the European benchmark, rose to more than €43 per megawatt-hour, reaching an intraday record high. On Thursday, the price slightly fell to €39.82.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
<p>On Wednesday, the prices of European natural gas soared by almost 40%, for the first time since June. The price levels reached more than €40 per megawatt-hour, driven by fears over possible supply disruption in Australia. There, workers of major liquefied natural gas plants were reportedly planning strike action in a fight for higher salaries and better job security. On top of that, some traders closed out their bets that gas prices would fall, which also fueled price movements.</p>
<p>Callum Macpherson, head of commodities at Investec, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/10/european-gas-prices-expected-to-rise-amid-australia-lng-supply-fears.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;A fear that an outage in Australia could increase demand from Asia buyers for LNG that might otherwise come to Europe, has led to today&#8217;s spike in prices.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>John Evans, an analyst at brokerage PVM, commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Australia is now the highest exporter of LNG, beating Qatar and the US, but with production issues and compromised gas fields, European buyers are fearful of security in supply and have resorted to tank filling from the cash market before the onset of winter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Prices on the Dutch Title Transfer Facility, the European benchmark, rose to more than €43 per megawatt-hour, reaching an intraday record high. On Thursday, the price slightly fell to €39.82. As of the press moment, the gas price at the Dutch Title Transfer Facility makes up €36.16.</p>
<h2>What Is Happening in Australia?</h2>
<p>Over the past decade, Australia’s LNG exports have grown exponentially, making it the country with the largest operating LNG export capacity in the world. Last year, Australia recorded an all-time high in liquefied natural gas export earnings, with volumes and prices driven by the energy security crisis that followed the outbreak of the war between Russia and Ukraine. As per the Australian Petroleum Production &amp; Exploration Association (APPEA), the record export income led to support for thousands of jobs, substantial direct government revenues, and significant expenditure locally.</p>
<p>However, it turns out that revenue generated from gas export does not mean benefits for those involved in the working processes. Currently, there are high risks of potential strikes at three major liquefied natural gas facilities in Australia that could disrupt about 10% of global exports of fuel. The owners of the facilities, Chevron and Woodside Energy Group, are now holding talks with unions to avoid the protests.</p>
<p>&#8220;We will continue to engage our employees and their representatives as we seek outcomes that are in the interests of both employees and the company,&#8221; said a Chevron representative.</p>
<p>Unions representing 700 workers at the LNG facilities have been complaining about low pay and bad working conditions. As a result, they have applied for &#8220;protected action ballot orders&#8221; that give them the right to hold votes on strike action. According to those familiar with the matter, the ongoing negotiations with Woodside and Chevron are at different stages. But considering how the processes are run, industrial action is likely to take place towards the end of August and could carry on for months if not resolved. The talks will continue until next Tuesday.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/markets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">market news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/">European Gas Prices Surge Almost 40% amid Supply Concerns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/european-gas-prices-surge-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indices]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cpi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gdp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266576</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
<p>The decelerating inflation reduces some of the pressure from the Fed, however, remains high over the central bank's 2% target. Thus, the Fed is less to announce rate cuts anytime soon. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
<p>On Thursday, August 10, 2023, the Bureau of Labor Statistics reported the US CPI data for the month of July at 3.2% showing clear signs of receding inflation numbers. Also, the annual inflation rate was below the 3.3% forecast.</p>
<p>However, it was still higher than the month of June, and the first increase in more than a year&#8217;s time. Excluding the volatile prices of food and energy, the core Consumer Price Index (CPI) also rose by 0.2% in the month. This was in alignment with expectations and resulted in a year-over-year rate of 4.7%, marking the lowest level since October 2021. The annual rate for the core CPI was slightly below the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones</a> consensus estimate of 4.8%.</p>
<p>Markets reacted positively with Dow Jones futures shooting up by 200 points and Treasury yields moving lower. Sung Won Sohn, chief economist at SS Economics said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is not quite ‘mission accomplished’ yet, but significant progress on the inflation front has been made. On balance, the inflation picture has improved significantly. The Federal Reserve will stop raising the interest rate soon.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Sectors Affecting US CPI Inflation Data</h2>
<p>The majority of the monthly increase in inflation was due to higher shelter costs, which experienced a 0.4% rise, resulting in a 7.7% increase over the past year. Within the shelter category, rents also rose by 0.4%. This category accounted for over 90% of the overall increase and holds about one-third of the CPI weighting.</p>
<p>Food prices saw a 0.2% increase during the month, while energy prices only rose by 0.1%, despite notable surges in crude oil prices and pump prices.</p>
<p>Prices for used vehicles declined by 1.3%, while medical care services experienced a 0.4% decrease. Airline fares, which had seen a substantial surge during the early days of the Covid pandemic, fell by 8.1% in the month. This is the same decrease as in June, thus resulting in an overall decline of 18.6% from a year ago.</p>
<h2>The Fight Against Inflation Continues</h2>
<p>Collectively, the most recent set of data demonstrates that although inflation has significantly decreased from its peak in mid-2022, it remains notably higher than the Federal Reserve&#8217;s desired 2% threshold. This level of inflation makes it unlikely that there will be any interest rate cuts in the near future.</p>
<p>However, the decelerating inflation levels are taking off some pressure from the Fed. Seema Shah, chief global strategist at Principal Asset Management <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/10/cpi-inflation-july-2023-.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While inflation is moving in the right direction, the still-elevated level suggests that the Fed is some distance from cutting rates. Indeed, disinflation is unlikely to be smooth and will require some additional economic pain before the 2% target comes sustainably into view.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The increased interest rates have yet to impact economic growth significantly: GDP recorded growth of 2% and 2.4% in the first two quarters of 2023, while the Atlanta Fed forecasts a third-quarter growth rate of 4.1%. Although payroll gains have slowed down, they remain robust, and unemployment is at its lowest level since late 1969.</p>
<p>Having raised benchmark interest rates 11 times since March 2022, central bank officials are widely anticipated to pause in September. However, there is an ongoing debate about the next course of action. Policymakers have expressed varying opinions in public comments leading to confusion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/">US CPI Inflation Surge at 3.2% Below Forecast, Markets React Positively</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-cpi-inflation-surge-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usd coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[usdc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=266609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
<p>Circle revealed that it is actively pursuing partnerships to promote the adoption of USD Coin.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
<p>Prominent Stablecoin issuer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Circle</a> is demonstrating its commitment to adaptability and resilience as it faces renewed competition from unexpected players.</p>
<p>As non-crypto giants such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PayPal Holdings Inc</a> (NASDAQ: PYPL) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/paypal-paypal-usd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">enter</a> the field, Circle’s CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jeremy-allaire/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jeremy Allaire</a> revealed in an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-10/circle-usdc-stablecoin-issuer-says-1-billion-cash-to-counter-paypal-binance?in_source=embedded-checkout-banner" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a> with Bloomberg that the company is relying on a substantial cash cushion exceeding $1 billion to weather the storm while addressing a decline in the market share of its stablecoin.</p>
<h2>Circle Reserve and USDC Market Share Slump</h2>
<p>At the beginning of the year, Circle&#8217;s USD Coin (USDC) was riding high with a circulation of approximately $45 billion. However, that figure has since plummeted to around $26 billion. This downward trajectory stands in stark contrast to the growth of Tether (USDT), the largest stablecoin by market capitalization, during the same period.</p>
<p>Jeremy Allaire reiterated that various &#8220;tail-risk events&#8221; in the crypto industry have had an impact on USD Coin’s adoption. He highlighted that the fall of Terra, Binance&#8217;s conversion shift, the FTX crisis, and regional bank failures all led to Circle&#8217;s difficulties.</p>
<p>Despite these obstacles, Circle&#8217;s revenue production model has proven resilient, particularly through interest income generated by assets backing the stablecoin, such as dollar deposits and short-term Treasuries. Circle is now in a position to gain from rising interest rates.</p>
<p>Circle&#8217;s financial performance in the first half of the year reflects its resilience. With $779 million in revenue, Circle surpassed its total revenue of $772 million for the entire preceding year.</p>
<p>In addition, adjusted earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization (EBITDA) reached $219 million, outpacing the $150 million achieved in the previous year. Bolstered by a substantial cash reserve exceeding $1 billion as of June, Circle is well-equipped to forge ahead with its strategic plans.</p>
<p>Allaire emphasized that the vision for Circle&#8217;s future is grounded in the mainstream adoption of stablecoins, envisaging them as the financial medium of the Internet era. He views PayPal&#8217;s recent announcement as just the initial step in this journey.</p>
<p>He expects a greater range of financial services companies and online payment firms to enter the stablecoin arena, increasing competition and accelerating the sector&#8217;s progress.</p>
<h2>The Future Ahead of Circle</h2>
<p>Circle revealed that it is actively pursuing partnerships to promote the adoption of USD Coin. The company is also enhancing transparency by sharing financial reports and collaborating with Deloitte as an auditor.</p>
<p>The company said it is also looking into partnerships for greater adoption of its USDC. However, Circle&#8217;s approach focuses on collaboration without adopting the white-label model used by competitors such as Paxos Trust Co.</p>
<p>Even as the Federal Reserve considers decreasing interest rates, Allaire remains bullish about Circle’s prospects, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-usdc-reserves-us-default/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">noting</a> that historically, a low-rate environment has boosted crypto activity.</p>
<p>Circle’s development of new revenue sources, like the recent launch of a crypto wallet service following the acquisition of CYBAVO in 2022, demonstrates the company’s dedication to innovation and diversification.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/vc-andreessen-horowitz-zero-knowledge/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/">Circle Relies on $1B Cash Reserve to Fight Competition</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/circle-1b-reserve-competition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4133 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1061478 metric#prefetches=204 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=105.37 metric#ms-cache=5.02 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2390 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->