<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:12:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Formula One Ticket Provider Platinum Group Unveils NFT Tickets for Sunday’s Monaco Grand Prix</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elemint]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[formula 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[formula one]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[platinum group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256725</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/">Formula One Ticket Provider Platinum Group Unveils NFT Tickets for Sunday&#8217;s Monaco Grand Prix</a></p>
<p>The NFT tickets will be minted via the Ethereum scaling layer two blockchain Polygon (MATIC). </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/">Formula One Ticket Provider Platinum Group Unveils NFT Tickets for Sunday&#8217;s Monaco Grand Prix</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/">Formula One Ticket Provider Platinum Group Unveils NFT Tickets for Sunday&#8217;s Monaco Grand Prix</a></p>
<p>The sixth race of the 22-round season for the Formula One (F1) Grand Prix held in Monaco over the weekend has attracted the attention of crypto enthusiasts. Furthermore, as a country within the European market, which recently passed the Markets in Crypto-Assets Act (MiCA) legislative standards, it is bound to attract significantly higher crypto enthusiasts during the F1 event. As a result, Platinium Group, a global sports ticketing platform, has partnered with Elemint, a blockchain infrastructure focused on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> industry, and Web3 marketing and development agency, Bary, to help in the creation and distribution of the NFT tickets.</p>
<p>According to Elie Zerbib, Co-Founder of Bary, certain NFT holders may be offered tickets to the most exclusive party of the 69th edition Grand Prix championship. Additionally, the F1 NFT holders will stand a chance to get more rewards in future events in addition to using them as tickets, which is meant to encourage holders.</p>
<p>“By providing a completely seamless experience on the main website, the user doesn&#8217;t need to have any Web3 knowledge to purchase the NFT ticket,” <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/05/26/f1-ticket-provider-platinum-group-introduces-nft-tickets-for-global-racing-event/" target="_blank">said</a> Zerbib. “We make users understand the benefits that come with this new type of ticketing and onboard them on a journey that will change their F1 experience.”</p>
<p>Notably, the NFT tickets will be minted via the Ethereum scaling layer two blockchain Polygon (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MATIC</a>). This is meant to provide quality services to the NFT ticket holders. According to Jacques-Henri Eyraud, CEO of Elemint, the use of NFT in the sports industry is revolutionary in engaging fans.</p>
<p>“Web3 technologies make it possible to design ticketing solutions that are more secure and more adapted to the specificity of each event,” said Eyraud. “The experience becomes more personalized and fun for fans of all types of sports competitions.”</p>
<h2>Closer Look at the NFT Market and Sporting Industry</h2>
<p>With the emergence of the metaverse industry, NFTs have grown into a billion-dollar industry. Moreover, minting quality  NFTs in masses on top of blockchains like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> takes hundreds of thousands of dollars if not millions. Nevertheless, the underlying NFT community gives the project value through a real-world utility like ticket entrance to events among others.</p>
<p>According to market aggregate data provided by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>-backed CoinMarketCap, the NFT market had a total market capitalization of approximately $3,500,191,542 on Friday. Total sales in the past 24 hours were about $32,631,070 with Ethereum occupying the entire top ten.</p>
<p>The GamiFi industry occupies a significant portion of the NFT market amid the transition from Web2 gaming to web3. The NFT market has, however, a long way to go to mainstream adoption as the lack of crypto education among most investors has been identified as a significant stumbling block.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/">Formula One Ticket Provider Platinum Group Unveils NFT Tickets for Sunday&#8217;s Monaco Grand Prix</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/formula-one-nft-tickets-monaco-grand-prix/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance and Gulf Innova Lands Approval to Operate JV in Thailand</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gulf Innova]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256720</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/">Binance and Gulf Innova Lands Approval to Operate JV in Thailand</a></p>
<p>The launch of the crypto exchange in Thailand comes at an opportune time, as the country continues to embrace digital innovation and blockchain technology.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/">Binance and Gulf Innova Lands Approval to Operate JV in Thailand</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/">Binance and Gulf Innova Lands Approval to Operate JV in Thailand</a></p>
<p>The world’s largest crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has teamed up with Gulf Innova Co Ltd, a major technology firm in the Gulf area, to launch a new crypto exchange in Thailand. With the launch scheduled for the fourth quarter of 2023, this collaboration could shape the future of Thailand&#8217;s crypto landscape.</p>
<p>Binance shared the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/gulf-binance-secures-digital-asset-operator-licenses-in-thailand-3415121915568823678?ref=AZTKZ9XS&amp;utm_source=BinanceTwitter&amp;utm_medium=GlobalSocial&amp;utm_campaign=GlobalSocial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a> in a blog post, stating that its joint venture with Gulf Innova known as “Gulf Binance Co Ltd” secured the digital asset operator licenses from Thailand&#8217;s Ministry of Finance for a digital asset platform. The joint venture will be regulated by the country’s Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>According to the announcement, the joint venture aims to tap into the growing demand for digital assets in the country and provide a reliable and secure platform for Thai investors to participate in the crypto market. With Binance&#8217;s reputation as a leading global crypto exchange and Gulf Innova&#8217;s technological expertise and regional presence, the joint venture aims to provide a seamless and secure trading experience for Thai investors.</p>
<p>By leveraging Binance&#8217;s robust infrastructure and Gulf Innova&#8217;s understanding of the local market, the partnership is well-positioned to address the unique needs and challenges of the Thai crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>Since striking an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gulf-energy-invests-binance-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">agreement</a> on a joint venture in 2022, Binance and Gulf have been collaborating closely with Thailand&#8217;s regulators to establish a compliant-first exchange that rigorously follows the SEC&#8217;s requirements.</p>
<p>The partnership&#8217;s commitment to regulatory compliance will be crucial in ensuring a transparent and trusted trading environment. By working closely with Thai authorities, the joint venture will adhere to regulatory guidelines and implement robust security measures to protect users&#8217; assets and personal information.</p>
<h2>A Right Time for the Thai Crypto Industry?</h2>
<p>The launch of the crypto exchange in Thailand comes at an opportune time, as the country continues to embrace digital innovation and blockchain technology. Currently, the 2023 FinTech Festival, where diverse industry topics such as Blockchain and Web3 will be explored, is also set to take place later this year.</p>
<p>Additionally, the nation’s apex bank, the Bank of Thailand has revealed plans to roll out virtual banks as the government tries to boost competition. With a growing tech-savvy population and a favorable regulatory environment, Thailand has the potential to become a hub for cryptocurrency adoption and blockchain development in Southeast Asia.</p>
<p>Ultimately, Gulf Binance&#8217;s objective is to be Thailand&#8217;s premier provider of infrastructure services for the digital asset ecosystem. A crucial component of this ambition is to develop local Web3 expertise while also assisting in the expansion of the broader blockchain industry.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, the collaboration could pave the way for further advancements in Thailand&#8217;s fintech world. As the exchange gains traction and garners user trust, it may expand its services to include additional financial products and services, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Decentralized Finance</a> (DeFi) offerings.</p>
<p>The joint venture&#8217;s success in Thailand could also serve as a model for future partnerships and collaborations in other countries within the region.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/">Binance and Gulf Innova Lands Approval to Operate JV in Thailand</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-gulf-innova-jv-thailand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Klarna Halves Q1 Net Loss and ‘On Track to Achieve Profitability This Year’</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airbnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etsy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[klarna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nike]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256685</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/">Klarna Halves Q1 Net Loss and &#8216;On Track to Achieve Profitability This Year&#8217;</a></p>
<p>Swedish fintech mainstay Klarna cut its Q1 net loss to $120.7 million while boosting operating income by 22% YoY.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/">Klarna Halves Q1 Net Loss and &#8216;On Track to Achieve Profitability This Year&#8217;</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/">Klarna Halves Q1 Net Loss and &#8216;On Track to Achieve Profitability This Year&#8217;</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/klarna/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Klarna Bank AB</a> significantly improved its Q1 bottom line after halving the net loss sustained for the period compared with last year. For the first quarter of the year, the Swedish fintech giant posted a net deficit of 1.3 billion Swedish krona ($120.7 million). This reverse is down 50% from Klarna’s year-ago outing as the company looks ahead toward profitability. In Q1 2022, the company sustained a loss of 2.6 billion krona.</p>
<p>Klarna’s significant strides during the first quarter were also reflected in its total net operating income, up 22% year-over-year at 5 billion Swedish krona. In a statement, the Stockholm-based company’s CEO Sebastian Siemiatkowski hinted at a positive outlook for H2 2023. However, the Klarna CEO also reflected on the fintech firm’s commendable Q1 outing, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This quarter, we’ve impressively managed to grow GMV and revenue, at the same time as we cut costs and credit losses and also investing ambitiously in AI-driven products. We are on track to achieve profitability this year, all while revolutionizing shopping and payments through our AI-powered approach.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last November, Siemiatkowski said Klarna would become profitable again in 2023.</p>
<h2>Klarna Improved Q1 Net Loss Attributable to Several Business Decisions, Including Extensive Partnerships &amp; AI Push</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.klarna.com/us/" target="_blank">Klarna</a> attributed its substantially reduced Q1 net loss to declining customer defaults and its income diversification strategy. The Buy Now Pay Later (BNPL) facilitator, which <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-fintech-rivals-revolut-wise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reduced its headcount</a> by 10% last May, has tapped other revenue sources, including marketing. Klarna’s Q1 2023 growth also surpassed e-commerce trends due to its swift adoption of artificial intelligence (AI) throughout its operations. Furthermore, the company recently secured several notable partnerships with globally recognized companies such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/airbnb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Airbnb Inc</a> (NASDAQ: ABNB).</p>
<p>The Airbnb deal offers seamless, flexible, and sustainable payment solutions to global guests of the San Francisco-based lodging company. The business collaboration between both companies promises to prove lucrative, with Airbnb anticipating over 300 million guest arrivals this year.</p>
<p>In the first quarter of 2023, Klarna also forged new retail partnerships with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/samsung/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Samsung</a>, Uniqlo, and Boden. Furthermore, the online financial services provider strengthened existing ties with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nike</a> (NYSE: NKE), Etsy (NASDAQ: ETSY), and Tod’s.</p>
<p>Klarna’s AI push has seen the firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-adopts-chatgpt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">partner with</a> ChatGPT creator OpenAI to deploy the generative technology for improved efficiency and consumer outcomes. The OpenAI partnership is the first for a European tech platform and underscores Klarna’s goal to help merchants target customers more effectively.</p>
<p>In April, Klarna earned a credit rating of BBB/A-3 with a stable outlook from S&amp;P Global. At the time, the rating agency said its assessment reflected the Swedish fintech’s ability to reclaim profitability and remain competitive in key markets.</p>
<h2>2022 Downsizing &amp; Growing Pains</h2>
<p>Klarna, which currently boasts over 150 million customers, hired liberally between 2020 and 2021 to leverage pandemic-induced growth. However, the company downsized in May 2022 under investor pressure to trim operations. In H1 2022, Klarna lost over $580 million, burning through cash to support expansions into the US and the UK.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/">Klarna Halves Q1 Net Loss and &#8216;On Track to Achieve Profitability This Year&#8217;</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/klarna-q1-net-loss/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Treasury Yield Falls amid Rate Hikes and Debt Ceiling Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury yield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yield Falls amid Rate Hikes and Debt Ceiling Concerns</a></p>
<p>The ongoing negotiations surrounding the US debt ceiling have been a key focal point for investors as the June 1 deadline approaches.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yield Falls amid Rate Hikes and Debt Ceiling Concerns</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yield Falls amid Rate Hikes and Debt Ceiling Concerns</a></p>
<p>The United States Treasury bond market experienced a decline in yields on Friday as investors eagerly await the release of key inflation data and updates on debt ceiling negotiations.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/26/us-treasury-yields-investors-await-key-inflation-data.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a>, the yield on the 10-year Treasury fell by 3 basis points to 3.829%, while the 2-year Treasury yield dropped by nearly 6 basis points to 4.57%. It is important to note that yields and prices move in opposite directions. A basis point is one-hundredth of a percentage point, which equals 0.01%. Thus, a 3 basis point reduction signifies that the 10-year Treasury yield has decreased by 0.03% from its prior level.</p>
<p>Treasury yield fluctuation provides information on investor sentiment and market dynamics. When yield falls, it indicates that investors are seeking safer assets in response to a variety of circumstances, interest rate hikes, geopolitical events, or changes in monetary policy expectations.</p>
<p>The release of the April Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) price index, considered the Federal Reserve&#8217;s favored gauge of inflation, was keenly anticipated by investors. The PCE index gives insight into changes in consumer prices paid for goods and services, serving as an important indication of inflationary pressures in the economy.</p>
<p>Per the data revealed, the PCE came in at 4.7% year-on-year, higher than the previous reading of 4.6%.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">PCE Services inflation continued to rise to 5.5% (prev. 4.6%), and goods inflation also rebounded to 2.1% (prev. 1.6%). <a href="https://t.co/Uhv8C8L9xO" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Uhv8C8L9xO</a></p>
<p>— MacroMicro (@MacroMicroMe) <a href="https://twitter.com/MacroMicroMe/status/1662079119566467077?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank">May 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Treasury Yield Performance: Impact of Interest Rate Hike</h2>
<p>The US Federal Reserve has complete control over the country’s monetary policies, and interest rates which ultimately impact the Treasury Yield performance. Markedly, the Fed effectively decides how banks lend and borrow money among themselves.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve has continued to raise interest rates, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-fed-25-basis-point-rate-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">increasing the rate by 25 basis points</a> earlier in May, a move that is generating concern about the potential impact. The apex institution has been boosting the interest rate on a continuous basis in order to prevent soaring inflation. The most recent increase is the tenth in about a year, and it is the Fed&#8217;s fastest rate climb since the early 1980s.</p>
<p>However, officials have sent conflicting signals about the possible path of further interest rate hikes. While some officials have expressed a preference for pausing the rate-hiking campaign, others believe that further rate hikes might be necessary to take the inflation to the desired level of around 2%.</p>
<h2>Sentiments Surrounding the Debt Ceiling Talks</h2>
<p>The ongoing negotiations surrounding the US debt ceiling have been a key focal point for investors as the June 1 deadline approaches, heightening concerns about a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dollar-debt-limit-default-risks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">potential default</a> on the country’s debt obligations. While talks have shown signs of progress, there are still sensitive issues that need to be addressed, according to Republican negotiator Rep. Patrick McHenry.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the resolution of these issues is crucial to avoid a potential default on US debt obligations, which could have far-reaching implications for financial markets. Market participants remain hopeful for a successful resolution that will restore market confidence and demonstrate the commitment of the US government to meet its debt obligations.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/">US Treasury Yield Falls amid Rate Hikes and Debt Ceiling Concerns</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-debt-ceiling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guilty Pleas in Coinone Case: Defendants in South Korea Admit Charges</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/">Guilty Pleas in Coinone Case: Defendants in South Korea Admit Charges</a></p>
<p>The legal process is going on, with the next hearing scheduled for June 6th.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/">Guilty Pleas in Coinone Case: Defendants in South Korea Admit Charges</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/">Guilty Pleas in Coinone Case: Defendants in South Korea Admit Charges</a></p>
<p>On May 25th, broker Ko Mo and former Coinone listing director Jeon Mo pleaded guilty to several charges during their first hearing before the judge.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.yna.co.kr/view/AKR20230525091000004?section=economy/cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">local media,</a> Ko Mo was accused of soliciting and delivering up to 6 million won in cryptocurrencies and cash to Jeon Mo and Kim Mo. Jeon, on the other hand, was accused of receiving payments in cryptocurrencies and cash totaling 1.92 billion won ($1.51 million) for listing coins such as &#8220;Furiever Coin&#8221;, which was linked to a kidnapping and murder investigation in Gangnam district, Seoul.</p>
<p>However, their lawyers argued that they have not yet had complete access to all the evidence records, so they will provide a final opinion after reviewing them.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Basically, we acknowledge the accusation, but since we haven&#8217;t been able to access all the evidence records, we will provide a final opinion after reviewing them.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The next hearing for Ko and Jeon is scheduled for June 6th, and it is expected that the legal process related to the Coinone case will continue.</p>
<h3>Defendants in Coinone Case Seek Resolution with Lawyers Ahead of June Hearing</h3>
<p>Kim Mo, the former leader of the Coinone team, and Hwang Mo, another broker, were the latest to be arrested and accused of requesting the listing of various cryptocurrencies issued in South Korea on Coinone and subsequently engaging in illegal exchanges on the platform.</p>
<p>Kim Mo is accused of receiving a total of 1.04 billion won (around $800.000) from Ko and Hwang, while Hwang is accused of requesting the listing of the coin and making payments to Jeon and Kim.</p>
<p>The defendants are in communication with their lawyers to reach an agreement regarding their guilt in the upcoming hearing scheduled for June 15th.</p>
<h2>South Korea Advances in Regulatory Matters to Protect Its Citizens</h2>
<p>At the end of last month, the National Assembly of South Korea <a href="https://forkast.news/headlines/south-korea-crypto-bill-review/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">approved</a> a cryptocurrency regulation bill, which requires cryptocurrency service providers to keep user funds separate from corporate funds to prevent misappropriation of funds, such as the FTX case.</p>
<p>Thanks to this bill, which is in its final stages of approval, individuals who commit financial crimes with cryptocurrencies in the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-security-tokens-regulation/">Asian country</a> may face sentences ranging from 5 years to life imprisonment.</p>
<p>On May 25th, the National Assembly of South Korea also <a href="https://www.news1.kr/articles/5058538" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">approved</a> the &#8220;Kim Nam Guk Prevention Law&#8221;, which requires high-ranking officials to fully disclose their cryptocurrencies to promote integrity and transparency within the government.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-cryptocurrency-tracking/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> by Coinspeaker, the South Korean government plans to launch a cryptocurrency tracking system in the middle of the year to prevent all kinds of scams and crimes related to them. They even announced that they are preparing to build a criminal justice system that complies with international laws to prosecute cybercriminals.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/">Guilty Pleas in Coinone Case: Defendants in South Korea Admit Charges</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinone-case-defendants-south/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini to Set Up Its Base in Europe, Headquarters to Be Opened in Dublin</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cameron winklevoss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tyler winklevoss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256672</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/">Gemini to Set Up Its Base in Europe, Headquarters to Be Opened in Dublin</a></p>
<p>Gemini also plans to expand its workforce after the EU adopted the new Markets in Crypto-Assets Regulations (MiCA), which were formally approved on May 16.  </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/">Gemini to Set Up Its Base in Europe, Headquarters to Be Opened in Dublin</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/">Gemini to Set Up Its Base in Europe, Headquarters to Be Opened in Dublin</a></p>
<p>Cryptocurrency firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a> has <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gemini-chooses-ireland-europe-headquarters" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">revealed</a> that Dublin, Ireland, will be the home of its new European headquarters. On May 25, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, owners of the crypto firm, told reporters that the established technology and innovation community, a strong regulatory landscape, and a huge talent pool were all factors that influenced their decision to choose Dublin.</p>
<p>The latest move has been dubbed as one that will see the American crypto firm spread its reach across the European continent.</p>
<p>The billionaire investors, who founded Gemini, also met with  Leo Varadkar, Prime Minister of the Northwestern European country, stating that Ireland is their doorway into the European Union as they plan to spread their business across the continent.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/cameron-winklevoss/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cameron Winklevoss</a> stated that the firm reviewed all of the EU as potential entry points, and they felt comfortable with Ireland and the reputation of the regulator. Following the official announcement, the prime minister also took to Twitter to extend congratulations to Gemini for achieving this feat.</p>
<p>Varadkar recognized the profound importance of this recent milestone for the Irish economy and its commitment to fostering innovation.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange currently boasts of a cryptocurrency trading platform in Ireland and 11 other European countries as of the last quarter of 2022, all launched as part of its plans to become a household name in the European crypto scene.</p>
<p>Gemini also already has an established presence in Dublin, where it boasts an operational office comprising a workforce of 12 individuals. This came after Gemini was awarded a virtual asset service provider license from the Central Bank of Ireland in July 2022.</p>
<p>According to the twin brothers, their company has its eyes set on broadening its workforce in Europe after the EU adopted the new Markets in Crypto-Assets Regulations (MiCA), which were formally approved on May 16.</p>
<p>The latest move by Gemini comes as regulatory pressure grows in the United States, something that has seen severe criticism, with some market experts describing it as a war on digital assets.</p>
<p>The crypto firm was recently the subject of a series of charges by the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>). Cameron Winklevoss described the situation as challenging and accused the SEC of lacking consistency in its actions.</p>
<p>In April, Gemini announced plans to establish an engineering hub in India to leverage its growing pool of tech talent.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/">Gemini to Set Up Its Base in Europe, Headquarters to Be Opened in Dublin</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-europe-headquarters-dublin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of Brazil Includes 14 Participants in Its CBDC Pilot</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[banco central do brasil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital real]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256660</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/">Bank of Brazil Includes 14 Participants in Its CBDC Pilot</a></p>
<p>The Brazil Central Bank Digital Currency will initially focus on wholesale interbank transaction payment solutions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/">Bank of Brazil Includes 14 Participants in Its CBDC Pilot</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/">Bank of Brazil Includes 14 Participants in Its CBDC Pilot</a></p>
<p>Banco Central do Brasil (the Central Bank of Brazil) plans to include more participants in its digital currency scheme. The list, released by the bank on May 24, includes the names of all the participants with whom the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a> digital real is set to launch. The final list of 14 participants was compiled from 36 bids submitted by individuals and collaborating entities, totaling more than 100 institutions.</p>
<h2>Brazil Digital Real Pilot Will Begin with 14 Participants, Including Visa and Microsoft</h2>
<p>Intending to launch it fully in 2024, the Brazilian central bank announced the beginning of its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) last year. The solution&#8217;s initial purpose is to ease wholesale interbank transactions, and eventually, it will be made accessible to customers through tokenized bank deposits. The CBDC solution aims to make transactions instantly settleable and lower overall transaction costs.</p>
<p>This phase of the digital real pilot aims to test privacy and programmability functions to ensure that the process of exchanging information between various participants on the platform will be easy. It will also test the programmability and interoperability of the services the participants offer.</p>
<p>The participants on <a href="https://www.bcb.gov.br/detalhenoticia/17897/nota" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the recently released list</a> include both single and collaborating entities. They include names like Bradesco, Banco Inter, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a>, and 7comm; XP and Visa; Bano ABC, Hamsa, and LoopiPay; Itau Unibanco; Microsoft in collaboration with other institutions; and the Bank of Brazil.</p>
<p>The list includes a wide range of organizations, including cooperatives, public banks, payment solution providers, financial market infrastructure operators, providers of crypto asset services, and payment arrangement providers. With all these entities in place, the Brazilian central bank intends to add the chosen participants to the digital pilot platform by June 2023.</p>
<h2>Brazil CBDC Pilot Will Initially Focus on Wholesale Payment Solutions</h2>
<p>The Brazil CBDC, digital real, is an extension of the Brazilian physical currency. It can be exchanged for the traditional currency and will have the same price and value as the traditional currency. This initiative will promote the greater inclusion of Brazilian citizens in the financial system. The solution combines the features of fiat and digital currencies, allowing the digital currency to benefit from the price stability attributes of fiat currencies while leveraging blockchain technologies for faster and more secure transactions.</p>
<p>One of the reasons the solution primarily focuses on wholesale transactions instead of retail is that Brazil already has an established digital payment system, Pix. Pix is already one of Brazil&#8217;s largest e-commerce payment solutions; it was launched in 2022 and is currently used by over 60% of Brazilians.</p>
<p>Rather than trying to compete with this established solution, Banco Central do Brasil will follow Pix&#8217;s model in other areas of financial services, particularly at the wholesale level.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/">Bank of Brazil Includes 14 Participants in Its CBDC Pilot</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-brazil-participants-cbdc-pilot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Currency Group (DCG) to Close Down Its Prime Brokerage Subsidiary TradeBlock</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradeblock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) to Close Down Its Prime Brokerage Subsidiary TradeBlock</a></p>
<p>TradeBlock will officially begin the process of shutting down on May 31. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) to Close Down Its Prime Brokerage Subsidiary TradeBlock</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) to Close Down Its Prime Brokerage Subsidiary TradeBlock</a></p>
<p>Digital Currency Group (DCG), a New York-based venture capital firm that invests and provides services to crypto companies is winding down its TradeBlock subsidiary.</p>
<p>According to a May 25 <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-25/digital-currency-group-closes-tradeblock-institutional-platform/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from Bloomberg, the company, headed by Breanne Madigan, who previously worked at <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/goldman-sachs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Goldman Sachs</a> for 15 years, will begin the shutdown of the platform by the end of the month, specifically on May 31.</p>
<p>TradeBlock, dedicated to providing trade execution and prime brokerage services to only institutional investors, was purchased by CoinDesk, a crypto news media owned by DCG, through an undisclosed financial transaction in 2020.</p>
<p>Following the acquisition, the media house incorporated TradeBlock&#8217;s indexing services into its operations, while other aspects of the firm were transformed into what is known as TradeBlock.</p>
<h2>DCG Blames Prolonged Crypto Winter and Regulatory Uncertainties for Closure</h2>
<p>Unfortunately, DCG has decided to cease the operations of the institutional trading platform after three years of service due to prevailing economic conditions and the prolonged crypto winter, which significantly impacted the entire industry.</p>
<p>The company also blamed the regulatory environment surrounding the emerging economy in the United States as a significant contributor to the business failure.</p>
<p>&#8220;Due to the state of the broader economy and prolonged crypto winter, along with the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the US, we made the decision to sunset the institutional trading platform side of the business,&#8221; a spokesperson told Bloomberg.</p>
<h2>DCG Faces Financial Challenges</h2>
<p>DCG and its portfolio of companies have faced a number of financial challenges over the past year. These financial constraints stemmed partly from the collapse of the crypto giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> in November, forcing many entities, including BlockFi, into bankruptcy.</p>
<p>The latest closure makes it the second business the firm has shut down in 2023. In January, DCG <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> the liquidation of its wealth management firm, HQ Digital, citing challenging economic situations.</p>
<p>The venture capital has reduced a significant portion of its workforce across several units to weather the storm. DCG slashed 13% of its internal headcounts at the start of the year.</p>
<p>One of its subsidiaries, Luno, laid off 35% of employees in January, cutting around 330 jobs, followed by Genesis, its crypto brokerage firm. Genesis <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-creditor-committee-genesis-dcg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suffered</a> a liquidity crisis that led to suspending deposits and withdrawals as well as redemptions and new loan originations from the platform. The move comes after it failed to raise $1 billion from investors to support its business.</p>
<p>In a recent turn of events, DCG <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-genesis-dcg-630m-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">failed</a> to meet the $630 million debt payment owed to Genesis. The firm took hundreds of millions in loans from Genesis last year at &#8220;prevailing market interest rates&#8221;. The funds were supposed to be repaid in May 2023. However, DCG has failed to honor the loan agreement and is actively pursuing discussions to refinance its debt.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/">Digital Currency Group (DCG) to Close Down Its Prime Brokerage Subsidiary TradeBlock</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-close-down-tradeblock/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nvidia Set to Join Apple, Microsoft, Amazon in the Trillion-Dollar Market Cap Group</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank of americs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[boa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nvidia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256638</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/">Nvidia Set to Join Apple, Microsoft, Amazon in the Trillion-Dollar Market Cap Group</a></p>
<p>Due to a favorable forecast and AI adoption, Nvidia has seen explosive growth and could soon hit the trillion-dollar market cap.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/">Nvidia Set to Join Apple, Microsoft, Amazon in the Trillion-Dollar Market Cap Group</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/">Nvidia Set to Join Apple, Microsoft, Amazon in the Trillion-Dollar Market Cap Group</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/nvidia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nvidia Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) is fast approaching the trillion-dollar market cap due to its explosive stock surge. On Thursday, the chip maker’s shares jumped 26% following a robust earnings outlook and increased production scale.</p>
<p>Nvidia’s market valuation sits at $950 billion, which is almost $200 million higher than it was at Wednesday’s close. The Santa Clara-based software and fabless company’s market capitalization is now twice as large as its Taiwanese rival &#8211; <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TSMC</a>.</p>
<p>Several analysts and observers believe that Nvidia could soon become a trillion-dollar company. Currently, other companies with at least $1 trillion in valuation include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN).</p>
<p>Needham analyst Rajvindra Gill commented on Nvidia potentially becoming the fifth publicly traded US company to attain the trillion-dollar market cap. Gill said Needham, in 2021, had suggested that Nvidia would be the first semiconductor company to hit $1 trillion. He still believes that Nvidia can hit that valuation regardless of the highs and lows the company has experienced over the last few years.</p>
<h2>Surge in Demand for Nvidia Products Propelled Stock to Trillion-Dollar-Market-Cap Status</h2>
<p>Nvidia’s growth trajectory to $1 trillion could culminate in a matter of days after the company raised its quarterly sales guidance. The company is experiencing surging demand due to accelerated AI adoption and an $11 billion sales forecast for fiscal Q2. In a statement from earlier this week, Nvidia chief executive officer Jensen Huang <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/nvidia-announces-financial-results-for-first-quarter-fiscal-2024" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The computer industry is going through two simultaneous transitions – accelerated computing and generative AI. Our entire data center family of products – H100, Grace CPU, Grace Hopper Superchip, NVLink, Quantum 400 InfiniBand, and BlueField-3 DPU – is in production. We are significantly increasing our supply to meet surging demand for them.”</p></blockquote>
<p>This development has hiked the price of Nvidia’s shares and stoked a rally in other AI-exposed stocks. For instance, yesterday, tech-rooted companies, including C3.ai Inc (NYSE: AI), Palantir Technologies (NYSE: PLTR), Microsoft, Alphabet, and Advanced Micro Devices (NASDAQ: AMD) all rose substantially in premarket trade.</p>
<p>With Nvidia’s stock up more than 108% year-to-date and 50% higher-than-expected sales guidance, Gill spoke of the company’s favorable macroeconomic indices. Gill said Nvidia’s customers are racing to meet generative AI-based and large language model (LLM) demands. Meeting these demands will definitely augur well for Nvidia, its stock, and its valuation.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of America</a> (NYSE: BAC) senior analyst Vivek Arya described Nvidia’s latest quarterly sales forecast as the company’s most significant.  Arya and other analysts have now hiked their price targets on NVDA.  One analyst favored a staggering 64% upside on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Some analysts opine that Nvidia’s short-term explosive growth indicates the potential of generative AI as the next big growth driver. However, others remain reserved and wonder if the bullish AI phase would stand the test of time.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/">Nvidia Set to Join Apple, Microsoft, Amazon in the Trillion-Dollar Market Cap Group</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/nvidia-trillion-dollar-market-cap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hardware Wallet Provider Trezor Sees 900% Jump in Sales amid Ledger Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trezor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=256617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/">Hardware Wallet Provider Trezor Sees 900% Jump in Sales amid Ledger Controversy</a></p>
<p>The controversy surrounding Ledger's key-recovery service has boosted sales for its competitor Trezor. Besides, Trezor  also addressed concerns over security and develops an auditable secure element through its sister company Tropic Square.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/">Hardware Wallet Provider Trezor Sees 900% Jump in Sales amid Ledger Controversy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/">Hardware Wallet Provider Trezor Sees 900% Jump in Sales amid Ledger Controversy</a></p>
<p>The controversy surrounding Ledger&#8217;s recently released <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-ledger-delays-key-recovery-service/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">key-recovery service</a> has ultimately benefitted hardware wallet competitor Trezor. Hardware wallet manufacturer Trezor recently reported a 900% surge in week-on-week sales.</p>
<p>Recently, Ledger introduced the Ledger Recover service enabling users to securely store encrypted backups of their seed phrases through three custodians. This service allows users to restore their private keys in case of forgotten or lost seed phrases and requires KYC verification as an opt-in feature.</p>
<p>However, Ledger received a strong backlash from the community for the idea of sharing the seed phrases with anyone other than wallet owners. The community members also criticized Ledger for a breach of trust and privacy.</p>
<p>In response to the concerns shared by the community, Ledger decided to pause the release. The company said that it will be working on refactoring the code while prioritizing transparency and verifiability.</p>
<p>On the other hand, as a fully open-source company, Trezor undergoes regular audits by independent technical experts. This helps to ensure that its processes are secure and prevent any possibility of remote seed phrase extraction. Speaking on the development, Trezor CEO Matěj Žák said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In Trezor, we believe that hardware wallets – cold storages that promise 100% self-custody should, at no stage, make the seed phrase accessible to anyone but the user.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Hardware Wallet Trezor Addresses Concerns Over Old Vulnerability</h2>
<p>Recently, cybersecurity firm Unciphered stated that it has found a way to hack into Trezor&#8217;s T hardware wallet. This raised concerns regarding the security levels offered by the hardware wallet service provider.</p>
<p>Unciphered noted that it made use of an “unpatchable hardware vulnerability with the STM32 chip that allows us to dump the embedded flash and one-time programmable (OTP) data”.</p>
<p>Later, Trezor’s CTO Tomáš Sušánka clarified that the firm had identified the RDP downgrade attack vulnerability in a 2020 <a href="https://blog.trezor.io/our-response-to-the-read-protection-downgrade-attack-28d23f8949c6" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a>. Sušánka said that this attack “requires the physical theft of a device and highly sophisticated technical knowledge and advanced equipment. Even with the above, Trezors can be protected by a strong passphrase, which adds another layer of security that renders an RDP downgrade useless”.</p>
<p>Besides, he added that they have made significant progress in addressing this issue by creating the world&#8217;s first auditable and transparent secure element in collaboration with their sister company, Tropic Square.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gta-6-play-to-earn-model-crypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/">Hardware Wallet Provider Trezor Sees 900% Jump in Sales amid Ledger Controversy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wallet-trezor-jump-sales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4659 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1252469 metric#prefetches=204 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=16 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=96.94 metric#ms-cache=6.76 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1826 metric#ms-cache-ratio=7.0 -->