<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 20:39:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Who is Vitalik Buterin? Discover ETH Founder&#8217;s Home, Net Worth And Family</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/education/who-is-vitalik-buterin-discover-eth-founders-home-net-worth-and-family/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coingape Staff]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vitalik buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131277</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vitalik Buterin is the creator, writer, programmer, and developer of the cryptocurrency Ethereum. He rose to prominence after launching the cryptocurrency Ethereum. Between 2010 and 2011, he became involved in the world of cryptocurrency. He co-founded Ethereum with Joseph Lubin, Charles Hoskinson, Anthony Di Lorio, and Gavin Wood. Who is Vitalik Buterin? Vitalik Buterin was <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/education/who-is-vitalik-buterin-discover-eth-founders-home-net-worth-and-family/" title="Who is Vitalik Buterin? Discover ETH Founder&#8217;s Home, Net Worth And Family"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/education/who-is-vitalik-buterin-discover-eth-founders-home-net-worth-and-family/">Who is Vitalik Buterin? Discover ETH Founder&#8217;s Home, Net Worth And Family</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="801" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13180040/Vitalik1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Vitalik Buterin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vitalik_Buterin" rel="nofollow">Vitalik Buterin</a> is the creator, writer, programmer, and developer of the cryptocurrency Ethereum. He rose to prominence after launching the cryptocurrency Ethereum. Between 2010 and 2011, he became involved in the world of cryptocurrency. He co-founded Ethereum with Joseph Lubin, Charles Hoskinson, Anthony Di Lorio, and Gavin Wood.</p>
<h2>Who is Vitalik Buterin?</h2>
<p>Vitalik Buterin was born on January 31, 1994, in Kolomna, Russia. He is Dmitry and Natalia Buterin&#8217;s son. His father was a well-known computer scientist who assisted Vitalik in learning the intricacies of the field. Vitalik spent his first six years of life in Russia. Following that, his family left Russia for Canada to give him more opportunities than those available in his native country. He is currently a citizen of both Canada and the Russian Federation. Vitalik was gifted in math and computer programming from a young age. He received &#8220;gifted&#8221; student recognition all throughout his time in school.</p>
<h3><b>Buterin early education and student life</b></h3>
<p>Vitalik was enrolled in Abelard School, a private school in Toronto, after the Buterin family arrived in Canada. Buterin learned the fundamentals of bitcoin from his father when he was 17 years old. While Vitalik was interested in Bitcoin, he had no way of obtaining it. He lacked the equipment to mine coins and the funds to buy them. Instead, Vitalik found work writing blog posts about the topic. He received five bitcoins for each article he published. Vitalik Buterin would use that experience to co-found Bitcoin Magazine at the end of 2011.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><iframe title="15 Things You Didn’t Know About Vitalik Buterin" width="678" height="381" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fxJ6mjhi-J8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buterin decided to attend the University of Waterloo after graduating from high school. During that time, he took advanced cryptography courses and worked as a research assistant for Ian Goldberg, the former Tor Project board chairman and co-creator of Off-the-Record Messaging.</p>
<p>Vitalik took bronze in the International Olympiad in Informatics in 2012. With his success, he was able to collaborate with many other developers all over the world. Vitalik was still looking for new opportunities in 2014. Peter Thiel, a billionaire, established his own &#8220;Thiel Fellowship.&#8221; The organization offered Vitalik a $100,000 grant, prompting him to drop out of the University of Waterloo and focus full-time on Ethereum.</p>
<h3><b>The birth of Ethereum</b></h3>
<p>Buterin began developing <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ethereum-price-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> in order to address flaws that he saw in projects such as Bitcoin and published his whitepaper in 2013. Following this initial advance, Ethereum co-founder Gavin Wood published an Ethereum technical book. This describes how the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) works. EVM is the primary Ethereum technology on which the scripting-rich language demonstrates its full potential.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ok, I am going to just stop commenting on bitcoin issues almost entirely and focus on ethereum tech.</p>
<p>I think the community needs to go through *a lot* of healing, and the firebrands on all sides that are *so sure* that their side is righteous and the other evil deeply worry me.</p>
<p>&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/930288421045542913?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 14, 2017</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Buterin and his team were able to present the first fully functional version of Ethereum, Frontier, in 2015, after a lengthy crowdfunding campaign. With its activation, the Ethereum platform took off, and technological behemoths such as IBM and Microsoft became interested in the project.</p>
<p>The team raised over 31,000 BTC from the sale of ETH, which was approximately $18 million at the time. The Ethereum team established the Ethereum Foundation, a non-profit organisation based in Switzerland, to oversee the development of Ethereum&#8217;s open-source software.</p>
<p>Despite some turbulence, Ethereum&#8217;s crowdfunding campaign was a success. Overall, the Ethereum design is intended to follow several principles, including simplicity, universality, modularity, agility, non-discrimination, and non-censorship.</p>
<h3><b>Vitalik home and Family</b></h3>
<p>Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s father, Mr. Dumitry Buterin, is a computer scientist. He was married to Natalia Ameline at the time Vitalik was born. Mr. Dumitry later divorced Natalia and married another woman named Maia. Misha and Katya Buterin, Vitalik&#8217;s stepsisters, were born after his father married Maia. Vitalik used to live in Canada with his stepmother Maaia and biological father, Dumitry Buterin.</p>
<p>At the moment, Vitalik Buterin does not own a home. He spent the majority of his childhood and adolescence in Toronto, Canada. Furthermore, because Ethereum was founded in Switzerland, Vitalik spent several years there. He now resides in Singapore but travels to various countries on a regular basis.</p>
<h3><b>Vitalik Buterin Net Worth and Salary</b></h3>
<p>Vitalik Buterin, co-founder of the cryptocurrency Ethereum, programmer and author, has a fortune of $1 billion. The value of the Ethereum cryptocurrency that he owns is the primary source of his income. He also owns several other virtual currencies and is paid handsomely by the Ethereum Foundation.</p>
<p>However, Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s net worth fluctuates on a daily basis, sometimes dramatically, due to fluctuations in the value of cryptocurrencies. Vitalik also owns approximately 352,000 Ethereum currencies.</p>
<h3><b>Vitalik Buterin other investments</b></h3>
<p>He also owns Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Bitcoin (BTC), Dogecoin (DOGE), Zcash (ZEC), and other<a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> cryptocurrencies</a>. He has stated that the value of Buterin&#8217;s other currencies is less than 10% of the value of Ethereum.</p>
<p>Vitalik also owns tokens called OmiseGo (OMG), a Kyber Network token (KNC), Maker (MKR), and Augur (REP), with values that do not exceed 10% of the value of Ethereum.</p>
<p>In addition, the Ethereum Foundation pays him $144,000 per year. The payment is made in Swiss francs, making his annual salary 135,000 CHF. He also has corporate stakes in the startups Clearmatics and StarkWare. They&#8217;ve both made millions of dollars.</p>
<h4><b>Buterin&#8217;s Achievements and Philanthropy</b></h4>
<p>Buterin (who dropped out of university) has an honorary doctorate from the University of Basel in addition to receiving a Peter Thiel Fellowship for the development of Ethereum. His other achievements include a bronze medal in the 24th International Olympiad in Informatics in 2012.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ethereum&#39;s Vitalik Buterin Wins World Technology Network Award <a href="http://t.co/VyFJ0foSgY">http://t.co/VyFJ0foSgY</a> <a href="http://t.co/dq7qAFfuR8">pic.twitter.com/dq7qAFfuR8</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CoinDesk (@CoinDesk) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinDesk/status/535116460688154624?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 19, 2014</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Buterin is a very generous philanthropist. His contributions began in 2017, when he donated more than $750,000 in ETH to the Machine Intelligence Research Institute, an organization dedicated to the development of safer artificial intelligence. Buterin has since donated more than $1 billion in cryptocurrencies to various organizations around the world.</p>
<h3><b>Buterin&#8217;s Future Plans</b></h3>
<p>Along with Ethereum, Buterin is also working on L4, Plasma Group, and other blockchain projects. Buterin may be interested in contributing to the upcoming metaverse given his initial desire to make Ethereum a &#8220;world computer.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;The &#8220;<a href="https://coingape.com/blog/what-is-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">metaverse</a>&#8221; will happen, but I don&#8217;t think any of the existing corporate attempts to intentionally create the metaverse are going anywhere,&#8221; Buterin said in a tweet in July 2022.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The &quot;metaverse&quot; is going to happen but I don&#39;t think any of the existing corporate attempts to intentionally create the metaverse are going anywhere. <a href="https://t.co/tVUfq4CWmP">https://t.co/tVUfq4CWmP</a></p>
<p>&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1553526863783657472?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>This was a direct attack on Meta Platform&#8217;s founder and CEO, Mark Zuckerberg, as Meta, formerly known as Facebook, Therefore, despite being only 28, Buterin has already earned a place at the table of cryptocurrency entrepreneurs. Buterin might be the most significant figure in the entire crypto-sphere after Satoshi Nakamoto.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/education/who-is-vitalik-buterin-discover-eth-founders-home-net-worth-and-family/">Who is Vitalik Buterin? Discover ETH Founder&#8217;s Home, Net Worth And Family</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13180040/Vitalik1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Prediction: Market Recovery Sets ETH Prices For 8.8% jump</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/ethereum-price-prediction-market-recovery-sets-eth-prices-for-8-8-jump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=131335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Price Prediction: The Ethereum(ETH) price ended a consolidation phase with a long bullish candle breakout from $1300. Thus, this breakout indicates the buyers are ready to resume the prior recovery. The altcoin is currently in a retest phase, trying to attain sustainability above the flipped support.  Key points:  A High momentum breakout from the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/ethereum-price-prediction-market-recovery-sets-eth-prices-for-8-8-jump/" title="Ethereum Price Prediction: Market Recovery Sets ETH Prices For 8.8% jump"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/ethereum-price-prediction-market-recovery-sets-eth-prices-for-8-8-jump/">Ethereum Price Prediction: Market Recovery Sets ETH Prices For 8.8% jump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ethereum eth" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942.jpeg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-678x381.jpeg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-150x84.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethereum Price Prediction: The <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/heres-ethereum-eth-price-analysis-for-the-coming-week-buy-now/">Ethereum(ETH) price</a> ended a consolidation phase with a long bullish candle breakout from $1300. Thus, this breakout indicates the buyers are ready to resume the prior recovery. The altcoin is currently in a retest phase, trying to attain sustainability above the flipped support. </span></p>
<h2><b>Key points: </b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A High momentum breakout from the $1300 resistance indicates the buyers are confident in reaching a higher price</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The RSI indicator, which measures the speed and magnitude of an asset&#8217;s recent price movements, has surged into bullish territory.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Ether is $9.1 Billion, indicating an 85% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/q/qg4LbWWw.png" alt="Ethereum Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1109" />Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A recent V-shaped recovery from the $1080 support pushed the <a href="https://coingape.com/these-on-chain-indicators-offer-insight-into-the-next-ethereum-eth-price-action/">Ethereum price</a>s to $1300 local resistance. However, with the increasing uncertainty in the crypto market, this altcoin struggled to surpass the mentioned resistance and went sideways for around two weeks. Thus, the daily chart showed a narrow range formation between the $1300 and $1240 levels.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics today released November&#8217;s <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-us-cpi-inflation-falls-to-7-1-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-skyrockets/">Consumer Price Index (CPI)</a> data of 7.1%, down from 7.7% in October. This less-than-expected CPI hinted at decreasing inflation and caused a price recovery in crypto markets.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a result, the Ethereum price soars 3.5% and currently trades at the $1319 mark. The long bullish candle breached the $1300 monthly resistance, offering a suitable footing for buyers to lead prices higher.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, if the prices show sustainability above $1300, the buyers may drive the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoin</a> 8% higher to revisit the $1420 mark.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a contrary note, a daily candle closing below $1300 will undermine the bullish momentum and may extend the prevailing downtrend.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>MACD:</strong> the rising <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/macd-moving-average-convergence-divergnece/">MACD</a> and signal lines indicate growth in underlying bullishness. Moreover, a potential crossover of these slopes above the neutral line will accelerate the bullish momentum. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMAs:</strong> today’s price jump breached a dynamic resistance of 50-day EMA. However, if the coin witnessed a minor correction, this EMA could offer suitable support to resume price recovery.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethereum Coin Price Intraday Levels-</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $1229</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bearish  </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Medium</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance level- $1300  and $1420</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support level- $1160 and $1100</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/ethereum-price-prediction-market-recovery-sets-eth-prices-for-8-8-jump/">Ethereum Price Prediction: Market Recovery Sets ETH Prices For 8.8% jump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Hearing: CEO John J. Ray iii Claims &#8220;Embezzlement&#8221; Root Cause Of FTX Collapse</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/ftx-hearing-ceo-john-ray-claims-embezzlement-root-cause-of-ftx-collapse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131333</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In an ongoing Congressional hearing, FTX&#8217;s newly appointed chief executive John J Ray III had a mouthful to talk about the FTX and its founder, Sam Bankman-Fried. He told the panel that SBF &#8220;should have known&#8221; his actions and conflict of interest in the corporate relationship between the FTX crypto exchange and its trading arm <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-hearing-ceo-john-ray-claims-embezzlement-root-cause-of-ftx-collapse/" title="FTX Hearing: CEO John J. Ray iii Claims &#8220;Embezzlement&#8221; Root Cause Of FTX Collapse"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-hearing-ceo-john-ray-claims-embezzlement-root-cause-of-ftx-collapse/">FTX Hearing: CEO John J. Ray iii Claims &#8220;Embezzlement&#8221; Root Cause Of FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1472" height="1010" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/14011044/12f234d7-26a2-49ea-87db-9d4722178c1b-1-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="John J Ray" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>In an ongoing Congressional hearing, FTX&#8217;s newly appointed chief executive <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-ceo-john-j-ray-blasts-sbf-ahead-ftx-tomorrows-congressional-hearing/">John J Ray III</a> had a mouthful to talk about the FTX and its founder, Sam Bankman-Fried. He told the panel that SBF &#8220;should have known&#8221; his actions and conflict of interest in the corporate relationship between the FTX crypto exchange and its trading arm <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/alameda-research/">Alameda Research</a> would result in the empire&#8217;s final collapse.</p>
<h2>John J. Ray Grills SBF For FTX Crash</h2>
<p>In his remarks, Ray asserted that assets belonging to <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> customers were combined with those of Bankman-Fried&#8217;s trading company, Alameda. He further stated that the FTX exchange also made it possible for Alameda to efficiently borrow money without restrictions.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/manhattan-court-finds-ftx-founder-sbf-guilty-to-wire-fraud/">Manhattan Court Finds FTX Founder SBF Guilty To Wire Fraud</a></em></p>
<p>In the prepared testimony, he said that Alameda additionally used client funds for trades, subjecting them to significant losses.</p>
<h2>Investigation Baffles Congress</h2>
<p>John J Ray testified before a congressional committee on Tuesday that it was inherently dangerous for a corporation operating in the cryptocurrency sector to include its own tokens as an asset on its balance sheet. He mentioned this by citing the exchange&#8217;s native token, <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftt/">FTT</a>.</p>
<p>Additionally, Ray remarked on FTX&#8217;s use of Quickbooks, stating:</p>
<blockquote><p>[FTX] used Quickbooks — a multi-billion-dollar company using Quickbooks. Nothing against Quickbooks, very nice tool, just not for a multi-billion-dollar company.</p></blockquote>
<p><em><strong>Read More: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/">SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair</a></em></p>
<p>Representative Frank Lucas from Oklahoma stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>Bankman-Fried clearly tried to exhibit himself as the brightest of the bright, but being bright neither makes you honest nor a fool, does it?</p></blockquote>
<p>The quick use of profanity by <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sam-bankman-fried/">SBF</a> in his opening remarks was criticized by Missouri Representative <a rel='nofollow'  href="http://cleaver.house.gov/" rel="nofollow">Emanuel Cleaver</a> as being &#8220;extremely offensive&#8221; to Congress.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a title="“SBF Bought Political Influence,” Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-bought-political-influence-says-us-rep-will-it-save-him-with-jail-term/" rel="bookmark">“SBF Bought Political Influence,” Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?</a></em></p>
<p>In light of recent developments, the congressman continued, he would be thinking about presenting a resolution to rename cryptocurrency &#8220;creepy dough currency.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-hearing-ceo-john-ray-claims-embezzlement-root-cause-of-ftx-collapse/">FTX Hearing: CEO John J. Ray iii Claims &#8220;Embezzlement&#8221; Root Cause Of FTX Collapse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/14011044/12f234d7-26a2-49ea-87db-9d4722178c1b-1-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will This Move By Tether Finally Put All FUDs To Rest?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/this-move-by-tether-finally-put-all-fuds-to-rest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 17:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FUD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131328</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With mounting concerns over Tether&#8217;s growing number of secured loans and it being a reason for the stablecoin issuer&#8217;s eventual demise, Tether came out with an official announcement later today. The crypto firm is now planning to minimize its loan exposure to zero by the year 2023. Tether&#8217;s 2023 Goal According to its announcement, the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/this-move-by-tether-finally-put-all-fuds-to-rest/" title="Will This Move By Tether Finally Put All FUDs To Rest?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/this-move-by-tether-finally-put-all-fuds-to-rest/">Will This Move By Tether Finally Put All FUDs To Rest?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="600" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13230509/img_187217_tether_usdt_bg.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Tether FUD" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>With mounting concerns over Tether&#8217;s growing number of secured loans and it being a reason for the stablecoin issuer&#8217;s eventual demise, <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/tether/">Tether</a> came out with an official announcement later today. The crypto firm is now planning to minimize its loan exposure to zero by the year 2023.</p>
<h2>Tether&#8217;s 2023 Goal</h2>
<p>According to its <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://tether.to/en/tether-addresses-fud-around-secured-loans-reveals-plans-to-reduce-these-to-zero-in-2023/" rel="nofollow">announcement</a>, the internal team at Tether is prioritizing transparency, accountability and operational eminence to safeguard itself from any calamity. Unlike the growing number of crypto firms going bankrupt or on the brink of facing <a href="https://coingape.com/alameda-genesis-relationship-risks-dcg-bankruptcy-claims-messari-founder/">bankruptcy</a> risks due to high leverage, widespread fraud, and poor risk management, Tether plans to continue its 8-year long legacy forward.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/why-publish-your-usdt-reserves-tether-responds/">Why Doesn’t Tether Publish USDT Reserves” : Founder Responds</a></em></p>
<p>After The Wall Street Journal reported that the stablecoin operator&#8217;s growing list of loans would make it impossible for it to repay redemptions in the event of a crisis, Tether announced that it would remove all secured loans from its backing in 2023.</p>
<p>In response to the most recent attack on Tether, the company states that,</p>
<blockquote><p>Tether is professionally &amp; conservatively managed and this will be demonstrated once again by successfully winding down the lending business without losses</p></blockquote>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a title="Just-In: Tether CTO Criticizes Coinbase For Asking Users Convert USDT To USDC" href="https://coingape.com/tether-cto-coinbase-decision-switch-to-usdc/" rel="bookmark">Tether CTO Criticizes Coinbase For Asking Users Convert USDT To USDC</a></em></p>
<p>Additionally, the announcement further states that &#8220;The secured loans held in the reserves are overcollateralized and covered by extremely liquid assets&#8221;.</p>
<h2>$6.1 Billion In Loans</h2>
<p>According to the firm, as of September 30, its loans totaled $6.1 billion, or 9% of Tether&#8217;s total assets. In the third quarter, the group&#8217;s consolidated total assets even exceeded $68 billion.</p>
<p>Tether previously asserted that it would ensure that borrowers were provided highly liquid collateral for these loans, but now the operator apparently intends to do away with them entirely.</p>
<h2>Tether FUD followed By Binance</h2>
<p>The news comes after the collapse of the crypto exchange <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a>, and the more recent rumor surrounding <a href="https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/">Binance&#8217;s partial reserves</a> leading to a lingering fear among the crypto community.</p>
<p>Tether also recently introduced the <a href="https://coingape.com/tether-launches-offshore-chinese-yuan-cnh%E2%82%AE-on-tron/">Chinese Yuan (CNHT)</a> to its growing family of stablecoins which includes <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/usdt/">USDT, </a>EURT and <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/tether-mxnt/" rel="nofollow">MXNT</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/this-move-by-tether-finally-put-all-fuds-to-rest/">Will This Move By Tether Finally Put All FUDs To Rest?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13230509/img_187217_tether_usdt_bg.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Twitter Explodes Over Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Arrest</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-twitter-explodes-over-sam-bankman-frieds-arrest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gaurav Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 17:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX CEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SBF was arrested by the Royal Bahamas Police after learning that the US government has filed criminal charges against him. Sam Bankman-Fried said that he doesn’t think he will be arrested when asked about the possibility on 12 December in an interview with Unusual Whales. The crypto community, including politicians, influencers, and crypto executives, had <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-twitter-explodes-over-sam-bankman-frieds-arrest/" title="Crypto Twitter Explodes Over Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Arrest"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-twitter-explodes-over-sam-bankman-frieds-arrest/">Crypto Twitter Explodes Over Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Arrest</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1040" height="693" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09233925/swarajya_2022-11_c4729cdd-0b00-432a-888c-e403b949e0a0_1200x_1_89.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="sbf arrested" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>SBF was arrested by the Royal Bahamas Police after learning that the US government has filed criminal charges against him. Sam Bankman-Fried said that he doesn’t think he will be arrested when asked about the possibility on 12 December in an interview with Unusual Whales.</p>
<blockquote><p>The crypto community, including politicians, influencers, and crypto executives, had their fair share of say about the publicly hated FTX founder.</p></blockquote>
<p>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, the New York Democratic Representative, tweeted, &#8216;Bankman-Fried was set to testify before the House tomorrow. Tonight he was arrested. While I am disappointed we will not have the opportunity to present our line of questioning, we look forward to more information coming to light and justice being served in this case.&#8217;</p>
<p><iframe title="Crypto Twitter Explodes Over the Sam Bankman-Fried&#039;s Arrest" width="678" height="381" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LyA5avOWD9U?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Bankman-Fried was set to testify before the House tomorrow. Tonight he was arrested.</p>
<p>While I am disappointed we will not have the opportunity to present our line of questioning, we look forward to more information coming to light and justice being served in this case. <a href="https://t.co/HS9u1n5Kur">https://t.co/HS9u1n5Kur</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (@AOC) <a href="https://twitter.com/AOC/status/1602470171364712449?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 13, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div>
<p>United States Senator <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/SenToomey/status/1601231211640201216?s=20&amp;t=8OMXncm4cGpQ8KWq82dSwQ" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Cynthia Lummis</a> said that the officials took the right call to hold the former CEO of FTX accountable for the “good, old-fashioned fraud” that he committed.</p>
<div><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/TrungTPhan/status/1602465478051794945?s=20&amp;t=8OMXncm4cGpQ8KWq82dSwQ" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Trung Phan</a>, the co-host of Not Investment Advice, tweeted that SBF’s irresponsible public behavior will make his defense attorney’s job much harder.&#8217; Meanwhile, the crypto community took this opportunity to make fun of SBF and enjoy his downfall for having robbed them of billions. There were tons of memes related to SBF following his arrest.</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-twitter-explodes-over-sam-bankman-frieds-arrest/">Crypto Twitter Explodes Over Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Arrest</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09233925/swarajya_2022-11_c4729cdd-0b00-432a-888c-e403b949e0a0_1200x_1_89.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Wanted To Keep SEC Out Of Crypto Regulation: FTX Hearing</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/sbf-wanted-to-keep-sec-out-of-crypto-regulation-ftx-hearing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FTX Hearing News: The Congressional hearing on the FTX crisis is turning out to be very interesting with the comments from CEO John J. Ray III. As Sam Bankman-Fried continues to be in police custody in the Bahamas, CEO John Ray testified before the committee on Tuesday. In a latest, the Congress representatives said SBF <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-wanted-to-keep-sec-out-of-crypto-regulation-ftx-hearing/" title="SBF Wanted To Keep SEC Out Of Crypto Regulation: FTX Hearing"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-wanted-to-keep-sec-out-of-crypto-regulation-ftx-hearing/">SBF Wanted To Keep SEC Out Of Crypto Regulation: FTX Hearing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/29135150/ftx-logo-1668407425.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ftx" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>FTX Hearing News</strong>: The Congressional hearing on the FTX crisis is turning out to be very interesting with the comments from CEO John J. Ray III. As Sam Bankman-Fried continues to be in police custody in the Bahamas, CEO John Ray testified before the committee on Tuesday. In a latest, the Congress representatives said SBF wanted to keep the US Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) away from the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/cryptocurrency-market/">crypto industry</a>. Meanwhile, the crypto market reacted positively to the news of SBF arrest on Tuesday.</p>
<p>In the last 24 hours, Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) prices rose by 5% and 6% respectively, in the last 24 hours, according to price tracking platform <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>. As of writing, BTC price stands at $17,757, while that of ETH stands at $1,327.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-move-442-million-xrp-court-grants-deadline-motion/">XRP News: Whales Move 442 Million XRP; Court Grants Deadline Motion</a></p>
<h2>&#8220;SEC Out Of Crypto&#8221;</h2>
<p>During the hearing, Congress Representative <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/YahooFinance/status/1602696655291097089" rel="nofollow">Brad Sherman</a> began his statement with the mention of &#8220;inmate 14372&#8221; referring to SBF. He said the popular crypto personality had actually one intention, which was to prevent the SEC from regulating crypto industry. The hearing comes at a time when another major crypto exchange <a href="https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/">Binance is facing criticism</a> for its financial reserves policy.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Now Sam Bankman-Fried, or should I say inmate 14372, had one purpose in all of his efforts here in Congress. He&#8217;s a well-known figure, only one wearing shorts. His one purpose was to keep the SEC out of crypto.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier, CEO John Ray spoke about the irregularities in recordkeeping at FTX. He said there was literally no recordkeeping at FTX whatsoever. The CEO added that in terms of governance, there was no distinction between FTX and Alameda Research. Also, FTX is conducting the bankruptcy operations in an unprecedented way in paperless mode, he said. It was also revealed that FTX had lost over $7 billion in value.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/">Where Is BNB Coin Price Headed To Amid Binance FUD And Withdrawals?</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-wanted-to-keep-sec-out-of-crypto-regulation-ftx-hearing/">SBF Wanted To Keep SEC Out Of Crypto Regulation: FTX Hearing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/29135150/ftx-logo-1668407425.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: How Far BTC May Prolong Its Ongoing Rally?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-how-far-btc-may-prolong-its-ongoing-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=131327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Price Prediction: The Bitcoin price shows the formation of a rising parallel channel pattern in the daily time frame chart. The technical setup carries a bull trend within two parallel walking trendlines and offers multiple entry opportunities at the support trendline. However, the coin price current moving near the pattern resistance trendline indicates a <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-how-far-btc-may-prolong-its-ongoing-rally/" title="Bitcoin Price Prediction: How Far BTC May Prolong Its Ongoing Rally?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-how-far-btc-may-prolong-its-ongoing-rally/">Bitcoin Price Prediction: How Far BTC May Prolong Its Ongoing Rally?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28131750/bitcoin1.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction BTC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Prediction: The Bitcoin price shows the formation of a rising parallel channel pattern in the daily time frame chart. The technical setup carries a bull trend within two parallel walking trendlines and offers multiple entry opportunities at the support trendline. However, the coin price current moving near the pattern resistance trendline indicates a <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-prediction-analyst-predicts-a-pull-back-before-bitcoin-bull-run/">minor pullback</a> is possible before the next recovery jump.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points:</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A rising parallel channel pattern governs Bitcoin’s price recovery</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The recent price jump reclaimed the 20-and-50-day EMAs, offering additional support levels to prolong price recovery. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Bitcoin is $25.8 Billion, indicating a 31% gain.</span></li>
</ul>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why Is The Bitcoin Price Gaining Today?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On December 13th Tuesday, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics disclosed the Consumer Price Index (CPI) data for November. The report showed the <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-us-cpi-inflation-falls-to-7-1-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-skyrockets/">November CPI data of 7.1%,</a> down from 7.7% in October.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A less-than-expected CPI accentuates the cooling inflation and bolsters US Fed to be less aggressive with the interest rate hike. Thus, the leniency in the interest rate hike will allow several businesses to borrow loans from banks with reasonable interest rates and eventually help in economic growth.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, the price jump pushed Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance rate above 41%, the highest since October 29th.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/y/Y07CAs9w.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction" width="1562" height="818" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past two weeks, Bitcoin has struggled to break a local resistance of $17300. This power struggled to reclaim higher levels, created a sense of uncertainty in the crypto market, and led the majority of altcoins on a sideways rally.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the Bitcoin price witnessed a significant inflow today and jumped 3.3%. The long bullish candle assisted buyers in surpassing the weekly resistance of resistance $17300, suggesting the resumption of prior recovery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moreover, the rising price action revealed that Bitcoin follows an <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/parallel-channel-pattern/">ascending parallel channel</a>; pattern. By the press time, the Bitcoin price trades at $17740 and retests the pattern’s resistance trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A usual reaction to the current situation would be that Bitcoin price will turn down from the overhead trendline and plunge back to support. However, untill this support trendline is intact, the recovery will continue to raise the BTC price higher.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, the next bull cycle within this pattern could push the prices to the $18500 mark.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the contrary note, a breakdown below the pattern’s support trendline will undermine the recovery rally and may trigger a significant correction.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical investor:</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Bollinger band indicator:</strong> the rising price hit the indicator’s upper band, suggesting a sudden growth within a short span. Thus, a minor pullback is expected to check price sustainability at higher levels.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative Strength Index:</strong> An upswing in the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> above the neutral indicator, the market sentiment favors Bitcoin growth.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $17782</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bullish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Low</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $18500 and $19600</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $17300 and $16700</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-price-prediction-how-far-btc-may-prolong-its-ongoing-rally/">Bitcoin Price Prediction: How Far BTC May Prolong Its Ongoing Rally?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28131750/bitcoin1.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Manhattan Court Finds FTX Founder SBF Guilty To Wire Fraud</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/manhattan-court-finds-ftx-founder-sbf-guilty-to-wire-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The FTX founder has found himself in a whirlwind of federal indictments today, with the Securities And Exchange Commission charging Sam Bankman-Fried with defrauding investors by using billions of dollars in customer funds for undisclosed venture capital, and now also by the Manhattan federal court, where SBF has been charged with conspiracy to commit wire <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/manhattan-court-finds-ftx-founder-sbf-guilty-to-wire-fraud/" title="Breaking: Manhattan Court Finds FTX Founder SBF Guilty To Wire Fraud"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/manhattan-court-finds-ftx-founder-sbf-guilty-to-wire-fraud/">Breaking: Manhattan Court Finds FTX Founder SBF Guilty To Wire Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="720" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13212129/hhhjial999-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="sbf manhattan" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> founder has found himself in a whirlwind of federal indictments today, with the Securities And Exchange Commission charging <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sam-bankman-fried/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> with defrauding investors by using billions of dollars in customer funds for undisclosed venture capital, and now also by the Manhattan federal court, where SBF has been charged with conspiracy to commit wire fraud among many others.</p>
<h2>SBF&#8217;s Manhattan Indictment</h2>
<p>According to an indictment presented by the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/united-states/">United States</a> Attorney for the Southern District of New York, the founder of FTX, Samuel Bankman-Fried, was charged with eight counts of criminal offenses, including conspiracy and wire fraud, for the alleged misuse of customer cash.</p>
<p>The indictment brings allegations of wire fraud, commodities fraud, securities fraud, and money laundering against Bankman-Fried in connection with an alleged plot to redirect FTX customer cash to the SBF-owned cryptocurrency hedge fund,  <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/alameda-research/">Alameda Research</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong></em> <em><a href="https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/">SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair</a></em></p>
<p>Additionally, he has also been accused of breaking campaign funding laws by conspiring with others to make corporate contributions to political candidates and committees that exceeded the $25,000 yearly cap and making donations in other people&#8217;s names to circumvent that cap.</p>
<h2>SBF&#8217;s Fall From Grace</h2>
<p>The probe has been front-lined by the Complex Frauds and Cybercrime Unit at the Southern District of New York U.S. Attorney’s Office.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a title="“SBF Bought Political Influence,” Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-bought-political-influence-says-us-rep-will-it-save-him-with-jail-term/" rel="bookmark">“SBF Bought Political Influence,” Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?</a></em></p>
<p>Bankman-Fried, the once poster boy of the crypto industry, was taken into custody in the Bahamas on Monday evening, less than a month after the dramatic collapse of the FTX <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/">exchange</a> sent shockwaves through the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/">cryptocurrency</a> world.</p>
<h2>Multiple Charges Levied</h2>
<p>Tuesday turned out to be an eventful day for the United States <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sec/">Securities and Exchange Commission</a> (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), as both agencies brought civil enforcement actions before the federal court in New York.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> </em><em><a title="Here’s What SBF Planned To Say In His Testimony Today" href="https://coingape.com/heres-what-sbf-planned-to-say-in-his-testimony-today/" rel="bookmark">Here’s What SBF Planned To Say In His Testimony Today</a></em></p>
<p>According to a representative for the U.S. Attorney&#8217;s Office, Bankman-Fried has not yet been extradited to the United States.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/manhattan-court-finds-ftx-founder-sbf-guilty-to-wire-fraud/">Breaking: Manhattan Court Finds FTX Founder SBF Guilty To Wire Fraud</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13212129/hhhjial999-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;SBF Bought Political Influence,&#8221; Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/sbf-bought-political-influence-says-us-rep-will-it-save-him-with-jail-term/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 14:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With the gradual unfolding of the high-pitched drama surrounding the FTX collapse and its founder Sam Bankman-Fried, the community stands divided on the various tactics exercised by SBF to gain prominence in the industry. From loaning out $43 million to crypto news media company TheBlock to donating prominent political candidates for their election campaigns &#8212; <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-bought-political-influence-says-us-rep-will-it-save-him-with-jail-term/" title="&#8220;SBF Bought Political Influence,&#8221; Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-bought-political-influence-says-us-rep-will-it-save-him-with-jail-term/">&#8220;SBF Bought Political Influence,&#8221; Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="650" height="488" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13184239/ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-fried.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="sbf political influence" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>With the gradual unfolding of the high-pitched drama surrounding the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> collapse and its founder Sam Bankman-Fried, the community stands divided on the various tactics exercised by SBF to gain prominence in the industry. From loaning out $43 million to crypto news media company <a href="https://coingape.com/sbfs-alameda-research-secretly-financed-the-block-crypto-news-website/">TheBlock</a> to donating prominent <a href="https://coingape.com/just-in-sbf-political-donations-can-be-reclaimed-as-fraudulent-transfers/">political candidates</a> for their election campaigns &#8212; SBF penetrated deep into reshaping his image as the next crypto messiah.</p>
<h2>SBF&#8217;s Political Goals</h2>
<p>The 30-year old cryptocurrency wunderkind <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sam-bankman-fried/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> has splurged tens of millions of dollars over the past year trying to alter the way Washington and the rest of the world viewed cryptocurrencies and other digital assets.</p>
<p>In just three years, he built the industry-leading <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/crypto-exchange-2/">cryptocurrency exchange</a> FTX, which was reportedly valued at $32 billion. He rose from anonymity to become the second-largest Democratic donor in the midterm elections, gaining massive political clout, with a few extremely influential officials.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a title="FTX News: SBF Says Senate Hearing “Not Currently Scheduled” For Attending" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-sbf-journey-from-jp-morgan-con-artist/" rel="bookmark">SBF Says Senate Hearing “Not Currently Scheduled” For Attending</a></em></p>
<p>According to OpenSecrets, a nonprofit located in Washington, D.C., the founder and former CEO of FTX contributed about $40 million to <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/democratic-elections/">Democrats this election cycle</a>, second only to George Soros, who distributed around $128 million.</p>
<h2>Reasons For Political Influence</h2>
<p>In a recent interview on CNBC&#8217;s episode of <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1602647911690633217" rel="nofollow">Squawk Box</a>, when asked whether or not the now-behind-bars founder &#8220;bought Washington&#8221; &#8212; implying to the term of buying political power through donations, the U.S. Representative, Patrick McHenry acknowledged the fact by saying &#8220;he [SBF] tried&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">&quot;Wouldn&#39;t it be easy to change the rules so that the SEC could protect investor interest?&quot; <a href="https://twitter.com/BeckyQuick?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BeckyQuick</a> asks <a href="https://twitter.com/PatrickMcHenry?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@PatrickMcHenry</a> about <a href="https://twitter.com/FTX_Official?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FTX_Official</a>: <a href="https://t.co/Qw1YOJieTm">pic.twitter.com/Qw1YOJieTm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Squawk Box (@SquawkCNBC) <a href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1602648889810903041?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 13, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Patrick emphasizes on the fact that, in <a href="https://coingape.com/sbf-chat-leak-now-cz-is-a-hero-says-sbf-after-ftx-crash/">SBF&#8217;s interview with Vox</a>, it shows that &#8220;he was a manipulator of world-class capacity and he&#8217;s trying to pull off something that was light-touch regulation for his platform&#8221;</p>
<p>While talking about Bankman-Fried&#8217;s actual reason for gaining political traction, Patrick states that,</p>
<blockquote><p>He worked with the Securities Exchange Commission and the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/cftc-cryptocurrency/">CFTC</a>, seeking out a commodity regulatories regime for his platform. So, what I&#8217;m looking at is a proper balance so that consumers will not fall prey to any successor of FTX.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Donations Being Returned?</h2>
<p>However, it doesn&#8217;t seem all good with the FTX founder&#8217;s political ambitions, as few of the political candidates who he donated to, are returning their funds back. The total returned or re-donated contributions represent almost $1.2 million of Bankman-Fried’s political contributions, which is roughly 3% of all his campaign donations.</p>
<p>And with the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sec/">SEC</a> charging him with fraud, hours before his <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-ceo-john-j-ray-blasts-sbf-ahead-ftx-tomorrows-congressional-hearing/">Congressional hearing</a>, on late Monday evening, things look pretty bleak for SBF &#8212; crypto&#8217;s once shining star.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong></em> <em><a href="https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/">SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair</a></em></p>
<p>In the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/united-states/">United States</a>, deceiving investors can result in sentences of more than 10 years in prison.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-bought-political-influence-says-us-rep-will-it-save-him-with-jail-term/">&#8220;SBF Bought Political Influence,&#8221; Says US Rep; Will It Save Him With Jail Term?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13184239/ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-fried.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: US CPI Inflation Falls To 7.1%, Bitcoin And Ethereum Price Skyrockets</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/breaking-us-cpi-inflation-falls-to-7-1-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-skyrockets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumer Price Index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) prices skyrocketed after the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics released the Consumer Price Index (CPI) data for November. The CPI in the US falls to 7.1% from 7.7% in October. The expected CPI data for November was 7.3%.  Bitcoin (BTC) price rallied over 3% after the inflation data. In the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-us-cpi-inflation-falls-to-7-1-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-skyrockets/" title="Breaking: US CPI Inflation Falls To 7.1%, Bitcoin And Ethereum Price Skyrockets"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-us-cpi-inflation-falls-to-7-1-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-skyrockets/">Breaking: US CPI Inflation Falls To 7.1%, Bitcoin And Ethereum Price Skyrockets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1260" height="841" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/10155403/190599647515011-1260x841-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Breaking: US CPI Inflation Falls To 7.1%, Bitcoin And Ethereum Price Skyrockets" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) prices skyrocketed after the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics released the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/consumer-price-index-cpi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Consumer Price Index</a> (CPI) data for November. <span class="headlines-description">The CPI in the US falls to 7.1% from 7.7% in October. The expected CPI data for November was 7.3%. </span></p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) price rallied over 3% after the inflation data. In the last 24 hours, the BTC price is now up 6% from a low of $16,944, hitting a high of $17,905. The trading volume rises over 25%, indicating participation from traders.</p>
<p>Ethereum (ETH) price also rallied over 3% after the CPI release, with the current price trading at $1,336. The 24-hour low and high are $1,246 and $1,338, respectively, indicating a rally of over 7%. The trading volume rose 35% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2>US CPI Inflation For November Comes In At 7.1%</h2>
<p><span class="headlines-description">The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics on December 13 <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.bls.gov/news.release/cpi.nr0.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> the November CPI data of 7.1% against the market expectations of 7.3%. The Core CPI comes in at 6.0% against the expected 6.1% in November, falling from 6.3% in October. </span></p>
<p><span class="headlines-description">The energy index increased by 13.1%, and the food index was up by 10.6 %, all of these increases were smaller than for the period ending October. However, compared to the previous month, the CPI edged up 0.1% only, less than forecasts of 0.3%.</span></p>
<p>Wall Street also expected the CPI data to come in lower as a result of cooling inflation. U.S. stocks jumped Monday, with investors anticipating softer inflation and a smaller interest-rate increase from the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/federal-reserve-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve</a> this week. The Dow Jones futures are up 2.5% on Tuesday, and the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq futures are up nearly 2.8% and 3.5%.</p>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-crash-incoming-after-us-cpi-and-fed-rate-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-b88u0q r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">JPMorgan</span></a><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> predicts a 10% rally in stocks if the U.S. </span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-b88u0q r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">CPI</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> comes in at 6.9% or lower. However, JPMorgan expected a CPI reading of 7.2%. While the U.S. stock market showed less correlation with the crypto market in recent times, the lower CPI also helped Bitcoin and Ethereum price rally.</span></p>
<p>Popular analysts <a href="https://coingape.com/popular-analysts-predict-bitcoin-and-ethereum-prices-for-christmas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Michael van de Poppe and “Wolf of Wall Street” Jordan Belfort</a> predicted that Bitcoin and Ethereum prices could rally by Christmas, with US CPI and Fed rate hike being the crucial factors indicating the crypto market bottom.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price To Rally More With Dovish Fed</h2>
<p>The fall in November CPI will influence the Federal Reserve’s interest rate hike decision the next day. <a href="https://coingape.com/fed-chair-jerome-powell-interest-rate-hike-inflation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fed Chair Jerome Powell earlier indicated</a> a slowdown in the rate hike pace in December and the coming months.</p>
<p>According to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">CME FedWatch Tool</a>, a probability of a 50 bps rate hike before the CPI number was 72.3%. After the CPI data, a probability of a 50 bps rate hike jumped over 80%.</p>
<p>The <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/index/dxy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">US Dollar Index</a> fell by 1.30% to 103.70 after the CPI numbers. Thus, investors can expect an increase in Bitcoin and Ethereum prices in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-price-breaks-higher-wall-street-expectations-on-us-cpi-inflation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin And Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street On US CPI</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/breaking-us-cpi-inflation-falls-to-7-1-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-skyrockets/">Breaking: US CPI Inflation Falls To 7.1%, Bitcoin And Ethereum Price Skyrockets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/10155403/190599647515011-1260x841-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where Is BNB Coin Price Headed To Amid Binance FUD And Withdrawals?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 14:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance (BNB) Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance BNB Coin Price News: Small and retail crypto traders are still struggling to come to terms with the adverse impacts of the FTX bankruptcy. In this context, major crypto exchange Binance stayed away from the FTX related contagion. In fact, the exchange benefitted from the Sam Bankman-Fried crypto empire collapse with many traders trusting <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/" title="Where Is BNB Coin Price Headed To Amid Binance FUD And Withdrawals?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/">Where Is BNB Coin Price Headed To Amid Binance FUD And Withdrawals?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/22165905/bnb1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Binance BNB" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Binance BNB Coin Price News</strong>: Small and retail crypto traders are still struggling to come to terms with the adverse impacts of the FTX bankruptcy. In this context, major crypto exchange Binance stayed away from the FTX related contagion. In fact, the exchange benefitted from the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sam-bankman-fried/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> crypto empire collapse with many traders trusting Binance to be safe. However, it appears that CZ&#8217;s crypto exchange just started to face the heat from the regulators as well as traders.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-price-breaks-higher-wall-street-expectations-on-us-cpi-inflation/">Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street Expectations On US CPI Inflation</a></p>
<h2>Binance FUD News</h2>
<p>In the last few days, reports suggested that the exchange is yet to provide meaningful financial data to boost investor confidence. Following the crypto bloodbath due to FTX collapse, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/binance/">Binance</a> CEO CZ proposed that all the exchanges publish the proof of reserves to encourage full transparency. This was supposed to be a protective measure that would also restore confidence in the crypto companies.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the crypto community expressed concerns over a report on Binance reserves the exchange released recently. The Binance <a href="https://coingape.com/how-proof-of-reserve-works/">proof of reserves</a> essentially mean the volume of assets it holds in custody for its users. Amid all the FUD around Binance reserves, the BNB Coin Price is trading in the red while most cryptocurrencies are following an upward curve. As of writing, BNB price stands at $272, down 5.50% in the last one week, according to price tracking platform <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" rel="nofollow">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/top-3-metaverse-tokens-to-buy-in-the-dip-before-2023-apecoin-decentraland-the-sandbox/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">Top 3 Metaverse Tokens To Buy In The Dip Before 2023- Apecoin, Decentraland, The Sandbox</a></p>
<h2>BUSD Big Whale Tranaction</h2>
<p>On the other side, whales appear to be trying to be on the safer side. A whale alert on BUSD was found with the transfer of 300 million BUSD. The <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/ethereum/0xbc86cbbffe24d53f3835f62902214753ee7537108dde9de37688c7902551a2e2" rel="nofollow">big whale transaction</a> was made from an unknown wallet to Paxos Treasury.</p>
<p>Know More: <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-move-442-million-xrp-court-grants-deadline-motion/">Whales Move 442 Million XRP; Court Grants Deadline Motion</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bnb-coin-price-binance-news-withdrawals/">Where Is BNB Coin Price Headed To Amid Binance FUD And Withdrawals?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/22165905/bnb1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP News: Whales Move 442 Million XRP; Court Grants Deadline Motion</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-move-442-million-xrp-court-grants-deadline-motion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xrp price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP News: The US district court granted the motion pushed by the US SEC and Ripple to set a deadline for the non parties to ask to seal any portions of the Summary Judgment material. The proposed deadline was set to be of January 4, 2023. However, this hasn’t stopped the crypto whale from accumulating <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-move-442-million-xrp-court-grants-deadline-motion/" title="XRP News: Whales Move 442 Million XRP; Court Grants Deadline Motion"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-move-442-million-xrp-court-grants-deadline-motion/">XRP News: Whales Move 442 Million XRP; Court Grants Deadline Motion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="801" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/18192715/Ripple_image_extra-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="xrp news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>XRP News:</strong> The US district court granted the motion pushed by the US SEC and Ripple to set a deadline for the non parties to ask to seal <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-deadline-whales-move-143-million-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">any portions of the Summary Judgment</a> material. The proposed deadline was set to be of January 4, 2023. However, this hasn’t stopped the crypto whale from accumulating XRP tokens.</p>
<h2>XRP whales on a move</h2>
<p>As per the data provided by WhaleAlert, crypto whales have moved more than 442 million XRP tokens (approx worth $170 million) in multiple transactions over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Crypto whales bought 156 million XRP tokens (worth approx $60 million) over the past day. However, most of the transactions came from the Binance crypto exchange. While the largest recorded transaction has been of adding $18.8 million worth of XRP tokens.</p>
<p>However, more than <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1602443188190445570" target="_blank" rel="noopener">188.5 million XRP tokens</a> (approx worth $72.8) were moved from unknown wallets to others.</p>
<p>The global crypto market registered a broad recovery on Tuesday. XRP price surged by around 3% in the last 24 hours. While XRP is trading at an average price of $0.385, at the press time. Its 24 hour trading volume stands at $943 million.</p>
<p>However, XRP is still holding a market cap of over $19.4 billion while facing legal troubles from the US SEC.</p>
<h2>Whales booking profit?</h2>
<p>Data also depicts that the whales have moved a bulk of XRP tokens to the crypto exchanges amid the price surge. More than 98 million XRP tokens (approx worth $38 million) were sent to exchanges in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>Over 68 million XRP tokens (approx worth $26 million) were sent to the Bitstamp crypto exchange in multiple transactions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-whales-move-442-million-xrp-court-grants-deadline-motion/">XRP News: Whales Move 442 Million XRP; Court Grants Deadline Motion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/18192715/Ripple_image_extra-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gala Games Crypto Price Prediction: Here’s Why It May Rise 30% In Coming Weeks?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/gala-games-crypto-price-prediction-heres-why-it-may-rise-30-in-coming-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GALA price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=131308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gala Games Crypto Price Prediction: The GALA coin price falling under the influence of two converging trendlines showcased the formation of a wedge pattern in the daily time frame chart. Though this pattern is currently carrying a downtrend, in theory, it is marked as a bullish continuation pattern. Here’s how this pattern may influence the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/gala-games-crypto-price-prediction-heres-why-it-may-rise-30-in-coming-weeks/" title="Gala Games Crypto Price Prediction: Here’s Why It May Rise 30% In Coming Weeks?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/gala-games-crypto-price-prediction-heres-why-it-may-rise-30-in-coming-weeks/">Gala Games Crypto Price Prediction: Here’s Why It May Rise 30% In Coming Weeks?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/27000145/gala-1200.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Gala Games Hack Update: Binance Discusses Recovery Plans" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://coingape.com/blog/year-ender-top-metaverse-projects-to-invest-in-2023-heres-the-list/">Gala Games</a> Crypto Price Prediction: The GALA coin price falling under the influence of two converging trendlines showcased the formation of a <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/wedge-pattern/">wedge pattern</a> in the daily time frame chart. Though this pattern is currently carrying a downtrend, in theory, it is marked as a bullish continuation pattern. Here’s how this pattern may influence the near future price of GALA coin. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points: </span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lower price rejection candles at 0.024 project a higher chance for a bullish reversal.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rising RSI indicator slope indicates the market sentiment is gradually leaning on buying side.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in the GALA is $42.5 Million indicating a 6.2% loss.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/5/5Ejn73P2.png" alt="Gala Games Crypto Price Prediction" width="1946" height="1109" />Source-Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Narrowing price action within the wedge pattern indicates that the seller failed to carry deeper corrections, reflecting a loss of bearish momentum. Moreover, this pattern will signal a sign of recovery when the GALA price breaks the pattern’s resistance trendline.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, amid the ongoing <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-ethereum-price-prediction-heres-how-bitcoin-may-escape-ongoing-uncertainty/">uncertainty in the crypto market, t</a>he GALA coin price is trapped within a narrow range. Thus It has been nearly a month since the altcoin resonated between $0.28 and $0.24 horizontal levels.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By the price time, the GALA price trades at $0.245 and shows signs of reversal from the $0.24 support. This potential bullish reversal should drive the price 15% higher to hit the range resistance of $0.282.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moreover, if the market sentiment favors buyers, an upside breakout from $0.28 will intensify the buying pressure and may prolong the price rally by another 15% to reach the combined resistance of the downsloping trendline and $0.323.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conversely, a daily candle below the $0.24 support will prolong the prevailing downtrend to the support trendline.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMAs:</strong> the downsloping EMAs(20, 50, 100, and 200) reflect an established downtrend in GALA price. Moreover, if the prices tried to rise higher, each of these EMAs stands as significant resistance and undermines bullish growth.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative Strength Index:</strong> the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI slope</a> is rising despite a sideways price action, accentuating the buying pressure is growth within a range. This so-called bullish divergence indicates a higher possibility for 30% growth in GALA.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">GALA intraday price levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot price: $0.024</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bearish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Medium</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance level- $0.281 and $0.32</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support level- $0.24 and 0.2</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/gala-games-crypto-price-prediction-heres-why-it-may-rise-30-in-coming-weeks/">Gala Games Crypto Price Prediction: Here’s Why It May Rise 30% In Coming Weeks?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/27000145/gala-1200.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Guide To Different Color Check Marks On Twitter</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/a-guide-to-different-color-check-marks-on-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=131307</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/a-guide-to-different-color-check-marks-on-twitter/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09120915/Poster-Image-68.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="A Guide To Different Color Check Marks On Twitter"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/a-guide-to-different-color-check-marks-on-twitter/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09120915/Poster-Image-68.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="A Guide To Different Color Check Marks On Twitter"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09120915/Poster-Image-68.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s How Much Indian Govt Collected From Taxing Crypto</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/heres-how-much-indian-govt-collected-from-taxing-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=131264</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/heres-how-much-indian-govt-collected-from-taxing-crypto/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13180048/poster74.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Here&#8217;s How Much Indian Govt Collected From Taxing Crypto"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/heres-how-much-indian-govt-collected-from-taxing-crypto/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13180048/poster74.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Here&#8217;s How Much Indian Govt Collected From Taxing Crypto"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13180048/poster74.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nishant Shukla]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf alameda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec chairman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Staes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission, chairperson, Gary Gensler charged FTX&#8217;s former CEO Sam Bankman Fried with indulging in fraudulent activity. Garry Gensler slams SBF over defrauding customers and said &#8220;Sam Bankman-Fried built a house of cards on a foundation of deception while telling investors that it was one of the safest buildings in crypto.&#8221; SBF <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/" title="SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/">SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13121221/SBF-jail.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="SBF Arrested" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The Securities and Exchange Commission, chairperson, Gary Gensler charged FTX&#8217;s former CEO Sam Bankman Fried with indulging in fraudulent activity. Garry Gensler <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-219" rel="nofollow">slams SBF over defrauding customers</a> and said &#8220;Sam Bankman-Fried built a house of cards on a foundation of deception while telling investors that it was one of the safest buildings in crypto.&#8221;</p>
<h2>SBF uses customer funds for real estate purchases</h2>
<p>As per the accusation, former FTX founder SBF concealed information about the company&#8217;s money-mixing practices with Alameda Research, the &#8220;special treatment&#8221; accorded to Alameda, and the use of client cash for business ventures, political contributions, and &#8220;lavish real estate purchases.&#8221;</p>
<h2>SEC chairman calls SBF&#8217;s fraud a wake-up call</h2>
<p>SEC Chairman also targets other crypto exchanges and calls<a href="https://coingape.com/sbf-arret-xrp-lawyer-guarantees-of-caroline-testifying-against-sbf/"> SBF</a>&#8216;s fraud a wake-up call. In addition to this, he also urges other crypto firms to comply with laws. He also highlighted the importance of compliance by mentioning that it will protect both those who invest on and those who invest in crypto platforms.</p>
<p>Notably, after the arrest of the FTX co-founder Senator, the attorney general of the Bahamas Sen. Ryan Pinder KC stated that US government is &#8220;likely&#8221; to request Sam Bankman-extradition.</p>
<p>Notably, the US and the Bahamas government have an extradition agreement according to which suspects who face accusations would be punishable by more than a year in jail in either nation may be sent back to US.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/sbf-built-a-house-of-cards-says-sec-chair/">SBF Built A House Of Cards, Says SEC Chair</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13121221/SBF-jail.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Reveals Charges Hours Before SBF&#8217;s Court Appearance</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/sbf-to-appear-in-bahamas-court-as-sec-reveals-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jai]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=131288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/sbf-to-appear-in-bahamas-court-as-sec-reveals-charges/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/07172821/Sam-Bankman.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="SEC Reveals Charges Hours Before SBF&#8217;s Court Appearance"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/sbf-to-appear-in-bahamas-court-as-sec-reveals-charges/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/07172821/Sam-Bankman.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="SEC Reveals Charges Hours Before SBF&#8217;s Court Appearance"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/07172821/Sam-Bankman.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street Expectations On US CPI Inflation</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-price-breaks-higher-wall-street-expectations-on-us-cpi-inflation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumer Price Index]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum prices break higher before the U.S. Consumer Price Index (CPI) data release for November. Bitcoin (BTC) price jumps a month higher after moving in range since FTX bankruptcy. The Bitcoin price rallied over 3% from a low of $16,944, hitting a high of $17,424. The trading volume rises nearly 15%, indicating limited <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-price-breaks-higher-wall-street-expectations-on-us-cpi-inflation/" title="Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street Expectations On US CPI Inflation"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-price-breaks-higher-wall-street-expectations-on-us-cpi-inflation/">Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street Expectations On US CPI Inflation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1280" height="854" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/17134244/Crypto-market-cap-reclaims-1-trillion-mark-as-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-rally.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street Expectations Over US CPI Inflation" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Bitcoin and Ethereum prices break higher before the U.S. <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/consumer-price-index-cpi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Consumer Price Index</a> (CPI) data release for November. Bitcoin (BTC) price jumps a month higher after moving in range since <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> bankruptcy. The Bitcoin price rallied over 3% from a low of $16,944, hitting a high of $17,424. The trading volume rises nearly 15%, indicating limited participation from traders.</p>
<p>Ethereum (ETH) price also rallied over 2%, with the current price trading at $1,285. The 24-hour low and high are $1,246 and $1,283, respectively. The ETH price is moving in the range since the last month. The trading volume rose 25% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Expectations Over US CPI Data</h2>
<p>The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics will release the US CPI data for November today. The inflation rate is expected to slow for a fifth straight month to 7.3% in November, compared to 7.7% in October. Moreover, the Core CPI is expected to edge lower to 6.1% in November from 6.3% in October.</p>
<p>Wall Street expects the CPI data to come in lower as a result of cooling inflation. U.S. stocks jumped Monday, with investors anticipating softer inflation and a smaller interest-rate increase from the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/federal-reserve-system/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Federal Reserve</a> this week.</p>
<p><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-b88u0q r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">JPMorgan</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> predicts a 10% rally in stocks if the U.S. </span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-b88u0q r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">CPI</span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"> comes in at 6.9% or lower. However, JPMorgan expects a CPI reading between 7.2% and 7.4%. While the U.S. stock market showed less correlation with the crypto market in recent times, the lower CPI will benefit the Bitcoin and Ethereum prices.</span></p>
<p>Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, Credit Suisse, Barclays, Bloomberg, Jefferies, Citi, Wells Fargo, and Nomura expect the CPI data to be <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">7.2%. Meanwhile, BMO, CIBC, Gurvain Capital, and TD Securities anticipate the CPI number at 7.3%. Therefore, the CPI data can come in lower than the expected 7.3% for November.</span></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price and Fed 50 Bps Rate Hike</h2>
<p>The CPI data will influence the Federal Reserve&#8217;s interest rate hike decision the next day. <a href="https://coingape.com/fed-chair-jerome-powell-interest-rate-hike-inflation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Fed Chair Jerome Powell earlier indicated</a> a slowdown in the rate hike pace in December and the coming months.</p>
<p>According to <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME FedWatch Tool</a>, a probability of a 50 bps rate hike is 72.3%. Wall Street also expects the Fed to stick to a 50 bps rate hike in November.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin and Ethereum prices will remain volatile in the week. However, the BTC price breaking above the <a href="https://coingape.com/popular-analysts-predict-bitcoin-and-ethereum-prices-for-christmas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$17.3k level is significant for a market bottom</a>.</p>
<p class="c-title entry-title tittle">Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-crash-incoming-after-us-cpi-and-fed-rate-hike/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Price Crash Incoming After US CPI And Fed Rate Hike?</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-ethereum-price-breaks-higher-wall-street-expectations-on-us-cpi-inflation/">Bitcoin, Ethereum Price Breaks Higher, Wall Street Expectations On US CPI Inflation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/17134244/Crypto-market-cap-reclaims-1-trillion-mark-as-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-rally.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 3 Metaverse Tokens To Buy In The Dip Before 2023- Apecoin, Decentraland, The Sandbox</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/top-3-metaverse-tokens-to-buy-in-the-dip-before-2023-apecoin-decentraland-the-sandbox/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Priyanka Payal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ApeCoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentraland (Mana)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Sandbox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=131094</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Metaverse Tokens To Buy In 2023: Cryptocurrency prices were slightly up at the time of reporting as the price of major cryptocurrencies rose marginally during the early morning trading hours on Tuesday (13 December 2022). The global crypto market cap is $848.03B, a 0.83% increase over the last day. Meanwhile, Bitcoin and Ethereum are up <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/top-3-metaverse-tokens-to-buy-in-the-dip-before-2023-apecoin-decentraland-the-sandbox/" title="Top 3 Metaverse Tokens To Buy In The Dip Before 2023- Apecoin, Decentraland, The Sandbox"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/top-3-metaverse-tokens-to-buy-in-the-dip-before-2023-apecoin-decentraland-the-sandbox/">Top 3 Metaverse Tokens To Buy In The Dip Before 2023- Apecoin, Decentraland, The Sandbox</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/07180938/Metaverse.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Metaverse Tokens This Week" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Metaverse Tokens To Buy In 2023:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cryptocurrency</a> prices were slightly up at the time of reporting as the price of major cryptocurrencies rose marginally during the early morning trading hours on Tuesday (13 December 2022). The global crypto market cap is $848.03B, a 0.83% increase over the last day. Meanwhile, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> and Ethereum are up 1.45% and 2.10%, respectively.</p>
<p>The price of some of the leading <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/what-is-metaverse/#:~:text=Metaverse%20is%20any%20shared%20virtual,computer%2Dgenerated%20objects%20and%20avatars." target="_blank" rel="noopener">Metaverse</a> tokens, namely ApeCoin, Decentraland and The Sandbox, traded in the red today. In this article, we will discuss three metaverse tokens that are trading lower but worth buying the dip. The trio can likely give you attractive returns in 2023. The critical factors we have considered while picking these coins include their utility, robust financial backing, and data on token transfers by date. However, since one shoe doesn&#8217;t fit all sizes, other factors have also been kept in mind while doing this analysis.</p>
<h3>Top 3 Metaverse Tokens To Buy In The Dip: Here’s the list</h3>
<h3><strong>Apecoin (APE)</strong></h3>
<p>The live ApeCoin price today is USD$4.03 with a 24-hour trading volume of usd$269,824,043. ApeCoin is down 6.52% in the last 24 hours. The current CoinMarketCap ranking of Apecoin is 30, with a live market cap of USD$1,455,674,698. It has a maximum supply of 1,000,000,000 APE coins.</p>
<p>Apecoin price has gained nearly 5.95% in the last one week, while its last one month&#8217;s performance is +51.31%. Apecoin is a buy at the moment because the announcement of ApeCoin&#8217;s [APE] staking rewards have grown the hype around the token.<br />
Many crypto communities have tried to profit from <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/staking/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">staking</a> rewards. Users can get their hands on the rewards by becoming a part of any of the four staking pools. One such way is to buy APE and commit it to the pool.</p>
<p>Since the staking of ApeCoin has gone live, the demand for the APE coin has increased, increasing its price. Staking can increase or reduce the price of your coins because it is affected by the market forces of supply &amp; demand.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Chart on 30-day active addresses for ApeCoin</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-131096" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13140226/AAA.png" alt="ApeCoin Price" width="932" height="563" /></p>
<p>As can be seen in the above shared image, it is observed that daily active addresses for ApeCoin saw a tremendous spike over the last few weeks. Subsequently, ApeCoin’s network growth has also increased. This indicates that the number of wallets transferring APE for the very first time had gone up.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>ApeCoin Investors’ list</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-131097" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13140433/Apecoin-investor.png" alt="Investors list" width="859" height="471" /></p>
<h2><strong>Decentraland</strong></h2>
<p>The current <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/decentraland/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Decentraland</a> price is USD$0.377683, down 0.18% in the last 24 hours. It has a 24-hour trading volume of USD$26,615,920. With a live market cap of USD$700,634,261, the current CoinMarketCap ranking of the metaverse token is 56. The maximum supply of MANA coins is not available. In the last one week, MANA&#8217;s price has fallen by 6.74%. The past one month and six months&#8217; performance of the metaverse token stands at -15.14% and -54.42%.</p>
<p>Companies that have invested in Decentraland include Republic Realm, Samsung 837X, and Sotheby. Formed in 2017, Decentraland is one of the older projects. As of October 24, it was the third-largest metaverse token in terms of market capitalization.</p>
<p><strong>Decentraland Investors’ list</strong></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-131099" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13140659/Decentraland-investors.png" alt="Decentraland" width="877" height="385" /></p>
<p><strong>Token Transfers by data chart:</strong></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-131118" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13150833/Decentraland-onchain.png" alt="Decentraland Price" width="1879" height="685" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>The Sandbox</h3>
<p>The <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/sandbox/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sandbox</a> price today is USD$0.551138 with a 24-hour trading volume of USD$75,106,148. The Sandbox price is down 0.43% in the last 24 hours. With a live market cap of USD$826,415,252, the current CoinMarketCap ranking of Sandbox is 49. It has a maximum supply of 3,000,000,000 SAND coins. In the last one week, The Sandbox price has fallen nearly 8.92%; it has dropped 35.75% in the last six months.</p>
<blockquote><p>With the virtual reality (VR) aspect, this project is discovering the vision of the metaverse. The Sandbox is basically a game, and it has the support of gaming brands such as Atari, which could help it navigate unfavorable market conditions.</p></blockquote>
<p>Another promising factor about this project is its limited coin supply of 3 billion tokens, of which 1.5 billion are in use. Seeing the increasing popularity of &#8220;The Sandbox,&#8221; several projects have bought land on the platform by entering into partnerships. These include British multinational universal bank HSBC, Standard Chartered Bank (Hong Kong), and PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC).</p>
<p><strong>The Sandbox’s Investors’ list</strong></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-131119" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13150947/Sandbox-investors.png" alt="The Sandbox" width="826" height="673" /></p>
<p><strong>Token Transfers by data chart:</strong></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-131120" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13151029/Sandbox-onchain.png" alt="The Sandbox" width="1879" height="622" /></p>
<h2><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>
<p>The term &#8220;metaverse&#8221; has become a sizzling topic these days. The world&#8217;s biggest tech companies are investing heavily to build the metaverse for the future. These include Facebook, Microsoft, Google, Epic games, and the list goes on. Although the technology is yet to enter the mainstream, it is quickly gathering the attention of tech as well as crypto investors. It can thus be said that metaverse coins present an untapped opportunity for 2023.</p>
<p>The positive news is that since metaverse projects are comparatively new, coin prices are relatively low — below $1 in some cases. This opens the investment opportunity for almost everyone. However, this doesn&#8217;t mean that all projects are worth your money.</p>
<p><em><strong>Disclaimer:</strong></em></p>
<p><em><strong>It is to be noted that the crypto market is highly volatile, and the metaverse concept is deeply rooted in cryptocurrency and blockchain. There is always a probability that what seems to perform well in the future plunges down for several reasons. Our article is not investment advice but a short analysis and personal opinion. It is always recommended to do your research before making any investment decision.</strong></em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/top-3-metaverse-tokens-to-buy-in-the-dip-before-2023-apecoin-decentraland-the-sandbox/">Top 3 Metaverse Tokens To Buy In The Dip Before 2023- Apecoin, Decentraland, The Sandbox</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/07180938/Metaverse.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk No Longer The World’s Richest Person</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-no-longer-the-worlds-richest-person/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=131200</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-no-longer-the-worlds-richest-person/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13172417/poster73.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk No Longer The World’s Richest Person"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/elon-musk-no-longer-the-worlds-richest-person/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13172417/poster73.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Elon Musk No Longer The World’s Richest Person"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/13172417/poster73.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
