<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 19:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Floki partners with Binance Pay to boost Floki Shop adoption</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-partners-with-binance-pay-to-boost-floki-shop-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 19:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-partners-with-binance-pay-to-boost-floki-shop-adoption/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Floki revealed the strategic partnership on Twitter and via a Medium post on Tuesday. Binance Pay becomes Floki&#8217;s main crypto payments provider and will aid in a campaign to boost adoption of the merchandise store Floki Shop. Customers can now buy items from the merch store using funds in the Binance Pay account. Floki Inu [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-partners-with-binance-pay-to-boost-floki-shop-adoption/">Floki partners with Binance Pay to boost Floki Shop adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr" style="font-weight: bold;font-style: italic"><em><strong>Floki revealed the strategic partnership on Twitter and via a Medium post on Tuesday.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr" style="font-weight: bold;font-style: italic"><em><strong>Binance Pay becomes Floki&rsquo;s main crypto payments provider and will aid in a campaign to boost adoption of the merchandise store Floki Shop.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr" style="font-weight: bold;font-style: italic"><strong><em>Customers can now buy items from the merch store using funds in the Binance Pay account.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/floki/">Floki Inu</a> has struck a strategic partnership with crypto payments provider Binance Pay, the cryptocurrency platform <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu/status/1615404238963605520" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Pay is a payments feature in the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> ecosystem. Floki, on the other hand, is popularly referred to as &ldquo;the people&rsquo;s cryptocurrency&rdquo;, and its native token FLOKI was inspired by top meme coins such as Shiba Inu (SHIB).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Floki partners Binance Pay</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Per a <a href="https://realflokiinu.medium.com/floki-has-partnered-with-binance-pay-210d29db4194" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Medium post</a> the Floki team published on Tuesday, &nbsp;Binance Pay is now Floki&rsquo;s official digital assets payments service provider. The Binance app payments feature will provide crypto payments for Floki Shop, a newly launched Floki merchandise store from where people can buy unique items, including fashion pieces.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FLOKI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#FLOKI</a> HAS FORMED A STRATEGIC PARTNERSHIP WITH <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BINANCE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BINANCE</a> PAY!</p>
<p>Binance Pay is the main crypto payment solution we will be using for Floki&rsquo;s new merch store, Shop Floki!</p>
<p>Shop Floki will go live and start taking orders on the 19th of January, by 8PM UTC.<a href="https://t.co/b2Xgno8tS0">https://t.co/b2Xgno8tS0</a> <a href="https://t.co/8DX9QcJU8x">pic.twitter.com/8DX9QcJU8x</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FLOKI (@RealFlokiInu) <a href="https://twitter.com/RealFlokiInu/status/1615404238963605520?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">With this partnership, Floki will also work with Binance Pay to boost further adoption of the merch store. According to details in the announcement, the two companies will look to achieve this via a strategic and coordinated marketing campaign.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, Binance Pay will feature the Floki store campaign on the payment provider&rsquo;s homepage for a month. It will also include push notifications to millions of Binance Pay&rsquo;s users across the globe, Floki added in the announcement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance Pay allows for borderless and secure user-to-user crypto payments, with customers able to access the service from within the Binance app.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/floki-partners-with-binance-pay-to-boost-floki-shop-adoption/">Floki partners with Binance Pay to boost Floki Shop adoption</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon completes hard fork to boost network performance</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-completes-hard-fork-to-boost-performance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 18:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hard Fork]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-completes-hard-fork-to-boost-performance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon announced the scheduled hard fork had succeeded on Tuesday, 17 January, 2023. The software upgrades will help address the issue of gas-fee spikes and potentially disruptive chain reorganizations. Polygon is looking at other technical upgrades such as zkEVM and parallelization as the team eyes further improvements to the network. Polygon, the Web3 infrastructure platform [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-completes-hard-fork-to-boost-performance/">Polygon completes hard fork to boost network performance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Polygon announced the scheduled hard fork had succeeded on Tuesday, 17 January, 2023.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The software upgrades will help address the issue of gas-fee spikes and potentially disruptive chain reorganizations.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Polygon is looking at other technical upgrades such as zkEVM and parallelization as the team eyes further improvements to the network.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/polygon/">Polygon</a>, the Web3 infrastructure platform built on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, has successfully completed its scheduled mainnet upgrade, according to an <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygon/status/1615370181630652417" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a> from the team behind the blockchain project.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Upgrade to help boost Polygon performance</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The proof-of-stake (PoS) upgrade is a hard fork that the community approved in a recent vote, with the implementation aimed at reducing gas fees spikes on the Ethereum scaling solution. With the hard fork it means that although the network could still see spiking gas fees during peak demand sessions, this will now more likely mirror Ethereum&rsquo;s current gas dynamics.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Polygon team, the upgrade will smooth out any gas fee spikes and allow for seamless interaction with the chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The software update is also meant to address chain reorganizations, or &ldquo;reorgs&rdquo;, which can impact transaction finality and be disruptive to the chain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Polygon highlighted the above proposals in a post <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/hardfork-incoming-upgrading-polygon-pos-chain-to-boost-performance" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">published</a> on 12 January.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Alongside the completed hard fork that is set to boost network performance and predictability, there are longer-term targets still aimed at making the blockchain protocol ideal for a growing community of users. These will include technical upgrades such as <a href="https://polygon.technology/blog/innovating-the-main-chain-a-polygon-pos-study-in-parallelization" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">parallelization</a> and <a href="https://polygon.technology/solutions/polygon-zkevm" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Polygon zkEVM</a> being worked on.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Major Web3 projects such as Uniswap and Aave are on the Polygon PoS chain, along with thousands of other decentralised applications (dApps). The chain has registered more than 207 million unique addresses and processed over 2.3 billion transactions.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/polygon-completes-hard-fork-to-boost-performance/">Polygon completes hard fork to boost network performance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kevin O&#8217;Leary says another &#8216;meltdown to zero&#8217; will 100% happen</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/kevin-oleary-says-another-meltdown-to-zero-will-100-happen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 17:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/kevin-oleary-says-another-meltdown-to-zero-will-100-happen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin O&#8217;Leary thinks&#160;the crypto market should be ready for another FTX-like collapse, noting this will 100% happen. According to the venture capitalist and &#8220;Shark Tank&#8221; star, crypto needs to move away from a &#8220;unregulated cowboy environment&#8221; that&#8217;s full of rogue players.&#160; The billionaire investor thinks the scenarios where an exchange goes burst will keep happening [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kevin-oleary-says-another-meltdown-to-zero-will-100-happen/">Kevin O&#8217;Leary says another &#8216;meltdown to zero&#8217; will 100% happen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Kevin O&rsquo;Leary thinks&nbsp;</strong></em><em><strong>the crypto market should be ready for another FTX-like collapse, noting this will 100% happen.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>According to the venture capitalist and &ldquo;Shark Tank&rdquo; star, crypto needs to move away from a &ldquo;unregulated cowboy environment&rdquo; that&rsquo;s full of rogue players.</em></strong>&nbsp;</li>
<li><strong><em>The billionaire investor thinks the scenarios where an exchange goes burst will keep happening over and over until regulations begin to change some of the factors enabling the failures</em></strong>.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Kevin O&rsquo;Leary, the Chairman of O&rsquo;Leary Ventures and a seasoned investor, has shared his outlook on the crypto market, suggesting in a recent interview that the industry could yet see another major meltdown.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Particularly, the &lsquo;Shark Tank&rsquo; star believes more unregulated <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> will fail, even as the regulatory landscape improves to put rogue players in check.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">O&rsquo;Leary says new exchange collapses 100% will happen</h2>
<p dir="ltr">O&rsquo;Leary came under heavy criticism in the aftermath of the collapse of FTX, with his role as a spokesperson attracting the ire of Crypto Twitter even as the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ftx-token/">FTX Token</a> plummeted and he claimed he lost money on the exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Now he says he can never buy any of these exchange tokens, and that platforms incentivising customers to buy tokens with offers of trading fee discounts are perpetuating a scheme that will see many people lose their money.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Asked whether he thinks there&rsquo;s going to be another FTX, O&rsquo;Leary noted there would. He <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xckrkxhrP4M" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">told</a> Kitco News anchor David Lin on Tuesday that it doesn&rsquo;t worry him.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>I&rsquo;m not worried, but if you&rsquo;re asking me, will there be another meltdown to zero absolutely 100% it&rsquo;ll happen, and it&rsquo;ll keep happening over and over. All of these exchanges, all of the unregulated exchanges are having massive outflows now. The smart money has got the joke, they saw what happened with FTX and are not sitting around for an explanation</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The venture capitalist went on to highlight that any exchanges not willing to be fully and properly audited &ndash; those that still don&rsquo;t fancy transparency &ndash; will see an exodus of institutional capital. On such exchanges he said, the &ldquo;unregulated cowboy environment&rdquo; will end. And there are going to be many more collapses as the space matures under a robust regulatory framework.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>I think we just need to treat crypto like any other regulated asset</em>,&rdquo; he noted, adding that this is likely to happen sooner as more companies, including USD Coin stablecoin issuer Circle, pursue a proper regulatory environment.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/kevin-oleary-says-another-meltdown-to-zero-will-100-happen/">Kevin O&#8217;Leary says another &#8216;meltdown to zero&#8217; will 100% happen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB muted despite BNB Chain&#8217;s burn of $600M worth of tokens</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-muted-despite-bnb-chains-burn-of-500m-worth-of-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 17:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-muted-despite-bnb-chains-burn-of-500m-worth-of-tokens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BNB worth more than $600 million have been removed from circulation, Binance announced on Tuesday. This was the 22nd BNB burn, with data showing over 44 million BNB tokens have been cut from the total supply. Binance launched BNB in 2017 with a maximum supply of 200 million and has planned to cut the supply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-muted-despite-bnb-chains-burn-of-500m-worth-of-tokens/">BNB muted despite BNB Chain&#8217;s burn of $600M worth of tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>BNB worth more than $600 million have been removed from circulation, Binance announced on Tuesday.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>This was the 22nd BNB burn, with data showing over 44 million BNB tokens have been cut from the total supply.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Binance launched BNB in 2017 with a maximum supply of 200 million and has planned to cut the supply to 100 million.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">BNB Chain today completed its 22nd burn event, with the quarterly burn for the first installment in 2022 seeing the blockchain platform remove over 2 million BNB worth more than $500 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/22nd-bnb-burn-8657700843018962092" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> earlier Tuesday, BNB Chain burned a total of 2,064,494.32 BNB worth approximately $617,696,701. The programed burn occurred at around 0800 UTC on 17 January 2023, with the transaction ID also showing the burn was completed at block height 290943059. The total fee a measly 0.002 BNB.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Coin burning is when a certain amount of crypto is destroyed &amp; permanently removed from circulation to reduce the supply of the crypto. </p>
<p>To burn coins you send them to a black hole address, after which cannot be used for anything.</p>
<p>They are burned. Destroyed. Gone forever.</p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1615392551019892738?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Despite the BNB burn news, the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/">Binance Coin</a> remained muted and mirrored the slowdown across crypto after last weekend&rsquo;s massive pump.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BNB is up more than 10% in the past week and nearly 25% higher in the past 30 days, having rallied to $314 per token &ndash; its highest price level since late November. However, as noted, today&rsquo;s announcement hasn&rsquo;t seen a major reaction from BNB holders.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token currently trades around $302 with slight gains of 1.3% over the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BNB Chain to burn 100 million BNB</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While the maximum supply of BNB was initially 200 million when the cryptocurrency launched in 2017, an exploit on the BSC Token Hub bridge on 7 October, 2022 impacted total supply and thus affected the Q4 BNB burn. This is because the incident saw the minting of an extra two million BNB, which had then increased the token&rsquo;s maximum supply to 202 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from <a href="https://bnbburn.info/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">bnbburn</a>, the circulating supply of BNB currently stands at roughly 157 million. Approximately 44 million coins from the total supply of 202 million has so far been destroyed, almost halfway to the target of removing 100 million BNB from circulation.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bnb-muted-despite-bnb-chains-burn-of-500m-worth-of-tokens/">BNB muted despite BNB Chain&#8217;s burn of $600M worth of tokens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin and AI: Deal in Crypto Intelligently</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ai-deal-in-crypto-intelligently/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ai-deal-in-crypto-intelligently/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The global AI market is forecast to grow $1394.30 billion in 2023. Investors and traders can tap into AI to benefit from features such as automation and accuracy. Bitcoin and AI also have the capacity to combat frauds in transactions across global markets. Have you ever thought that where technology will extend us, either intelligent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ai-deal-in-crypto-intelligently/">Bitcoin and AI: Deal in Crypto Intelligently</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>The global AI market is forecast to grow $1394.30 billion in 2023.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Investors and traders can tap into AI to benefit from features such as automation and accuracy.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>Bitcoin and AI also have the capacity to combat frauds in transactions across global markets.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Have you ever thought that where technology will extend us, either intelligent machines will replace us together or they will combine with humans to develop a third merger that will be four times more explosive than intelligent machines and humans? This is a long debate, but one thing is sure: artificial intelligence has plotted a strong position in this landscape, and almost every aspect is making full use of this.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This article is a mixture of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> with AI. Artificial Intelligence will be a role model for crypto enthusiasts to understand the crypto league and their sit in this landscape.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Salient stories</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A well-known market research firm Fortune Business Insight has predicted that the global AI market will extend to $1394.30 billion in the year 2023. Furthermore, Ai will drive better outcomes for crypto investors as it will predict the market value of coins perfectly. The pattern detection ability of AI will greatly influence the functionality of crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and AI will combat many frauds that occur in transactions, and these transactions will be provided lethal speed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the crypto field, fraudulent activities have been the greatest threat, and if someone becomes a victim of these fraudulent activities, that will be a disaster. AI power will ensure a greater monitoring system around the digital currencies landscape, further fuming these currencies&rsquo; personalities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AI provides better products that give the crypto the upper hand, and one such product is Trading Bots uses a range of AI tools like Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and others to enhance the crypto trading experience. Furthermore, these tools do not only work best for predicting the prices of crypto but for many other things like providing information about the crypto landscape, what&rsquo;s new inside the crypto world, and many others.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Apart from these stories, there is a lot to debate. First among them is what people say about these coins. Different perceptions fall into the debate. First, a suitable amount of the population believes that these currencies can replace traditional paper currency in what sense, and secondly, many countries do not have to provide legal status, these countries and why major Tech companies of the world have yet to recognize the use of these coins.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The nature of these coins suggests that these coins are highly volatile, and predicting the exact future position of these coins is impossible. Even powerful AI tools cannot predict the real scenario. AI will just put efficiency but not to 100%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When technology emerges, it also gives new opportunities for attackers to invade the system. Crypto trading is honey for the attackers, where they can exploit sweet. AI plays a beautiful role in this regard, but these attackers will adopt new ways to invade the system.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Positive signs&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AI is a new and innovative thing for finance, especially <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/trade/hub/">crypto trading</a>, and can lead to many amazes for crypto. And will help traders to extract the goods. But the story has not one hero but many others too.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The technological Landscape will grow in the coming time, which will help digital currencies to gather what they have lost. The year 2022 was a disaster for these coins, but technology will lead them to a stronger position in the coming time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Despite poor performance in the year 2022, the demand for crypto is enhancing, which will further add to the significance of crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When major companies recognize these currencies, the real game will start, and many companies have shown greater interest in this regard.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Final Thoughts</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There is a lot of heat going on regarding Bitcoin and AI, and the reason for such heat is simply the innovation they bring into this landscape. The digital landscape is all about techno products and their services, and both these dilemmas are best in the business.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the one hand, Artificial Intelligence has been placing its theme in every aspect of the business. On the other hand, crypto, like Bitcoin, leads to innovative ways of investing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>And when both these things have merged, results are not hidden from anyone. One can use the internet to know better, and if not, then simply adopt both things, and then you will get to know about the difference.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitcoin and AI are providing many facilities to crypto companies and investors. The fascinating thing about AI is to predict the outcomes, which readily helps investors and companies to plot the future position of these digital coins.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, this AI will lead to more secure transactions for investors and add greater measures for monitoring illegal activities within the crypto landscape.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There are AI bots for efficient trading that work as great news providers to traders, and together they perform the function of alerting the traders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Last but not least, people&rsquo;s perspective heavily influences the growth of these coins; when major companies or financial experts declare anything negative about them, then they will not merge in such a form to replace the traditional paper currencies. Still, if they feel positivity while using these coins, it will be easier for crypto like Bitcoin to make things happen.&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you are looking for the best crypto trading platform, then there is no need to search further. Just click on <a href="https://the-immediateconnect.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Immediate Connect</a>, and this will lead you to a well-reputed trading platform that offers a range of solutions to find a better roadmap to make dollars from crypto.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-and-ai-deal-in-crypto-intelligently/">Bitcoin and AI: Deal in Crypto Intelligently</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 6 highly adopted Fintech trends to follow in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-highly-adopted-fintech-trends-to-follow-in-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-highly-adopted-fintech-trends-to-follow-in-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital assets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-highly-adopted-fintech-trends-to-follow-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency and cross-border payments will be a key trend in 2023 amid greater adoption across the digital assets industry. Embedded financial systems and innovating in the digital age are also set to be big trends. The coming year is undoubtedly going to provide a watershed moment for the broader fintech industry. Time marches on, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-highly-adopted-fintech-trends-to-follow-in-2023/">The 6 highly adopted Fintech trends to follow in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Cryptocurrency and cross-border payments will be a key trend in 2023 amid greater adoption across the digital assets industry.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><em><strong>Embedded financial systems and innovating in the digital age are also set to be big trends.</strong></em></li>
<li dir="ltr"><strong><em>The coming year is undoubtedly going to provide a watershed moment for the broader fintech industry.</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Time marches on, and soon it will be a new year. Due to the fast development of fintech, the environment and available tools will change significantly before the year&rsquo;s end.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is the best time of year to take a glimpse into the future and make predictions for the next year. We asked a small group of experts in the field what they thought the fintech industry would be like in 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Key fintech trends in the year 2023</h2>
<h3 dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency</h3>
<p dir="ltr">When it comes to the fintech trends we&rsquo;ve seen, 2023 will be a year of maturity for the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/">crypto industry</a>, with increased monitoring and control from authorities throughout the globe, but it will also witness the exit of many rogue actors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The failure of many crypto enterprises in 2022 will prompt authorities to take a closer look at and maybe adjust the laws and standards that have already been put in place.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Companies in the fintech and cryptocurrency industries, such as <a href="https://the-bitcoin360-ai.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin 360 AI</a>, will need to strive to restore their customers&rsquo; faith in them after the FTX crash and the subsequent bear market. We think this will help the sector grow healthily, with crypto and fintech companies caring more about being open and making sure their customers are safe.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the end, 2023 will be remembered as the year when crypto made a comeback after being written off in the wake of the crypto winter and other unpleasant occurrences. I believe widespread crypto adoption will occur when users and conventional financial institutions get more familiar with the technology and the upcoming regulatory clarification. To meet ever-increasing consumer demands, more businesses will join the industry.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last but not least, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/glossary/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/">CBDCs</a> will become more prominent as central banks look for improved means of managing monetary policy, keeping tabs on capital movements, and developing alternatives to the current global payments system. New pilot programs and rollouts have recently been announced in Japan and India. Still, there are privacy concerns that must be resolved before widespread use.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Embedded financial systems</h3>
<p dir="ltr">After the COVID-19 pandemic, there was a dramatic increase in the use of technology in place of physical means of communication. The shift in customer behavior was brought about by the rise of e-commerce and the digitization of financial services.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, fintech firms have been catching up to and even surpassing conventional banks in terms of acquiring customers&rsquo; confidence in financial services. As a result of these developments, embedded finance now has unprecedented potential for growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">We forecast that by 2023, embedded finance will have won over a large portion of the financial sector in emerging markets. Embedded finance, driven by inclusive fintech businesses, has the potential to provide a voice to those who have been historically underserved by the banking system.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">To a similar extent, developing markets may provide a more liberating setting, with cheaper prices and a broader client base, which in turn may spur more innovation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, the adoption of embedded finance may be bolstered by deeper partnerships between conventional financial institutions like banks and payment providers, and fintech firms.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Innovating in the digital age&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">As the pace of digital transformation continues to quicken, new banking requirements will become more important to investigate throughout the next wave of transition.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">There will be an emphasis on the capacity to tailor-make bespoke financial services for consumers. Since the basics of digitizing banking have been set, the industry can now focus on creating and distributing new goods and services in real-time and across devices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As with other fintech trends, the idea of integrating banking into social media messaging applications and even the Internet of Things is indicative of a shift toward a more comprehensive omnichannel strategy. For big banks to be a part of their customers&rsquo; lives, they need to build banking into more than just smartphones.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Cross-border transactions&nbsp;</h3>
<p dir="ltr">There has been persistent debate about whether or not globalization will succeed. As the flow of people, commodities, and services, as well as money, will determine future expansion, this is naturally of interest to the payments sector.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Those working in the remittance sector, for instance, will see their clientele changed by the number of individuals who have been uprooted due to natural disasters and armed conflict. Many business-to-business commentators have noted a recent trend away from global interconnectedness and toward more individual autonomy.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, globalization has been firmly established in the global economy, and the dynamics between developing and developed nations will persist. Thus, cross-border capital flows will persist, and financial technology will play an important role in easing them.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This could mean helping merchants take advantage of opportunities for cross-border e-commerce or making it easier for tech companies to send work to freelancer hubs all over the world.&nbsp;</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Corporate expenditures</h3>
<p dir="ltr">We anticipate that in 2023, cost management will get more attention, and businesses will be better able to assess and select where to reduce expenses and where they should push back on future-proofing expenditures.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">After a negative fourth quarter of growth, the Bank of England has warned that a two-year recession is possible in the United Kingdom. To effectively manage the current economic crisis, we anticipate that finance executives will face more pressure to drive their organization towards greater financial discipline.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">That&rsquo;s on top of the general trend toward elevating the chief financial officer to an advising role.</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, we expect that financial executives would look for fintech trends that might assist them in bringing corporate spending under control. Before companies can have control over their budgets, they need to know when and where all of their costs come from.</p>
<h3 dir="ltr">Incentives and commitment</h3>
<p dir="ltr">The youngest generation of consumers is responsible for the recent surge in online retail sales, and businesses now have greater incentives and greater difficulty engaging with this demographic.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Generation Z is the on-demand generation of tech-savvy, socially conscious, value-seeking consumers born after 1995. A growing number of our younger cardholders are cashing in their rewards for smaller amounts and more often.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is in stark contrast to our more seasoned cardholders, who tend to hang on to their rewards for the long haul. Younger generations are concerned not only with having quick access to cashing out their incentives but also with having an impact.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Beginning in 2023, users will be able to donate their earned rewards to causes and organizations close to their hearts.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Summarizing the fintech trends 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s hard to say how the next year will play out. Yet, 2023 will be a watershed year for the financial industry, ushering in a slew of new rules, market shifts, and technological innovations. Even if one does not work in the financial technology industry, one may still be affected by the developments in this area.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As a result, the six different FinTech trends to watch in 2023 are embedded financial systems, digitalization, cryptocurrency, cross-border payments, corporate expenditure, and loyalty and reward systems.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-highly-adopted-fintech-trends-to-follow-in-2023/">The 6 highly adopted Fintech trends to follow in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/the-6-highly-adopted-fintech-trends-to-follow-in-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alchemy Pay (ACH) price forecast after jumping 50% in one day</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemy-pay-ach-price-forecast-after-jumping-50-in-one-day/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemy-pay-ach-price-forecast-after-jumping-50-in-one-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemy-pay-ach-price-forecast-after-jumping-50-in-one-day/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ACH/USD jumped 50% in one trading day A falling wedge pattern supports the bullish case The risk of a false breakout remains The cryptocurrency market suffered from the FTX scandal as investors fled away in light of yet another scam in the industry. But despite the numerous predictions that the industry will fail, the recent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemy-pay-ach-price-forecast-after-jumping-50-in-one-day/">Alchemy Pay (ACH) price forecast after jumping 50% in one day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>ACH/USD jumped 50% in one trading day</li>
<li>A falling wedge pattern supports the bullish case</li>
<li>The risk of a false breakout remains</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market suffered from the FTX scandal as investors fled away in light of yet another scam in the industry. But despite the numerous predictions that the industry will fail, the recent price action is encouraging for speculators.</p>
<p>Take, for instance, Alchemy Pay (ACH). It was the leading cryptocurrency yesterday, as it gained about 50% against the US dollar.</p>
<p>Alchemy Pay is the pioneer of the world&rsquo;s first payment gateway solution to connect fiat currencies and crypto economies. In short, it aims at building <a href="https://alchemypay.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Alchemy-Pay-White-Paper.pdf">a bridge between crypto and fiat worlds</a>.</p>
<p>With a circulating supply of 4.9 billion, the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s maximum supply will be 10 billion. At the current market price, Alchemy Pay has a market capitalization close to $60 million, and over 180 billion coins are traded daily.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/17/1673964014784-f810bd34-5c3a-4d8e-8430-c56fc4bd8bc0.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="489"></p>
<p><a href="http://tradingview.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ACH/USD chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>A falling wedge points to more upside, but fears of false breakouts remain</h2>
<p>Until recently, ACH/USD traded with a heavy tone &ndash; just like the overall cryptocurrency market. But the recent bounce in Bitcoin and other major cryptocurrencies led to small coins catching a bid.</p>
<p>As such, the price action broke out of a falling wedge pattern. Such a pattern signals a reversal; most of the time, the market retraces more than half of the pattern&rsquo;s distance.</p>
<p>However, it does not mean that the market cannot make a new low.</p>
<p>Therefore, any long trade should have a stop-loss order at the lowest point in the falling wedge, while the take-profit should be placed around half the distance the market traveled on its way lower. In other words, 0.035 should be appropriate.</p>
<p>The fear is that yesterday&rsquo;s bounce is yet another false breakout. A quick look at what happened in the past shows similar breakouts that turned out to be nothing but false ones as the market reversed and made a new low.</p>
<p>Summing up, if the recent lows hold, ACH/USD has more upside potential.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemy-pay-ach-price-forecast-after-jumping-50-in-one-day/">Alchemy Pay (ACH) price forecast after jumping 50% in one day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/alchemy-pay-ach-price-forecast-after-jumping-50-in-one-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GALA crypto price gains steam after new token burn news</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-crypto-price-gains-steam-after-new-token-burn-news/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-crypto-price-gains-steam-after-new-token-burn-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 12:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-crypto-price-gains-steam-after-new-token-burn-news/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>GALA price has surged by over 250% from the lowest point in December. The developers are working on the Meow NFT Match. Gala crypto price has been in a strong bullish trend in 2023, making it one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the industry. The token surged to a high of $0.054, which was about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-crypto-price-gains-steam-after-new-token-burn-news/">GALA crypto price gains steam after new token burn news</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">GALA price has surged by over 250% from the lowest point in December.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The developers are working on the Meow NFT Match.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Gala crypto price has been in a strong bullish trend in 2023, making it one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the industry. The token surged to a high of $0.054, which was about 250% from its lowest point in December.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why Gala token is soaring</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are several reasons why GALA crypto has surged in the past few weeks. First, the developers announced a deal that will see the network partner with The Rock to produce two films. This is notable since The Rock is one of the best-known actors in the industry. He is also known for appearing in some of the top-selling movies. However, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-price-falls-after-gala-games-deletes-hollywood-star-partnership-tweet/"><u>here</u></a>, Gala deleted the tweet making the announcement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, Gala developers announced that they will incorporate mobile gaming in their ecosystem. This means that developers will be able to create games that can be downloaded from Android and iOS stores. As a result, they will have a large market considering that there are more than 5 billion smartphone users internationally.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Third, the most recent reason why Gala has surged is the new introduction of pay by burn approach. In a statement, the developers said that all purchases made in Gala&rsquo;s ecosystem using the GALA token will see it get burned. When the Gala is burned it will be added to an emissions pool to be re-emitted through the Founders Nodes in the normal distribution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">A quick update on pay-by-burn of all <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GALA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$GALA</a> on the platform from our President of Blockchain, <a href="https://twitter.com/BitBenderBrink?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BitBenderBrink</a>! </p>
<p>Winter is for building, and we have been busy! <a href="https://t.co/UDbsznAt68">pic.twitter.com/UDbsznAt68</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gala Games (@GoGalaGames) <a href="https://twitter.com/GoGalaGames/status/1613653138703282177?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the developers, burning these tokens will help to provide more utility to the ecosystem. Meanwhile, the developers are working on the&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-soars-by-15-today-here-is-why/"><u>Meow Match</u></a>, which is a major upgrade to the network. In the first quarter, they will onboard Meow Match to the Gala Platform, launch Cat NFTs, and transform all earned in-game cats into claimable NFTs. In the second quarter, the Meow NFTs will be upgraded to utilize cat NFTs.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Gala price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/00/17/1673957122663-294994c9-cf91-46ab-9c25-ba43bad2932b.png" style="width: 684px;height: 324px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="684" height="324"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The 4h chart shows that GALA price has been in an unstoppable bull run in the past few weeks. As it rose, it managed to move above the important resistance level at $0.050, which was the highest point on Monday. Gala has moved above the ascending triangle pattern and the 25-day and 50-day moving averages.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Notably, Gala is not yet in an overbought level. Therefore, there is a likelihood that the coin will continue soaring as buyers target the key resistance level at $0.060. A drop below the key support level at $0.050 will invalidate the bullish view</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Gala</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk2Mzc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy GALA with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Bitstamp</h3>

    <p>Bitstamp is a leading cryptocurrency exchange which offers trading in fiat currencies or popular cryptocurrencies.

Bitstamp is a fully regulated company which offers users an intuitive interface, a high degree of security for your digital assets, excellent customer support and multiple withdrawal methods.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/bitstamp-crypto?guid=OTk2Mzc&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;state=TX&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy GALA with Bitstamp today            </a>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-crypto-price-gains-steam-after-new-token-burn-news/">GALA crypto price gains steam after new token burn news</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/gala-crypto-price-gains-steam-after-new-token-burn-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade, XRP, and Tron Price Prediction for 2023, 2025 and Beyond</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-xrp-and-tron-price-prediction-for-2023-2025-and-beyond/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-xrp-and-tron-price-prediction-for-2023-2025-and-beyond/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alice Davies]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-xrp-and-tron-price-prediction-for-2023-2025-and-beyond/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market moves in mysterious ways. Or not, if you look at the historical trends. Each bull market has been followed by a prolonged &#8220;crypto winter,&#8221; in which prices dip across the board. After this, the market typically recovers when the Bitcoin halving occurs, with the next one scheduled for early 2024. This means [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-xrp-and-tron-price-prediction-for-2023-2025-and-beyond/">Metacade, XRP, and Tron Price Prediction for 2023, 2025 and Beyond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The crypto market moves in mysterious ways. Or not, if you look at the historical trends. Each bull market has been followed by a prolonged &ldquo;crypto winter,&rdquo; in which prices dip across the board. After this, the market typically recovers when the Bitcoin halving occurs, with the next one scheduled for early 2024.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This means that 2023 could see rising crypto prices as the 2022 bear market is placed firmly in the rearview mirror. XRP (XRP), Metacade (MCADE), and Tron price predictions are now turning bullish.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade price prediction: Will MCADE reach $5 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">After recently announcing that Metacade received $1.12 million in funding during the beta phase of the presale in 3 weeks, the raise amount quickly jumped to $1.9m in closed in stage 1, the MCADE token is now expected to skyrocket after the event is complete.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MCADE could reach $1 during 2023, which would be a massive 50x gain after the presale. <strong>After the Bitcoin halving event and into 2025, MCADE has the potential to reach $5-7 when the next bull market comes around</strong>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is Metacade (MCADE)?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> is building the biggest arcade on the blockchain and will offer a range of different play-to-earn (P2E) games. Users can compete in online tournaments against players from all over the world and will benefit from a variety of innovative earning mechanics in the Metacade.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>The project is driven by the community and aims to become a central hub for GameFi users.</strong> To help the community, the Create2Earn feature will reward users for sharing useful information about the platform, as well as for posting game reviews and interacting with other members.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade is also helping the wider GameFi industry to grow. Job opportunities will be offered to gamers through the Work2Earn feature, which can help the community to break into Web3 while ensuring that projects get a constant supply of crypto enthusiasts to eagerly drive development.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Metagrants program is an innovative fundraising method for developers. The Metacade community will vote to decide which new games sound the best before providing early-stage funding to help in the development process for new GameFi titles.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How does Metacade work?&nbsp;</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token is used to reward members of the community and to gain access to P2E tournaments. It will also be used for staking and voting in governance proposals when the platform&rsquo;s decentralized autonomous organization (<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-dao/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>DAO</u></a>) goes live in 2023-24.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">XRP price prediction: Will XRP reach $4 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>XRP could blow past its previous all-time high if (or when) the project finally beats its court case with the SEC</strong>. This case has held back the price of XRP for some time, yet it still remains a top 10 cryptocurrency by market cap. In 2023 and beyond, the XRP token could certainly reach $4.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is XRP?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">XRP facilitates high-speed, low-cost financial transactions across national borders and aims to provide instant liquidity for central banks and other financial institutions. XRP is also the native token for the XRP Ledger, which is a decentralized blockchain network that can support the development of many different applications.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple, the parent company for the XRP project, has formed major partnerships with institutions such as JP Morgan, <a href="https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/-/media/boe/files/fintech/ripple.pdf?la=en&amp;hash=75E5F445230B8A2B794C208D29619A3E33F1FFE7" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>The Bank of England</u></a>, and Santander, which reflects its lofty ambitions as a decentralized payment solution.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tron price prediction: Will TRX reach $0.26 in 2025?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Tron price predictions are bullish; however, TRX is a relatively stable cryptocurrency in terms of price action. The token can absorb market volatility due to high levels of liquidity, so the Tron price prediction may seem lower than expected.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This liquidity benefits the blockchain and enables rapid transactions at low cost, but it also means that the Tron price prediction is unlikely to rise to the same extent as MCADE. Experts are predicting a $0.26 valuation for the TRX token, which is a 5x gain for Tron&rsquo;s price prediction by 2025.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What is TRX?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">TRX is the native token for the Tron blockchain, which is a common method for sending cryptocurrency across the world due to rapid transaction finality. The Tron ecosystem is home to a variety of different DeFi services and other decentralized applications (dApps), including games, borrowing protocols, and exchanges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Tron blockchain regularly processes hundreds of millions of dollars worth of transactions on a daily basis. It can process <a href="https://www.analyticsinsight.net/big-eyes-coin-solana-and-tron-are-redefining-speed-and-profit-making-in-the-blockchain-sector/#:~:text=Tron%20is%20a%20decentralized%20virtual,transaction%20speeds%20(2000%20tps)." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>2000 transactions per second (TPS)</u></a> and has a block finality time of three seconds. While the Tron price prediction is less bullish than alternative cryptocurrencies, it is a strong investment for the future.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade has the biggest return potential over the coming years</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The <a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Metacade</u></a> platform could grow to become one of the biggest projects in the GameFi sector. Through its advanced earning mechanics and a vast selection of different blockchain-based games, the project is expected to attract a huge community of gamers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MCADE token is currently just $0.01. The presale is a unique opportunity to get involved in a high-potential crypto project at low prices, but the token will continue to rise in value until it hits $0.02 during the final stage of the presale. This event could turn out to be the biggest investment opportunity for 2023 and beyond, so investors should be quick to jump into the Metacade presale before it&rsquo;s too late.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>You can buy XRP and TRX at eToro&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://coinjournal.net/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=OTk2MjM" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><strong>You can participate in the MCADE presale&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=launch" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><strong><u>here</u></strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-xrp-and-tron-price-prediction-for-2023-2025-and-beyond/">Metacade, XRP, and Tron Price Prediction for 2023, 2025 and Beyond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-xrp-and-tron-price-prediction-for-2023-2025-and-beyond/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
