<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Google to Face Fresh Lawsuit from US Department of Justice</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doj]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meta]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/">Google to Face Fresh Lawsuit from US Department of Justice</a></p>
<p>Tech giants including Meta Platforms, Amazon, and Apple are also being grilled for their acquisition of smaller rivals in a bid to squash out competition.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/">Google to Face Fresh Lawsuit from US Department of Justice</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/">Google to Face Fresh Lawsuit from US Department of Justice</a></p>
<p>The United States Department of Justice (DoJ) is reportedly finalizing plans to file a new lawsuit against Google and its parent company, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alphabet-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alphabet Inc</a> (NASDAQ: GOOGL). The news was first <a href="https://bloom.bg/3Xzn6PJ" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by Bloomberg which said the suit is on track to be filed as early as this week according to anonymous sources close to the probes.</p>
<p>The regulator is allegedly digging into the tech giant’s dominance in the advertising sector, invoking another anti-competitive crackdown that once plagued the dominant tech giants in the United States.</p>
<p>Google is the online search unit of Alphabet Inc which maintains dominance over other related search engines including Microsoft’s Bing. The outfit makes about 80% of its revenue from digital advertising, an industry that is valued at more than $278 billion in the United States alone. Google allegedly controls the majority of the technology that is used to serve advertisers and users as well as maintain dominance on Google PlayStore.</p>
<p>The global ad tech ecosystem is worth over $626 billion and Google’s dominance is beyond just the United States. While the regulators have found faults with the company’s dominance, Google has always argued that the market is quite competitive and that it has to fight for market share with the likes of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/amazon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Amazon.com Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AMZN) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT).</p>
<p>Google’s ad business connects advertisers with publishers in a highly customized way such that only the right target audience is reached. With the sophistication of the firm’s ad business, it is expected to make as much as $73.8 billion this 2023 fiscal year, a humongous capital base that is notably bigger than the market cap of some competitors like social media platform, Twitter Inc.</p>
<h2>Recurring Antitrust Lawsuits on Google</h2>
<p>This current lawsuit filed against Google by the Department of Justice has positioned Alphabet Inc as the firm that has come into the crosshairs of federal prosecutors the most considering its previous antitrust lawsuit is set to go on trial this September.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/googl-stock-down-1-as-google-got-slammed-its-third-antitrust-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">previous lawsuit</a> was filed back in 2020 under Attorney General William Barr in relation to its search engine business. The regulator posited that Google was squashing competitors with its algorithm. In addition, the DoJ claimed Google used exclusive distribution deals with wireless carriers and phone makers to lock out competition.</p>
<p>Tech giants <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/googl-stock-down-1-as-google-got-slammed-its-third-antitrust-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">including</a> Meta Platforms, Amazon, and Apple are also being grilled for their acquisition of smaller rivals in a bid to squash out competition. Meta Platforms&#8217; acquisition of Instagram and Apple’s Store policies are some of the salient issues being reviewed by regulators.</p>
<p>The multi-billion mega acquisition of gaming publisher <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/googl-stock-down-1-as-google-got-slammed-its-third-antitrust-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Activision Blizzard Inc</a> (NASDAQ: ATVI) by Microsoft was also placed on anticompetitive review as American regulators are pushing to maintain a free and healthy market for all stakeholders.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/">Google to Face Fresh Lawsuit from US Department of Justice</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/google-lawsuit-us-department-justice/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Islamic Fintech Startup Wahed Opens Physical Office in UK</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 14:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[klarna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revolut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wahed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233721</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/">Islamic Fintech Startup Wahed Opens Physical Office in UK</a></p>
<p>Wahed has a plan to help its customers grow their funds in the most Sharia-compliant way.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/">Islamic Fintech Startup Wahed Opens Physical Office in UK</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/">Islamic Fintech Startup Wahed Opens Physical Office in UK</a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">American financial technology and service provider, Wahed has extended its global reach with a newly opened office in the United Kingdom (UK). As </span><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/24/islamic-fintech-wahed-opens-physical-bank-branch-in-london.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by CNBC, the new office is like a storefront that looks like that of </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apple Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: AAPL), and it will house staff members that will provide account opening services and investment counseling for prospective customers.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wahed is touted as an Islamic finance banking firm that adheres to the tenets of Sharia investments to serve its users. The bank does not pay interest on savings, and it does not invest its customer’s money in a wide range of conventional investment options including lending businesses, alcohol, and tobacco amongst others.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bank encourages its users to invest their money into </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-an-exchange-traded-fund-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exchange Traded Funds</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (ETFs) that track the price of gold, an avenue to enable its users to hedge their capital against growing fiat inflation. The differential appreciation in the price of Gold per time is what the customer’s loss or gain will be.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the evolution of digital banking, there are a lot of startups offering tailored services for users in the space today. While the ones operating in the UK, including </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/revolut/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Revolut</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and Klarna do not have storefronts, Wahed’s Chief Executive Officer, Junaid Wahedna said the company’s idea to open physical offices is to bolster the trust of the Muslim community in the UK.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“They have trust issues,” he added. “And so they want to see a physical presence before they trust you with money.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With about 3.9 million Muslims in the United Kingdom, Wahed has a ready customer base, however, the firm said its services will not only target Muslims but also other Abrahamic faiths including Judaism and Christianity.</span></p>
<h2><b>Wahed UK Office to Meet Investor’s Needs</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are many intricacies to digital banking, however, many investors, especially millennials and Gen Z have adapted to them as compared to banking in physical offices. Wahed has the plan to help its customers grow their funds in the most Sharia-compliant way.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wahed is even optimistic that the company has a major role to play in serving Muslims that are largely considered generally underserved.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“I think it really fits with the Muslim community and what their needs are,” Wahedna said. “Because otherwise, what happens is the Muslim community, because they’re underserved, they keep their money in cash under their mattress, or in something that’s very unsafe, and they lose their money every few years because there’s a scam in the community or someone takes advantage of them. And that poverty cycle just continues.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wahedna criticized the usury model of most lending service providers today, adding that most fintech platforms are adding to the increasing cost of living for most people. The company is largely operating at a loss even though its outfit in Malaysia and the US had broken even.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saudi Aramco Entrepreneurship Capital, professional footballer, Paul Pogba is amongst the backers of the firm which has raised $75 million to date.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/">Islamic Fintech Startup Wahed Opens Physical Office in UK</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/islamic-fintech-startup-wahed-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ECB Says Digital Euro Will Be Free, Outlines More Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 14:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital euro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ecb]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233749</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/">ECB Says Digital Euro Will Be Free, Outlines More Plans</a></p>
<p>The ECB believes that the digital euro answers the increasing preference for digital payment.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/">ECB Says Digital Euro Will Be Free, Outlines More Plans</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/">ECB Says Digital Euro Will Be Free, Outlines More Plans</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/key/date/2023/html/ecb.sp230123~2f8271ed76.ga.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Speaking</a> to a European Parliament committee on the 23rd of January, an executive board member of the European Central Bank (ECB), Fabio Panetta, revealed that the digital euro will be free to use. The central bank has been committed to developing the digital version of a central bank currency. Upon its successful launch, the central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>) will extend payment options beyond cash offerings.</p>
<p>In a statement, the executive board member noted that the bank launched an investigation into a digital euro over a year ago, with close involvement of the European Parliament. According to the research, people are transitioning from cash payments to digital transactions. The use of cash payments in European countries over the last three years reduced from 72% to 59%. With digital payments gaining ground, many are changing their payment behavior, and fewer people settle for cash payments.</p>
<p>The bank reiterated that the digital euro is not replacing fiat currency but rather complementing it. Panetta stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our priority for the digital euro project has always been clear: to preserve the role of central bank money in retail payments by offering an additional option for paying with public money, including where this is not possible today, for example in e-commerce. The digital euro would not replace other electronic payment methods, or indeed cash. Rather, it would complement them. And by doing so, it would safeguard our monetary sovereignty while strengthening Europe’s strategic autonomy.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>ECB Comments on Digital Euro</h2>
<p>Also, people prefer that there is an option to pay with public money. The ECB believes that the digital euro answers the increasing preference for digital payment. According to Panetta, the CBDC gives Europeans access to another choice of payment that is free and available everywhere in the jurisdiction. The executive member is confident in the digital euro’s accessibility and convenience to help the currency attract more adoption and financial inclusion.</p>
<p>Additionally, the member of the European Central Bank noted that the digital euro would have a single set of rules enabling intermediaries to create products and services built on the CBDC. Panetta added that it would be best for the digital euro’s basic services to be free since it would be for the general public&#8217;s good.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Together with the European Commission, we are still analyzing a possible compensation model for the digital euro. In parallel, we are reviewing all the design options to bring them together in a high-level design for the digital euro in the spring. We are also finalizing our prototyping work and seeking input from the market to get an overview of options for the technical design of possible digital euro components and services.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Another plan for the digital euro by the ECB is to make it usable without barriers. The committee explained that the currency would be accessible globally to fulfill its role as a monetary anchor. Moving on, the ECB intends to further its investigation into the digital euro this year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/">ECB Says Digital Euro Will Be Free, Outlines More Plans</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-digital-euro-free-plans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Announces New Investments in OpenAI</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 12:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[msft stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233710</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/">Microsoft Announces New Investments in OpenAI</a></p>
<p>Microsoft has been working on transforming Azure into an AI supercomputer, primarily through its investments in OpenAI over the years.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/">Microsoft Announces New Investments in OpenAI</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/">Microsoft Announces New Investments in OpenAI</a></p>
<p>American technology corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/">Microsoft</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT) has <a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2023/01/23/microsoftandopenaiextendpartnership/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> a multibillion-dollar investment in Artificial intelligence company OpenAI, which is also the maker of ChatGPT. The tech company noted that the investment is towards advancing AI breakthroughs to ensure the benefits spread across the world. Although Microsoft did not specify the amount invested in OpenAI, Semafor <a href="https://www.semafor.com/article/01/09/2023/microsoft-eyes-10-billion-bet-on-chatgpt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> earlier this month that the agreement is worth $10 billion.</p>
<p>Microsoft&#8217;s latest investment in the artificial intelligence company comes after two previous financial commitments. The first two investments happened in 2019 and 2021, respectively. Microsoft backed OpenAI with $1 billion in July 2019, which made the tech company the exclusive cloud computing services provider for the AI firm. The agreement will continue under the most recent deal.</p>
<p>Explaining the plan for the partnership with OpenAI, Microsoft said it would continue to develop its cloud computing platform Azure to enable customers with AI applications on a broader level. The tech company will also leverage OpenAI&#8217;s technology to introduce new categories of digital experiences. It also mentioned Microsoft&#8217;s Azure OpenAI Service, which enables developers to build cutting-edge AI applications with direct access to OpenAI models. At the same time, Azure will back all OpenAI workloads as the exclusive cloud provider for the artificial intelligence company. The CEO and Chairman of Microsoft <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/satya-nadella/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Satya Nadella</a> commented on the relationship with OpenAI:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We formed our partnership with OpenAI around a shared ambition to responsibly advance cutting-edge AI research and democratize AI as a new technology platform. In this next phase of our partnership, developers and organizations across industries will have access to the best AI infrastructure, models, and toolchain with Azure to build and run their applications.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Microsoft has been working on transforming Azure into an AI supercomputer, primarily through its investments in OpenAI over the years. The joint venture unveiled its first top-5 supercomputer in 2020 and moved further in constructing multiple AI supercomputing systems. Additionally, OpenAI deployed the infrastructures for its models used in Azure to power AI products.</p>
<p>OpenAI&#8217;s CEO Sam Altman also said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The past three years of our partnership have been great. Microsoft shares our values and we are excited to continue our independent research and work toward creating advanced AI that benefits everyone.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>At press time, Microsoft stock is trading up 0.04% to $242.66 in premarket trading. This comes after the company closed up 0.98% to $242.58. Apart from jumping 2.37% over the past month and a little more than 1% since the year began, MSFT has been steadily plunging for the past year.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/">Microsoft Announces New Investments in OpenAI</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-investments-openai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FBI Confirms North Korea Was Behind $100 Million Harmony Hack</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 12:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fbi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[harmony protocol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lazarus group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[north korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[north korea crypto theft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/">FBI Confirms North Korea Was Behind $100 Million Harmony Hack</a></p>
<p>Hackers used a privacy protocol called RAILGUN to try to conceal their transactions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/">FBI Confirms North Korea Was Behind $100 Million Harmony Hack</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/">FBI Confirms North Korea Was Behind $100 Million Harmony Hack</a></p>
<p>The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) has concluded its investigations into last year&#8217;s crypto hack that saw US-based Harmony protocol, lose $100 million worth of crypto. According to the FBI, the investigation has revealed that the June attack was perpetrated by two North Korea-backed hacking groups. They are the Lazarus Group and the APT38. Interestingly, the finding is not far off from earlier suspicions that made the rounds shortly after the massive exploit happened.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the breakthrough came on January 13 when the bad actors attempted to move over $60 million of ETH that they stole during the attack. The FBI confirms that the hackers used a privacy protocol called RAILGUN to try to conceal their transactions. They were able to send some of the funds to various crypto exchanges and convert them to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>. However, some exchanges were also able to freeze and recover the remaining funds while the hackers attempted to swap them for Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>More Than Just Hack, Says FBI</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, the number of such attacks being perpetrated by North Korean cyber groups has been on the rise. Lazarus Group was said to have been responsible for the $625 million <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lazarus-group-ronin-bridge-hack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ronin bridge hack</a>.  And per an Associated Press report, North Korean hackers have stolen at least $1.2 billion worth of cryptocurrency since 2017.</p>
<p>However,  these groups reportedly do more than just hacks. They also front as venture capitalists, banks, or recruiters at other times. Nonetheless, the FBI has vowed to do everything within its power to check the antics of North Korea. Part of the statement reads:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The FBI will continue to expose and combat the DPRK’s use of illicit activities &#8211; including cybercrime and virtual currency theft &#8211; to generate revenue for the regime.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the FBI also claims that North Korea has a mission. That is to use the laundering of virtual currency to finance its missiles and weapons programs. However, the body <a href="https://www.fbi.gov/news/press-releases/fbi-confirms-lazarus-group-apt38-cyber-actors-responsible-for-harmonys-horizon-bridge-currency-theft" target="_blank" rel="noopener">says</a> it will continue collaborating with its investigative partners to frustrate their efforts.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/">FBI Confirms North Korea Was Behind $100 Million Harmony Hack</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/fbi-north-korea-100m-harmony-hack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Logitech Posts Fiscal Q3 2023 Results, Sees Sales Slide 22% YoY</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 11:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logitech]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233700</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/">Logitech Posts Fiscal Q3 2023 Results, Sees Sales Slide 22% YoY</a></p>
<p>Computer mice, keyboards, and webcams maker Logitech has lowered its full-year sales outlook after an underwhelming fiscal Q3 2023 report. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/">Logitech Posts Fiscal Q3 2023 Results, Sees Sales Slide 22% YoY</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/">Logitech Posts Fiscal Q3 2023 Results, Sees Sales Slide 22% YoY</a></p>
<p>Logitech International SA (NASDAQ: LOGI) recently posted its Q3 2023 earnings report, which showed a 22% drop in quarterly sales. The underwhelming performance also underscored Logitech&#8217;s preliminary results, with a halt in customer purchases of new equipment amid slowdown worries.</p>
<p>For its fiscal Q3 2023, Logitech reported sales of $1.27 billion, with category sales declining 22% and 17% in both US dollars and constant currency. In addition, the Swiss-American computer mice maker also reported that gaming sales fell 16% and 10%, respectively. Meanwhile, video collaboration sales declined 21% in US dollars and 16% in constant currency, with keyboard and combo sales sliding 22% and 17%, respectively.</p>
<p>Logitech&#8217;s reported revenue of $1.27 billion also missed revenue estimates by $50 million, with Non-GAAP operating income sliding 32% to $204 million. In the year-ago quarter, this figure stood at $302 million. Amid the challenging environment, GAAP operating income declined 33% to $177 million compared to $263 million in the year-ago quarter. Meanwhile, cash flow from operations was $280 million, which brings the company&#8217;s cash balance to $1.04 billion. Furthermore, Logitech returned $486 million of cash to shareholders via its annual dividend payment and share repurchases. This sum also includes $90 million returned this quarter.</p>
<p>Weighing in on Logitech&#8217;s latest fiscal quarterly performance, the company&#8217;s president and chief executive officer Bracken Darrell <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230123005789/en/Logitech-Announces-Q3-FY-2023-Results" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;These quarterly results reflect the current challenging macroeconomic conditions, including currency exchange rates and inflation, as well as lower enterprise and consumer spending. With these external headwinds, we continued to aggressively manage our costs in the quarter while at the same time growing market share in key categories. Our long-term strategies remain unchanged, and we remain committed to the growth trends that fuel our business.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Rise &amp; Fall in Demand</h2>
<p>During the pandemic, Logitech experienced a surge in demand for its home office devices and computer gaming products. However, that boon has abated as countries lift restrictions and fewer people remain trapped at home for work or pleasure. In addition, the constant state of high inflation has also driven up costs and discouraged consumers from spending.</p>
<p>Logitech also experienced production headwinds in China as it struggled to obtain components for its factories. These difficulties were paramount during city-wide shutdowns of activities and operations in China due to a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/topics/coronavirus-updates/">Covid</a> resurgence.</p>
<h2>Grim Outlook for Logitech Following Fiscal Q3 2023 Outing</h2>
<p>Two weeks ago, when Logitech initially lowered its performance forecast for the year, Darrell noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are disappointed in these preliminary third-quarter results. They reflect challenging macroeconomic conditions, including a slowdown in sales to enterprise customers in the quarter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Following its latest financial statement, Logitech plans to hold a financial results videoconference today to discuss takeaways. In addition, the dual-headquartered computer peripheral and software manufacturer also retained its financial outlook for the current year. Logitech still expects its full-year sales to drop by 13%-15% in constant currency and a non-GAAP operating income of between $550 and $600 million.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/">Logitech Posts Fiscal Q3 2023 Results, Sees Sales Slide 22% YoY</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/logitech-fiscal-q3-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shadow Fork for Ethereum Shanghai Mainnet Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 11:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/">Shadow Fork for Ethereum Shanghai Mainnet Goes Live</a></p>
<p>The successful launch of testnet means Ethereum is still on schedule to deliver the withdrawal features five to eight weeks from now.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/">Shadow Fork for Ethereum Shanghai Mainnet Goes Live</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/">Shadow Fork for Ethereum Shanghai Mainnet Goes Live</a></p>
<p>There&#8217;s been a lot of talk going around the upcoming <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> hardfork aka the Shanghai hardfork scheduled probably by February end. This is the most-discussed event currently in the crypto community since it will unlock $26 billion worth of staked ETH in the market.</p>
<p>On Monday, January 23, the Ethereum core developers <a href="https://decrypt.co/119851/ethereum-shanghai-mainnet-shadow-fork-goes-live" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the successful deployment of the first mainnet shadow fork designed to test the readiness of the withdrawal capability for ETH staking. The mainnet shadow forks basically represent a full dress rehearsal of system upgrades. They allow developers to test any design flaws or tweak any outstanding issues. Thus, Monday&#8217;s test successfully previewed the upcoming Ethereum shanghai upgrade.</p>
<p>Since Ethereum&#8217;s historic Merge event in September 2022, Shanghai will be the first major upgrade in the Ethereum ecosystem. The Merge event transitioned the Ethereum blockchain into a complete proof-of-stake system. It allowed users to deposit ETH with the network and thereby become validators to help authenticate on-chain transactions.</p>
<p>Since the launch of the Beacon Chain in December 2020, Ethereum (ETH) users have deposited $26.5 billion worth of ETH to earn staking rewards. However, with the implementation of the Shanghai upgrade, users will be able to withdraw both, their original deposits as well as newly minted ETH.</p>
<p>Marius Van Der Wijden, the Ethereum core developer announced on Monday that the shadow fork for the first Ethereum withdrawal mainnet was successfully launched. Although there were a few minor issues, they stand corrected.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Withdrawal-Mainnet-Shadow-Fork-1 is finalizing 🚀🚀🚀</p>
<p>It started out with a few issues because the config wasn&#39;t correctly applied on geth (we disallow overriding the mainnet config). The config is applied correctly and all nodes are in agreement. We will start some evil nodes,.</p>
<p>&mdash; MariusVanDerWijden (@vdWijden) <a href="https://twitter.com/vdWijden/status/1617530244302532615?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Ethereum Shanghai Hardfork on Schedule</h2>
<p>The latest development means that the Ethereum network is still on schedule to deliver the withdrawal features five to eight weeks from now. This timeline remains the top priority for the network&#8217;s core developers who were eager to deliver ETH withdrawal capability as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Originally, the Shanghai upgrade was likely to have bigger enhancements such as proto-danksharding and EOF update to the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). However, both these upgrades have been postponed in order to ensure that ETH withdrawals could debut by March 2023.</p>
<p>Last week, several Ethereum core developers expressed their frustration to forego the update for the encoding method used to roll out Shanghai. This was another sacrifice made by the developers to hasten the Shanghai release.</p>
<p>Analysts at JP Morgan noted that the ability of ETH stakers to withdraw funds “could usher in a new era of staking” for major crypto exchange Coinbase.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/">Shadow Fork for Ethereum Shanghai Mainnet Goes Live</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shadow-fork-shanghai-mainnet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple in Talks with Disney Over VR Headset Content</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virtual Reality & Augmented Reality News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple ar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple glasses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple headset]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple mixed reality headset]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple virtual reality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple vr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233642</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/">Apple in Talks with Disney Over VR Headset Content</a></p>
<p>Apple's mixed reality headset is expected to launch in the spring, and deliveries will begin by fall 2023. The device will be exclusive, for a limited audience, rather than mainstream.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/">Apple in Talks with Disney Over VR Headset Content</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/">Apple in Talks with Disney Over VR Headset Content</a></p>
<p>Tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) is in talks with at least six media companies over the development of virtual reality (VR) content for its mixed reality headset. Among the partners are <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/disney/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Walt Disney Company</a> (NYSE: DIS) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sony/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sony Corporation</a> (NYSE: SONY).</p>
<p>Apple has been experimenting with virtual reality and augmented reality technologies for a long time. Back in 2020, it <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/aapl-stock-up-0-6-as-apple-acquired-virtual-reality-company-nextvr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquired</a> a California-based VR company NextVR to create a separate unit to focus on VR and AR products. Earlier, the company was working on developing its own Apple Glasses headsets designed to work like the Google Glass smart glasses that are lightweight and offer digital representation overlaid with the real world. However, Apple recently indefinitely <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-halts-apple-glasses/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">postponed</a> its active work on the product. There are rumors that the company has been experiencing significant technical challenges. One of the possible options for using such glasses could replace a smartphone, and some employees of the company generally doubt that such things can be done.</p>
<p>Instead, Apple tasked its AR team to intensify work on the AR headsets. The mixed reality headset is expected to launch in the spring, and deliveries will begin by fall 2023. Apple does not reveal much information about the upcoming headset. However, there are rumors that its price will be around $3,000. The price shows that the device will be exclusive, for a limited audience, rather than mainstream.</p>
<p>Apparently, Apple AR/VR headset will be a standalone device with powerful chips that will put the performance on par with Apple&#8217;s Macs. Equipped with two chips inside, the headset will also be able to perform independently of an iPhone or a Mac.</p>
<p>The headset will have several external cameras that can track hand movements. It can also be done due to special 3D sensors that will read users&#8217; eyes to control gestures. There will also be support for voice control, skin detection, spatial detection, and expression detection. Users will be able to look at an item on the display to select it, using hand gestures to interact with the item.</p>
<p>When it comes to design, the Apple headset is expected to look similar to other headsets on the market. But it will have a lightweight construction, about 300 to 400 grams, to ensure users&#8217; comfort.</p>
<p>Notably, Apple is also designing an App Store for the headset. The content will focus on gaming, streaming video, and video conferencing. The company has even designed a separate &#8220;xrOS&#8221; system for the headset. A FaceTime experience will use cameras to project a person&#8217;s full face and body into a virtual environment for one-on-one calls, and there will also be other apps like Calendar, Mail, Safari, and more. TV+ material will also be updated in order to comply with the headset.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/">Apple in Talks with Disney Over VR Headset Content</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-disney-vr-headset-content/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swiss Bank Cité Gestion Is First Private Bank to Tokenize Its Shares</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cite gestion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kkr]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233661</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/">Swiss Bank Cité Gestion Is First Private Bank to Tokenize Its Shares</a></p>
<p>The company also planned to offer qualified US-based investors access to funds offering exposure to direct equities, private credit, and secondary transactions.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/">Swiss Bank Cité Gestion Is First Private Bank to Tokenize Its Shares</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/">Swiss Bank Cité Gestion Is First Private Bank to Tokenize Its Shares</a></p>
<p>Independent Swiss Private Bank Cité Gestion, which was established in 2009, is using Taurus technology to <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/24/swiss-bank-cite-gestion-becomes-first-private-bank-to-tokenize-its-own-shares/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tokenize</a> its own shares. This move is a part of the company&#8217;s continuous attempts to grow its roots deeper into the world of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>It is the first time a private bank has rolled out shares as ledger-based securities under Swiss Law. It will collaborate with the digital assets company Taurus to authorize its tokenized shares along with handling the smart contract that develops the shares and offers asset servicing of its securities.</p>
<p>Tokenization, or the digitization of several asset categories, has been a popular movement among financial establishments as it allows TradFi participants to draw more investors via blockchain technology. In an official statement from Taurus, it was said that this new trend of digitization of private assets and securities has become the novel standard in the virtual asset industry.</p>
<p>On a similar note, investment management company Hamilton Lane (HLNE) announced that it will tokenize three of its funds in collaboration with the digital asset securities firm Securitize. The main vision behind tokenization for the firm was to help offer private market investment opportunities to institutional or ultra-high-net-worth investors.</p>
<p>The company also planned to offer qualified US-based investors access to funds offering exposure to direct equities, private credit, and secondary transactions, which will be tokenized through Securitize&#8217;s virtual transfer agency.</p>
<p>This announcement was also followed by another investment company KKR, revealing its plans in September to tokenize its Health Care Strategic Growth Fund on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/avalanche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Avalanche</a> Blockchain.</p>
<p>The tokenization of Swiss firm Cité Gestion’s shares was processed while complying with the standards designated by the Capital Markets and Technology Association (CMTA), which is a Geneva-based non-profit organization.</p>
<p>The tokens were built using CMTA, an open-source smart contract offered by the CMTA and particularly committed to the tokenization of securities. Taurus, which was founded in April 2018, acquired a securities license the year before from the Swiss Financial Market Supervisory Authority to deliver investors and banks the ability to trade several assets, which included tokenized securities.</p>
<p>The firm has had a long history of tokenization as it has till now, been involved in 15 projects that comprise equity, private debt, and structured products from companies in Switzerland and Europe.</p>
<p>In December last year, Cité Gestion reached an agreement to unite its business with the multi-family investment office Sartus Capital. Sartus Capital, on the other hand, was established in 2016 and has its headquarters in Geneva.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/">Swiss Bank Cité Gestion Is First Private Bank to Tokenize Its Shares</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/swiss-cite-gestion-tokenize-shares/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court Fast-tracks Oral Argument in Grayscale vs SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=233665</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/">Court Fast-tracks Oral Argument in Grayscale vs SEC Case</a></p>
<p>Grayscale is now neck deep with the lawsuit and there are many assumptions from members of the public with respect to the potential bottlenecks that the lawsuit might present.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/">Court Fast-tracks Oral Argument in Grayscale vs SEC Case</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/">Court Fast-tracks Oral Argument in Grayscale vs SEC Case</a></p>
<p>The dates for hearing the oral argument in the ongoing lawsuit between <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale Investments</a> and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) has been expedited by the District Columbia Court of Appeals. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/24/dc-appeals-court-expedites-oral-arguments-in-grayscale-lawsuit-against-sec.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, the Court has fixed March 7 as the date for both parties to present their oral arguments, fast-tracking a process that Grayscale had expected will not come until sometime in the second quarter.</p>
<p>Grayscale is one of the most prominent subsidiaries of the Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert’s crypto empire that is facing liquidity strain through its broad exposure to the recently collapsed FTX Derivatives Exchange. Grayscale sued the SEC back in June last year after the financial markets regulator denied its application to convert its flagship Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) to a full-fledged Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF).</p>
<p>The SEC’s denial was hinged on the premise that Grayscale did not provide convincing evidence that it can prevent the underlying market manipulation that is peculiar to the digital currency ecosystem. After approving the Bitcoin Futures ETF from firms like ProShares, Grayscale Investments believes the SEC does not have the moral grounds to deny its application.</p>
<p>The lawsuit was filed in just about a week when it received a rejection from the commission and the firm went as far as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-obama-lawyer-spot-etf-verdict/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hiring</a> Donald B Verrilli to join its law team. Verrilli was a top Solicitor during the President Obama administration and he is known for his high-profile winnings at the time. With Verrilli’s input, the firm said it was confident of victory at the trials.</p>
<p>Grayscale’s request is not far-fetched and it just revolves around getting the court to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-lawsuit-sec-bitcoin-spot-etf-bid-rejection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">review</a> the SEC’s decisions and determine whether they are consistent with its previous rulings.</p>
<h2>Grayscale vs SEC: Potential Bottlenecks</h2>
<p>Grayscale is now neck deep with the lawsuit and there are many assumptions from members of the public with respect to the potential bottlenecks that the lawsuit might present. While the company has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grayscale-clarifies-lawsuit-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">addressed</a> some common frequently asked questions (FAQs) last year, it has notably promised to refund investors capital should it lose the lawsuit to the SEC.</p>
<p>As of January, the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust holds a total of $14.5 billion in assets under management, and though the crypto winter has caused a significant value plummet, the product is still revered as one of the most important in the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>With the lawsuit now in full steam, there are chances that the expedited argument hearing as determined by the Court of Appeals will imply the justice system wants a speedy resolution of the conflict. As it stands, investors may stand to benefit more should the lawsuit close before the bankruptcy proceedings of Genesis Global, another subsidiary of DCG is completed.</p>
<p>The assumption is that the bankruptcy may have an undertone that will stir Grayscale to liquidate the more than 600,000 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> assets it has in custody, a scenario that will impact investors much more.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-lay-off-10-staff/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/">Court Fast-tracks Oral Argument in Grayscale vs SEC Case</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/court-grayscale-sec-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>