<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:51:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andy Watson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[m-ventures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mexc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/">M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3</a></p>
<p>The need for better transparency and compliance with laid down rules will be critical in 2023.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/">M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/">M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3</a></p>
<p>In a recent speech, Leo Zhao, a venture partner of M-Ventures which is <a href="https://www.mexc.com/">MEXC</a>, a global cryptocurrency exchange, talked about the various opportunities and prospects the cryptocurrency market could provide for institutions in 2023.</p>
<p>Leo explored the following core points:</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1">How blockchain layer-2 solutions and Zero Knowledge Proofs technology are maturing.</li>
<li aria-level="1">The state of crypto mainstream adoption</li>
<li aria-level="1">Transparency and regulatory compliance</li>
</ul>
<h2>Review of the Current Market</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Ugly</strong></li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>LUNA and FTX</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Bad</strong></li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>The significant drop in Crypto Market cap and Defi TVL</li>
<li>The decrease of crypto developer activities</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Good</strong></li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>VCs keep investing in the industry</li>
<li>The Ethereum Merge, the boom of L2 TVL, accrual in value</li>
<li>NFT gets the mainstream spotlight</li>
</ol>
<p>To summarize the current state of the crypto market in 2022, he compared last year’s events to the Box Office movie, The Good, Bad, and the Ugly. In his assessment, the movie best summarized everything that panned out last year. From the record-high inflation, the continuous FED interest rate hikes, and the effect rising fund rates had on the capital market, which eventually precipitated the severe decline last year.</p>
<p>Typically, he noticed, when the regulatory “tide” recedes, the financial markets tend to de-leverage quite quickly, and it was evident last year. When the cracks began to widen, most firms found themselves swimming naked. In Terra and LUNA’s case, it was more severe. At peaks, they were valued at $40 billion and $20 billion, respectively. They crashed, and people, including institutions that had exposure, lost money. In FTX’s case, they raised $2 billion, only for them to take out $8 billion of the much-needed liquidity from the gapping crypto market. These quick, damaging sequels have punctured investor trust in the industry. Confidence can only be reclaimed through solid, genuine actions.</p>
<p>Liquidity is currently low and investors are playing safe. Looking at crypto charts, the total market capitalization dropped from $3 trillion at 2021 peaks to around $800 billion, shedding 73 percent. On the other hand, the total value locked (TVL) across DeFi protocols in all blockchains shrunk from $218 billion to $54 billion, representing a 75 percent decline.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-1.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="565" /></p>
<p>In reflection of the general apprehensions across the board, developer activities for Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) and non-EVM blockchains have also contracted significantly.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-2.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="910" height="1038" /></p>
<p>However, this is one big exception. Despite the free-falling markets, crypto venture capitalists with deep pockets are doubling down. They appear to be scooping worthy projects. As charts reveal, bear markets are historically the best time to invest.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-3.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="392" /></p>
<p>The impact of the Ethereum Merge is also clear. The Merge was historic for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> and its effects are being felt today. ETH is gradually becoming ultrasound money. In 97 days after the upgrade, only 2000 ETH has been added to circulation instead of the 1.1 million worth $1.2 billion that could have been added, and possibly sold by miners.</p>
<div style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-4.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="530" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Photo: Ultrasound.Money</p></div>
<h2>What Crypto Must Overcome</h2>
<ol>
<li aria-level="1">Limits in infrastructure</li>
<li aria-level="1">Poor user interface and experience</li>
<li aria-level="1">Opaqueness and compliance</li>
</ol>
<p>To resolve these challenges and create opportunities, problems must first be detailed. Leo Zhao previewed that the three main problems mentioned above should be satisfactorily resolved.</p>
<p>The current misconception in crypto and blockchain scenes, he said, was the assumption that infrastructure only encapsulated layer-1 and layer-2 platforms. In his view, there are centralized elements of blockchain that must first be tackled. He cites GitHub, a repository that can easily censor Tornado Cash codes. Besides, there are cross-chain bridges that are continuously being targeted, costing protocols millions of dollars.</p>
<p>Unlike web2 where navigation and interactions are smooth, it is scary for ordinary, non-techie individuals to use blockchain-based solutions. On average, even storing seed phrases can be terrifying for the average user.</p>
<p>Zhao also took issue with centralized institutions saying there should be more transparency and a clearer regulatory framework to spark adoption.</p>
<h2>Trends and Opportunities in 2023</h2>
<ul>
<li>L2 and ZK Technology for scaling blockchains are maturing:</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>TVL of popular Ethereum L2s like Arbitrum and Optimism is rising</li>
<li>ZK</li>
<li>Other modular blockchain solutions</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Mainstream Adoption</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>NFT everything. People no longer need to ask &#8220;what is NFT&#8221;, instead &#8220;which NFT should I ape into?&#8221; Gaming, Social and Music</li>
<li>MPC wallet and Smart Contract Wallet</li>
<li>The migration of Web2 users</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>Transparency and Compliance</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>CEXs now have to be more transparent or get displaced by DeFi</li>
<li>There is more clarity on crypto assets regulations</li>
<li>Hong Kong</li>
</ol>
<p>To streamline processes, Zhao said the following trends and opportunities could rise in 2023 and subsequent years:</p>
<p>First, he notes that scaling solutions are maturing and are being adopted. Although TVL dropped in USD terms, more people appear to be locking their assets in DeFi protocols since the number rose from 250k to nearly 4 million ETH. At this pace, he predicts more activities to be migrated from the mainnet to layer-2 as more interesting opportunities arise, ranging from layer-2 as-as-service for specific applications. Zhao also said developers will also look to release more reliable bridges and aggregators.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-5.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="556" /></p>
<p>Besides L2, ZK Rollup solutions are catching up, especially with zkSync and StarkWare deploying solutions. As the sector booms, Zhao sees opportunities in ZKP Hardware, personal data marketplace, and ZK-powered cross-chain bridges.</p>
<div style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-6.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="453" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Photo: Dune Analytics</p></div>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> usage might have dropped in 2022 but Zhao thinks the sub-sector could flourish in 2023. As data shows, the number of users with Lens Profile is on the rise. The Lens Protocol is a permissionless, composable, and decentralized social graph. All these social graphs are NFTs, meaning all your social activities can be integrated by developers. The way Lens Protocol is designed, this technology could revolutionize the way social apps are built, while also heavily influencing music and gaming.</p>
<div style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-7.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="469" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Photo: Dune Analytics</p></div>
<p>Web3 dApps, especially wallets, will likely have better designs in 2023. Just like how there are social recovery, logins, and semi-custodial controls of accounts in platforms like Google and Facebook, it will be possible for web3 users to invite users to co-manage accounts through email and other means.</p>
<div style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-8.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="735" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Photo: 1kx</p></div>
<p>There will also be a paradigm shift in gaming. Whilst traditional desktop and mobile gaming have a $90 billion annual revenue, Play-to-Earn (P2E) blockchain games are still in development and are in the “web page” gaming era. P2E and blockchain gaming are getting started as their infrastructure, including those of better distribution, trading, and engines, are being developed.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3-9.png" alt="M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3" width="1024" height="394" /></p>
<p>Lastly, the need for better transparency and compliance with laid down rules will be critical in 2023. If centralized institutions fail to comply, their market share could be gnawed by innovative DeFi protocols, launched on the blockchain, offering higher levels of transparency. As this takes shape, more governments will be required to provide more clarity on the regulatory framework for crypto and blockchain to be adopted by the next billion users.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>As he concluded, Zhao advised developers to pick out these opportunities and build on them. He urged crypto venture capitalists to keep investing in solid ideas above as they will ultimately light up the future and provide a better financial world.</p>
<h2>About M-Ventures</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/MVenturesLabs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">M-Ventures</a> is a crypto fund under MEXC Global, with $100m+ AUM and 300+ portfolio investments. We constantly study the market and the different sectors of the crypto industry to search for the next billion-dollar ideas. It&#8217;s my pleasure to take this opportunity to share with you some of our observations.</p>
<h2>About MEXC</h2>
<p>MEXC is the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency trading platform, providing one-stop cryptocurrency trading services for spot, ETF, futures, Staking, NFT Index, and more. MEXC currently serves more than 10 million users worldwide and embraces the philosophy of &#8220;Users first, MEXC&#8217;s Changing for you&#8221;.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/">M-Ventures Partner Leo Zhao’s Speech on 2023 Trends and Opportunities in Web3</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/m-ventures-leo-zhao-2023-web3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Global Dismisses Additional 30% of Staff</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 12:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[genesis global]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231600</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/">Genesis Global Dismisses Additional 30% of Staff</a></p>
<p>Genesis conducted the latest staff cut after the company informed clients about "reducing costs and driving efficiencies" amid challenging times for many crypto firms.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/">Genesis Global Dismisses Additional 30% of Staff</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/">Genesis Global Dismisses Additional 30% of Staff</a></p>
<p>With fingers crossed on what the crypto economy is this year, Genesis Global Trading recently dismissed more staff. This came after the company laid off 20% of its workforce in August 2022. When Genesis Global Trading let go of some people last year, it had about 260 employees. At the same time, the company was struggling with major losses connected to the crash of Three Arrows Capital. Also, it was the same time as CEO Michael Moro was exiting his role. Replacing Moro was the Chief Operating Officer Derar Islim, who joined Genesis in 2020. Islim, who was taking over, commented on the staff cut at Genesis and the change in structure. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The changes and investments we&#8217;re announcing today affirm our commitment to operational excellence as we continue to expand our services to meet the needs of our clients today and into the future.</p></blockquote>
<p>The downturn started with the failure of the crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>. Genesis said in November that it had $175 million in locked funds in its FTX trading account. Shortly after, it announced that its lending arm would halt its own customer withdrawals.</p>
<h2>Genesis Lays off More Staff</h2>
<p>Less than a year after the initial staff reduction, Genesis has eliminated another 30% of its employees. Now, the company&#8217;s headcount has drastically lessened to about 145, considering the two staff cuts. A spokesperson of the company mentioned two departments that were affected mainly by the decision. They are the sales and the business-development departments. The representative continued:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As we continue to navigate unprecedented industry changes. Genesis has made the difficult decision to reduce our headcount globally. These measures are part of our ongoing efforts to move our business forward. We sincerely appreciate the hard work of our talented and dedicated team as we continue to work to identify the best outcome for Genesis&#8217;s business, clients and employees for the long term.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Genesis conducted the latest staff cut after the company informed clients about &#8220;reducing costs and driving efficiencies&#8221; amid challenging times for many crypto firms. The company said in a letter that it needs to &#8220;take some additional time&#8221; to navigate through a tough financial time.</p>
<p>In other news, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-900m-gemini-clients/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">wrote</a> last month about Genesis Global owing over $900 million to Gemini clients. This is because Genesis has been dealing with liquidity issues since FTX&#8217;s collapse. Notably, Genesis and Gemini Earn partnered on Gemini Earn, which allows investors to earn 8% interest by lending out their digital assets.</p>
<p>The entire market is at its lows. Mortgage demand dropped 13.2% as 2022 folded, an uncertain 2023 outlook <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/2023-outlook-treasury-yields/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">caused treasury yields to decline</a>, and the bearish crypto market remained.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/">Genesis Global Dismisses Additional 30% of Staff</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-dismisses-30-staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ECB Official Pushes for CBDC Development Citing Betterment for Consumers</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 12:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/">ECB Official Pushes for CBDC Development Citing Betterment for Consumers</a></p>
<p>The ECB executive called the European Union’s Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) an important step.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/">ECB Official Pushes for CBDC Development Citing Betterment for Consumers</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/">ECB Official Pushes for CBDC Development Citing Betterment for Consumers</a></p>
<p>Fabio Panetta, the executive board member of the European Central Bank (ECB), recently published a pushing forward the need for developing a central bank digital currency (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CBDC</a>). As per the previous reports, the ECB has been already working on its CBDC &#8211; Digital Euro &#8211; and could see it coming into the market by 2025.</p>
<h2>ECB and CBDC</h2>
<p>In his arguments in the blog post on January 5, Panetta presented his latest arguments noting that by developing CBDCs, central banks “will safeguard the trust on which private forms of money ultimately depend&#8221;.</p>
<p>Panetta began his arguments by adding how the last of 2022 was pretty rough for the cryptocurrency market. “Last year marked the unraveling of the crypto market as investors moved from the fear of missing out to the fear of not getting out,” he said. The ECB executive has been a skeptic of cryptocurrencies in the past as well.</p>
<p>Thus, the recent unraveling of events in the crypto space gave Panetta the chance to double down on his skepticism. The ECB executive notes that these massive failures in quick successions reflect the incredibly high leverage in the crypto space. He further adds that this exposes the  &#8220;inadequate governance structures&#8221; of the crypto ecosystem. Lashing out at the crypto space, Panetta <a href="https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/blog/date/2023/html/ecb.blog230105~75d5aee900.en.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">adds</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The crypto market rout has left the financial system largely unscathed. Many therefore think it preferable to let crypto burn rather than regulate at the risk of legitimising cryptos. Let me voice two important reservations about this view. First, despite their fundamental flaws, it is not certain that crypto assets will ultimately self-combust. Second, the cost to society of an unregulated crypto industry is too high to ignore&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<h2>ECB Executive Pushes for MiCA</h2>
<p>Citing the king of losses that retail investors faced with the fall of the crypto market last year, Panetta notes that it is imperative to bring a proper regulatory framework in place. &#8220;We need to build guardrails that address regulatory gaps and arbitrage and tackle the significant social costs of cryptos head-on, he added.</p>
<p>The ECB executive called the European Union’s Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) an important step. However, he adds that it is insufficient to address matters related to crypto asset lending or non-custodial wallet services. He also noted that “Trading in unbacked digital assets should be treated by regulators like gambling.”</p>
<p>Panetta believes that this treatment would include both &#8211; taxation as well as measures to protect vulnerable customers. But this could have its own shortcomings as well. Only CBDC is “a risk-free and dependable digital settlement asset,” and preserving the trust in central banks will help to safeguard the trust in digital assets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/">ECB Official Pushes for CBDC Development Citing Betterment for Consumers</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ecb-official-cbdc-development-consumers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CME Group and CF Benchmarks Teams Up to Launch New Metaverse Reference Rates</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 12:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cf benchmarks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cme group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse Reference Rates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231616</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Teams Up to Launch New Metaverse Reference Rates</a></p>
<p>The move to provide the three new metaverse reference rates comes off as a unique contribution by the CME Group and CF Benchmarks to help with the evolution of the Web 3.0 ecosystem.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Teams Up to Launch New Metaverse Reference Rates</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Teams Up to Launch New Metaverse Reference Rates</a></p>
<p>American global markets firm, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cme-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CME Group Inc</a> (NASDAQ: CME), and CF Benchmarks have partnered to launch three new metaverse reference rates as both sought to extend their footprints in the emerging Web3.0 world. According to a published <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cme-group-and-cf-benchmarks-to-launch-three-new-metaverse-reference-rates-and-real-time-indices-on-january-30-301714319.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, the three new metaverse reference rates include Axie Infinity (AXS), Chiliz (CHZ), and Decentraland (MANA).</p>
<p>The metaverse is a loosely used term for virtual reality-based social interactions that many believe will dominate Web3.0, considered as the next iteration of the internet. With different crypto projects building different aspects of the metaverse, the duo of the CME Group and CF Benchmarks has highlighted a need to create a more trusted reference rate for investors following these digital currencies.</p>
<p>&#8220;As we continue to see a rising interest in Metaverse projects, CME Group, in partnership with CF Benchmarks, will expand its suite of regulated, non-tradable Cryptocurrency Reference Rates and Real-Time Indices to include three new Metaverse tokens,&#8221; said Giovanni Vicioso, CME Group Global Head of Cryptocurrency Products. &#8220;With increased price transparency across more cryptocurrency products, market participants will be able to price sector-specific portfolios, develop structured products with greater confidence and manage price risk around various Metaverse-based projects.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to the CME Group, the metaverse reference rates will be computed by prices adapted from exchanges listed as the go-to places for its benchmarks. These trading platforms include <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bitstamp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitstamp</a>, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a>, itBit, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kraken/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Kraken</a>, and LMAX Digital. Per the announcement, the Metaverse Reference Rates is not a futures product that can be traded by investors.</p>
<p>The metaverse reference rate will be published once a day at 4 pm London Time, but according to the CME Group, it will be accessible round the clock all year long.</p>
<h2>CME Group and CF Benchmarks Solidifying the Metaverse</h2>
<p>The move to provide the three new metaverse reference rates comes off as a unique contribution by the CME Group and CF Benchmarks to help with the evolution of the Web 3.0 ecosystem.</p>
<p>Without a trusted price source, regulators especially will always assume that key tokens are susceptible to algorithmic manipulation. By riding on the reputation of the CME Group, Axie Infinity, Chiliz and Decentraland will further be able to boast of price accuracy in league <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC) and other assets previously profiled by the duo.</p>
<p>&#8220;These benchmarks will provide accurate and resilient pricing data for tokens linked to the Metaverse, an exciting new scion of crypto where properties and communities can exist wholly within a virtual realm,&#8221; said Sui Chung, CEO of CF Benchmarks. &#8220;CF Benchmarks is proud to continue its work with CME Group, providing investors with exposure to all facets of the digital asset class with reference rates that meet the high benchmarking standards they&#8217;ve come to expect.&#8221;</p>
<p>Many are optimistic that such related price benchmarks will serve as a yardstick for new institutional investors to back the new assets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/">CME Group and CF Benchmarks Teams Up to Launch New Metaverse Reference Rates</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/cme-group-cf-benchmarks-metaverse-reference/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Giant DCG Shuts Down HQ Subsidiary amid Global Economic Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 12:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dcg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital currency group (dcg)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hq]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231615</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/">Crypto Giant DCG Shuts Down HQ Subsidiary amid Global Economic Crisis</a></p>
<p>DCG once appeared to be untouchable but may fast be losing its stability.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/">Crypto Giant DCG Shuts Down HQ Subsidiary amid Global Economic Crisis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/">Crypto Giant DCG Shuts Down HQ Subsidiary amid Global Economic Crisis</a></p>
<p>Digital Currency Group (DCG) has announced that it is shutting down operations at its wealth management division HQ. According to a <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/genesis-parent-company-dcg-shutters-its-wealth-management-division" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by The Information, DCG is taking such a drastic step due to the prevalent economic situation across the world. To that effect, a spokesperson for the firm released a statement saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Due to the state of the broader economic environment and prolonged crypto winter presenting significant headwinds to the industry, we made the decision to wind down HQ, effective January 31, 2023.”</p></blockquote>
<p>DCG May Be Facing Liquidity Issues amid HQ News</p>
<p>Without a doubt, DCG is one of the companies hardest hit by the implosion of the FTX exchange in early November. The firm, which owns major crypto players such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Grayscale</a> and beleaguered Genesis, has had it rough since the beginning of last year.  But so did most firms globally. Things took a turn for the worse for the company, however, when <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> eventually <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blockfi-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> for bankruptcy.</p>
<p>It is also worth noting that the news of HQ shutting down comes on the same day that Genesis announced a massive layoff itself. Genesis disclosed earlier that it would be parting ways with 30% of its staff.</p>
<p>With many of its subsidiaries having one trouble or the other, legitimate concerns are now being raised about the future of DCG itself.</p>
<p>Recall that back in November, CEO Barry Silbert assuaged investor fears, assuring them there was nothing to worry about. That was despite DCG owing about $575 million to Genesis. Genesis later <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/genesis-restrictions-ftx-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halted</a> withdrawals barely a few days later as a result of this and is yet to resume withdrawals as of this writing.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, there are reasons to believe that the financial woes of DCG&#8217;s subsidiaries simply reflect the situation at the top. In December,  a creditor committee investigating Genesis’ liquidity crunch hinted that DCG may also be in financial trouble. More so, Dutch cryptocurrency exchange Bitvavo has also come forward with another claim that DCG owes nearly $300 million. Bitvavo even hinted that the company does not appear to be able to pay back.</p>
<p>In a bid to distance itself from the situation, DCG claims that it has no business with the matter as it is entirely Genesis’ liability.  Nonetheless, DCG once appeared to be untouchable but may fast be losing its financial stability.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/">Crypto Giant DCG Shuts Down HQ Subsidiary amid Global Economic Crisis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dcg-shuts-down-hq-subsidiary/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NY Attorney General Sues Former Celsius Network CEO for Defrauding Clients</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 12:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alex mashinsky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celcius network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/">NY Attorney General Sues Former Celsius Network CEO for Defrauding Clients</a></p>
<p>New York’s state attorney general Letitia James revealed on Twitter that she is suing the former Celsius Network head for defrauding investors out of billions of dollars. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/">NY Attorney General Sues Former Celsius Network CEO for Defrauding Clients</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/">NY Attorney General Sues Former Celsius Network CEO for Defrauding Clients</a></p>
<p>Who would have thought that the once-upon-a-buzzing crypto industry would have to fight so many legal battles? While former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sam Bankman-Fried</a> is still making headlines amid his court cases, Celsius Network CEO Alex Mashinsky has been sued for defrauding investors. Celsius Network filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in July 2022, saying it would help the company stabilize and develop a restructuring plan. After filing for bankruptcy in the US Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York, the CEO boasted of a solid and experienced team to help through the restructuring process.</p>
<p>Before filing for bankruptcy, Celsius halted customer withdrawals in June, citing “extreme market conditions.” The CEO resigned in September, shortly after he reportedly withdrew $10 million from Celsius weeks before the company stopped withdrawals.</p>
<h2>NY Attorney General Sues Celsius Network Ex-CEO</h2>
<p>New York’s state attorney general Letitia James <a href="https://twitter.com/NewYorkStateAG/status/1611023481285578752" target="_blank" rel="noopener">revealed on Twitter</a> that she is suing the former Celsius Network head for defrauding investors out of billions of dollars. She wrote that the Mashinsky deceived people about the risks associated with investing in the crypto company. In a statement, she explained that he failed to expose the company’s deteriorating financial condition to its clients and also failed to register in New York.</p>
<p>The Attorney General added that the former Celsius Network CEO “tricked hardworking people into investing their life savings into Celsius.” To make the deceit attractive, the executive promised substantial financial returns to the investors and claimed that the platform was more secure than a financial institution. However, these promises and claims went down the drain as Celsuis crashed, and investors were left with losses.</p>
<blockquote><p>“I’m suing to get New Yorkers their money back and ban Mashinsky from doing business in New York. We will continue to protect people from the risks of investing in cryptocurrency.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the lawsuit addressed how the Ex CEO was not honest about his claims about the number of Celsius users. In response to the Attorney General’s Twitter thread, American stockbroker Peter Schiff asked what took the lawyer so long. He referenced a YouTube video posted last year about Mashinsky’s scam before the crash.</p>
<p>Schiff is a known <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> critic who believes that Bitcoin will eventually fall. He <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-drop-10000-peter-schiff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> in August that Bitcoin was on its way to dropping below $10,000, saying the bull run in the crypto market at the time was not sustainable. He outrightly noted that the market would plunge and advised people who took advantage of the rally to pull out. In his explanation, some people bought BTC years ago and have made enough profits from it. Hence, these investors should get over Bitcoin to avoid tragic stories.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/">NY Attorney General Sues Former Celsius Network CEO for Defrauding Clients</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/attorney-general-celsius-network-ceo-defrauding/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Official Has High Hopes for Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sanaa Sharma]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/">Microsoft Official Has High Hopes for Metaverse</a></p>
<p>Microsoft association with Metaverse firm Touchcast has resulted in data manufacture of the Fiat model, which according to Bzeih, is a "natural progression". </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/">Microsoft Official Has High Hopes for Metaverse</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/">Microsoft Official Has High Hopes for Metaverse</a></p>
<p>American multinational technological corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a> (MSFT) has high <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/01/05/microsoft-exec-says-metaverse-is-must-have/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">hopes</a> for the metaverse in the future. In a talk recently, Microsoft Chief Strategy Officer Henry Bzeih claimed that the world would inch towards a more profound virtual arena, with a hybrid prototype being the next big thing for customers and corporate relationships.</p>
<p>According to Bzeih, the discussion on the client experience and feedback will have to include the utility of the metaverse. Bzeih has had a twenty-eight-year-long stint in automotive and technology-related space.</p>
<p>Bzeih adds to his talk by explaining that Microsoft is essentially working on mobility cross-functionality, which helps modify how customers utilize the platforms to shop. A particular to be noted here is the way customers purchase cars at present. Instead of taking the effort to go to a local dealer to select their preferred car, the client can simply change the colors, features, and utilities of the car on metaverse. He also mentioned Fiat 500e, which will be showcased in Microsoft&#8217;s digital car showroom.</p>
<p>Microsoft association with Metaverse firm Touchcast has resulted in data manufacture of the Fiat model, which according to Bzeih, is a &#8220;natural progression&#8221;. Microsoft is looking at the world of metaverse development from an audience&#8217;s perspective in an enablement mode. The company is working on curating its clientele&#8217;s edge-to-cloud product and solution regions.</p>
<p>The problem lies in being able to bring forth the metaverse-enable car sale and purchase to the US market. The entire procedure is somewhat tedious as it needs to comply with the idea of independent franchise owners who usually, find the metaverse rather difficult to understand. The way forward, according to Bzeih, is to create a hybrid version that allows enterprises the assurance and safety that the massive amount of money invested in physical institutions doesn&#8217;t go waste.</p>
<p>The Tech giant was also recently in news for disallowing its customers to mine cryptocurrencies on its online services without prior written permission.</p>
<p>While the company did not provide information on the ban, in an update on Azure, it said that crypto mining in all online services has been halted to protect the partner ecosystem. This is, however, not the first time a major tech company has prohibited crypto mining on its online platform. Google also has an equivalent policy that doesn&#8217;t allow people to mine without prior written approval.</p>
<p>Moreover, Amazon&#8217;s AWS also restricts crypto mining for its twelve-month free trial. Customers could be levied a fee if they opt to mine on AWS and may have their accounts suspended.</p>
<p>Previously, a Microsoft-owned video game Minecraft prohibited non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) from its game to make sure that the players have a safe and inclusive experience.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/">Microsoft Official Has High Hopes for Metaverse</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-official-hopes-metaverse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shopify Adds Support for Avalanche NFTs</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shopify]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[venly]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/">Shopify Adds Support for Avalanche NFTs</a></p>
<p>Using Venly, sellers on Shopify can sell NFTs, offer NFT-gated experiences or use NFTs for authentication by tying them to physical products.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/">Shopify Adds Support for Avalanche NFTs</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/">Shopify Adds Support for Avalanche NFTs</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/shopify/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shopify</a> merchants can now mint and list their <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a> through their storefronts using one of the platform’s blockchain apps &#8211; Venly. Merchants do not need to refer clients to popular, dedicated NFT marketplaces like OpenSea, Rarible, or Magic Eden. They can instead use Venly to mint NFTs on Avalanche.</p>
<p>Layer-1 blockchain platform Venly announced the addition of Avalanche support on Thursday via its Shopify NFT minting app. The service was previously only accessible to select Shopify users but is now open to all merchants. According to Venly, shoppers will not need to have an Avalanche wallet to buy NFTs. They will not have to handle crypto either but can make fiat payments following which they will receive a link to a newly-created Avalanche wallet holding the freshly-minted NFT, which they are free to transfer to another wallet.</p>
<p>Using Venly, sellers on Shopify can sell NFTs, offer NFT-gated experiences or use NFTs for authentication by tying them to physical products. CEO and co-founder Tim Dierckxsens believes creators and artists could potentially sell NFTs through social media channels that can integrate or link to Shopify stores.</p>
<p>“Our growing blockchain ecosystem demonstrates our commitment to supporting merchants as they sell NFTs directly through their storefronts, helping to further grow participation in Web3 and expand what’s possible in commerce,” said Shopify Blockchain Ecosystem Lead Christina Lomazzo in a release.</p>
<p>Venly offers blockchain wallet solutions and was founded in 2018 and is one of the blockchain app partners integrated within the Shopify platform. It first launched its Shopify minting tool on the Polygon network late in 2021, with Avalanche now being the second network to be supported. The startup plans to add support for Hedera and Ethereum scaling network Immutable X in the future.</p>
<p>The decision to focus on layer-1 platforms and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> layer-2 networks was motivated by the goal of providing low gas fees to users as mainnet gas fees can be costly and hard to predict.</p>
<p>Dierckxsens says the blockchain startup started off offering NFT minting tools to brands and artists on the e-commerce platform but noted that there was an increasing demand for an easy-to-use, no-code tool that any merchant could use to create NFTs. Venly was then asked by Shopify to create an app for sellers that would help streamline the process of selling NFTs to mainstream users.</p>
<p>“I believe it&#8217;s one of the biggest evolutions [for NFTs] where this can be taken to a mass market and you don&#8217;t need to understand the necessity of crypto to make the purchase,” Dierckxsens said in a Decrypt <a href="https://decrypt.co/118449/shopify-merchants-can-now-sell-avalanche-nfts-through-their-online-stores" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">interview</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/">Shopify Adds Support for Avalanche NFTs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/shopify-avalanche-nfts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TON Foundation Launches TON Storage, Decentralized File-sharing Solution</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[telegram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ton foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[toncoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231583</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/">TON Foundation Launches TON Storage, Decentralized File-sharing Solution</a></p>
<p>The TON Storage will use financial incentives from Toncoin with the help of smart contracts on the blockchain.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/">TON Foundation Launches TON Storage, Decentralized File-sharing Solution</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/">TON Foundation Launches TON Storage, Decentralized File-sharing Solution</a></p>
<p>The Ton Foundation, a non-commercial organization behind TONCOIN, has announced the launch of its TON Storage, a decentralized file-sharing and data storage solution. The Ton Storage is developed similarly to the Torrent file system, which encompasses peer-to-peer technology, but runs on the Ton open blockchain. As such, the TON developers anticipate taking head-on projects like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/filecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Filecoin</a> and Storj.</p>
<h2>Inner Workings of Ton Storage</h2>
<p>The Ton network, a proof-of-stake blockchain developed by Telegram Messenger founders, has grown to a billion-dollar ecosystem in a few years. The Ton Storage is expected to help user store files of any size on the decentralized Ton network.</p>
<p>Notably, TON Storage will use financial incentives with the help of smart contracts on the blockchain. As such, users will be guaranteed security and the ability to share with other network users freely.</p>
<p>“A node operator and a user create a smart contract on the TON blockchain that guarantees that the user will pay a fixed amount in Toncoin to store files for a predetermined amount of time,” the company <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/the-ton-foundation-launches-ton-storage--a-next-generation-file-storage-solution-301713227.html">noted</a>.</p>
<p>What makes Ton Storage unique from competitors is the fact that anyone can become a node operator and receive payments from other users for hosting files. Consequently, the Ton Foundation anticipates helping grow the on-chain activity of the underlying blockchain.</p>
<p>Moreover, the TON Storage combines uniquely with TON Sites and TON DNS to enable different sites to launch seamlessly without requiring a fixed IP address, a centralized domain, or a certified centralized centre. As a result, all TON Sites can be hosted on TON Storage without the need for a traditional web server.</p>
<p>Anatoly Makosov, a founding member of the TON Foundation, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/in/news-releases/the-ton-foundation-launches-ton-storage--a-next-generation-file-storage-solution-301713232.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The launch of TON Storage was long-awaited; this technology can be used by both individual users and services with a multimillion-dollar audience. Providing a reliable distributed storage solution is the next step in realizing our vision of a decentralized, open internet. We can&#8217;t wait to see what products our community will create using this technology.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Toncoin  Market Outlook</h2>
<p>According to our latest crypto price oracles, the Toncoin price is exchanging around $2.18 on Friday, down approximately 1.27 percent in the past 24 hours. The Toncoin has a fully diluted market capitalization of approximately $10,874,034,882 with a 24-hour trading volume of about $36,007,209.</p>
<p>Backed by a non-commercial group of supporters, the Ton network promises to disrupt the perception of decentralization. Furthermore, the Ton network can scale its throughput to millions of transactions per second.  The Ton network uses smart contracts that are executed using TON Virtual Machine (TVM).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/">TON Foundation Launches TON Storage, Decentralized File-sharing Solution</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ton-foundation-storage-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Decides to Cut Price for Model 3 and Y in China for Second Time in 3 Months</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model y]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=231577</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/">Tesla Decides to Cut Price for Model 3 and Y in China for Second Time in 3 Months</a></p>
<p>The price reductions became necessitated when Tesla recorded a very low delivery count in December last year, the lowest in more than 5 months.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/">Tesla Decides to Cut Price for Model 3 and Y in China for Second Time in 3 Months</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/">Tesla Decides to Cut Price for Model 3 and Y in China for Second Time in 3 Months</a></p>
<p>American multinational electric vehicle maker, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has cut the price of its flagship Model 3 and Model Y cars in China. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/06/tesla-slashes-model-3-model-y-prices-in-china-for-second-time-in-3-months.html">reported</a> by CNBC, this is the second time since October that the automaker will be making such a move amid growing competition among local auto brands.</p>
<p>According to prices shown on its dashboard, the new starting price for Model 3, for instance, was cut to 229,900 yuan ($33,427) from 265,900 yuan. Generally, the prices of the Model 3 and Model Y have been slashed within the range of 6% and 13.5% respectively. Judging by the total cuts since October, Tesla’s customers in China, its second-largest EV market, will now be getting a discount of up to 10,000 yuan.</p>
<p>Electric Vehicles are considered a game-changing innovation with respect to targeted efforts to combat climate change. As innovative as they are, prices are often a hassle that has largely kept the average customer away from purchasing these EVs. With the latest bouts of price slashes, Tesla is bringing its once-highly-priced cars at par with local players in order to draw more customers.</p>
<p>“Tesla’s price adjustments are backed by innumerous engineering innovations,” Grace Tao, Tesla’s vice president in charge of external communications in China, posted on her Weibo social media account on Friday. ”[They] answer the government’s call to promote economic development and encourage consumption.”</p>
<p>The price reductions became necessitated when Tesla recorded a very low delivery count in December last year, the lowest in more than 5 months. The company had to make the adjustment as the incentive that sutured the industry, and the Chinese government’s subsidy program ended.</p>
<h2>Tesla Urged to Cut Price Some More</h2>
<p>Despite the latest price cuts, Tesla is being prompted by the China Merchants Bank International (CMBI) to further effect additional price cuts on its electric cars selling in the Chinese market. CMBI had earlier flagged the caution that there may be price wars in the Chinese EV market, a trend that has been confirmed by Tesla’s latest price slash.</p>
<p>“Tesla needs to further cut prices and expand its sales network in China’s lower-tier cities amid ageing models,” said CMBI analyst Shi Ji.</p>
<p>With Tesla also building its GigaFactory in Berlin, Shi Ji believes the Shanghai outlet may have more vehicles for sale than there is demand for if more drastic incentives are extended to buyers.</p>
<p>“We expect new EV production capacity in China to outpace new demand in 2023 and Tesla Shanghai’s capacity utilization could drop to about or even below 80% this year if its Berlin plant ramps up,” he added.</p>
<p>Tesla’s share price slumped by 5.75% in the pre-market to $104. The firm has a lot of grounds to cover in its share price, and enhanced sales that the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-cars-china-tsla-stock/">price slash</a> in China may bring may reboot investors’ confidence in the firm across the board.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bmw-ivision-dee-prototype-2025/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/">Tesla Decides to Cut Price for Model 3 and Y in China for Second Time in 3 Months</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cut-price-model-3-y-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>