<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:44:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Foxconn Says April Sales Drop 12% due to Decline in Smartphone Shipments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foxconn]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253569</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/">Foxconn Says April Sales Drop 12% due to Decline in Smartphone Shipments</a></p>
<p>The growth of artificial intelligence technology is expected to increase the overall demand for fast-processing electronics.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/">Foxconn Says April Sales Drop 12% due to Decline in Smartphone Shipments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/">Foxconn Says April Sales Drop 12% due to Decline in Smartphone Shipments</a></p>
<p>Foxconn Technology Co Ltd (Taiwan: 2354), one of the largest global employers in the electronics manufacturing industry and a major supplier to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple Inc</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) announced a sales decline of 11.77 percent in April, YoY basis. However, the company’s revenue was in line with prior estimates, which came in at T$429.2 billion, approximately $14 billion. As the smartphone shipment declines, the Taiwanese electronic company anticipates its sales to decline in the current quarter.</p>
<p>The company will, however, report first-quarter earnings results on May 11, when it is expected to issue full-year guidance. According to the company’s unaudited consolidated monthly revenue report for April, revenue in smart consumer electronics products delivered double-digit growth. Additionally, the company noted that cumulative revenue for the first four months of 2023 came in at  NT$ 1,891.9 billion, down approximately 0.14 percent YoY.</p>
<p>“The decline in smartphone shipments during Q1 2023 marks the first ever Q1 decline since 2019 and is attributed to extended inventory, weakened demand, and inflation. The overall feature phone segment declined by 19 percent YoY is driven by muted demand and an increase in feature phone to smartphone upgrade,” Shipra Sinha, an analyst at Industry Intelligence Group CyberMedia Research <a href="https://www.imdb.com/news/ni64066277/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<h2>Foxconn Sales and the Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The company is heavily reliant on the global consumption of new products, especially from Apple. As the dollar purchasing power declines due to high inflation, Foxconn forecasts more pay. However, the company hopes Apple’s entrance to the Indian market will revamp its quarterly sales. Moreover, India is considered an emerging market with a high demand for electronics for its high population, although smartphone shipments declined by 21 percent YoY during the first quarter.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Apple posted first quarter revenues of about $94.8 billion, down 3 percent YoY basis. As the global smartphone industry transitions from old to new products, Foxconn expects its sales to decline in the second quarter. Moreover, new products for Apple among other manufacturers are expected to come in at the end of the year as usual to coincide with holiday festivities.</p>
<p>Notably, Falcon shares dropped approximately 3 percent in the past month to trade around NT$ 53.80 on Friday. Nevertheless, it was a choppy day for the entire electronics industry with most down about 3 percent in the day.</p>
<h2>Bigger Picture</h2>
<p>The growth of artificial intelligence technology is expected to increase the overall demand for fast-processing electronics. Already, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR), one of Foxconn’s major customers in North America, has made tremendous progress in AI development through collaboration with OpenAI. As a result, Foxconn is looking at profitable years ahead despite short-term constraints.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/">Foxconn Says April Sales Drop 12% due to Decline in Smartphone Shipments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foxconn-april-sales-drop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance to List FLOKI and PEPE in Innovation Zone</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[floki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pepe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253555</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/">Binance to List FLOKI and PEPE in Innovation Zone</a></p>
<p>The announcement from Binance seems to have caused some excitement in the market as PEPE saw a surge of over 40%, while FLOKI increased by over 60%.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/">Binance to List FLOKI and PEPE in Innovation Zone</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/">Binance to List FLOKI and PEPE in Innovation Zone</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-will-list-floki-floki-and-pepe-pepe-in-the-innovation-zone-f68a3bc6eb014ed9bacf1d6c71dc1134" target="_blank" rel="noopener">confirmed</a> the listing of Floki Inu (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/floki/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FLOKI</a>) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/pepe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PEPE</a> in the Innovation Zone on its platform. According to the firm, a listing fee of 0 BNB applies to trade pairs featuring the duo of FLOKI and PEPE.</p>
<p>As per a published statement, Binance also ascertained that by the latter part of today, the exchange would have opened trading for the spot pairs like FLOKI/USDT, FLOKI/TUSD, PEPE/USDT, PEPE/TUSD.</p>
<p>Hence, users are encouraged to start depositing any or both of the two memecoins in anticipation of trading. Deposits of FLOKI and PEPE will be made possible from today but users will not be allowed to withdraw until May 6th.</p>
<p>Changpeng &#8216;CZ&#8217; Zhao, the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Binance previously hinted that the exchange was skeptical about listing PEPE citing the fact that the meme coin lacks transparency and has a high-risk nature. During one of his &#8216;Ask Me Anything&#8217; sessions, CZ showed his approval of Shiba Inu over the cartoon-characterized meme coin PEPE.</p>
<p>“We don’t like coins that have a very small circulating supply… but they have a large total supply in reserve,” he said in a Twitter Spaces held earlier this month, adding that “with a tiny bit of circulating supply, some of the coins are famous and people want them as price is going really high. But then as more supply comes into circulation the price may drop, well most likely will drop or at least have a higher risk of dropping. We try to avoid it.”</p>
<p>At the same time, he also pointed out that he was not directly involved in listings.</p>
<p>“We actually have strict policies that even if we are talking with a project team, we forbid them disclosing anything about listings, etc,” Zhao added.</p>
<h2>FLOKI, PEPE, Other Memecoin Gain Attention</h2>
<p>Considering the earlier stance of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CZ</a>, it came as a surprise when the exchange confirmed the listings. About 48 hours after the listing goes live, both FLOKI and PEPE will be added as new borrowable assets on Isolated Margins alongside their new margin pairs FLOKI/USDT, and PEPE/USDT.</p>
<p>The announcement seems to have caused some excitement in the market as PEPE saw a surge of over 40%, while FLOKI increased by over 60%.</p>
<p>FLOKI has been on other top cryptocurrency exchanges before now but the listing with Binance has been anticipated for a very long time. In March, KoinBX, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/koinbx-list-floki-offering-inr-trading-pair/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> plans to list FLOKI to trade with USDT and INR trading pairs. Generally, there has been a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/meme-coin-market-madness-crypto-heads-everywhere-go-barking-mad-for-floki-inu-and-dogetti-in-the-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rave about FLOKI</a> and many other memecoins</p>
<p>The platform behind the memecoin Floki has proved its utility over time with several solutions like a crypto debit card, a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Non-Fungible Token</a> (NFT)-based game, and various NFT collections.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/">Binance to List FLOKI and PEPE in Innovation Zone</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-floki-pepe-innovation-zone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warner Bros. Discovery Q1 2023 Results Sees Media Giant Realize Streaming Profit despite Sustaining Overall Loss</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[disney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[netflix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warner bros discovery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253538</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/">Warner Bros. Discovery Q1 2023 Results Sees Media Giant Realize Streaming Profit despite Sustaining Overall Loss</a></p>
<p>Due to its commendable Q1 2023 streaming numbers, Warner Bros. Discovery expects its streaming business to stay profitable this year. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/">Warner Bros. Discovery Q1 2023 Results Sees Media Giant Realize Streaming Profit despite Sustaining Overall Loss</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/">Warner Bros. Discovery Q1 2023 Results Sees Media Giant Realize Streaming Profit despite Sustaining Overall Loss</a></p>
<p>On Friday, May 5, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/warner-bros-discovery/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Warner Bros Discovery</a> (NASDAQ: WBD) reported its <a href="https://wbd.com/warner-bros-discovery-reports-first-quarter-2023-results/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Q1 2023 earnings</a> before the bell that came in mixed. For instance, the media and entertainment giant reported a significant overall loss despite raking in profit from its streaming endeavors. Warner Bros. Discovery lost $930 million in quarterly free cash flow even though its direct-to-consumer segment realized a $50 million profit for the same period.</p>
<p>Following its streaming success, the New York-based company expects its streaming business to remain profitable in 2023. This forecast comes in a year ahead of expectations.</p>
<p>For Q1 2023, Warner Bros. Discovery raked in a revenue haul of $10.7 billion compared to the consensus estimate of $10.78 billion. In addition, the multinational mass media and entertainment conglomerate also sustained a loss per share of 44 cents versus 1 cent expected. Warner Bros. Discovery’s net loss for the first quarter came in at $1.1 billion, with an adjusted EBITDA of $2.6 billion.</p>
<h2>Warner Bros. Discovery CEO Comments on Q1 2023 Earnings</h2>
<p>In an earnings release, Warner Bros. Discovery President and Chief Executive Officer David Zaslav commented on the quarterly outing, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is an important time for Warner Bros. Discovery. We’ve come through some major restructurings and have repositioned our businesses with greater precision and focus. And we see a number of positive proof points emerging, with DTC perhaps the most prominent.”</p></blockquote>
<p>According to the CEO, the company’s “meaningful turn this quarter with $50 million in segment EBITDA and 1.6 million net adds” puts it on the right trajectory.</p>
<p>Zaslav concluded by saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Even in today’s challenging marketplace, we are positioned to drive free cash flow and deleverage our balance sheet, and we remain confident in our ability and strategy to attain our financial targets.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Warner Bros. Discovery is scheduled for a conference call today at 8:00 a.m. ET to discuss its quarterly results.</p>
<p>Warner Bros. Discovery executives took pride in the entertainment giant’s ability to reverse losses in its streaming operations. Like several media powerhouses, the company has switched its focus to streaming video following the increasing subscription cancellation of traditional pay TV. The media company ended Q1 with 97.6 million streaming subscribers. This number represents a sizable increase of 1.6 million subscribers from the preceding quarter.</p>
<p>Despite a fiercely competitive streaming space, Warner Bros. Discovery hopes to keep thriving for the foreseeable future. The company currently ties with the likes of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/netflix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Netflix</a> (NASDAQ: NFLX), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/disney/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Disney</a> (NYSE: DIS), and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> (NASDAQ: AAPL) for streaming subscribers.</p>
<h2>Warner Bros. Discovery Streaming Shakeups</h2>
<p>Warner Bros. Discovery is onboarding Discovery+ content to HBO Max and relaunching the streamer as Max in the US later in the month. Zaslav has slashed content spending to spur efforts to make Warner Bros. Discovery’s streaming business profitable. The CEO’s cost-cutting measures include pulling dozens of films and television series from HBO Max. According to a spokesperson for the streaming platform, most of the affected shows are reality or kids and family content that did not resonate with large audiences.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/">Warner Bros. Discovery Q1 2023 Results Sees Media Giant Realize Streaming Profit despite Sustaining Overall Loss</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/warner-bros-discovery-q1-2023-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zimbabwe Central Bank Introduces Plan to Sell Gold-Backed Digital Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rbz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reserve bank of zimbabwe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253515</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/">Zimbabwe Central Bank Introduces Plan to Sell Gold-Backed Digital Tokens</a></p>
<p>The central bank of Zimbabwe introduced this gold-backed digital currency to combat the volatility of its national currency. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/">Zimbabwe Central Bank Introduces Plan to Sell Gold-Backed Digital Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/">Zimbabwe Central Bank Introduces Plan to Sell Gold-Backed Digital Tokens</a></p>
<p>In a notice on Thursday, May 4, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ) invited financial institutions and individuals to subscribe to its upcoming gold-backed digital currency. As per the initial plans, the gold-backed digital tokens will be available to investors starting May 8.</p>
<p>The central bank also plans to sell these tokens at a minimum price of $10 for individuals and $5,000 for financial institutions and corporates. As per the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe, this digital currency will be available in the USD and local currency. However, the local currency will have a 20% margin higher than the willing-buyer willing-seller interbank mid-rate.</p>
<p>For the past few years, Zimbabwe&#8217;s economy has been quite under stress amid the solid devaluation of its national currency. During the month of March, Zimbabwe reported inflation of 87.6% after hitting a high of 285% in 2022. As a result, its national currency has remained extremely volatile. Last month in April, RBZ stated that the gold-backed tokens will help to combat the volatility of its national currency.</p>
<h2>Two Phases of Issuance and Usage of Gold-Backed Digital Tokens</h2>
<p>The central bank of Zimbabwe said that it will split the issuance and usage of the gold-backed digital currency into two phases. During the first phase, tokens will be issued for investment purposes and will be available for sale through banks. These tokens will be held in digital wallets or cards and will be available in person-to-person as well as person-to-business transactions.</p>
<p>The central bank <a href="https://www.chronicle.co.zw/gold-backed-digital-tokens-by-next-week-rbz/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Holders of physical gold coins, at their discretion, will be able to exchange or convert, through the banking system, the physical gold coins into gold-backed digital tokens.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As per the latest Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-04/zimbabwe-sets-price-to-lure-buyers-for-gold-backed-digital-money" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the introduction of digital tokens is the latest move by the South African nation in supporting its local currency, which has seen a 37% devaluation against the US Dollar since the beginning of 2023.</p>
<p>As per the Bloomberg report, the Zimbabwean dollar is quoted at 1,001 against the US Dollar. However, it sells 1,750 on the streets of Harare, the capital city.</p>
<p>For the gold-backed digital currency, the Monetary Policy Committee approved the plan in March, eight months after the country introduced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/how-to-invest-in-gold-beginners-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">gold</a> coins as a store of value.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/">Zimbabwe Central Bank Introduces Plan to Sell Gold-Backed Digital Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/zimbabwe-central-bank-gold-backed-tokens/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Hikes Price for Model S and X Cars in China by $2,747</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla model s]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla model y]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253509</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/">Tesla Hikes Price for Model S and X Cars in China by $2,747</a></p>
<p>Following months of repeated price cuts, Tesla has raised the price of some of its EV offerings in China to remain competitive. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/">Tesla Hikes Price for Model S and X Cars in China by $2,747</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/">Tesla Hikes Price for Model S and X Cars in China by $2,747</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA) has hiked the price of its new Model S and Model X electric vehicles in China by 19,000 yuan ($2,751). On Friday, the company’s website reflected the product price increase, which comes on the heels of price hikes for its other cars.</p>
<h2>Tesla Models S and X EVs to Sell for 808,900 Yuan and 898,900 Yuan in China</h2>
<p>As it stands, Tesla’s Model S costs 808,900 yuan compared to its previous price of 789,900 yuan. In addition, the company’s Model S Plaid variation also commands a steeper purchase price of 1,028,900 yuan compared to 1,009,900 before. Furthermore, Tesla’s Model X sports utility vehicle now sports a price tag of 898,900 yuan versus its previous retail price of 879,900 yuan.</p>
<p>Earlier in the week, Tesla also hiked the price of its Model 3 and Y EVs in China and other markets, including the United States. The renewable energy-oriented multinational automotive company’s price hikes come after its sustained price cuts. Over the last few months, Tesla slashed the prices of its popular EVs to induce more demand amid an increasingly competitive space.</p>
<p>Tesla reduced the price of its Model 3 sedan and Model Y sports utility vehicles <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-cars-china-tsla-stock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">in the fourth quarter</a> of last year, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/price-cuts-tesla-model-3-model-y/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">continuing to do so</a> past Q1 2023. After recording a meager delivery count late last year, the company saw the need for price reductions.</p>
<h2>Musk on Tesla’s Growth Outlook</h2>
<p>At Tesla’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-q1-2023-deliveries/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q1 2023</a> earnings call, chief executive officer <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> said the company will target higher sales volumes than higher margins. However, Musk also added that he expects his EV company to “generate significant profit through autonomy” over time. As the outspoken business executive put it at the time:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’ve taken the view that pushing for higher volumes and a larger fleet is the right choice here versus a lower volume and higher margin. However, we expect our vehicles, over time, will be able to generate significant profit through autonomy.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Musk also <a href="https://www.rev.com/blog/transcripts/tesla-tsla-q1-2023-earnings-call-transcript" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">explained</a> to investors:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We do believe we’re laying the groundwork here, and then it’s better to ship a large number of cars at a lower margin and subsequently harvest that margin in the future as we perfect autonomy. This is an extremely important point.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The Tesla chief pointed out that the Model Y became Europe’s best-selling vehicle of any kind in the first quarter. He also revealed that the fully electric mid-size SUV was the best-selling non-pickup vehicle in the US during the same period. Musk noted that these accomplishments came despite production and delivery headwinds and commended the team. The CEO concluded his address by stating that Tesla sought to keep making and selling as many cars as possible despite unfavorable macroeconomic parameters. Stressing that it’s now a good time for the company to strengthen its dominance in the EV industry, Musk added he would remain growth-oriented.</p>
<p>For the first quarter of 2023, Tesla delivered 422,875 vehicles, surpassing its previous record of 405,278 in Q4 2022.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/">Tesla Hikes Price for Model S and X Cars in China by $2,747</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-price-model-s-x-cars-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adidas Q1 2023 Sales Revenue Down 1% after Terminating Rapper Ye’s Contract</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adidas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253492</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/">Adidas Q1 2023 Sales Revenue Down 1% after Terminating Rapper Ye’s Contract</a></p>
<p>Adidas has failed to give an explicit plan of what it is going to do with unsold Yeezy stock.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/">Adidas Q1 2023 Sales Revenue Down 1% after Terminating Rapper Ye’s Contract</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/">Adidas Q1 2023 Sales Revenue Down 1% after Terminating Rapper Ye’s Contract</a></p>
<p>The Q1 2023 sales performance of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/adidas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Adidas</a> exceeded expectations despite its terminated partnership deal with Ye, formerly Kanye West. Adidas announced an operating profit of 60 million euros, surpassing analysts’ expectations of 15 million euros. However, due to the loss of Yeezy sales, higher supply chain costs, and discounts, Adidas&#8217; gross margin fell to 44.8%.</p>
<h2>Adidas in Q1 2023</h2>
<p>Though the sale revenue beat expectations, it trails the previous year’s record by 1%. Adidas generated a sales revenue of 5.274 billion euros in Q1 2023, a decline from 2022’s 5.302 billion. According to compiled consensus estimates, analysts expected a year-on-year decrease of 4%.</p>
<p>Last year, Adidas ended its lucrative partnership with Ye without any spelled-out plan to get rid of its stock of unsold Yeezy customized shoes. The Ye crooner made a series of anti-Semitic online posts, which cost him his partnership deal with the sports brand. His Instagram and Twitter accounts were also suspended to that effect.</p>
<p>In response to Ye’s series of posts, the sportswear brand stated: “Adidas does not tolerate antisemitism and any other sort of hate speech. Ye’s recent comments and actions have been unacceptable, hateful, and dangerous, and they violate the company’s values of diversity and inclusion, mutual respect and fairness.”</p>
<p>As expected, Adidas&#8217; sales in Q1 2023 declined by 400 million euros ($441.56 million), affecting revenue generation in North America, Greater China, and EMEA regions. The Yeezy crisis majorly affected the North American market and Greater China, with a YoY sales decline of 20% and 9%, respectively. Surprisingly, Adidas sales in Q1 2023 jumped by 4% in EMEA regions. Adidas&#8217; Q1 revenue in Latin America puts up a stunning performance with a 48.7% increase.</p>
<h2>Why Did Adidas&#8217; Sales Revenue Plummet in Q1?</h2>
<p>Speaking on the declined sales revenue, the CEO of Adidas Bjorn Gulden has explained that the decline in the sale of the Yeezy collection is the key factor behind their plummeting sales revenue. Despite the Q1 2023 performance, the Adidas executive remains optimistic about the three other quarters of the year, <a href="https://www.adidas-group.com/en/media/news-archive/press-releases/2023/adidas-reports-revenues-on-prior-year-level-in-the-first-quarter/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">saying</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Q1 ended a little better than we had expected. We still have a long way to go, but I am very happy with the progress we have made and what we have achieved so far.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The sportswear brand has explained that other factors like geopolitical uncertainties, economic headwinds, and consumer sentiment will affect its sales performance in 2023. Adidas has failed to give an explicit plan of what it is going to do with unsold Yeezy stock. The closure of the Yeezy inventory will slough Adidas&#8217; operating profits by €500 million in addition to the projected one-off cost of €200 million. Overall, Adidas will expectedly lose approximately €700 million in 2023.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/">Adidas Q1 2023 Sales Revenue Down 1% after Terminating Rapper Ye’s Contract</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/adidas-q1-2023-sales-revenue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Upgrade: Cardano’s Layer 2 Scalability Solution Launches on Mainnet, Here’s What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 12:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[aptos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano (ada)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra upgrade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scalability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/">Hydra Upgrade: Cardano&#8217;s Layer 2 Scalability Solution Launches on Mainnet, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
<p>The Cardano community is expecting at least, three key releases from the platform this year.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/">Hydra Upgrade: Cardano&#8217;s Layer 2 Scalability Solution Launches on Mainnet, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/">Hydra Upgrade: Cardano&#8217;s Layer 2 Scalability Solution Launches on Mainnet, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
<p>Cardano may have taken its quest for scalability to another level with its Hydra upgrade which has now gone live on mainnet. The update was shared by Input Output Hong Kong (IOHK), the start-up behind the Cardano protocol. According to IOHK&#8217;s Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/InputOutputHK/status/1654034234200162304?t=Naokzk8bWC_adeyXMdVm4g&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, the first Hydra head has opened on the mainnet.</p>
<p>For clarity, the Hydra head is the first member of the Hydra family protocol. And according to the Cardano team, each head “works as an off-chain mini ledger shared between a small group of participants”.</p>
<p>Like many other Layer 1 blockchain protocols, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cardano</a> has been keen to prove its network&#8217;s dominance by improving scalability as well as expanding usability. And, Hydra provides the perfect solution for these needs.</p>
<h2>Benefits of the Hydra Upgrade</h2>
<p>The solution will allow developers to create specialized smart contracts on the Cardano blockchain. It will help to boost transaction speed by increasing throughput, which translates to the number of transactions per second (TPS). It will also help reduce transaction fees on the network to the barest minimum. And lastly, the upgrade is expected to address security issues on the network and most importantly, improve its scalability capabilities.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it might be worth mentioning that the Cardano community is expecting at least, three key releases from the platform this year. After waiting long for last year&#8217;s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/cardano-vasil-upgrade-3-month-delay/">Vasil upgrade</a>, they now expect releases that will cover stablecoins, scalability, and the platform’s continuing development of oracles. However, by launching on mainnet, it appears that the development of Hydra is top-priority for the Cardano ecosystem in 2023.</p>
<p>But Sebastian Nagel &#8211; one of the developers working on the Cardano Hydra protocol, has hinted that there will be no need for a hard fork. That is since this is not a full upgrade per se. Nonetheless, he confirms that the Hydra head is the foundational block. That is, it is the basis on which other protocols that will help Cardano achieve scalability will be built.</p>
<h2>L1 Protocols Are Competing</h2>
<p>Without a doubt, there is an unsaid scalability competition among Layer 1 protocols. This is as they race to put themselves at the atop the smart contract and decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) space.</p>
<p>For example, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> network has its eyes fixed on Layer 2 solutions such as Optimism (OP), Polygon zkEVM, and Arbitrum (ARB) to mention a few.</p>
<p>Coinspeaker also recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/mysten-labs-sui-mainnet-layer-1/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> about Mysten Labs&#8217; Sui network making a statement of its own. The protocol launched on mainnet with a surprisingly high throughput of 300,000 TPS. Solana (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SOL</a>), Aptos (APT), and many more are also constantly looking for ways to improve their networks&#8217; performance.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/">Hydra Upgrade: Cardano&#8217;s Layer 2 Scalability Solution Launches on Mainnet, Here&#8217;s What to Expect</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hydra-upgrade-cardano-layer-2-mainnet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stripe Expands Access to Its Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp with New Hosted Option</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 12:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253448</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/">Stripe Expands Access to Its Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp with New Hosted Option</a></p>
<p>The Stripe-hosted onramp was created with Web3 companies in mind. It is designed to cater to their varied use cases.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/">Stripe Expands Access to Its Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp with New Hosted Option</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/">Stripe Expands Access to Its Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp with New Hosted Option</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/stripe/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Stripe</a>, a financial infrastructure provider for businesses, has launched a fiat-to-crypto onramp to make it easier for Web3 companies to help their US-based clients to buy cryptocurrency. According to a Thursday <a href="https://stripe.com/en-lt/newsroom/news/fiat-to-crypto-onramp" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">release</a> by the firm, it is also making the onramp to all Web3 users, including those on the waitlist.</p>
<p>Businesses that provide crypto and blockchain-enabled products or services often face onboarding challenges when potential customers do not own the crypto required to perform transactions. Stripe’s onramp will now allow customers to buy crypto when they need it. For example, a user looking to buy an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a> can use the onramp to purchase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> or <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Solana</a> and immediately use it to buy the NFT.</p>
<p>The onramp can be implemented as a crypto-purchasing widget that developers can insert into their website or app using just 10 lines of code or as a Stripe-hosted onramp at crypto.link.com, to which companies can direct their US-based clients. The embeddable onramp option will be helpful for crypto and blockchain-focused companies that want to have complete control of their branding and customer experience, while the Stripe-hosted option provides an easier way for customers to use Web3-enabled products and services.</p>
<blockquote><p>James Mudgett, vice president of Web3 products at Brave noted: “We&#8217;re thrilled to partner with Stripe as they expand their offerings in the crypto space. We&#8217;re excited to offer a fiat payment solution that will allow us to reach new Web3 users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The onramp has built-in fraud prevention and identity verification tools to help companies meet KYC and compliance requirements. It also optimizes conversion and authorization rates for transactions.</p>
<p>First-time users will have to go through identity verification only once and add then add their payment information to a Link account. Link will store their payment details and use them for future payments at Link-enabled businesses.</p>
<h3>Accelerating Web3 Adoption by Introducing a Variety of Use Cases</h3>
<p>The Stripe-hosted onramp was created with Web3 companies in mind. It is designed to cater to their varied use cases. Some of the companies set to implement the onramp include the privacy-focused browser Brave which is Web3-optimized through its self-custody <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/brave-dex-nft-wallet-browser/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Brave Wallet</a>. The wallet can be used to store digital assets and interact with decentralized applications (dApps). Brave Wallet users can soon buy crypto directly into their accounts using the Stripe onramp.</p>
<p>Another Web3 company is Safe, a platform that helps users manage digital assets on Ethereum and the EVM. Developers can now bridge the barrier between Web2 and Web3 by embedding Stripe’s onramp in their dApps directly from the Safe{Core} SDK.</p>
<p>Decentralized exchange aggregator 1inch will integrate the Stripe onramp to let users easily and quickly start funding their <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> wallet.</p>
<p>Lens Protocol, a decentralized social protocol that allows creators to monetize content, will use the onramp on the decentralized social network LensFrens to allow users to collect content smoothly while supporting their favorite Web3 creators within the Lens ecosystem.</p>
<p>“With our onramp options, Web3 companies can now outsource a bunch of the very important but tricky pieces to Stripe – things like conversion and auth optimization, identity verification, fraud prevention, and so on. This allows companies to focus on what’s unique to their business, and helps their customers start using Web3 services quickly and safely,” said Guillaume Poncin, head of engineering for crypto at Stripe.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/">Stripe Expands Access to Its Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp with New Hosted Option</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-fiat-to-crypto-onramp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Treasury Yield Spikes as Investors Fear Recurring Banking Crisis</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 12:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[federal reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pacwest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treasury yield]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[us treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253507</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/">US Treasury Yield Spikes as Investors Fear Recurring Banking Crisis</a></p>
<p>Amid the broader banking crisis, investors are still concerned about the next move of the government in terms of Federal Reserve policy.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/">US Treasury Yield Spikes as Investors Fear Recurring Banking Crisis</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/">US Treasury Yield Spikes as Investors Fear Recurring Banking Crisis</a></p>
<p>United States Treasury yields <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/us-treasury-yields-ahead-of-key-jobs-report.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">spiked</a> earlier today after fluctuations experienced on Thursday. The yield on the 10-year Treasury went up by almost 5 basis points or 3.407% while that of the 2-year Treasury jumped by 9 basis points or 3.823%. The percentage surge covered up some of the losses encountered in the previous trading day.</p>
<p>The Treasury yield dip that happened earlier left investors with jitters about a recurring banking crisis after the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-market-silvergate-bank-insolvency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">collapse of Silvergate Bank</a>, Silicon Valley Bank, and Signature Bank. Most investors took extra caution and went in search of traditional safer alternatives like government bonds.</p>
<p>PacWest Bancorp (NASDAQ: PACW), a bank holding company that recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-crash-banking-stock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">suffered</a> huge losses announced its plans to consider strategic options.</p>
<p>One of such options is that the regional bank is currently considering <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-sale-stock-drawdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">selling</a> off all its assets outright. This sale will include the community lender Pacific Western Bank and a long list of commercial and consumer lending ventures. Therefore, selling its entire assets may prove difficult as sources have it that only a few potential buyers would be interested in acquiring the entire Los Angeles-based financial institution.</p>
<p>PacWest Bancorp views the potential sale as a strategy to maximize its shareholder value amid declining stock. At present, the bank holding company&#8217;s shares have <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/pacwest-shares-western-alliance-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dipped</a> by more than 50%. On Thursday, PacWest shares closed at  $3.17, down 50.62% from its opening price on the same day.</p>
<p>“In light of the recent events, management took immediate steps to maximize liquidity, including the exploration of strategic asset sales, which has led to the transfer of our $2.7 billion Lender Finance loan portfolio to held for sale,” said Paul Taylor, PacWest President and Chief Executive Officer (CEO).</p>
<h2>Federal Reserve Increases Interest Rate despite Banking Crisis</h2>
<p>Amid the broader banking crisis, investors are still concerned about the next move of the government in terms of Federal Reserve policy. After several hikes in interest rates including the 25 basis point <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/fed-increased-interest-rate-0-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">increase</a> introduced over the past few months amid the banking crisis, investors are no longer sure of what to expect.</p>
<p>Following the recent increment earlier this week, the central bank hinted that the rate increase may be suspended soon.</p>
<p>In the meantime, investors are still bothered that the central bank may eventually cut rates towards the end of the year, especially with a looming recession. Fed Chairman <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jerome-powell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jerome Powell</a> once suggested that it was too early to do so. However, he also mentioned that whatever changes and policy decisions that would be implemented in the future would be data-dependent.</p>
<p>These data are likely to include April’s nonfarm payroll, unemployment and wage growth figures. In turn, these parameters would help to determine if there has been less stress in the labor market. The report is expected to indicate that about 180,000 jobs have been added, according to economists surveyed by business and financial information outlet Dow Jones.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/">US Treasury Yield Spikes as Investors Fear Recurring Banking Crisis</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-treasury-yield-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hong Kong IPO Market to Rebound This Year after Turbulent 2022</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 11:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IPO News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deloitte]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hong kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ipo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kpmg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stock market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=253437</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/">Hong Kong IPO Market to Rebound This Year after Turbulent 2022</a></p>
<p>Despite the raging impact of inflation in different economies, monetary authorities have not been sitting on their oars, rather, they have been fighting the surge through consistent interest rate hikes.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/">Hong Kong IPO Market to Rebound This Year after Turbulent 2022</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/">Hong Kong IPO Market to Rebound This Year after Turbulent 2022</a></p>
<p>The Hong Kong <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-initial-public-offering-ipo/#:~:text=Initial%20Public%20Offering%20Investors&amp;text=The%20IPO%20gives%20them%20a,a%20profit%20for%20the%20buyer." target="_blank" rel="noopener">Initial Public Offering</a> (IPO) market has failed to get lifted from its dampened sentiment after the listing of Chinese liquor company ZJLD Group failed relatively. As <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/05/hong-kongs-ipo-market-still-waiting-to-rebound-after-recent-flop.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> by CNBC, the shares of ZJLD Group tumbled as hard as 18% on its first day of trading back on April 27, showcasing how much lack of confidence exists in the industry.</p>
<p>Last year was a very turbulent year for the global financial ecosystem as skyrocketing inflation rocked almost every economy. With fiat currencies losing their intrinsic value, many investors went on the sidelines, pursuing safe assets that can at least help preserve capital. While most stock markets saw a battery over the past year, Hong Kong’s was particularly of interest.</p>
<p>Known as a major financial hub in the Asia-Pacific region, the slow growth of the stock market shows the economy is far from rebounding to normal levels.</p>
<p>“The sentiment in the IPO markets has not built up yet,” Ringo Choi, Asia-Pacific IPO leader at EY said in a statement, adding that “a lot of industries are suffering at the moment.”</p>
<p>Choi noted that the tech firms in Hong Kong are experiencing major pressure from the US-China economic and trade tensions. Additionally, he believes the poor outlook also stems from the falling prices for electric vehicles in the region.</p>
<p>Since the pandemic, the valuations of companies have been dwindling and the current economic climate is making it impossible to revisit these impressive levels anytime soon.</p>
<p>“Valuations at this moment have not picked up as compared to two to three years ago. We still need some time,” said Robert Lui, Hong Kong offering leader of Deloitte China’s Capital Market Services Group.</p>
<h2>Impact of Interest Rate Hikes on the Hong Kong IPO Market</h2>
<p>Despite the raging impact of inflation in different economies, monetary authorities have not been sitting on their oars, rather, they have been fighting the surge through consistent <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-stock-indices-fed-interest-rate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">interest rate hikes</a>. With the Hong Kong stock and IPO market, in general, down by 15% in 2022, it was considered one of the worst performers for the year.</p>
<p>One of the key factors that experts have highlighted is the impact of China’s zero-Covid policy as well as the uncertainty that comes with interest rate hikes.</p>
<p>“The concern is still about the high-interest rate environment and a lot of the attention in the Greater China region is about the recovery of the economy,” said Irene Chu, Partner at KPMG China.</p>
<p>Despite this gloomy outlook, experts are bullish that the year 2023 will mark a major turnaround for the Hong Kong stock market. This bullish sentiment is notably shared by the trio of Deloitte China, EY, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/kpmg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">KPMG</a>. This assurance stems from the fact that the Chinese and Hong Kong borders are now reopening for business with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-hub-hong-kong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more relaxed rules</a> that can generally bolster growth in the short to mid-term.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/block-q1-2023-report/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/">Hong Kong IPO Market to Rebound This Year after Turbulent 2022</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-ipo-market-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4652 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1316082 metric#prefetches=204 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=13 metric#store-hits=211 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=117.84 metric#ms-cache=7.56 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2222 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.4 -->