<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 04:12:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Best AI cryptocurrencies to invest in: Shiba Memu, SingularityNET</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-shiba-memu-singularitynet/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-shiba-memu-singularitynet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 04:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/best-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-shiba-memu-singularitynet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Artificial intelligence is the biggest theme in the market this year. Most companies have unveiled their artificial intelligence plans. Shiba Memu and SingularityNET are some of the best AI coins. Artificial Intelligence (AI) has become the fastest-growing technology in the world. In the corporate scene, companies like Nvidia, Microsoft, and C3.ai have seen their stocks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-shiba-memu-singularitynet/">Best AI cryptocurrencies to invest in: Shiba Memu, SingularityNET</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Artificial intelligence is the biggest theme in the market this year.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Most companies have unveiled their artificial intelligence plans.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu and SingularityNET are some of the best AI coins.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Artificial Intelligence (AI) has become the fastest-growing technology in the world. In the corporate scene, companies like Nvidia, Microsoft, and C3.ai have seen their stocks surge this year. Nvidia, a GPU manufacturer, has seen its market cap surge to over $1 trillion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many companies have unveiled their AI plans. Microsoft has launched a suite of AI tools, including Copilot. On Tuesday, the company revealed pricing of these products, with a monthly subscription of Copilot going for $30. Google has launched Bard while Elon Musk has launched xAI. In this article, we will look at the best AI cryptocurrencies to buy.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu (SHMU)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is a new cryptocurrency that has a lot of potential. Currently in presale, the developers have raised almost $1 million in less than three weeks. This makes it one of the fastest-growing cryptocurrencies this year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu, as you can see in this&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>is a cryptocurrency that is at the intersection of two trends: artificial intelligence and meme coins. As the name suggests, the token as inspired by&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/shiba-inu/"><u>Shiba Inu</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the second-biggest meme coin in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu will have some AI tools. For one, it will be the first crypto platform to use AI to market itself. In this, the network will learn new marketing strategies, create its own press releases, and promote itself across all popular social networks. The goal is to create a platform that is self-reliant and transparent in the market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">All this content will be shown in the intuitive Shiba Memu dashboard. This dashboard will show the performance of its content and identify key trends.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There are three main reasons why Shiba Memu&rsquo;s token will do well. First, as mentioned, it is in the two popular industries this year. Second, the token has the momentum it needs to become the next big thing. In this, it has raised over $977k within a few days. Finally, it could jump because of the macro element since America&rsquo;s inflation is falling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">You can buy the Shiba Meme token&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SingularityNET (AGIX)</h2>
<p dir="ltr">SingularityNET is another AI-focused cryptocurrency to buy. AGIX, its ecosystem token, is one of the top-performing cryptocurrencies this year, having gained by over 500%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">SingularityNET is a&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/cardano/"><u>Cardano</u></a><strong>&ndash;</strong>based blockchain that is creating a platform for decentralized artificial intelligence. Its ecosystem is made up of projects that are changing the industry in a large scale.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For example, there is Rejuve.ai, a platform that is focused on longevity research. It has built a decentralized network of researchers, clinicians, and data contributors.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other parts of the network&rsquo;s ecosystem are Awakening Health, SingularityDAO, Cogito, and Nunet. Cogito is building a new class of digital assets known as tracercoins that leverage risk-weighted reserves and AI-powered stabilization.</p>
<p dir="ltr">SingularityNET is a good AI coin to invest for two main reasons. First, unlike many other cryptocurrencies, it has a real ecosystem that is growing. Second, the token has a proven track record of performance.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/best-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-shiba-memu-singularitynet/">Best AI cryptocurrencies to invest in: Shiba Memu, SingularityNET</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/best-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-invest-in-shiba-memu-singularitynet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Actor Ben McKenzie says crypto is like a ‘Ponzi scheme’</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/actor-ben-mckenzie-crypto-is-like-ponzi-scheme/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=146730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>McKenzie says cryptocurrencies resemble an MLM scheme. He calls for the need to better regulate and license this market. Bitcoin is currently up a whopping 80% versus the start of 2023. An 80% year-to-date rally in Bitcoin is not enough to substantiate the legitimacy of cryptocurrencies for actor Ben McKenzie. McKenzie dubs crypto an MLM [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/actor-ben-mckenzie-crypto-is-like-ponzi-scheme/">Actor Ben McKenzie says crypto is like a ‘Ponzi scheme’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>McKenzie says cryptocurrencies resemble an MLM scheme.</li>
<li>He calls for the need to better regulate and license this market.</li>
<li>Bitcoin is currently up a whopping 80% versus the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<p>An 80% year-to-date rally in <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> is not enough to substantiate the legitimacy of cryptocurrencies for actor Ben McKenzie.</p>
<h2>McKenzie dubs crypto an MLM scheme</h2>
<p>McKenzie does not see cryptocurrencies as financial assets per se.</p>
<p>He views them more as a &ldquo;story&rdquo; that can be pushed out of existence if people stopped believing in them. On CNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/18/cryptocurrency-closely-resembles-a-ponzi-scheme-or-multi-level-marketing-says-actor-ben-mckenzie.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Squawk Box</a>&rdquo;, the actor who played James Gordon in &ldquo;Gotham&rdquo; said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Crypto resembles a Ponzi scheme or multi-level marketing scheme. In MLMs, 99% of people lose and 1.0% benefit. In crypto, it&rsquo;d be exchange owners, VC firms, people that issue the coins.</p></blockquote>
<p>Still, the U.S. Securities &amp; Exchange Commission has recently received several applications including from <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/03/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-application-refiled-naming-coinbase-as-surveillance-sharing-partner/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> for a Spot Bitcoin ETF that signal institutional interest in BTC.</p>
<h2>McKenzie says regulation will help</h2>
<p>Last month, the regulator sued both Binance and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/coinbase/">Coinbase Global Inc</a> for violating U.S. securities laws.</p>
<p>According to Ben McKenzie, greater regulation and more sophisticated licensing could indeed help turn crypto into a proper financial market.</p>
<blockquote><p>You&rsquo;re talking about an unregulated, unlicensed market run through shell corps in Caribbean. Crypto has benefitted from gray area between how we classify securities and commodities.</p></blockquote>
<p>The veteran actor is even more bearish on cryptocurrencies other than Bitcoin as the latter is at least limited in terms of supply. Also on Tuesday, Professor Carol Alexander of Sussex University said <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/18/bitcoin-btc-mid-year-update-market-experts-predict-prices-for-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC could hit $50,000</a> by the end of 2023.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/actor-ben-mckenzie-crypto-is-like-ponzi-scheme/">Actor Ben McKenzie says crypto is like a ‘Ponzi scheme’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shinhan Bank, SCB TechX pilot cross-border stablecoin payments on the Hedera</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-pilot-cross-border-stablecoin-payments-on-the-hedera/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-pilot-cross-border-stablecoin-payments-on-the-hedera/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-pilot-cross-border-stablecoin-payments-on-the-hedera/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shinhan Bank and Siam Commercial Bank&#8217;s SCB TechX recorded real-time, low-cost remittances. The pilot on the Hedera network involved cross-border stablecoin payments using South Korean won (KRW), the Thai Baht (THB), and the New Taiwan dollar (NTD). Shinhan Bank and Siam Commercial Bank&#8217;s SCB TechX have reportedly completed a proof-of-concept (PoC) pilot for stablecoin remittances [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-pilot-cross-border-stablecoin-payments-on-the-hedera/">Shinhan Bank, SCB TechX pilot cross-border stablecoin payments on the Hedera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Shinhan Bank and Siam Commercial Bank&rsquo;s SCB TechX recorded real-time, low-cost remittances.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The pilot on the Hedera network involved cross-border stablecoin payments using South Korean won (KRW), the Thai Baht (THB), and the New Taiwan dollar (NTD).</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Shinhan Bank and Siam Commercial Bank&rsquo;s SCB TechX have reportedly completed a proof-of-concept (PoC) pilot for stablecoin remittances on the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/hedera/">Hedera network</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This was the second PoC test on Hedera&rsquo;s distributed ledger network after the initial program launched in 2021 and which involved Standard Bank. In this latest pilot, the company sought to check on the efficiency, cost and settlement speed of cross-border payments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ In a continuation of their work on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DLT?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DLT</a>-enabled cross-border remittances, <a href="https://twitter.com/ShinhanBankENG?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ShinhanBankENG</a> &ndash; in collaboration with SCB TechX &amp; other financial institutions &ndash; has today announced the successful completion of a <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/stablecoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#stablecoin</a> remittances PoC pilot on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Hedera?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Hedera</a>.<a href="https://t.co/OUAxOfU2U4">https://t.co/OUAxOfU2U4</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Hedera (@hedera) <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera/status/1681169052423667713?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to details shared in a <a href="https://hedera.com/blog/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-successfully-pilot-stablecoin-remittances-on-the-hedera-network"><u>press release</u></a>, the banks achieved real-time foreign exchange settlement across three currencies &ndash; the South Korean won (KRW), the Thai Baht (THB), and the New Taiwan dollar (NTD).</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;Shinhan Bank&rsquo;s Chief of Blockchain division Byunghee Kim said in a statement:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The successful completion of this second PoC marks an important step forward in our efforts to make cross-border payments faster, cheaper, and more accessible to people around the world&hellip; With this next phase of PoC, we are pleased to have demonstrated how the use of Hedera&rsquo;s EVM-compatible technology helps eliminate intermediaries, reduce costs, and speed up the remittance process</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">EVM-compatibility for the PoC means the system will be open to any EVM-based stablecoin issuers, with this likely to also see more banks and other financial institutions tap into its potential as the cross-border payments ecosystem expands.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-pilot-cross-border-stablecoin-payments-on-the-hedera/">Shinhan Bank, SCB TechX pilot cross-border stablecoin payments on the Hedera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shinhan-bank-scb-techx-pilot-cross-border-stablecoin-payments-on-the-hedera/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>United States SEC officially accepts Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF application</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC has been receiving Bitcoin ETF resubmissions after it rejected previous applications for inadequacy. Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund was the last company to submit a Bitcoin ETF application to the SEC. The SEC has accepted several other BTC ETFs after the respective companies amended and resubmitted. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">United States SEC officially accepts Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF application</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>The US SEC has been receiving Bitcoin ETF resubmissions after it rejected previous applications for inadequacy.</li>
<li>Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund was the last company to submit a Bitcoin ETF application to the SEC.</li>
<li>The SEC has accepted several other BTC ETFs after the respective companies amended and resubmitted.</li>
</ul>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has officially accepted the Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF application, marking a momentous step towards embracing BTC ETFs.</p>
<p>Besides marking a turning point for the entire crypto industry, SEC&rsquo;s move suggests a potential turning point for widespread crypto adoption in the biggest economy in the world. If approved, the Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF will be the first of its kind, providing investors with exposure to <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin </a>without requiring them to hold any physical cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Crypto industry preparing for Bitcoin ETFs</h2>
<p>The SEC accepted Valkyrie&rsquo;s amended BTC ETF application after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/">rejecting previous Bitcoin ETF applications</a> noting that they were inadequate. The public has 21 days to comment after the Federal Register notice is published after which the public input will be reviewed.</p>
<p>Eric Balchunas, a senior ETF analyst at Bloomberg, immediately <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1681062886808879104">took to Twitter</a> to spread the word after the US SEC approved Valkyrie&rsquo;s application to register a spot Bitcoin ETF. Valkyrie was the very last company to apply for approval of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the flurry of companies that did. He added that the &ldquo;BRRR&rdquo; ticker was chosen by the Valkyrie Bitcoin ETF for its Nasdaq debut.</p>
<p>Other Bitcoin ETF applications that have been accepted by the SEC include applications made by Fidelity Investments, WisdomTree, VanEck, Invesco, and ARK 21Shares. This clearly shows that the SEC is considering the applications.</p>
<p>Approving the Bitcoin ETFs would be a major victory for the cryptocurrency industry in addition to the recent Ripple Labs win against the SEC.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/">United States SEC officially accepts Valkyrie Spot Bitcoin ETF application</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/united-states-sec-officially-accepts-valkyrie-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple invests in $54M round for AI-metaverse firm Futureverse</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple invested in the $54 million series A round for Futureverse.&#160; 10T Holdings led the funding round, which Futureverse says will go into scaling AI and metaverse technologies. Ripple has integrated Futureverse blockchain The Root Network and will see use of XRP as gas token. Futureverse, a company leveraging artificial intelligence (AI) and metaverse technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/">Ripple invests in $54M round for AI-metaverse firm Futureverse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ripple invested in the $54 million series A round for Futureverse.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">10T Holdings led the funding round, which Futureverse says will go into scaling AI and metaverse technologies.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Ripple has integrated Futureverse blockchain The Root Network and will see use of XRP as gas token.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Futureverse, a company leveraging artificial intelligence (AI) and metaverse technology to advance growth in the gaming industry, has closed a $54 million series A funding round.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The round was led by 10T Holdings, a leading late stage growth equity fund, and attracted the participation of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ripple/">Ripple</a>. Futureverse plans to deploy the funds towards initiatives targeted at scaling AI and metaverse technologies.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Per today&rsquo;s <a href="https://twitter.com/futureverse/status/1681315975470407680" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announcement</a>, the company plans to tap into the partnership with 10T and Ripple &ldquo;to take the metaverse from an abstract idea to a practical, accessible, and interactive destination.&rdquo;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Futureverse&rsquo;s AI-metaverse ecosystem</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Futureverse has plans to become the world&rsquo;s largest metaverse AI technology provider, layer 1 architect and creative studio. According to the company, this goal includes creating tools that support an open, scalable and interoperable infrastructure.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is a goal that has seen it quietly roll up 11 startups into one ecosystem that&rsquo;s currently among the largest collaborative ecosystems for the metaverse. Some of these companies include AI-protocol Altered State Machine, creative studio Non-Fungible Labs, decentralized communications protocol Sylo, and digital asset payments SDK Centrapay.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As part of the push to form a leading metaverse community, including for AI gaming powered by digital collectibles, Futureverse recently partnered with FIFA to launch an AI-powered consumer game dubbed AI League.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company also has a partnership with Muhammad Ali Enterprises in a deal set to see them launch &ldquo;Muhammad Ali &ndash; The Next Legends&rdquo;, &nbsp;which will become the first-ever AI-powered boxing game.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Partnership with The Root Network and Ripple</h2>
<p dir="ltr">As well as other key collaborations, Futureverse is looking to tap into the benefits of blockchain technology via the integration of its The Root Network and Ripple&rsquo;s XRPL.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Root Network is a blockchain and suite of protocols offering ready-made runtimes. Developers will be able to tap into this platform to build next-generation metaverse apps and games, the company noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The integration with XRPL allows for XRP to be used as a gas token and the XLS-20 NFT standard, the two companies said in a <a href="https://venturebeat.com/metaverse/futureverse-raises-54m-to-marry-ai-and-the-metaverse/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">statement</a>. And in a comment, Monica Long, president of Ripple, said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We are excited to continue to support the Futureverse vision and celebrate the Root Network&rsquo;s integration with the XRP Ledger. While we&rsquo;re at the earliest stages of what a project like this &mdash; and really the larger concept of the metaverse &mdash; can achieve, we at Ripple are thrilled to contribute to the foundational infrastructure layer and provide real utility to the end users of the open metaverse.</em>&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/">Ripple invests in $54M round for AI-metaverse firm Futureverse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/ripple-invests-in-54m-round-for-ai-metaverse-firm-futureverse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1inch price outlook as bulls give up XRP-fueled gains</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-price-outlook-as-bulls-give-up-xrp-fueled-gains/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-price-outlook-as-bulls-give-up-xrp-fueled-gains/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-price-outlook-as-bulls-give-up-xrp-fueled-gains/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>1inch price is down 16% at the time of writing after paring all 24-hour gains from above $0.59. The 1INCH token saw massive 24-hour trading volume on Korean exchange Upbit. On the technical side, 1INCH is poised above a key support area around $0.34. The price of 1inch token (1INCH) pumped in early trading hours [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-price-outlook-as-bulls-give-up-xrp-fueled-gains/">1inch price outlook as bulls give up XRP-fueled gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap">
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">1inch price is down 16% at the time of writing after paring all 24-hour gains from above $0.59.</p>
</div>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">The 1INCH token saw massive 24-hour trading volume on Korean exchange Upbit.</li>
<li dir="ltr">On the technical side, 1INCH is poised above a key support area around $0.34.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">The price of 1inch token (1INCH) pumped in early trading hours Monday, reaching highs of $0.59. However, just as quickly as it rose from lows of $0.39, the 1INCH price pared the gains and traded to $0.36.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to data from CoinGecko, 1inch is down 16% in the past 24 hours as of time of writing, with a look at the weekly time frame showing the token has cut recent gains to just 21%.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This contrasts with the explosive action that characterized the 1INCH market following Ripple&rsquo;s partial win in its ongoing regulatory battle with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">1INCH price outlook- what next?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Like XRP, which pumped more than 100% in the aftermath of Judge Analisa Torres&rsquo; ruling last week, 1inch price was mainly <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1681308870898229250" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">boosted</a> by huge volume on the South Korean crypto exchange Upbit. Indeed, in the past 24 hours, the coin&rsquo;s trading volume on the Upbit exchange hovered at around 31% of total daily volume.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Yet, trading volume has declined from more than $670 million on Monday to about $120 million at the time of writing &ndash; representing an 83% dip in the past 24 hours. As to why 1INCH price is down today, we see an overall negative flip for major cryptocurrencies led by Bitcoin&rsquo;s fall below $30k and Ethereum&rsquo;s struggles near $1.9k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Altcoins, including XRP, BNB and Solana also pared recent gains today. The downward pressure comes as bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network moved millions of dollars&rsquo; worth of altcoins to exchanges for liquidation and conversion into BTC and ETH.[<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/matic-link-aave-among-59m-worth-of-altcoins-moved-by-celsius/">Read more</a>]</p>
<p dir="ltr">1inch token is among those the platform moved to FalconX on Monday in preparation for offloading.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;<span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib" style="width: 600px"><span class="fr-img-wrap"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689694990537-25d2a6c3-2bec-4a49-a195-f76fb668b2a4.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="307"><span class="fr-inner">1inch price on the daily chart.Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/nRPcHxnF/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></span></span>If we look at the technical picture as suggested in the chart above, we have the daily RSI dipping near the equilibrium point to suggest bears could still take a swipe at bulls. 1INCH is also in danger of retreating to the 50-day exponential moving average.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The moving average currently offers a buffer zone near $0.34. On the upside, 1INCH is facing long term resistance as signaled by the 200-day EMA &ndash; currently at $0.45 after the coin&rsquo;s dip from above $0.59.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-price-outlook-as-bulls-give-up-xrp-fueled-gains/">1inch price outlook as bulls give up XRP-fueled gains</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/1inch-price-outlook-as-bulls-give-up-xrp-fueled-gains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>LEND Finance announces integration with LayerZero</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/lend-finance-announces-integration-with-layerzero/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/lend-finance-announces-integration-with-layerzero/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/lend-finance-announces-integration-with-layerzero/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Users can leverage LayerZero&#8217;s Ultra Light Nodes (ULNs) to lend assets across any blockchain. The integration also means borrowing and lending on LEND Finance is easy and cost-effective, all with single click capability. LEND Finance says it settled on LayerZero after Multichain shuttered its operations. Cross-chain lending protocol LEND Finance has announced an exclusive integration [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lend-finance-announces-integration-with-layerzero/">LEND Finance announces integration with LayerZero</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Users can leverage LayerZero&rsquo;s Ultra Light Nodes (ULNs) to lend assets across any blockchain.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The integration also means borrowing and lending on LEND Finance is easy and cost-effective, all with single click capability.</li>
<li dir="ltr">LEND Finance says it settled on LayerZero after Multichain shuttered its operations.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Cross-chain lending protocol LEND Finance has announced an exclusive integration with omnichain interoperability platform LayerZero.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The LayerZero team said in a <a href="https://medium.com/lendfinance/lends-development-update-with-layerzero-integration-reinventing-cross-chain-lending-e801622af386" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>blog post</u></a> that the decision to choose the &ldquo;omnichain interoperability protocol,&rdquo; was down to its innovative and lightweight cross-chain messaging. The original plan was to launch LEND with cross-chain protocol router <a href="https://coinjournal.net/multichain/">Multichain</a>, the platform that recently announced it was shuttering its operations.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As CoinJournal <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cross-chain-bridge-protocol-multichain-ceases-operations/">reported</a> last week, Multichain said it had come to the unfortunate decision of shutting shop after events that left the team with funds and access to key servers. Multichain founder and CEO as well as his sister have reportedly been detained in China.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">LEND, LayerZero to streamline cross-chain lending</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In its announcement on Tuesday July 18, LEND Finance said the partnership &ldquo;<em>brings fresh possibilities to the complex field of cross-chain lending</em>.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, LEND will tap into LayerZero&rsquo;s Ultra Light Nodes (ULNs) to make it easy and cost-effective for its users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Exciting News! &#127881; <a href="https://twitter.com/LEND_finance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LEND_finance</a>  is proud to announce our integration with <a href="https://twitter.com/LayerZero_Labs?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LayerZero_Labs</a>! </p>
<p>Their pioneering omnichain interoperability protocol takes cross-chain lending to a whole new level!</p>
<p>/1 &#129525;&#128071; <a href="https://t.co/7gMq8BPJ0A">pic.twitter.com/7gMq8BPJ0A</a></p>
<p>&mdash; LEND.finance (@LEND_finance) <a href="https://twitter.com/LEND_finance/status/1681273081472450562?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">According to LEND Finance, the integration allows its users to borrow and lend assets on any chain. Users will also be able to move to the most favaourable rates with just one click. The functionality will increase efficiency of the lending and borrowing process, with ecosystem users getting the added benefit of maximized DeFi earnings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For instance, borrowers can leverage LayerZero&rsquo;s ULNs for cross-chain messages, with instant access to liquidity on any chain all made possible with a single-click functionality. The overall benefit of this is the streamlined lending process that also comes with security checks.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/lend-finance-announces-integration-with-layerzero/">LEND Finance announces integration with LayerZero</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/lend-finance-announces-integration-with-layerzero/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer presale nets more investors with the addition of ETH and USDT buying options</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chancer is revolutionizing the betting industry by leveraging the power of blockchain technology. Chancer presale now allows investors to use ETH, USDT, BUSD, and BNB. Currently, CHANCER is selling for $0.01. Stage one of the Chancer presale has hit $823,011 days after it added Ethereum (ETH) and Tether (USDT) buying options to complement the current [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/">Chancer presale nets more investors with the addition of ETH and USDT buying options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Chancer is revolutionizing the betting industry by leveraging the power of blockchain technology.</li>
<li>Chancer presale now allows investors to use ETH, USDT, BUSD, and BNB.</li>
<li>Currently, CHANCER is selling for $0.01.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stage one of the Chancer presale has hit $823,011 days after it added <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/tether/what-is-tether/">Tether (USDT)</a> buying options to complement the current BNB and BUSD options. The addition of the two crypto options makes the project appeal to millions more blockchain aficionados and is likely to accelerate their presale.</p>
<p>In just four weeks, Chancer, which was initially hailed as one of the most interesting cryptocurrency ventures of 2023, has raised nearly $1 million. Chancer is a new <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/">blockchain</a> initiative that is upending the online gambling industry.</p>
<h2>Opening the door for Ethereum and Tether ecosystem</h2>
<p>Ethereum is valued at an astounding $240 billion, making it the second-largest coin in the world by market valuation after <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>. The addition of ETH was a very wise business move on the part of the project team given that there are over 238 million ETH holders worldwide.</p>
<p>ETH token holders will now have the opportunity of purchasing the new CHANCER token</p>
<p>Most blockchain presales use USDT and ETH for their presales and Chancer has just joined the list.</p>
<h2>Why investors are flocking to the new betting platform</h2>
<p>Chancer is developing the world&rsquo;s first decentralized social predictive markets platform. The new betting platform will allow Chancer token holders to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets based on their interests, expertise and social opportunities. Interested parties can purchase the CHANCER tokens <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">here</a>.</p>
<p>By &ldquo;removing the house&rdquo; and capturing a portion of the market, the project seeks to disrupt the worldwide gaming and betting industry while attracting attention by upending the established bookmaking and betting business model.</p>
<p>Chancer is attracting thousands of investors from both the cryptocurrency and betting sectors thanks to its innovative use of Google&rsquo;s WebRTC technology, which enables users to create their own odds and bets and then broadcast these to a global audience who can participate in live bets. Many anticipate that the project holds great potential given its rapid progress through its early stages including the currently rapidly selling presale.</p>
<p>It is obvious why Chancer is attracting thousands of investors from the cryptocurrency and betting sectors with its innovative approach to online betting that allows users to create their own odds and their own bets and then broadcast these to a global audience who can participate in live bets. Many anticipate that this token will sell out quickly at its current price of $0.01 and given how quickly the project is moving through its early stage.</p>
<p>Adam and Paul Kelbie, the company&rsquo;s founders, are actively interacting with their audience as well as a number of prominent influencers in the blockchain, gambling, sports, and online gaming areas. They are supported by a devoted group of &lsquo;Chancers&rsquo; who are spreading the word about their original concept. This might quickly take on the role of P2P social betting.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/">Chancer presale nets more investors with the addition of ETH and USDT buying options</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-nets-more-investors-with-the-addition-of-eth-and-usdt-buying-options/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin since the Merge?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Ever since the Merge went live in September, Ether has underperformed Bitcoin significantly&#160; This is despite the supply of Ethereum falling post-Merge More Ether is also being staked since the Shapella upgrade in April&#160; Demand has fallen with regard to Bitcoin, however, overriding the lower supply Regulatory crackdown and greater institutional interest in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/">Why is Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin since the Merge?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Ever since the Merge went live in September, Ether has underperformed Bitcoin significantly&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">This is despite the supply of Ethereum falling post-Merge</li>
<li dir="ltr">More Ether is also being staked since the Shapella upgrade in April&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Demand has fallen with regard to Bitcoin, however, overriding the lower supply</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory crackdown and greater institutional interest in Bitcoin appears to be driving the divergence, writes our Head of Research</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the more interesting trends to follow within crypto is that of the ETH / BTC chart. In other words, how the world&rsquo;s two largest cryptocurrencies move in relation to one another. Now ten months on from the Ethereum Merge, it feels like a good time to re-analyse the relationship.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Merge completely transformed Ethereum, switching the network to a proof-of-stake mechanism rather than the proof-of-work mechanism it was on previously. On the other hand, Bitcoin remains (and always will be) a proof-of-work blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This means that the fundamentals underlying the Ethereum network have flipped. Perhaps this is most noticeable when plotting the total circulating supply of ETH. The Merge going live in September 2022 sticks out like a sore thumb, with the supply (slightly) contracting from that date.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14475145">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Zooming in on the post-Merge period in the next chart shows the contraction. The supply has reduced at an average rate of 0.15% per month. Prior to the Merge, the supply grew by 0.41% per month. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14475270">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Moreover, the supply of liquid Ether has contracted even further than the above charts show. Looking at the total value of staked Ether, the pattern was relatively steady from when the staking contract opened in November 2020. This trend more or less continued as the Merge went live in September 2022. However, as seen on the next chart, the amount of staked Ether spiked notably in April of this year, as the Shapella upgrade went live.&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689688360391-8e5b27c9-08a2-4c45-87a3-0c4a800817f3.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="377"></p>
<p dir="ltr">This Shapella upgrade, also known as Shanghai, allowed staked Ether to finally be sold, with some of the early stakers having locked up their tokens since Q4 of 2020. Despite concern that this would lead to a vast amount of Ether flooding the market and denting the price, the opposite has happened. With the indefinite lock-up restriction no longer a factor, the Ether staked has spiked noticeably, with the trend far steeper in the three months since.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But how has this structural break on the supply side affected Ether&rsquo;s performance against Bitcoin? Less supply equals a higher price, right? Well, no actually. Almost on a dime from when the Merge went live, ETH has fallen relative to Bitcoin, as I have plotted on the below chart (the black line denotes the Merge in September).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14475531">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The reason, of course, is that price is governed by supply and demand, rather than just supply. And while supply has contracted, the demand side of the equation has not held up &ndash; at least relative to Bitcoin.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ether underperforms Bitcoin</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Two months after the Merge, FTX collapsed, sending the entire crypto sector for a spin. As is customary in times of price decline, Bitcoin fell less than the rest of the market. Thus, Ether falling against Bitcoin in the aftermath of the crash is not surprising.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, thus far in 2023, the crypto market has been on fire, with token prices accelerating across the board as the macro climate has softened amid falling inflation. The Nasdaq jumped 32% in the first six months of the year, its best half-year return since 1983. And yet, despite the crypto market riding this wave, Ether fell further still against Bitcoin, something which seemingly bucks the trend.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The reason is most likely regulation. The great regulatory crackdown in the US has been brutal on crypto, but Bitcoin has not been as squarely in the crosshairs as a lot of the market. This has led to Bitcoin dominance rising to its <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/"><u>highest level in two years</u></a>, now comprising over 50% of the entire cryptocurrency market cap. It opened the year at 42% (it was also roughly at this level at the time of the Ethereum Merge in September).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/06/18/1689688360114-9b756a88-6af6-47f6-bece-045bc86a408f.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="256"></p>
<p dir="ltr">This comes amid sentiment that Bitcoin could be carving out its own niche in the space. This is the view that many in the space have long held (and a Bitcoin maximalist&rsquo;s sworn mantra), but the difference now is that the law appears to be coming around to the same point of view. I&rsquo;ll let Coinbase CEO Brian Armstong put it more succinctly than I:&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;We go back to 2021, we wanted to become a public company, we described everything about our business, the assets that we list on our platform, how we do staking. The SEC at that point allowed us to become a public company&rdquo;.</em></p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;A totally different tone started to happen (about a year ago),&rdquo;</em> Armstrong continued. <em>&ldquo;We kind of got this information from the SEC that, well actually everything other than Bitcoin is a security.&rdquo;</em></p>
<p dir="ltr">Although Ether was not present on the list of tokens announced by the SEC that comprised securities, a list which included some other popular cryptos such as MATIC, SOL and ATOM, it has not been immune. Viewed more or less in a grey area, Ether nonetheless has suffered as the regulatory blows kept coming. While last week&rsquo;s XRP ruling is positive for the space, and there will be many more twists and turns to come, it still feels like Bitcoin has separated itself from the crowd.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further reinforcing this view is the slew of Bitcoin ETFs submitted for approval from some of the world&rsquo;s biggest asset managers, including Blackrock. Denied repeatedly to date, the presence of big names backing Bitcoin amid this suffocating US legal environment is another boon for the orange coin. And while one could (rightly) hypothesise that a Bitcoin ETF would make an Ether ETF more likely, there is no denying that Bitcoin has pulled further ahead in the race.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This has led to a situation in 2023 where Bitcoin has outperformed Ether, which seems surprising when the latter has tended to outperform the former during prior periods of price expansion. But it is always important to remember how brief the trading history for both Ether and Bitcoin is. Ether was only launched in 2015, and it was another couple of years before it traded with any genuine liquidity. So, leaning on past performance must always be done with a pinch of salt. Additionally, the crypto market has <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/no-bitcoin-has-never-seen-a-bear-market-before-this-time-its-different/"><u>never experienced</u></a> a macro environment like this.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, any hopes that the Merge would accelerate Ether into the stratosphere perhaps overlooked how much of the upgrade was priced in. This was in the works for a long time, repeatedly delayed before it finally came and went.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">All in all, this has led to Ether lagging Bitcoin, with the latter increasing its dominance over not only Ether, but the crypto market as a whole. Things are changing quickly in crypto, and Bitcoin has been weathering the turbulent waters better than altcoins in recent months, primarily due to the legal climate.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Then again, the way prices have been going, Ether investors can&rsquo;t be too unhappy &ndash; despite Ether&rsquo;s second-place medal, it is still up 57% thus far this year. It could be worse, even if they did back the wrong horse.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/">Why is Ethereum outperforming Bitcoin since the Merge?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/why-is-ethereum-outperforming-bitcoin-since-the-merge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
