<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Foot Locker Posts Q1 2023 Results, Sees Stock Sink 25% on Sales Drop</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/foot-locker-q1-2023-results/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foot locker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[target]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[walmart]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255716</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foot-locker-q1-2023-results/">Foot Locker Posts Q1 2023 Results, Sees Stock Sink 25% on Sales Drop</a></p>
<p>Sportswear and footwear retail company Foot Locker took a beating in its Q1 2023 report after sustaining an 11% drawdown in revenue. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foot-locker-q1-2023-results/">Foot Locker Posts Q1 2023 Results, Sees Stock Sink 25% on Sales Drop</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foot-locker-q1-2023-results/">Foot Locker Posts Q1 2023 Results, Sees Stock Sink 25% on Sales Drop</a></p>
<p>Foot Locker Retail Inc (NYSE: FL) plunged 25% following a big earnings miss in the Q1 2023 outing. For the first quarter of 2023, the sportswear and footwear retailer reported revenue of $1.93 billion versus the $1.99 billion analysts expected. In addition, the company realized earnings per share of 70 cents adjusted versus 81 cents expected.</p>
<p>Following Friday’s disappointing Q1 2023 report, Foot Locker lowered its guidance for the rest of 2023. The company also said it increased markdowns during the dismal quarter to increase sales. Foot Locker’s discounted prices for products during the quarter were also to clear excess inventories.</p>
<p>The company’s sales slide is reflected in its latest quarterly income, 11% lower than the $2.18 billion realized a year earlier. Furthermore, reported net income for the period came in at $36 million, or 38 cents a share, compared with $132 million, or $1.37 per share, the year before.</p>
<h2>Foot Locker CEO Ascribes Underwhelming Q1 2023 Performance to Bleak Economic Situation but Believes Better Days Lie Ahead</h2>
<p>In a statement, Foot Locker chief executive officer Mary Dillon reflected on the company’s poor showing, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our sales have since softened meaningfully given the tough macroeconomic backdrop, causing us to reduce our guidance for the year as we take more aggressive markdowns to both drive demand and manage inventory.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Despite Foot Locker’s gloomy prospects, Dillon remained upbeat, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/foot-locker-inc-reports-2023-first-quarter-results-301829162.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">highlighting</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Despite the challenging near-term trends, we remain committed to our long-term strategy, including making the necessary investments to drive our Lace Up plan and maintain conviction in our ability to execute against our new strategic imperatives.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The Lace Up plan Dillon referred to is a multipronged strategy to grow the New York-based shoe retailer’s market share by 2026. In that same time scale, Foot Locker also plans to stoke sales to $9.5 billion despite prevailing macroeconomic circumstances.</p>
<p>Under its Lace UP agenda, Foot Locker would diversify its brand portfolio and relaunch its product brand with new store formats. The company also seeks to maximize its customer loyalty scheme and invest in technology to enhance customer experience.</p>
<p>Foot Locker expects a sales drawdown of up to 8% for the year compared to its previous expectation of between 3.5% and 5.5%.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the company announced a new chief finance officer. Incoming Foot Locker finance chief, and former Kohl’s Corp executive, Mike Baughn, will assume the position of EVP and CFO on June 12th.</p>
<h2>Retail Sector Feeling the Economic Strain</h2>
<p>Foot Locker’s underwhelming quarterly report might not augur well for other players in the retail sector ahead of their own earnings reports.</p>
<p>Although Bank of America analysts identified better sales than expected from retailers, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/walmart/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Walmart</a> (NYSE: WMT) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/target/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Target </a>(NYSE: TGT), 45% of the retail sector has yet to report earnings. Furthermore, analysts pointed out that the brand strength of the retailers that posted commendable results was an influencing factor. In other words, other upcoming names not nearly as high-quality in recognition might not fare as well.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britain-semiconductor-chips-1-2b/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/foot-locker-q1-2023-results/">Foot Locker Posts Q1 2023 Results, Sees Stock Sink 25% on Sales Drop</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Britain Joins Semiconductor Chips Race, Introduces $1.2B Plan</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/britain-semiconductor-chips-1-2b/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britain-semiconductor-chips-1-2b/">Britain Joins Semiconductor Chips Race, Introduces $1.2B Plan</a></p>
<p>The British government has undertaken a focused approach in revamping its semiconductor industry and will capitalize on its strengths such as designing and producing non-silicon chips, and intellectual property rights. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britain-semiconductor-chips-1-2b/">Britain Joins Semiconductor Chips Race, Introduces $1.2B Plan</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britain-semiconductor-chips-1-2b/">Britain Joins Semiconductor Chips Race, Introduces $1.2B Plan</a></p>
<p>On Friday, May 19, Great Britain announced support of £1 billion ($1.2 billion) for its semiconductor industry. With this move, the United Kingdom joins the race with the US and EU to boost its domestic chipmaking capabilities and reduce its dependence on foreign players.</p>
<p>The investment is part of the country&#8217;s 20-year strategy for semiconductors, after facing lengthy delays in the past. Furthermore, it also outlines UK&#8217;s plan to secure its chip supplies as well as protect against other national security risks.</p>
<p>The strategy revealed on Friday, includes a range of measures which will offer a boost to Britain&#8217;s domestic chip sector. Additionally, it will also provide national security while mitigating the risk of supply chain disruptions. Also, with this move, the UK plans to increase cooperation with international partners.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, the UK struck a deal with Japan to boost the collaboration between the two nations for semiconductors and defense. Over the next two years between 2023-2025, the British government plans to invest £200 million and expand its commitment to £1 billion over the span of the next decade.</p>
<p>The funding will also help in improving the talent pipeline along with offering access to prototyping, tools, as well as business support. Speaking on the development, British Prime Minister Rishi Sunak <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/19/britain-launches-1point2-billion-of-support-for-semiconductor-industry.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> in a statement:</p>
<div>
<blockquote><p>“Semiconductors underpin the devices we use every day and will be crucial to advancing the technologies of tomorrow. Our new strategy focuses our efforts on where our strengths lie, in areas like research and design, so we can build our competitive edge on the global stage. By increasing the capabilities and resilience of our world-leading semiconductor industry, we will grow our economy, create new jobs and stay at the forefront of new technological breakthroughs.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Capitalizing on Their Expertise</h2>
<p>The UK has established an advisory panel comprising industry, government, and academia figures to collaborate on shared solutions and implementation. Instead of taking the route of mega-spending commitments as in the case of the US and EU, the UK shall take a different approach to boost the areas where its expertise lies.</p>
<p>The UK has no plans to build massive semiconductor plants like the ones created by Taiwan’s chipmaking giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TSMC</a>. Instead, it will focus on other parts of the semiconductor industry such as designing and producing non-silicon chips, and intellectual property rights.</p>
<p>The UK was to release its semiconductor strategy last year, however, it faced a series of delays amid the political instability in the country. On the other hand, the US and the EU have been already pledging billions of dollars.</p>
<p>Britain is a key player in the global chip market, focusing on design, intellectual property, research, and advanced compound semiconductor fabrication. It possesses valuable semiconductor assets, including the highly sought-after chip designer Arm, which is based in Cambridge and licenses chips used in approximately 95% of the world&#8217;s smartphones. Additionally, the country has made significant contributions to the development of ultra-thin semiconductor wafers using graphene.</p>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opera-integration-multiversx-mobile-desktop/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/britain-semiconductor-chips-1-2b/">Britain Joins Semiconductor Chips Race, Introduces $1.2B Plan</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opera Browser Finalizes Integration of MultiversX on Mobile and Desktop Platforms</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/opera-integration-multiversx-mobile-desktop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Muchoki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[egld]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google chrome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[internet explorer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft edge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mozilla firefox]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MultiversX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opera]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[safari]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opera-integration-multiversx-mobile-desktop/">Opera Browser Finalizes Integration of MultiversX on Mobile and Desktop Platforms</a></p>
<p>The integration helps Opera users navigate the Web3 industry through MultiversX with the help of EGLD coins.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opera-integration-multiversx-mobile-desktop/">Opera Browser Finalizes Integration of MultiversX on Mobile and Desktop Platforms</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opera-integration-multiversx-mobile-desktop/">Opera Browser Finalizes Integration of MultiversX on Mobile and Desktop Platforms</a></p>
<p>The Opera browser, one of the leading internet browsers with more than 300 million users across its mobile and desktop platforms, has announced a successful integration with MultiversX (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/elrond-egld/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">EGLD</a>), a metaverse-centric blockchain formerly known as Elrond. Following the integration, Opera users can download the configuration via a dedicated link to enable the access of features like dedicated wallpapers, and speed dials for quick access to essential MultiversX sites. The integration of the Opera browser with MultiversX will enhance the future growth prospects of both platforms. Furthermore, it is a seamless mainstream adoption of Web3 by Web2 users.</p>
<p>With the integration, Opera users can seamlessly interact with MultiversX digital assets including EGLD, ESDT tokens, and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>. Moreover, Opera users can easily browse the decentralized applications available on the MultiversX blockchain. According to market data provided by DefiLlama, the MultiversX blockchain has a total value locked (TVL) of approximately $54.11 million.</p>
<p>Among the top DeFi protocols on the MultiversX blockchains include xExchange, a decentralized exchange with a TVL of about $47 million. Other notable DeFi protocols on the MultiversX network include Proteo DeFi, AshSwap, and QuantumX network.</p>
<p>“There&#8217;s an undeniable advantage in creating a clear and easy pathway to the Web3 world within the quintessential Web2 portal, the browser. This can act as a powerful catalyst for wider adoption and exploration of the MultiversX blockchain ecosystem, while also providing a smooth and intuitive experience for existing users. We&#8217;re excited to be at the forefront of this significant shift, alongside Opera,” <a href="https://multiversx.com/blog/opera-multiversx-complete-integration" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> Beniamin Mincu, MultiversX CEO.</p>
<h2>MultiversX Market Outlook</h2>
<p>The MultiversX network is expected to significantly benefit from the integration of Opera amid huge competition in the blockchain industry. Ranked 51 by its total market capitalization, MultiversX (EGLD) had a total market capitalization of approximately $940 million on Friday and a 24-hour trading volume of about $13 million.</p>
<p>According to on-chain data provided by egldscan, MultiversX had total addresses of 2,242,304 with about 3,197 validators. The price of EGLD traded around $36.93, up approximately 2.3 percent in the past 24 hours. Moreover, the EGLD has a low token supply of about 31.4 million coins compared to most meme coins that count trillions of coins.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the EGLD coin is far from its ATH, around $545.64, down more than 93 percent according to market data provided by Coingecko.</p>
<p>The proof-of-stake network can deal with huge on-chain demand by enabling real-time splitting and merging of shards.</p>
<h2>Closer Look at Opera</h2>
<p>Opera browser is competing with the likes of Google Chrome, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a>&#8216;s Safari, Microsoft Edge, Mozilla Firefox, and Internet Explorer. Nevertheless, Opera has managed to remain among the top five most used browsers with the introduction of Opera One. Notably, Opera One is well-redesigned to engage with emerging technologies like artificial intelligence (AI).</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-uk-banking-license-england/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/opera-integration-multiversx-mobile-desktop/">Opera Browser Finalizes Integration of MultiversX on Mobile and Desktop Platforms</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolut UK Banking License Application Faces Rejection by Bank of England</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-uk-banking-license-england/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revolut]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-uk-banking-license-england/">Revolut UK Banking License Application Faces Rejection by Bank of England</a></p>
<p>Amid financial scrutiny, UK fintech giant Revolut faces rejection for its long-running banking license application. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-uk-banking-license-england/">Revolut UK Banking License Application Faces Rejection by Bank of England</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-uk-banking-license-england/">Revolut UK Banking License Application Faces Rejection by Bank of England</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/revolut/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Revolut</a> is facing a <a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2023/05/18/bank-england-reject-revoluts-bid-banking-licence/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">possible rejection</a> of its UK banking license application submitted to the Bank of England (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-england/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BoE</a>). The British neobank’s long-standing application for a UK banking license appears to be in jeopardy and could cause a big blow to the company’s operational growth plans. Revolut has been campaigning for a license for two years, with high-ranking executives recently confident about approval this year. Although the BoE declined to comment on the rejection reports, some believe Revolut’s financial shape could have been a factor. The leading fintech’s finances have been scrutinized this year after its auditor doubted 2021 revenue figures.</p>
<p>The Telegraph, citing inside sources, reported that the Prudential Regulation Authority (PRA) demanded certain obligations from Revolut in view of license approval. Obligations include producing accounts with unqualified audit opinions and simplifying their share structure. In March, the PRA, the BoE’s licensing arm, had also revealed to the government, plans to issue a statutory warning.</p>
<p>However, the PRA has yet to serve Revolut with the license more than seven weeks after the announcement. Meanwhile, some reports say Revolut is in urgent talks behind the scenes to salvage its license application.</p>
<h2>Failure to Secure UK License Would Not Impact Existing Revolut Services but Could Hurt the Bottom Line</h2>
<p>Although missing out on a UK license would not impact Revolut’s existing services, the neobank would be unable to offer more traditional services. Services off-limits include offering mortgages and loans to customers in the UK that could potentially drive up Revolut’s bottom line.</p>
<p>Revolut has yet to comment on the BoE’s move, with a spokesperson explaining the company does not address ongoing licensing applications. Despite some reports suggesting the London-based neobank might throw in the towel, others claim Revolut could continue pursuing a UK license.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, Revolut CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/nikolay-storonsky/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nikolay Storonsky</a> said the license issuance delay was due to the effects of the ongoing US banking crisis. According to the chief executive, the Silicon Valley Bank-triggered financial meltdown spooked regulators and increased paranoia in the industry.</p>
<h2>Revolut</h2>
<p>Revolut is a financial “super app” that launched in 2015 and offers a wide range of services to customers. These include current accounts, payments, digital currency trading, and overseas spending.</p>
<p>Founded by Storonsky and Vlad Yatsenko, the fintech has become one of the most valuable of its kind in the world. In addition, Revolut leveraged an aggressive global expansive scheme to become Britain’s most valuable tech start-up.</p>
<p>The explosive popularity of digital currencies in the last few years also precipitated Revolut’s initial success. In 2021, crypto trading accounted for a third of the London-based neobank’s revenue. However, the bear phase that characterized much of last year saw crypto trading sink to less than 10% of Revolut’s revenue.</p>
<p>Amid its licensing blues, Revolut has sustained numerous other challenges, including the recent exit of CFO Mikko Salovaara. Salovaara quit the company in early May for personal reasons over two years after joining in January 2021. His entry into Revolut coincided with the company’s submission of its license application.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/revolut-uk-banking-license-england/">Revolut UK Banking License Application Faces Rejection by Bank of England</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ibm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
<p>With increasing concern over data leaks, AI tool makers are working to assure concerned users that their data is safe.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/apple-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apple</a> has <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-restricts-use-of-chatgpt-joining-other-companies-wary-of-leaks-d44d7d34" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">banned</a> the use of the AI tool ChatGPT among its employees in a bid to prevent data breaches and leaks. This was reported by the Wall Street Journal, which cited an internal memo from the company.</p>
<h2>Apple and Other Companies Are Concerned about Data Safety</h2>
<p>The restriction makes Apple one of several businesses that are limiting the use of the software by some of its workers. The release said that the reason for this is that the iPhone maker believes that workers may inadvertently upload confidential files to the AI platform. The report said that the restriction introduced by Apple is not limited to ChatGPT but to any other AI platform that could result in any form of data leakage. Some of these are from the coding platform GitHub, which owns a tool called Copilot, and another one from Microsoft.</p>
<p>Since the news broke, Apple has yet to make a public statement in response to inquiries. However, AI analysts are of the opinion that the move to restrict the use of AI platforms by workers stems from the fact that platforms such as ChatGPT warn against the upload of sensitive data by users. Such warnings make sense as all data sent to its database is used to condition their AI models to improve them.</p>
<h2>Samsung Placed Temporary Ban on ChatGPT</h2>
<p>Raising privacy concerns over data, several companies, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan</a>, Bank of America, and Amazon, moved against the use of ChatGPT in January. Another entity that may be considering banning the use of the AI tool is Samsung. Last month, its engineer uploaded sensitive data in a bid to rectify a faulty database. In the meantime, the management of Samsung has placed a temporary restriction on the use of ChatGPT. The tech giant has already begun the development of its own in-house AI platform.</p>
<p>Apart from businesses, governments are also concerned about the threat of data leaks. The Italian government briefly banned the use of ChatGPT, raising issues with the safety of personal data on the platform. It has since changed its position by allowing the company behind ChatGPT, OpenAI, to continue operating in the country after demands by the Italian government were met.</p>
<h2>Private Versions of AI Tools</h2>
<p>With increasing concern over data leaks, AI tool makers are working to assure concerned users that their data is safe. ChatGPT recently released a private version of its tool called incognito mode. This version, according to OpenAI, ensures that uploaded data is not kept permanently in their database. Neither would the prompts be saved longer than necessary for checks to prevent abuse.</p>
<p>Microsoft also announced its work on a private version of its software targeted at companies. The AI version will not use company data in training, the company has assured.</p>
<p>IBM is also working on its private AI tool, as the company announced this month. Watsonx&#8217;s privacy-centered AI would ensure that users have no worries about data leaks.</p>
<p>&#8220;Clients can quickly train and deploy custom AI capabilities across their entire business, all while retaining full control of their data,&#8221; <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ibm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">IBM</a> CEO Arvind Krishna<a href="https://fortune.com/2023/05/09/ibm-watsonx-ai-productivity-data-privacy/" target="_blank"> said</a>.</p>
<p>However, these private versions are expected to be pricey.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/apple-bans-chatgpt-data-leaks/">Apple Bans Use of ChatGPT by Staff, Fearing Data Leaks</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HashKey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hashkey group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255667</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
<p>HashKey Capital emphasized that it plans to direct the investment into Web3 initiatives in order to broaden its crypto exposure.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
<p>Crypto investment company HashKey Group is looking towards leveraging Hong Kong’s digital assets efforts to <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-firm-seeks-funds-1-031450789.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">raise funds</a> at a valuation of over $1 billion to attract potential investors.</p>
<p>The Chinese Special Administrative Region is finalizing digital asset licensing legislation with the goal of becoming a worldwide crypto hub. Hong Kong has been making efforts to promote and regulate the digital asset industry, which could create a favorable environment for firms like HashKey Group.</p>
<p>HashKey is in early talks to raise between $100 million and $200 million, people familiar with the matter said. It is important to note that these details are based on insider information, and the terms of the deal, including the size and valuation, are subject to change as the negotiations progress and are not yet finalized.</p>
<p>Raising funds at a valuation above $1 billion suggests that HashKey Group has achieved significant growth and success in its operations. It also indicates investor confidence in the potential of the crypto industry despite the strains of the past year. It will be interesting to see how HashKey will use the raised funds to contribute to the development of Hong Kong&#8217;s digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, HashKey Capital, the investment arm of HashKey Group, recently <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-capital-fund-500m-web3/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> the closure of its third fund, HashKey FinTech Investment Fund III, which raised a total of $500 million. Notably, Fund III received significant support from institutional investors such as sovereign wealth funds, businesses, and family offices.</p>
<p>HashKey Capital emphasized that it plans to direct the investment into Web3 initiatives in order to broaden its crypto exposure. Additionally, the investment firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-wealth-management-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expanded</a> its business in April by adding wealth management services to its offering directory.</p>
<h2>HashKey Valuation and the Link with Hong Kong’s Crypto Push</h2>
<p>The push to support crypto is steadily gaining traction in Hong Kong. The Chinese government views Hong Kong as a testing ground for longer-term policy, even while banning most forms of crypto-activity on the mainland.</p>
<p>While regulators globally have been navigating the challenges of overseeing the crypto market following the market crash in the past year and notable incidents like the bankruptcy of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>, Hong Kong appears to be taking a more open stance by introducing a licensing framework and expanding access for retail investors.</p>
<p>The news of Hong Kong <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-consultation-paper-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">introducing</a> a new licensing regime for virtual-asset service providers and allowing retail investors to trade major tokens like Bitcoin and Ether showcases the city&#8217;s contrasting approach to regulating the crypto industry compared to regulators in other parts of the world.</p>
<p>By implementing a licensing regime, Hong Kong aims to establish a regulatory framework that promotes transparency, consumer protection, and the integrity of the virtual asset industry.</p>
<p>However, an Hong Kong official has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hong-kong-crypto-businesses-regulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">warned</a> that upcoming crypto regulation will not encourage a relaxed approach despite the city&#8217;s friendly stance on crypto and expanding access for retail investors.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hashkey-funds-1b-valuation/">HashKey Group to Raise Funds at $1B Valuation</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bictoin ordinals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[michael saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microstrategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nft]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255663</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
<p>MicroStrategy’s Michael Saylor recently suggested that Bitcoin Ordinals could immensely benefit the crypto ecosystem. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microstrategy-incorporated/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MicroStrategy Incorporated</a> (NASDAQ: MSTR) co-founder and Executive Chairman <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/michael-saylor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Michael Saylor</a> has discussed his company’s work with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/introduction-to-bitcoin-ordinals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin Ordinals</a>. In a media session, Saylor revealed that his company was exploring how the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a>-backed non-fungible tokens (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFTs</a>) could lead to software innovation. According to the innovative crypto executive, MicroStrategy was interested in assessing the application development potential of Bitcoin Ordinals.</p>
<p>Although Saylor did not expressly state the Ordinal use cases that MicroStrategy looked to tap into, he pointed out inherent Bitcoin blockchain diversity. Suggesting that the protocol of the world’s most prominent crypto is not solely for transactional purposes, the MicroStrategy co-founder explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The whole idea of burning a piece of data on the blockchain opens the door to the possibility that I might burn a digital signature, or I might burn a registration, or I might burn a hash of a document.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Views Bitcoin Ordinals as Instrumental to Mining Success</h2>
<p>At the Bitcoin 2023 in Miami, Saylor stressed that discussions regarding Ordinals are vital to Bitcoin-mining success over the long term. Furthermore, he added that application development that builds on BTC’s functionality could strengthen the token’s widespread adoption.</p>
<p>Saylor explained that the security of most enterprises pales compared to Bitcoin. Furthermore, he added that innovations that deploy Bitcoin and its paraphernalia as an operational factor could tap into a new level of security.</p>
<p>Saylor’s latest comments on Bitcoin Ordinals come on the heels of similar glowing remarks on the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w1PRsS4SyUc&amp;t=1254s" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">PBD Podcast</a>. On last week’s wide-ranging business podcast, the MicroStrategy Chairman described Ordinals as a catalyst for BTC adoption. As Saylor put it at the time:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Every time someone builds an application that’s cool on Bitcoin, like all the Ordinals and inscriptions and whatever that are driving up transaction fees, it is a catalyst.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Although Saylor admitted that Ordinals might have also been deployed for more frivolous reasons, he went against censoring the digital assets. The one-time MicroStrategy CEO described potential censorship of Bitcoin against specific uses as wrong and inconsistent with community values. “I do believe in rules without rulers,” Saylor emphasized.</p>
<h2>Ordinals Explained</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Ordinals, also known as Bitcoin NFTs, is an innovative development quickly gaining popularity among blockchain enthusiasts. Founded by Casey Rodarmor and created on the Bitcoin blockchain, the Ordinals protocol allows users to attach digital content to the smallest divisible unit of 1 Bitcoin (satoshi).</p>
<p>Bitcoin Ordinals differ from traditional NFTs with one distinguishing feature. Ordinals are found on-chain with raw data directly written on the network. On the other hand, NFTs are minted separately as new tokens, with potential files on other protocols.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> announced <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bitcoin-ordinals-nft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">plans to list</a> Bitcoin Ordinals on its NFT marketplace. The exchange has been aggressively expanding its NFT marketplace offerings and sees the Bitcoin NFTs as a worthy inclusion. In addition to onboarding Ordinals at the end of May, Binance would also provide loyalty support for Bitcoin NFT creators. Furthermore, the prominent exchange seeks to open up additional revenue-generating opportunities for said creators.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microstrategy-michael-saylor-bitcoin-ordinals/">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor Says Firm Exploring Use Cases for Bitcoin Ordinals</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[filecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255635</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
<p>Grayscale also noted that it doesn't believe that Filecoin is security and seeks to respond to the SEC staff with a legal basis for their position.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
<p>Earlier this week, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) classified the cryptocurrency <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/filecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Filecoin</a> as a security and even asked asset manager Grayscale to pull up their application for the Grayscale Filecoin Trust. However, Filecoin has rejected the observation from the SEC adding that FIL was not a security. The Filecoin Foundation described the blockchain network as “a decentralized, peer-to-peer network for storing files”.</p>
<h2>Is FIL a Security?</h2>
<p>In an email statement to the crypto news publication CryptoSlate, Filecoin <a href="https://cryptoslate.com/filecoin-foundation-rejects-secs-classification-of-fil-as-security/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Over the last decade, thousands of people around the world have contributed to this open-source project to create a decentralized, efficient, and robust foundation for humanity’s most important information. That includes hundreds of organizations and teams building on the network, thousands of storage providers, and 13,000 Github contributors, building a foundational layer for the next generation of the web.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC action, however, hasn&#8217;t triggered much movement in the Filecoin (FIL) price. As of press time, FIL is trading 1.98% down at a price of $4.46 and a market cap of $1.8 billion.</p>
<h2>SEC and Cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>The US securities regulator has been going hammer and tongs after crypto assets. SEC chair Gary Gensler also stated that almost every other cryptocurrency classifies as a security and thus shall be subject to federal securities laws.</p>
<p>Previously, Grayscale had filed for Form 10 to make the Grayscale Filecoin Trust a reporting company wherein they would quarterly reports as well as annual reports. However, the SEC asked Grayscale to withdraw this application. In its press release, Grayscale <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/en/news-release/2023/05/17/2671509/0/en/Grayscale-Investments-Shares-Update-Regarding-Grayscale-Filecoin-Trust-Registration-Statement-on-Form-10.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;On May 16, 2023, Grayscale received a comment letter from the SEC staff stating its view that the Trust’s underlying asset, FIL, meets the definition of a security under the federal securities laws, and that therefore the Trust appears to meet the definition of an investment company under the Investment Company Act of 1940. The SEC staff requested that Grayscale seek withdrawal of the registration statement promptly.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Grayscale also noted that it doesn&#8217;t believe that Filecoin is security and seeks to respond to the SEC staff with a legal basis for their position. It will be interesting to see what actions the SEC initiates on the decentralized storage platform, Filecoin.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/filecoin-foundation-sec-fil-security/">Filecoin Foundation Lashes Out at SEC for Classifying FIL as Security</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
<p>The letter did not mention a lawsuit, however, Musk threatened to seek legal redress if there is such a need when he first mentioned this violation back in April.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
<p>There appears to be a subtle data war brewing between Twitter Inc and American tech giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> (NASDAQ: MSFT). This claim stems from the <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/18/23729216/twitter-microsoft-api-data-sharing-elon-musk-satya-nadella" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">letter</a> sent by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>’s personal lawyer Alex Spiro to Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella over the misuse of access to social media’s API.</p>
<h2>The Issue at Hand</h2>
<p>The news was first reported by the New York Times which claims that Microsoft has been violating “multiple provisions” of the social media company’s developer agreement for an extended length of time. Twitter is accusing Microsoft of using its data APIs in 8 of its applications including Bing, xBox One, Azure, and Power Platform to mention a few.</p>
<p>Despite this extended usage, the Elon Musk team said appropriate permissions were only sought for two of the products. With Twitter notably adjusting its terms of use such that developers can generally pay for some of its data content, Microsoft pulled away from using the APIs sometime in April this year.</p>
<p>The letter claimed specifically there were “unauthorized uses and purposes” and that Microsoft failed to inform it of “any use case for six of the eight Microsoft Apps that it continued to operate until last month”.</p>
<p>“The Agreement makes clear that Microsoft was obligated to disclose and obtain approval for its intended use case for each Microsoft App, and to notify Twitter of any substantive modification to those use cases,” the letter reads, “Yet Microsoft did not identify any use case for six of the eight Microsoft Apps that it continued to operate until last month.”</p>
<p>The letter, having stated some of the perceived ways in which Microsoft violated its generosity also gave a very specific demand. This demand included a full “compliance audit” on all of the Microsoft apps that utilized Twitter’s data up until the time the support was shut down by the bigger tech giant. Microsoft was given until June 7th to comply with the demands.</p>
<p>The letter did not mention a lawsuit, however, Musk threatened to seek legal redress if there is such a need when he first mentioned this violation back in April.</p>
<h2>Twitter’s Data Abuse: Microsoft Responds</h2>
<p>The claim of Twitter’s data abuse has elucidated a response from Microsoft spokesperson Frank Shaw. In his response, Shaw said;</p>
<p>“Today we heard from a law firm representing Twitter with some questions about our previous use of the free Twitter API. We will review these questions and respond appropriately. We look forward to continuing our long-term partnership with the company.”</p>
<p>Twitter has been pursuing a number of monetization options since the acquisition of the company by Elon Musk was finalized. In the age of ChatGPT’s Large Language Model (LLM) data training, Twitter&#8217;s current adjustment of its terms of use might turn out to be very profitable for it in the long term.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/musk-lawyer-microsoft-twitter/">Elon Musk’s Lawyer Sends Letter to Microsoft CEO due to Abusing Twitter’s Data Access</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt app]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt app ios]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt app]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=255571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
<p>Previously, one of the simplest ways to access OpenAI’s software on a mobile device was to use Microsoft’s Bing app which offers access to ChatGPT. Now, with the app, using the chatbot will be easier and faster.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
<p>OpenAI Inc, a research laboratory that focuses on <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI), has <a href="https://openai.com/blog/introducing-the-chatgpt-app-for-ios" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> the launch of an iOS version of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a> app. According to the company, later, the app will also be available on Android. It will first be rolled out for users in the US, with more countries added in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>As OpenAI has stated, the ChatGPT app is free to use. Its features include synchronizing a user&#8217;s history across devices as well as integration of Whisper – an open-source speech-recognition system that enables voice input. The app is also free from ads. In addition, those who have a subscription to ChatGPT Plus get exclusive access to GPT-4’s capabilities, early access to features and faster response times.</p>
<p>ChatGPT Plus is a special offering that was introduced in February 2023. For as much as $20 per month, it offers upgraded features, such as faster response times, early access to new features and improvements, and the ability to use ChatGPT even during peak times.</p>
<p>The launch of the ChatGPT application is an initiative that has been expected, considering the buzz around the chatbot introduced by OpenAI in November 2022. Initially, the chatbot was a kind of an experiment. However, its popularity surged, with ChatGPT&#8217;s user base rapidly expanding. Currently, ChatGPT has over 100 million users. The ChatGPT website generates 1.8 billion visitors per month. Notably, this number has been achieved within a three-month period from February to April 2023. Due to such growth, the need for the ChatGPT app has been obvious.</p>
<p>Previously, one of the simplest ways to access OpenAI’s software on a mobile device was to use Microsoft’s Bing app which offers access to ChatGPT. Now, with the app, using the chatbot will be easier and faster.</p>
<p>According to the ChatGPT team, the app will be upgraded based on user feedback, with more features coming later.</p>
<p>The first rumours about OpenAI launching the ChatGPT application appeared back in February. There were also reports about the company working on new software that would create videos with the help of artificial intelligence. Earlier this week, we also <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-openai-open-source-ai-model/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> about ChatGPT preparing to release a new open-source language model.</p>
<h2>ChatGPT Leaving Rivals Behind</h2>
<p>The mobile ChatGPT app comes at a time when big tech players, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/google/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google LLC</a> and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms Inc</a> (NASDAQ: META), are experimenting with artificial intelligence. For example, Google is integrating AI capabilities into its search engine. Its Bard uses Google’s own LaMDA language model. Launched in 2021, Google LaMDA is considered to be one of the biggest competitors of ChatGPT. LaMDA has the ability to comprehend complex inquiries and discussions that span a wide range of subjects, it has been honed with the use of 1.56 trillion words and a whopping 137 billion parameters.</p>
<p>With more research into AI taking place, many bet on ChatGPT, saying that it wins over its competitors. The key advantages offered by ChatGPT are options for free and paid access, as well as collecting user feedback in order to improve the chatbot&#8217;s functionality. As a result, ChatGPT has secured a significant competitive advantage in the AI market, leaving competitors struggling to keep up.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/netflix-stock-jumps-ad-tier/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/chatgpt-app-ios-openai/">ChatGPT App for iOS Is Live, OpenAI Planning to Launch Android Version</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4509 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1289723 metric#prefetches=203 metric#store-reads=21 metric#store-writes=14 metric#store-hits=209 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=99.82 metric#ms-cache=6.15 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.1808 metric#ms-cache-ratio=6.2 -->