<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:26:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai classifier]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI classifier shutdown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[open ai classifier]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai chatgpt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
<p>The link leading to the tool is no longer functioning. However, OpenAI has promised to come up with other detection tools that users can trust. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
<p>OpenAI, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/artificial-intelligence-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) research laboratory and creator of a renowned AI chatbot <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/everything-you-need-to-know-about-chatgpt-ai-chatbot/#:~:text=What%20Is%20ChatGPT%3F,the%20field%20of%20artificial%20intelligence." target="_blank" rel="noopener">ChatGPT</a>, has quietly shut down its AI detection tool – AI Classifier. The suspension of the tool has been a result of a low rate of accuracy. As OpenAI has said, its team has been working towards incorporating feedback and is currently looking for more effective solutions.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://openai.com/blog/new-ai-classifier-for-indicating-ai-written-text" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">blog post</a> that has been initially released to introduce AI Classifier has now been updated with the following:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As of July 20, 2023, the AI classifier is no longer available due to its low rate of accuracy. We are working to incorporate feedback and are currently researching more effective provenance techniques for text, and have made a commitment to develop and deploy mechanisms that enable users to understand if audio or visual content is AI-generated.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>It turns out that the accuracy of the tool has been below what was expected. As OpenAI has revealed, its team evaluated a &#8220;challenge set&#8221; of English texts where the classifier correctly identified 26% of AI-written text as &#8220;likely AI-written&#8221;, while incorrectly labeling human-written text as AI-written 9% of the time. Notably, the tool was unreliable when working with texts with fewer than 1,000 characters. The longer the text was, the higher the accuracy could be. Thus, OpenAI referred to AI Classifier as a &#8220;not fully reliable&#8221; detection tool.</p>
<p>The link leading to the tool is no longer functioning. However, OpenAI has promised to come up with other detection tools that users can trust.</p>
<h2>Can AI Transform the Education Sector?</h2>
<p>Initially, AI Classifier was intended for educators who could use the tool to check on the integrity of students using the chatbot to write essays.</p>
<p>OpenAI said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We recognize that identifying AI-written text has been an important point of discussion among educators, and equally important is recognizing the limits and impacts of AI-generated text classifiers in the classroom.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>AI Classifier was seen as a resource to help educators, journalists, and researchers study misinformation. Thus, shutting down the detector has come as a downer for educators worldwide who have been struggling to identify AI-generated content.</p>
<p>In general, the development of AI has had an impact on every industry, solutions it provides have also started transforming education. AI solutions for education analyze enormous data sets using sophisticated algorithms, providing personalized and adaptable learning experiences. Students get personalized learning, prompt feedback, and access to immersive technologies like augmented and virtual reality in education. All this promotes independent learning and revolutionizes the way of studying. However, AI in education poses a few risks.</p>
<p>Firstly, there is a lack of human interaction and emotional support that students receive when using AI-powered educational tools. AI can personalized learning and instant feedback, but it can not replace the human and emotional support that students need to succeed.</p>
<p>Secondly, there are privacy concerns as AI systems might need to collect specific data about the identity of students or staff, which threatens their online identity and private information.</p>
<p>Further, AI might take out the thinking power of students and make them more dependent on technology instead of learning how to do things themselves.</p>
<p>As of 2023, AI in the education market is set to have an annual growth rate of about 36% from nowadays to 2030 with projected revenue of $32.27 billion.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/">OpenAI Shuts Down Its AI Detection Tool Due to Low Accuracy</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/openai-shuts-down-ai-detection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[openai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sam altman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wld]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264385</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
<p>During the token's launch, the circulating supply was limited to 143 million tokens, with 43 million of the asset reserved for early adopters and 100 million provided as loans to non-US market makers.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
<p>The highly anticipated crypto token, Worldcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/worldcoin/">WLD</a>), co-founded by OpenAI&#8217;s CEO Sam Altman, made a splash on its first day of trading as investors rushed to be part of the artificial intelligence (AI) hype. WLD&#8217;s value skyrocketed from its initial price of $1.70 to a high of $3.58 before settling at $2.52, according to CoinMarketCap data. Trading volume reached nearly $350 million on various exchanges, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-bybit-okx-worldcoin-wld/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">including</a> Binance, Bybit, and OKX.</p>
<p>Worldcoin&#8217;s impressive surge coincided with the release of its whitepaper, shedding light on the token&#8217;s tokenomics and underlying principles. According to the document, the total supply of WLD tokens is capped at 10 billion for the first 15 years of the network&#8217;s existence. After this period, voters may decide to introduce a 1.5% inflation rate.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin Not Available to Users Globally</h2>
<p>According to a Decrypt <a href="https://decrypt.co/149865/worldcoin-tokenomics-at-launch-supply-market-maker-loans" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, concerns have been raised over the discrepancy between the total supply of 10 billion tokens and the initial circulating supply of 106 million WLD tokens, valued at around $219 million. Industry experts, such as Tom Dunleavy, the founder of Alethia, have expressed concerns, pointing out that projects with similar tokenomics have been susceptible to quick sell-offs.</p>
<p>&#8220;Most tokens that have a small amount of distribution or a large fully diluted valuation have shown themselves to be easy targets for quick sell-offs. The history of airdrops, in general, has not been favorable,&#8221; said Dunleavy.</p>
<p>Worldcoin aims to establish itself as a financial and identity network, offering an app for payments and utilizing biometric data from &#8220;shiny, metal orbs&#8221; to create unique World IDs. This approach has sparked controversy, raising concerns over privacy and the availability of the whitepaper.</p>
<p>The report also disclosed that the whitepaper was not accessible in the US and UK but was available in Colombia, despite the ability for users to verify their identity in multiple regions. The lack of accessibility has led to further scrutiny.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin Launch Relies on Market Maker Loans</h2>
<p>During the token&#8217;s launch, the circulating supply was limited to 143 million tokens, with 43 million of the asset reserved for early adopters and 100 million provided as loans to non-US market makers. These loans have a three-month duration and allow market makers to buy WLD tokens instead of returning them.</p>
<p>The agreement with market makers has received mixed reactions. Sadettin Kerim, a digital assets product manager at Yapı Kredi, believes it offers them an advantage, allowing them to manipulate prices.</p>
<p>&#8220;The agreement is an absolute win for market makers. If they do not face a huge market demand, they will easily dip the price and then buy it back. It&#8217;s easy money for them,&#8221; Kerim told Decrypt.</p>
<p>Conversely, Dunleavy considers it speculative in the medium to long term, with no incentives for market makers after the three months.</p>
<h2>75% Worldcoin Token to be Distributed among the Community</h2>
<p>The whitepaper also outlined the allocation of WLD tokens, with 75% going to the Worldcoin community over time. The rest is divided among the initial development team, investors, and a reserve of 170 million WLD. The allocation to insiders increased to 25% due to the complexities and costs of developing and launching the network, as stated in the revised whitepaper.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bruno Faviero, co-founder and CEO of Magna, a token distribution platform, finds the low circulating supply, mainly in loans, difficult to gauge in terms of community response.</p>
<p>Despite the challenges and controversies surrounding Worldcoin, the project managed to verify the identities of more than 2 million people in 35 countries using biometric data. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that while World ID verification is available worldwide, WLD trading is restricted in the US and other territories.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/">Worldcoin Unveils Its Whitepaper Stirring Concerns Over Token Supply</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/worldcoin-whitepaper-token-supply/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xrp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
<p>Despite the surge in the crypto market, Ripple's legal victory does not guarantee smooth sailing for XRP or the broader altcoin sector.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP</a>, the digital currency associated with Ripple Labs Inc, has emerged as an unlikely white knight, turning the tides against its regulation concerns and reinvigorating the entire market.</p>
<h2>Long Drawn XRP Regulation Woes</h2>
<p>For years, XRP and Ripple Labs were subjected to intense regulatory scrutiny, with the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) claiming that the digital asset should be categorized as a security.</p>
<p>This classification would have subjected Ripple Labs to strenuous rules and potentially resulted in the delisting of XRP from key exchanges. However, earlier this month, the tide reversed in favor of the embattled cryptocurrency. The presiding US judge, Analisa Torres decided in favor of Ripple, ruling that XRP sales on public exchanges did not violate securities regulations.</p>
<p>Following the favorable ruling, XRP has <a href="https://www.aol.com/news/cryptoverse-ripple-effect-explosive-xrp-051511819.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reportedly</a> experienced an astounding 78% price increase. Such a rapid surge not only caught the attention of investors and traders but also positioned XRP as one of the best-performing digital assets in recent times.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-4th-largest-crypto-victory/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">surge</a> also led to a remarkable increase in XRP’s market capitalization, which soared to $36 billion from $25 billion, indicating a newfound sense of trust and belief in the asset’s potential. Moreover, XRP’s market share within the broader crypto market also witnessed a notable boost, climbing from 2% to 3.5%.</p>
<p>While this might seem modest at first glance, one must consider the vastness of the crypto market, where even a slight shift in market share represents billions of dollars in value.</p>
<p>The significance of Ripple’s victory cannot be overstated, as it has set a strong legal precedent for other altcoins and raised hopes that they too may be exempt from being classified as tightly-regulated securities. The verdict has inspired confidence among market participants, as indicated by the significant increase in the value of altcoins.</p>
<p>According to CoinGecko, the market cap of altcoins has risen to $665.2 billion from $636.38 billion prior to the ruling. This substantial increase reflects the renewed investor interest and confidence in these alternative digital assets.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Bitcoin, often considered a commodity rather than a security, also experienced a surge in value, reaching a 13-month high following the ruling. However, it is essential to note that Bitcoin’s price has retraced below the $30,000 mark at the time of writing.</p>
<h2>Looking Ahead amidst Challenges</h2>
<p>Despite the surge in the crypto market, Ripple&#8217;s legal victory does not guarantee smooth sailing for XRP or the broader altcoin sector. The regulatory landscape remains <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bank-of-america-ripple-sec-ruling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">uncertain</a>, and challenges persist, potentially impacting the future trajectory of these digital assets.</p>
<p>One significant hurdle is the possibility of the SEC appealing the recent ruling. Legal experts suggest that the SEC may not accept the court’s decision and could seek further legal recourse. An appeal would extend the period of uncertainty surrounding the XRP regulation status and could lead to fluctuations in its price and market sentiment.</p>
<p>Adding to the challenges, the rise of competitors such as stablecoins has provided alternative options for users seeking stability and utility in the crypto space. This increased competition may have affected XRP’s position in the market and its adoption for various use cases.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/">XRP Becomes White Knight of Crypto, Thwarts Regulation Woes</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/xrp-crypto-regulation-woes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin volatility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc price forecast]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264353</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
<p>The implied volatility levels mean that derivatives traders do not see any major price shake-ups happening in the interim.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
<p>Crypto options exchange Deribit may have reasons to believe that the near future holds some positives for Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/standard-chartered-bitcoin-btc-2024/">BTC</a>). This follows after the exchange&#8217;s Bitcoin volatility index recently reached its lowest level since 2021.</p>
<p>The index is a measure of the degree of fear that crypto users have in Bitcoin. And by a larger effect, may also indicate an absence of price volatility for <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a> in the near future.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Volatility Index Suggests a Near-Steady Next 30 Days for BTC Price</h2>
<p>DVOL is the Deribit Implied Volatility Index. It tracks the degree of volatility that is expected of a crypto asset over the next 30 days. In other words, the index shows how confident or negative investors are about a crypto&#8217;s price turbulence.</p>
<p>As earlier mentioned, the current implied volatility level is Deribit&#8217;s lowest since launching in 2021. However, it is also the lowest level in crypto&#8217;s entire history, according to the DVOL algorithm.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the crypto derivatives analytics platform Greeks Live has also shared a similar index. On Monday, July 24, Greeks Live <a href="https://twitter.com/GreeksLive/status/1683488907097264128?t=4oxZ6uSfL78HFKqlNfEcSw&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a> that the volatility index for both Bitcoin and Ether (ETH) combined has fallen to 37%. This represents a multi-year low, according to the platform. The analytics firm also explained further that continued low liquidity has severely affected implied volatility (IV) levels for Bitcoin. It wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is an indisputable fact that the overall volatility of cryptocurrencies is declining, which will inevitably force the implied volatility of cryptocurrencies to keep going to new lows.”</p></blockquote>
<p>By implication, the implied volatility levels mean that derivatives traders do not see any major price shake-ups happening in the interim. And there is also the belief that crypto markets may not see any major activity, at least, for the next few months.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, crypto markets appear to have been in a restful state since mid-March. Its total capitalization goes back and forth around the $1.2 trillion mark and there has been little to no significant change from this level.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/">Bitcoin Volatility Index Hits All-Time Low on Deribit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-volatility-index-deribit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsmc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264382</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
<p>According to Taiwan’s official Central News Agency, “the rapid growth of the artificial intelligence (AI) market has driven a surge in demand for TSMC’s advanced packaging.”</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tsmc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">TSMC</a> is intensifying its efforts towards AI with its latest plan to invest $2.9 billion in an advanced chip packaging plant in Taiwan. The semiconductor manufacturing company wants to capitalize on the trending AI buzz after recently noting the high demand for AI chips. Earlier in the month, TSMC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-sales-ai-tools-chips/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> higher sales than expected amid increased demand for AI tools and applications. Bloomberg calculations revealed that the company’s Q2 sales for June were NT$156.4 billion. Meanwhile, analysts’ expectation was NT$476.2 billion. Like TSMC, global chipmakers are looking to take advantage of the AI boom.</p>
<h2>TSMC to Invest in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant amid AI Boom</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.cna.com.tw/news/afe/202307250038.aspx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Taiwan’s official Central News Agency</a>, “the rapid growth of the artificial intelligence (AI) market has driven a surge in demand for TSMC’s advanced packaging”. The company is responding to the market demand by investing billions of dollars in the plant in Tongluo Science Park, Taiwan. By the side, the investment also creates up to 1,500 local job opportunities. The report added:</p>
<blockquote><p>“ At present, the management authority has officially issued a letter to approve the land lease application of TSMC Tongluo Science Park, and arranged a land lease briefing.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Before now, Goldman Sachs analysts raised their target on TSMC to NT$700, signaling their confidence in the company&#8217;s future performance. Evelyn Yu and Bruce Lu said they see the semiconductor manufacturer as the “key enabler” among other semi-coverage. The analysts referred to TSMC’s “leadership stance in leading-edge nodes and advanced packaging technology&#8221;.</p>
<p>While presenting the <a href="https://investor.tsmc.com/english/encrypt/files/encrypt_file/qr/phase4_reports/2023-07/2e2a9800157e3792623694196d1d71504313c375/2Q23ManagementReport.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Q2 earnings report</a>, C.C. Wei, the CEO of TSMC, spoke about the company’s performance with AI. He revealed that TSMC is recording solid demand for AI and noted that it has no problem in supporting the front-end part. However, the manufacturer is experiencing “some very tight capacity” on the advanced packaging side. Notably, the packaging stage is one of the final steps in semiconductor production. This is when the chips are placed in protective cases, creating connections needed for electronic devices.</p>
<p>Furthermore, fingers are crossed on if chip-related equipment manufacturers will benefit from the TSMC investment in an advanced chip packaging plant in Taiwan. The Central News Agency said the market is optimistic that the likes of Xinyun, Wanrun, and Hongsu will benefit from the operation of equipment factories.</p>
<p>TSMC recorded its first profit decline since 2019 during the second quarter. This is because companies that stockpiled during the pandemic are now struggling with excess processors as customers cut down on electronics expenses.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/">TSMC to Capitalize on AI Boom with $2.9B Investment in Advanced Chip Packaging Plant</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tsmc-ai-2-9b-investment-chip/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Babafemi Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264180</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
<p>The rebranding of Twitter as X is part of Musk’s vision to create an “everything app” like WeChat.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>

<p>The price of meme token Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) soared to its highest in recent times following a surprise announcement by Twitter owner Elon Musk. Musk triggered the surge when he announced plans to change the Twitter name to X. DOGE surged by 10% in the past 24 hours, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to CoinGecko data</a>.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin’s Rise in Popularity</h2>
<p>Dogecoin was created in 2013 as an internet meme token. Dogecoin’s popularity has grown over the years, thanks to its loyal fan base and celebrity endorsements, including from <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>.</p>
<p>Musk has always been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin, calling it the future of currency. In April, Musk replaced the Twitter logo with the Dogecoin logo briefly and sparked a 30% spike in the price of the asset. He also teased the possibility of DOGE payments for Twitter’s premium service subscription.</p>
<p>Because it has no real utility, experts warn that dogecoin is highly volatile and risky and that investors should be cautious before buying it. Should X allow DOGE as a means of payment, everything about the token could change.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Speculations Fanned by Musk</h2>
<p>Given Musk’s history with the meme token, it didn’t take long for the Twitter rebrand announcement to fuel speculations about DOGE. Since the token is already accepted as a form of payment at Tesla, analysts believe X could also do the same.</p>
<p>Real Vision CEO Raoul Pal said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“He will use crypto to be able to make global payments for creators, etc. My guess is he uses Doge.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>“The speculation is that advertisers could be able to pay DOGE for ads and for other uses on Twitter,” Kryptomon Chief Marketing Officer Tomer Nuni explained.</p>
<p>To broaden the speculation, some users pointed out the X and D in Elon Musk’s profile location. They conclude that while the X refers to the Twitter rebrand, the D could be a reference to Dogecoin. Notably, much of the speculative moves are happening on UpBit, which is known for attracting speculative plays.</p>
<h2>Twitter to Morph into an Everything App</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/twitter-risks-logo-letter-x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the rebranding of Twitter as X</a> is part of Musk’s vision to create an “everything app” like WeChat. The app is expected to offer various services such as audio, video, messaging, payments, and banking.</p>
<p>According to Twitter CEO Linda Yaccarino, users should expect more features and innovations with the rebrand to X. She noted that the company was “just getting started”.</p>
<p>Already, Musk has purchased the X.com domain, which now redirects to Twitter. He has also asked Twitter users to submit their logo suggestions.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/">Dogecoin Price Surges after Elon Musk Rebrands Twitter to X</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/dogecoin-price-twitter-x/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock asia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
<p>The changes in BlackRock's Asia-Pacific team come amid the SEC's decision on the future of the company’s spot Bitcoin ETF. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
<p>Investment management corporation <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock Inc</a> (NYSE: BLK) has made two important appointments within its expansion in Asia. In particular, the company has hired Mandy Lui as head of Greater China Wealth and Dennis Quah as head of Singapore Wealth.</p>
<p>Mandy Lui will be in charge of relationships with distributors throughout Hong Kong, Taiwan, and offshore China. Starting from the middle of August, former Baring Asset Management&#8217;s head of wealth and retail distribution will build strategic relationships with key distributors and ensure that BlackRock’s clients in the regions mentioned have access to the full range of investment capabilities.</p>
<p>As for Dennis Quah, he will be responsible for building relationships with consumer banks, private banks, and insurers, as well as helping in building client portfolios together with relevant specialists throughout the firm. Notably, Dennis Quah has twenty years of experience in asset management distribution. Previously, he worked for Columbia Threadneedle, Amundi, OCBC Bank, and Schroders.</p>
<p>James Raby, BlackRock’s Apac head of wealth, <a href="https://fundselectorasia.com/blackrock-hires-duo-to-build-out-greater-china-singapore-offering/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">commented</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are delighted to welcome leaders like Mandy and Dennis to the firm. Their deep local market understanding and expertise in helping clients build whole portfolios are highly valuable as we serve the new and evolving needs of our investors in this current market environment.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Speaking further of the two appointments, it is also worth mentioning another shift in BlackRock’s Asia-Pacific team. Earlier this year, Nicholas Chiu left the company. He was the co-manager of the BlackRock GF China Fund, the BlackRock GF Asian Dragon Fund, the BlackRock GF China Flexible Equity Fund, and the BlackRock Asia Fund.</p>
<p>With headquarters in New York, BlackRock has as many as 78 offices in 36 countries. The firm had approximately $8.59 trillion in assets in management as of December 31, 2022. In the first quarter of 2023, this number soared to $9.09 trillion. Within the next five years, BlackRock’s assets under management are set to exceed $15 trillion. With expansion into Asian markets, this is a milestone possible to achieve.</p>
<h2>BlackRock Waiting for Bitcoin ETF Approval</h2>
<p>The changes in BlackRock&#8217;s Asia-Pacific team come amid the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>&#8216;s decision on the future of the company’s spot Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) ETF. Over the past decade, the SEC has rejected as many as 30 spot Bitcoin ETF applications from big-name companies, but many anticipate the approval of BlackRock&#8217;s application. If approved, it will be the first Bitcoin ETF in the United States. And if it happens, as much as $30 trillion worth of capital could be made available to the Bitcoin market.</p>
<p>Joshua Chu, group chief risk officer at blockchain technology group XBE, Coinllectibles and Marvion, said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p data-testid="paragraph-5">&#8220;The fact that BlackRock, a well-respected and established asset management company, has filed for a Bitcoin ETF could be seen as a positive development in the quest for regulatory approval. It also shows resilience of the public&#8217;s interest in crypto.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p data-testid="paragraph-5">If approved, the new iShares Bitcoin Trust will be listed on the Nasdaq exchange. The pricing will be based on the CF CME Bitcoin Reference Rate. All shares in the ETF will be fully backed by BTC, and no new shares can be issued without delivery of the corresponding value of tokens.</p>
<p><a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/">BlackRock Expands Presence in Asia amid Its Bitcoin ETF Approval</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/blackrock-asia-bitcoin-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mercy Tukiya Mutanya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[linda yaccarino]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x platform]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264335</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
<p>As part of an overall rebranding of the app, Elon Musk announced that Twitter was changing its name to X and that the popular bird would be replaced by an “X” logo.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
<p>Elon Musk’s social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter, appears to be gearing up to make a foray into the world of cryptocurrencies. Amidst the looming possibility of an “X Coin”, Twitter Payments LLC has recently <a href="https://twitter.com/asunapg/status/1683448384437342208">obtained licenses</a> from several states that would permit it to process crypto payments.</p>
<p>This comes following reports in January that the social media giant was looking to diversify its revenue streams and launch an “everything app” whose features would include support for fiat and potentially cryptocurrency payments. The news of potential crypto integration drove the price of the dog-themed memecoin Dogecoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/dogecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DOGE</a>) to soar 7%.</p>
<p>The idea of crypto payments on the social media app has also been subject to criticism. Critics have raised concerns such as the question of regulatory approval, a valid concern given the increased regulatory scrutiny on cryptocurrency payments, especially in the United States. Technology costs and gaining the public’s trust were also presented as potential hurdles.</p>
<p>While Musk, a known Dogecoin supporter, has not explicitly named the coin the future currency of the “everything app,” the online Dogecoin community continues to speculate that he could. What is certain, in light of the recently obtained licenses, is that the company is still considering the possibility of crypto payments.</p>
<p>As part of an overall rebranding of the app, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a> announced that Twitter was changing its name to X and that the popular bird would be replaced by an “X” logo. The rebranding exercise is part of Musk’s attempts to diversify revenue streams and keep the company afloat amid declining ad revenue, which he had previously revealed had suffered a 50% blow. An integration of crypto payments could give X an edge over competitors such as Meta’s recently-launched Threads.</p>
<p>Commenting on the name change, the platform’s newly-appointed CEO Linda Yaccarino <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/07/24/tech/twitter-rebrands-x-elon-musk-hnk-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">stated</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s an exceptionally rare thing – in life or in business – that you get a second chance to make another big impression. Twitter made one massive impression and changed the way we communicate. Now, X will go further, transforming the global town square.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/technology/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tech news</a> on our website.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/">Elon Musk’s X Social Media Platform Eyes Crypto Payments</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-platform-crypto-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arkham intel exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[daniel shin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[do kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terraform]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ustc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264311</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
<p>The submission by two "on-chain sleuths" includes evidence of wallets owned by Kwon and Terra. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
<p>On Monday, July 24, Arkham Intel Exchange, a platform aimed at “deanonymizing the blockchain”, accepted the first submission for information on wallet addresses linked to Terraform Labs and its co-founder Do Kwon.</p>
<p>In a recent announcement on July 24, Arkham Intel Exchange disclosed that it received a submission from two &#8220;on-chain sleuths&#8221;. As a result, the platform rewarded them with a bounty payment of 9,519.2625 Arkham (ARKM), which is approximately $5,000 as per the current value. The announcement <a href="https://twitter.com/ErgoBTC/status/1683558237537435648" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reads</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Arkham Intel Exchange now has its first approved submission: new evidence of wallets owned by Do Kwon / Terraform Labs. An anonymous on-chain sleuth and @ErgoBTC were the successful bounty hunters.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The submission included evidence of wallets owned by Kwon and Terra. Ergo, one of the sleuths associated with OXT Research, stated that this information could potentially contradict public statements from Terra about holding only one Luna Foundation Guard wallet, which has 313 <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoins</a> as reserves.</p>
<p>Introduced earlier this month on July 10, Arkham received criticism from various members of the crypto community, who view it as nothing more than a glorified snitching service. The company enables users to offer bounties for information on blockchain transactions. These bounties later go public 90 days after approval on Arkham. As a result, any information regarding the Kwon and Terra wallet addresses may be accessible around late October.</p>
<h2>Developments in Terra Case</h2>
<p>Terra faced significant controversy during the 2022 crypto market crash when its algorithmic stablecoin, TerraClassicUSD (USTC), deviated from its peg to the US dollar. Kwon&#8217;s whereabouts remained unknown from May 2022 until March 2023 when he was arrested and later sentenced to four months in prison in Montenegro for using forged travel documents.</p>
<p>In South Korea, individuals connected to Terra are currently under investigation by local authorities regarding the exchange. Co-founder Shin Hyun-seong, also known as Daniel Shin, reportedly had his <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/terra-co-founder-daniel-shin-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">first hearing</a> in July for charges related to allegedly making illicit profits from the sale of LUNA tokens.</p>
<p>According to allegations, Daniel Shin, a co-founder of Terraform Labs alongside Do Kwon, reportedly sold approximately $118 million worth of LUNA tokens before the token&#8217;s crash in May 2022. Shin faces accusations of employing similar strategies to profit from investor funds at Chai Corporation, a fintech company he founded after leaving Terraform Labs.</p>
<p>Shin&#8217;s defense has denied that he “sold Luna at a high point and realized profits or that he made profits through other illegal methods”.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/">Arkham Intel Exchange Has Its First Approval on Wallets Belonging to Terra and Do Kwon</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/arkham-wallets-terra-do-kwon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng 'CZ' Zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=264318</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>The legal troubles continue to mount for Binance, as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) also filed a lawsuit against the exchange and CZ in June.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
<p>Renowned crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and its CEO <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/changpeng-zhao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao</a>, have announced intentions to file a motion to dismiss a lawsuit brought against it by the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/">CFTC</a>).</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.ilnd.431767/gov.uscourts.ilnd.431767.53.0_1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filing</a> submitted to an Illinois District Court, Binance and Zhao, and former Chief Compliance Officer Samuel Lim announced their intention to file two separate motions to dismiss the CFTC’s complaint before July 27.</p>
<p>The CFTC’s Complaint filed in March outlines a litany of allegations against Binance and its key executives. It accuses the crypto exchange of facilitating illegal crypto derivatives trading activities within the United States. According to the CFTC, Binance allowed US residents to access and trade crypto derivatives without proper registration, which contravenes the regulatory requirements set forth by the Commodity Exchange Act.</p>
<p>With the deadline for their response to the complaint approaching on July 27, 2023, the defendants are formulating their <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-cz-cftc-complaint/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">defense strategies</a>. Accordingly, the Foreign Binance Entities and CZ, who are named in the action, there’s a plan to file a combined motion to dismiss the CFTC&#8217;s Complaint.</p>
<p>In contrast, Lim is prepared to file a second motion to dismiss the complaint. However, Lim also plans to align certain aspects of his motion with the arguments presented in the motion filed by the Foreign Binance Entities and Zhao. This suggests that the defendants may work together on certain aspects of their defense.</p>
<p>Additionally, Binance requested the court’s permission to exceed the standard 15-page limit for its brief, which will be utilized to support the exchange’s motion to dismiss the CFTC’s lawsuit. Binance argues that the complexity of the CFTC’s lawsuit warrants a more extensive submission of up to 50 pages to adequately present its defense.</p>
<h2>Binance’s Ongoing Lawsuits with US Regulators</h2>
<p>The legal troubles continue to mount for Binance, as the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) also filed a lawsuit against the exchange and CZ in June. The SEC’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">complaint</a> spans a range of serious allegations against Binance and its CEO.</p>
<p>The regulatory body claims that Binance sold unregistered securities, a violation of securities regulations. Also, the SEC claims that Binance permitted US clients to access and use its worldwide platform despite not being authorized to do so. This accusation aligns with the CFTC’s lawsuit, which also contended that Binance permitted US residents to engage in prohibited activities on its platform.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the SEC accuses CZ of misusing customer funds, although specific details about the alleged misuse have not been disclosed yet. This allegation, if proven, could have significant consequences for the exchange and the CEO, potentially resulting in legal penalties and possibly reputational damage.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance is grappling with yet another legal challenge as the US Department of Justice (DOJ) reportedly launches an investigation. The investigation is <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-400m-zhao-trading-firm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">centered</a> around allegations that Binance allowed Russian nationals to use its platform, which could be in violation of US sanctions.<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/microsoft-bing-chat-chrome-safari/" rel="prev">next</a></p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/">Binance and Its CEO to Seek Dismissal of CFTC Lawsuit</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-ceo-dismissal-cftc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4311 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.1 metric#bytes=1098798 metric#prefetches=213 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=219 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=104.33 metric#ms-cache=5.57 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2785 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.3 -->