<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<atom:link href="https://coingape.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<description>CoinGape - 24*7 Crypto Updates</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 20:12:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/14183030/cropped-CoinGape_logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>CoinGape</title>
	<link>https://coingape.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top Crypto Instagram Accounts In 2023; Here Are Top Crypto Influencers To Follow</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/top-crypto-instagram-accounts-in-2023-here-are-top-crypto-influencers-to-follow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nishant Shukla]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 23:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto influencer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[instagram]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130779</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Finding the appropriate people to enlighten you on subjects like cryptocurrency can be difficult. One of the most widely used social media sites today, Instagram is also quickly developing into the hub of a thriving cryptocurrency ecosystem.  If you are a crypto enthusiast and seeking some knowledge in the world of cryptocurrency. Here we have <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/top-crypto-instagram-accounts-in-2023-here-are-top-crypto-influencers-to-follow/" title="Top Crypto Instagram Accounts In 2023; Here Are Top Crypto Influencers To Follow"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/top-crypto-instagram-accounts-in-2023-here-are-top-crypto-influencers-to-follow/">Top Crypto Instagram Accounts In 2023; Here Are Top Crypto Influencers To Follow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10213934/altcoins14.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Crypto influencer" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>Finding the appropriate people to enlighten you on subjects like cryptocurrency can be difficult. One of the most widely used social media sites today, Instagram is also quickly developing into the hub of a thriving cryptocurrency ecosystem.  If you are a crypto enthusiast and seeking some knowledge in the world of cryptocurrency. Here we have prepared a list of the top 10 crypto influencers who will surely clear your doubts, clarify the concepts, make investment recommendations, and update you on industry news.</p>
<h3><b>What Is a Crypto Influencer?</b></h3>
<p>The popularity of social media and growing interest in cryptocurrencies made it possible for crypto influencers to give regular accounts of the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/cryptocurrency-market/">cryptocurrency market</a>. A cryptocurrency influencer can be somebody with years of expertise investing in cryptocurrencies who posts content pertinent to cryptocurrencies and the decentralized economy on the Internet to inform and educate others.</p>
<p>Crypto influencers are essential in popularising cryptocurrencies and other related concepts like blockchain, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and the metaverse. For the purpose of reaching their target audience and educating people about cryptocurrencies, they publish information on a variety of social media platforms, including Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and LinkedIn.</p>
<p>Crypto influencers talk about weekly developments, their most recent investments, and predictions for the state of crypto marketing in the future. The digital economy is extremely volatile, though, so an influencer&#8217;s prediction could be inaccurate. It&#8217;s crucial to take a crypto trader&#8217;s recommendations with a grain of salt as a content consumer.</p>
<p>To all your crypto enthusiasts, here is a list of the top 10 crypto influencers to follow on Instagram.</p>
<h2><b>Robert Kiyosaki</b></h2>
<p>The best-selling author of the finance book Rich Dad, Poor Dad was unable to resist the pull of cryptocurrency investing. <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki" rel="nofollow">Robert Kiyosaki</a>, a well-known celebrity, started supporting decentralised finance in the early 2020s. Kiyosaki informs people about the importance of investing in cryptocurrencies through his Instagram video content, which is rich and relevant. He would occasionally give motivational sayings and quotes. Notably, Kiyosaki has 3M follower on Instagram. The engagement is 2.0071%.</p>
<p>Aside from cryptocurrency, Kiyosaki offers simple advice on how to increase your wealth by prudent saving and maximizing your investment portfolio.</p>
<h2>ShareCrypto</h2>
<p>ShareCrypto is for you if you prefer to read your cryptocurrency news on Instagram. The well-known Instagram account posts the most recent information on the cryptocurrency market in a concise and simple way. This informative account on instagram is followed by 427k people. The engagement on this account is 0.50%</p>
<h2><b>BitBoy Crypto</b></h2>
<p>Crypto enthusiast Ben Armstrong, often known as BitBoy Crypto, has a sizable Instagram following. The producer of the content is committed to disseminating bitcoin news and updates through videos, whether they are uploaded to YouTube or Instagram as vertical videos. Ben has been familiar with cryptocurrencies since 2011, making him one of the most reputable names in bitcoin trading. He wants to keep the public informed about the most recent trends. On his website bitboycrypto, he often contributes news pieces in addition to his daily video uploads. He is unquestionably among the top crypto influencers for staying up to date on new cryptocurrency developments. Bitboy Crypto is followed by 477k people on instagram and the engagement on this account is 0.16%.</p>
<h2><b>CryptoExplorer</b></h2>
<p>CryptoExplorer is Instagram account which runs by an unknown group of cryptocurrency enthusiasts. The account established an followers of over 642,000, thanks to compelling material and a variety of themes affecting the evolution of bitcoin. Their account is a treasure of of information about stocks, market value, and NFTs. The engagement on this account is 0.18%.</p>
<h2><b>Matthias Mende</b></h2>
<p>Matthias Mende, who has over 215,000 Instagram followers and a varied portfolio in both cryptocurrency trading and social media marketing, is one of Dubai&#8217;s top crypto influencers. The businessman is familiar with influencer marketing, having in 2011 run a social media company by the name of MEMMOS.</p>
<p>He started his career in cryptocurrency marketing with Block Gemini, where he held the position of Chief Strategic Officer from 2018 until 2021. Mende started his own blockchain-based platform for celebrity marketing called Bonuz as his interest in cryptocurrencies grew. Mende posts humorous commentary on motivational quotes and explanatory videos regarding cryptocurrencies and blockchain on Instagram. The engagement on his profile is 3.44%.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/top-crypto-instagram-accounts-in-2023-here-are-top-crypto-influencers-to-follow/">Top Crypto Instagram Accounts In 2023; Here Are Top Crypto Influencers To Follow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10213934/altcoins14.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s Ethereum (ETH) Price Analysis For The Coming Week; Buy Now?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/heres-ethereum-eth-price-analysis-for-the-coming-week-buy-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=130850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ethereum(ETH) price resonating within a range has recently revisited the $1300 mark. However, the higher price rejection candles at his barrier indicate a higher probability of price reversal. This bearish turndown may plunge prices to $1225 and extend the current consolidation.  Key points:  The 50-day EMA act as dynamic resistance for the Ethereum price  <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/heres-ethereum-eth-price-analysis-for-the-coming-week-buy-now/" title="Here’s Ethereum (ETH) Price Analysis For The Coming Week; Buy Now?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/heres-ethereum-eth-price-analysis-for-the-coming-week-buy-now/">Here’s Ethereum (ETH) Price Analysis For The Coming Week; Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="ethereum eth" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942.jpeg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-678x381.jpeg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942-150x84.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The <a href="https://coingape.com/crypto-prices-today-major-coins-trading-in-red-ethereum-eth-bitcoin-btc-plummets/">Ethereum(ETH)</a> price resonating within a range has recently revisited the $1300 mark. However, the higher price rejection candles at his barrier indicate a higher probability of price reversal. This bearish turndown may plunge prices to $1225 and extend the current consolidation. </span></p>
<h2><b>Key points: </b></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 50-day EMA act as dynamic resistance for the Ethereum price </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bullish breakout from $1300 will release the trapped bullish for a potential rally</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Ether is $2.8 Billion, indicating a 22.3% loss</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/l/lhKVZds8.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source- </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ethereum price has remained trapped within a narrow range for nearly two weeks. This <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/altcoins/">altcoin</a> has been walking sideways for the past two weeks and tested the horizontal levels of $1300 and $1225. Despite several attempts, the prices struggle to go beyond the mentioned level, indicating a sense of uncertainty in the market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Usually, a consolidation phase following a significant jump recovery offers a short period for prices to sustain higher levels. During this pause, the trades could replenish the bullish momentum for the resumption of the prior recovery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Therefore, the market participants bullish on Ethereum can get an entry opportunity at $1225 support. However, the safe trades may enter the market on a $1300 breakout to complete the range rally on a bullish note.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An upside breakout from the $1300 mark will accelerate the bullish momentum and drive the prices 9% higher at $1420.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, if the overall market remains bearish, a breakdown below $1225 will undermine the recovery sentiment and tumble the altcoin 6% down to $1158.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a nutshell, Ethereum could be a suitable trading opportunity upon range breakout and offer a directional rally.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical Indicator</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>MACD indicator</strong>: the decreasing gap between the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/macd-moving-average-convergence-divergnece/">MACD</a> and the signal line indicates the losing bullish momentum. Moreover, a potential bearish crossover between these slopes fuel in more selling pres in the market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMAs</strong>: the coin price wobbling between the 20-and-50-day EMA gives an extra edge for the range breakout.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethereum Cooin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $1272</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bullish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Medium</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $1300 and $1420</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $1225 and $1154</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/heres-ethereum-eth-price-analysis-for-the-coming-week-buy-now/">Here’s Ethereum (ETH) Price Analysis For The Coming Week; Buy Now?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/28174941/ethereum-1-e1665160126942.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin (BTC) Price Struggle To Surpass $17300 Lead To Deeper Correction?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/markets/will-bitcoin-btc-price-struggle-to-surpass-17300-lead-to-deeper-correction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Bollinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin price prediction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=markets&#038;p=130848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin price remains trapped within a narrow range, setting indecisiveness in the crypto market. However, the daily chart shows reversal signs at the range’s top resistance, which may plunge the prices back to the $16800 mark. Anyhow, is there a way for Bitcoin to end this consolidation? Key points: A potential reversal from $17300 <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/markets/will-bitcoin-btc-price-struggle-to-surpass-17300-lead-to-deeper-correction/" title="Will Bitcoin (BTC) Price Struggle To Surpass $17300 Lead To Deeper Correction?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/will-bitcoin-btc-price-struggle-to-surpass-17300-lead-to-deeper-correction/">Will Bitcoin (BTC) Price Struggle To Surpass $17300 Lead To Deeper Correction?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28131750/bitcoin1.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction BTC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Bitcoin price remains trapped within a <a href="https://coingape.com/markets/bitcoin-ethereum-price-prediction-heres-how-bitcoin-may-escape-ongoing-uncertainty/">narrow range</a>, setting indecisiveness in the crypto market. However, the daily chart shows reversal signs at the range’s top resistance, which may plunge the prices back to the $16800 mark. Anyhow, is there a way for Bitcoin to end this consolidation?</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Key points:</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A potential reversal from $17300 indicates prolonged consolidation in Bitcoin </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 50-day EMA stands as a dynamic resistance to rising prices</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intraday trading volume in Bitcoin is $12.7 Billion, indicating a 12% drop</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img decoding="async" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/snapshots/a/aRYRJbm1.png" alt="TradingView Chart" />Source-</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tradingview</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past two weeks, the Bitcoin price has been strictly moving within two horizontal $17300 and $16800, indicating an evident range-bound rally. After a massive inflow on November 8th, the coin price rebounded from the $16800 support and hit the $17300 resistance in one strike.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the buyers still struggle to escape this range, indicating the sellers continue to defend the higher levels. The higher price rejection candles at the $16800 barrier accentuate a high possibility of a bearish reversal.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus, this reversal set the Bitcoin price to tumble 2% to revisit $16800 support, suffering the ongoing consolidation will extend for a few more sessions.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the trades will need a breakout from the aforementioned range barriers to initiate a directional rally and possible targets.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Will Bitcoin price prolong its downfall?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A recent tweet from the on-chain data provider, glassnode, accentuates the realized loss by Bitcoin investors. The data shows the investor has realized over the last 365 days but also highlights a yearly Profit of $455B realized in the 2020-21 bull.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Over the last 365-days, a total of $213B in Realized Loss has been locked in by <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> investors.</p>
<p>This compares to yearly Profits of $455B realized in the 2020-21 bull.</p>
<p>This reflects a relative capital loss of ~47% of the bull market gains, similar in scale to the 2018 cycle. <a href="https://t.co/y5jaSWEZ83">pic.twitter.com/y5jaSWEZ83</a></p>
<p>&mdash; glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1600666899255529472?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 8, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Surprisingly, this capital loss of 47% bull market gains is similar to the scale of the 2018 cycle. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, these losses indicate weakness in holders&#8217; confidence which lean the market sentiment toward a selling motive.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Anyhow, will the market repeat history and trigger a rally like 2019, is a bit early to tell.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Technical investor:</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Relative Strength Index:</strong> the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/rsi-relative-strength-index/">RSI indicator(49.8%)</a> reflects the speed and magnitude of the coin’s recent price, indicating a neutral outlook from market participants.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>EMAs:</strong> the downloading EMAs(50 and 100) suggest an overall downtrend and give sellers an upper hand.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Price Intraday Levels</span></h2>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spot rate: $17154</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trend: Bullish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Volatility: Medium</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resistance levels- $17300 and $15700</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Support levels- $16800 and $15700</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/markets/will-bitcoin-btc-price-struggle-to-surpass-17300-lead-to-deeper-correction/">Will Bitcoin (BTC) Price Struggle To Surpass $17300 Lead To Deeper Correction?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/28131750/bitcoin1.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Even SBF Made Crisis Couldn&#8217;t Shock Bitcoin Long Term Holders</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-even-sbf-crisis-couldnt-shock-long-term-holders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Drop]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130844</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Price News: Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) led collapse of the FTX can be termed as the most damaging event in the history of Digital assets. With the FTX contagion spread, several crypto lending platforms and exchanges felt the heat of it. However, a report suggests that Bitcoin long term holders stood in solidarity amid the <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-even-sbf-crisis-couldnt-shock-long-term-holders/" title="Even SBF Made Crisis Couldn&#8217;t Shock Bitcoin Long Term Holders"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-even-sbf-crisis-couldnt-shock-long-term-holders/">Even SBF Made Crisis Couldn&#8217;t Shock Bitcoin Long Term Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10171726/bitcoin2.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Prices Today Bitcoin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Bitcoin Price News:</strong> Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) led <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/is-ftx-crash-an-end-of-crypto-how-this-debacle-unfolded/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">collapse of the FTX</a> can be termed as the most damaging event in the history of Digital assets. With the FTX contagion spread, several crypto lending platforms and exchanges felt the heat of it. However, a report suggests that Bitcoin long term holders stood in solidarity amid the crash.</p>
<h2>Are bitcoin holders strong?</h2>
<p>As per a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-November-2022.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report by ARK Invest</a>, despite increased volatility in the crypto market due FTX collapse the supply held by Bitcoin long term holders closed flat for the month of November. Meanwhile, net outflows from the crypto exchanges touched a time high (ATH).</p>
<p>Data depicts that Bitcoin price dropped by over 16% in the month of November. <a href="https://coingape.com/nasdaqs-next-move-affect-bitcoin-btc-price-in-the-short-term/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin price shrunk</a> under the investor cost basis which stands at $17,860. However, Bitcoin price closed at the $17,100 level.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin price dropped to a 2 year low due to FTX filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy Bitcoin long term holders stood strong. The report mentions that the total long term holder supply stabilized at 13.8 million Bitcoin. It is near to its all time high record.</p>
<h2>Cathie Wood on SBF led crackdown?</h2>
<p>Over this Cathie Wood, CEO of ARK Invest commented that the<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/CathieDWood/status/1601779274192605185" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> Bitcoin blockchain didn’t skip a beat</a> during the crisis. She added that SBF didn’t like Bitcoin as it&#8217;s transparent and decentralized. Wood claimed that SBF couldn’t control it.</p>
<p>Report added that the Bitcoin hash rate was corrected as <a href="https://coingape.com/on-chain-data-bitcoin-miner-capitulation-begins-more-pain-ahead-for-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin miners</a> felt suppressed due to the significant compression in profit margins. The crucial ratio between BTC realized profits and losses reached an all time low (ATL). This marks record breaking capitulation.</p>
<p>However, Bitcoin is trading at an average price of $17,178, at the press time. Bitcoin price is marginally up by 0.18% over the past 24 hours. However, its 24 hour volume stands at $12.8 billion. While BTC market cap stands at around $330.3 billion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-even-sbf-crisis-couldnt-shock-long-term-holders/">Even SBF Made Crisis Couldn&#8217;t Shock Bitcoin Long Term Holders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10171726/bitcoin2.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Binance Refutes 3Commas Hack Concerns Over Big Altcoin Buys</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/binance-3commas-hack-altcoin-news/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 12:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130845</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance 3Commas Hack News: While it is an encouraging sign for altcoins, the latest big buys on Binance was a point of concern for the crypto community. This is due to concerns over a potential Binance hack with the 3Commas API leak. However, the crypto exchange said it does not appear to be a case <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/binance-3commas-hack-altcoin-news/" title="Breaking: Binance Refutes 3Commas Hack Concerns Over Big Altcoin Buys"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-3commas-hack-altcoin-news/">Breaking: Binance Refutes 3Commas Hack Concerns Over Big Altcoin Buys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="649" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/29110026/paused-min.png" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="binance crypto exchange" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/29110026/paused-min.png 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/29110026/paused-min-300x162.png 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/29110026/paused-min-768x415.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p><strong>Binance 3Commas Hack News</strong>: While it is an encouraging sign for altcoins, the latest big buys on <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/binance/">Binance</a> was a point of concern for the crypto community. This is due to concerns over a potential Binance hack with the 3Commas API leak. However, the crypto exchange said it does not appear to be a case of hack of compromise of assets. Stating that &#8220;funds are SAFU,&#8221; the team said it was probing the related accounts for taking action if any required.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/twitter-influencer-fatman-secretly-linked-sbf-over-fuding-cryptocurrency/">Was Twitter Influencer “FatMan” Secretly Linked To SBF For Attacking This Crypto?</a></p>
<h2>Binance Account Exploit Through 3Commas API?</h2>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Hey guys. Unfortunately two days ago my Binance account got exploited through an API which I’ve created 2 years ago and haven’t used since which I assumed I deleted but apparently didn’t. It was used to make trades on low cap coins to push up the price to make profit.</p>
<p>&mdash; CoinMamba (@coinmamba) <a href="https://twitter.com/coinmamba/status/1600986997493231621?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 8, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>On Friday, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/coinmamba/status/1600986997493231621" rel="nofollow">Coin Mamba</a>, a crypto trader, claimed his 3Commas API was used to trade low cap altcoins and manipulate prices. Claiming that he had submitted the API only on the 3Commas platform, he warned users against having the cryptocurrencies on the Binance account. Meanwhile, it was reported on Sunday that certain altcoins saw trades in abnormally huge prices. <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1601750779156910080" rel="nofollow">Wu Blockchain</a>, the crypto reporter, said the altcoins were stolen by hackers associated with 3Commas platform.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;A large number of altcoins OM / AMP / NEXO / POLS / SUN / ARDR / BIFI / XVS / ARK / LOOM / OSMO were contra traded in Binance. It seems that some users’ API KEY has been stolen by hackers and related to 3Commas.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-under-pressure-as-another-whale-dumps-almost-10k-btc/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">Bitcoin Price Under Pressure As Another Whale Dumps Almost 10K BTC</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Binance team responded to claims of exploitation. The exchange&#8217;s management acknowledged the &#8220;abnormal price movements&#8221; for the cryptocurrencies. Stating that the activity does not seem to be related to any hack, Binance said the funds are actually safe.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This activity does not appear to be due to compromised accounts or stolen API keys; funds are SAFU.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Phishing Attack?</h2>
<p>On the other side, the <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://3commas.io/blog/december-10-update-on-investigation-api-key-exchange-attacks" rel="nofollow">3Commas team</a> said it was working with the Binance team on the issue. It said that old keys not in active use for more than 3 months would be revoked. It suggested that the incident could likely be a phishing case.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-warns-fed-hike-rate-will-amplify-recession/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">Elon Musk Warns Fed Rate Hike Will Amplify Recession</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance CEO CZ said the abnormal trades were only a result of &#8220;market behavior.&#8221; He said others followed accumulating after a trader deposited funds and began purchasing the altcoins. However, the crypto exchange said it had temporarily locked withdrawals on the accounts registering profits, following complaints on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/binance-3commas-hack-altcoin-news/">Breaking: Binance Refutes 3Commas Hack Concerns Over Big Altcoin Buys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/29110026/paused-min.png" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alameda&#8217;s Ex-CEO Caroline Ellison Hires Former SEC Official As Lawyer In FTX Probe</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/alamedas-ceo-caroline-ellison-hires-former-sec-official-as-lawyer-ftx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 19:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In connection with the ongoing investigation into the catastrophic failure of the cryptocurrency exchange FTX and its trading firm Alameda Research, the ex-CEO of Alameda, Caroline Ellison, has reached out to a former official of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to represent as her lawyer. Lawyer A Top Crypto Cop? Stephanie Avakian, a former <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/alamedas-ceo-caroline-ellison-hires-former-sec-official-as-lawyer-ftx/" title="Alameda&#8217;s Ex-CEO Caroline Ellison Hires Former SEC Official As Lawyer In FTX Probe"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/alamedas-ceo-caroline-ellison-hires-former-sec-official-as-lawyer-ftx/">Alameda&#8217;s Ex-CEO Caroline Ellison Hires Former SEC Official As Lawyer In FTX Probe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="2000" height="1333" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/11000709/bankman-fried-girlfriend-comp-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Alameda Caroline Lawyer" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>In connection with the ongoing investigation into the catastrophic failure of the cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> and its trading firm <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/alameda-research/">Alameda Research</a>, the ex-CEO of Alameda, Caroline Ellison, has reached out to a former official of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to represent as her lawyer.</p>
<h2>Lawyer A Top Crypto Cop?</h2>
<p>Stephanie Avakian, a former enforcement division chief at the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sec/">SEC</a>, was also in charge of many of the agency&#8217;s most high-profile <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/">cryptocurrency</a> prosecutions during her tenure over there.</p>
<p>Before joining the Washington DC-based law firm, WilmerHale, in 2020 — Stephanie served as the enforcement director for the SEC for a total of four years, during which she also served as the deputy director.</p>
<p>She shared the role of director with Steve Peikin, who is currently representing <a href="https://coingape.com/breaking-ftx-exchange-files-for-bankruptcy/">FTX in its bankruptcy proceedings</a>. During their time in office, the regulatory body increased the amount of enforcement activity inside the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/sbf-to-be-arrested-during-house-testimony-visit-to-the-us/">SBF To Be Arrested During House Testimony Visit To The U.S.?</a></em></p>
<p>As reported earlier on CoinGape, FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy team, Congress, regulators and <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-illegally-moved-millions-during-bankruptcy/">prosecutors from Manhattan</a> are investigating charges that billions of dollars in customer funds deposited at the exchange ended up being traded by Alameda, which is a Hong Kong-based sibling trading firm of the now defunct FTX empire.</p>
<h2>Stephanie&#8217;s Earlier Cases</h2>
<p>One of the cases that Stephanie reviewed earlier was that of <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ripple-xrp/">Ripple Labs</a>, a blockchain startup whose founders were charged with fraudulently generating $1.3 billion through the sale of unregistered securities backed by digital assets. The legality of crypto assets as securities is still up for discussion in the wake of the 2020 <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-files-final-submission-against-sec-lawyer-says-fighting-for-crypto/">SEC lawsuit</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong></em> <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-sec-holds-no-answers-for-ripples-argument-claims-counsel/"><em>SEC Holds No Answers For Ripple’s Argument, Claims Counsel</em></a></p>
<p>Apart from the cryptocurrency sector, Stephanie was in charge of overseeing enforcement actions taken against General Electric, Robinhood Markets, and Elon Musk, the new owner of Twitter.</p>
<h2>Negotiation In The Making?</h2>
<p><a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sam-bankman-fried/">Sam Bankman-Fried</a>, who founded FTX and served as its previous chief executive officer, has pointed the finger of blame at Alameda in multiple interviews with the media.</p>
<p>In contrast, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.crunchbase.com/person/caroline-ellison-2538" rel="nofollow">Ellison</a> has maintained her silence thus far, lending credence to the notion that she may be negotiating a cooperation agreement with the relevant authorities.</p>
<p><em><strong>Also Read:</strong> <a title="FTX News: Kevin O’Leary Claims He Can’t Call SBF Guilty Unless He’s Tried" href="https://coingape.com/ftx-news-kevin-oleary-claims-he-cant-call-sbf-guilty-unless-hes-tried/" rel="bookmark">Kevin O’Leary Claims He Can’t Call SBF Guilty Unless He’s Tried</a></em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/alamedas-ceo-caroline-ellison-hires-former-sec-official-as-lawyer-ftx/">Alameda&#8217;s Ex-CEO Caroline Ellison Hires Former SEC Official As Lawyer In FTX Probe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/11000709/bankman-fried-girlfriend-comp-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Crypto Network Launches FIFA World Cup 2022&#8217;s Official Metaverse Game</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/fifa-world-cup-official-metaverse-game-hedera-launches-crypto-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fifa world cup 2022]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hedera]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hedera hashgraph]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130833</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the football fever increases with every breath-taking match, an officially licensed FIFA World Cup Qatar 2022 metaverse game has been recently launched on the Hedera network, which is powered by its proprietary hashgraph technology; claimed as blockchain 2.0. FIFA Licensed Web3 Game Reality+ has partnered with OTZ Sports to launch &#8220;Own The Zone&#8221; Web3 <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/fifa-world-cup-official-metaverse-game-hedera-launches-crypto-network/" title="This Crypto Network Launches FIFA World Cup 2022&#8217;s Official Metaverse Game"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/fifa-world-cup-official-metaverse-game-hedera-launches-crypto-network/">This Crypto Network Launches FIFA World Cup 2022&#8217;s Official Metaverse Game</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1600" height="900" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10225713/skysports-world-cup-qatar-2022_5921764-1-1.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="FIFA World Cup 2022 hedera" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>As the football fever increases with every breath-taking match, an officially licensed <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/fifa-world-cup-2022/">FIFA World Cup Qatar 2022</a> metaverse game has been recently launched on the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/hedera-hashgraph/">Hedera network,</a> which is powered by its proprietary hashgraph technology; claimed as blockchain 2.0.</p>
<h2>FIFA Licensed Web3 Game</h2>
<p>Reality+ has partnered with OTZ Sports to launch &#8220;Own The Zone&#8221; Web3 game where fans get a chance to win limited-edition digital collectibles (<a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/nft-non-fungible-token/">NFTs</a>) and also real-world prizes.</p>
<p>On the initial match card, players will receive two of the eight on-pitch zones for free for each match.</p>
<p>After the original game has concluded, actual player activities within player zones will award points, which will all be tracked using the official FIFA live match data. The chances of winning tickets to The Best FIFA Football Awards and £5,000 per match day increase with the number of zones you own in the FIFA Match Day Sweepstake.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong></em> <em><a title="FIFA World Cup 2022: Only Messi Can Save Argentina Fan Token (ARG)?" href="https://coingape.com/fifa-world-cup-2022-argentina-vs-netherlands-messi-fan-token-arg/" rel="bookmark">FIFA World Cup 2022: Only Messi Can Save Argentina Fan Token (ARG)?</a></em></p>
<p>Additionally, Match Card results have an effect on the rarity level of Own The Zone digital collectibles, which are given to all participants as rewards for participating and are identified by various visual combinations to produce a completely unique piece of digital collectibles in the football <a href="https://coingape.com/blog/what-is-metaverse/">metaverse</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today, we’re excited to announce the launch of <a href="https://twitter.com/playOTZ?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@playOTZ</a>, the officially licensed <a href="https://twitter.com/FIFAcom?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FIFAcom</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/WorldCup?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#WorldCup</a> game built by <a href="https://twitter.com/RealityPlusWeb3?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RealityPlusWeb3</a> on the carbon-negative <a href="https://twitter.com/hedera?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Hedera</a> network for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Qatar2022?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Qatar2022</a>  <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3c6.png" alt="🏆" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MetaverseIsHedera?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#MetaverseIsHedera</a> <a href="https://t.co/ZQrkxEyvPk">pic.twitter.com/ZQrkxEyvPk</a></p>
<p>&mdash; HBAR Foundation (@HBAR_foundation) <a href="https://twitter.com/HBAR_foundation/status/1601578250857234433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Hedera&#8217;s Metaverse Push</h2>
<p>Hedera, the carbon-negative network, and the Hedera Token Service (HTS) are the driving forces behind the <a href="https://coingape.com/fifa-world-cup-2022-top-football-fan-tokens-ready-to-skyrocket/">FIFA World Cup 2022</a> licensed metaverse game. The construction of wallets and the minting of coins takes place naturally during the gameplay and registration processes, providing for a seamless transition of sports fans into the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More: </strong><a href="https://coingape.com/hedera-hashgraph-network-processes-207-million-transactions-in-march-with-hbar-gaining-200/">Hedera Hashgraph Processes ATH Transactions, HBAR Surges by 200%</a></em></p>
<p>Alex Russman, who acts as the VP at The <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.hbarfoundation.org/" rel="nofollow">HBAR Foundation</a>, an organization specifically set up to drive user adoption on the Hedera network, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>Own The Zone is not only launching with the world&#8217;s most loved global sports event, FIFA World Cup Qatar 2022, but also showcasing best-in-class technology and gameplay to the world&#8217;s largest fan communities.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Also Read:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/what-led-to-hederas-massive-growth-in-2022/">What Led To Hedera&#8217;s Massive Growth In Q3 of 2022?</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/fifa-world-cup-official-metaverse-game-hedera-launches-crypto-network/">This Crypto Network Launches FIFA World Cup 2022&#8217;s Official Metaverse Game</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10225713/skysports-world-cup-qatar-2022_5921764-1-1.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Was Twitter Influencer &#8220;FatMan&#8221; Secretly Linked To SBF For Attacking This Crypto?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/twitter-influencer-fatman-secretly-linked-sbf-over-fuding-cryptocurrency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pratik Bhuyan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 16:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ftx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sbf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to a report published on Wednesday,  federal prosecutors in the United States are investigating FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried for the manipulation of two cryptocurrencies earlier this year. They have begun an investigation to determine whether or not SBF manipulated the prices of TerraUSD and Luna to benefit FTX and its associate trading firm, Alameda <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/twitter-influencer-fatman-secretly-linked-sbf-over-fuding-cryptocurrency/" title="Was Twitter Influencer &#8220;FatMan&#8221; Secretly Linked To SBF For Attacking This Crypto?"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/twitter-influencer-fatman-secretly-linked-sbf-over-fuding-cryptocurrency/">Was Twitter Influencer &#8220;FatMan&#8221; Secretly Linked To SBF For Attacking This Crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="2048" height="1152" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10210129/skynews-terrence-a-duffy-sam-bankman-fried_5983633.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="fatman sbf" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>According to a report published on Wednesday,  federal prosecutors in the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/united-states/">United States</a> are investigating <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx/">FTX</a> founder Sam Bankman-Fried for the manipulation of two cryptocurrencies earlier this year. They have begun an investigation to determine whether or not SBF manipulated the prices of TerraUSD and Luna to benefit FTX and its associate trading firm, <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/alameda-research/">Alameda Research</a>.</p>
<h2>Was Terra FUD Planned?</h2>
<p>However, there&#8217;s one more aspect to this whole drama. It&#8217;s being alleged that, SBF&#8217;s Alameda possibly hired a Twitter influencer who would later go on to spread lies about the <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/luna/">Terra (LUNA)</a> project and its founder Do Kwon.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">RT: THE FACTS</p>
<p>• SBF/Alameda took down <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24UST&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$UST</a>, federal prosecutors now taking action against them for market manipulation.<br />• FatMan was hired by this group to cover their tracks by spreading disinfo about DK + <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LUNA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$LUNA</a>.</p>
<p>Guess how many will buy <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24LUNA&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$LUNA</a> when everyone learns the truth? <a href="https://t.co/K4H7vDJKEx">pic.twitter.com/K4H7vDJKEx</a></p>
<p>&mdash; <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/269b.png" alt="⚛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 🅻🆄🅽🅲 🅳<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f170.png" alt="🅰" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f17e.png" alt="🅾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/269b.png" alt="⚛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@LUNCDAO) <a href="https://twitter.com/LUNCDAO/status/1601586325215670276?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Going by the Twitter handle @fatmanterra, the profile has repeatedly spoken against the crypto project and about its eventual demise, pinning the faults on <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/do-kwon/">Do Kwon</a> and his team, Terraform Labs. The profile, however, remains anonymous.</p>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a title="Terra Do Kwon, LUNC Community Reacts To Court Rejecting Arrest Warrants" href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-lunc-community-reacts-to-court-rejecting-arrest-warrants/" rel="bookmark">Terra Do Kwon Reacts To Court Rejecting Arrest Warrants</a></em></p>
<p>The pseudonymous &#8220;FatMan&#8221;, first gained prominence when he publicly claimed that he had &#8220;proofs&#8221; of Do Kwon&#8217;s malpractice in the infamous UST depeg.</p>
<h2>FatMan vs Do Kwon</h2>
<p>Although, many claim that his proofs have been debunked by other community members, the profile still sticks to his views and has continually spoken against the Terra founder.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> I&#39;ve been using this account to document the Terra fraud, but there&#39;s a lot of info and it can be hard to parse. Here&#39;s a simple summary thread (linking to past tweets) outlining the key milestones in Do Kwon&#39;s destructive path of fraud &#8211; proving malice, greed, and crime.</p>
<p>&mdash; FatMan (@FatManTerra) <a href="https://twitter.com/FatManTerra/status/1570317225482928134?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 15, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The self-proclaimed &#8220;cryptocurrency &amp; finance researcher&#8221; has even denied the allegations of <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/sbf/">SBF</a> playing a role in the UST debacle of May 2022.</p>
<p>Instead, his latest tweet targets Terraform Labs for dumping their own $450 Million <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ust/">UST</a> into the market &#8212; thus leading to the<a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/cryptocurrency-5/"> cryptocurrency&#8217;s</a> eventual demise.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> New blockchain data reveals the root cause of the May UST depeg. In the 3 weeks leading up to the depeg, one entity dumped over $450m of UST on the open market. 4 days after their last sale, UST started collapsing.</p>
<p>That entity? None other than Terraform Labs. Details inside. <a href="https://t.co/aFfzgpBZ5A">pic.twitter.com/aFfzgpBZ5A</a></p>
<p>&mdash; FatMan (@FatManTerra) <a href="https://twitter.com/FatManTerra/status/1600091474682486784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 6, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Do Kwon Opens Up</h2>
<p>The Terra founder believes that <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/genesis-trading/">Genesis Trading</a> provided around $1 billion in UST to Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Alameda Research before the <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/stablecoins-2/">stablecoin’s</a> depeg in order to carry out the infamous trade.</p>
<p>He further went on to state:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the time has come for GenesisTrading to reveal if they provided the $1B UST shortly before the crash to SBF..The large currency contraction that UST went through in Feb 2021 was started by Alameda. What’s done in darkness will come to light.</p></blockquote>
<p><em><strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://coingape.com/terra-do-kwon-sbf-genesis-terra-luna-crisis/">Do Kwon Explains How SBF And Genesis Led Terra-LUNA Crisis</a></em></p>
<p>In a statement to the <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/12/07/business/ftx-sbf-crypto-market-investigation.html" rel="nofollow">Times</a> on Wednesday, Bankman-Fried said he was not aware of any &#8220;market manipulation&#8221; and definitely never planned to engage in any kind of market manipulation.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/twitter-influencer-fatman-secretly-linked-sbf-over-fuding-cryptocurrency/">Was Twitter Influencer &#8220;FatMan&#8221; Secretly Linked To SBF For Attacking This Crypto?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10210129/skynews-terrence-a-duffy-sam-bankman-fried_5983633.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breaking: Elon Musk Warns Of Suing Twitter Staff Over Confidential Data Leak</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/elon-musk-warns-of-suing-twitter-staff-over-confidential-data-leak/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anvesh Reddy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 14:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk Twitter News: In yet another shocking move, Elon Musk is reportedly threatening to sue Twitter employees who get involved in leaking the company&#8217;s confidential information. In an email to the Twitter staff, he warned against feeding detailed information to the media. Musk is also asking the employees to sign a pledge to confirm <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-warns-of-suing-twitter-staff-over-confidential-data-leak/" title="Breaking: Elon Musk Warns Of Suing Twitter Staff Over Confidential Data Leak"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-warns-of-suing-twitter-staff-over-confidential-data-leak/">Breaking: Elon Musk Warns Of Suing Twitter Staff Over Confidential Data Leak</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09131020/elon-33_1-sixteen_nine.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Elon Musk twitter" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Elon Musk Twitter News</strong>: In yet another shocking move, <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a> is reportedly threatening to sue Twitter employees who get involved in leaking the company&#8217;s confidential information. In an email to the Twitter staff, he warned against feeding detailed information to the media. Musk is also asking the employees to sign a pledge to confirm that they have understood the terms. He said such acts could amount to clearly violating the Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) that employees signed at the time of joining Twitter.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-btc-price-prediction-on-chain-data-indicates-whales-still-selling/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">Bitcoin (BTC) Price Prediction: On-Chain Data Indicates Whales Still Selling</a></p>
<h2>Pledge Against Data Leak</h2>
<p>The Tesla CEO reportedly mentioned in his email about acting against the company&#8217;s interests. He said the various instances of detailed leaks of confidential Twitter information was a clear evidence of it. According to Platformer journalist <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/ZoeSchiffer/status/1601582028100894721" rel="nofollow">Zoë Schiffer</a>, Musk had sent out a clear warning against media leaks. The warning comes after Musk recently reduced the company&#8217;s workforce by several thousands. He also introduced a string of rules around employee performance.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Breaking your word by sending detailed info to the media with the intent to harm Twitter will receive the response it deserves.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Accordingly, Musk is said to have given Twitter employees as deadline until 5 pm at the end of the day on Saturday to respond to his email.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/shiba-inu-coin-8-5-trillion-shib-moved-shib-burn-rate-drops/?utm_source=priceanalysisbar">8.5 Trillion Shiba Inu Moved; SHIB Burn Rate Declines</a></p>
<p>In a recent comment, the billionaire said a potential interest rate hike in the next Fed meeting would only make it worse for chances of recession. The Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) is scheduled to meet next between December 13 and 14, in what will be the last such policy meeting in 2022. <a href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-warns-fed-hike-rate-will-amplify-recession/">Musk&#8217;s comment</a> follows his recent prediction that the recession could drag until 2024.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-illegally-moved-millions-during-bankruptcy/">FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Illegally Moved Millions During Bankruptcy</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/elon-musk-warns-of-suing-twitter-staff-over-confidential-data-leak/">Breaking: Elon Musk Warns Of Suing Twitter Staff Over Confidential Data Leak</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09131020/elon-33_1-sixteen_nine.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawyer Calls SEC An “Innovation Killing Cesspool Of Corruption”</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-lawyer-calls-sec-an-innovation-killing-cesspool-of-corruption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 14:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple (XRP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP vs SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The lawsuit between the US SEC and Ripple is approaching its summary judgment. However, people linked with the case have been facing different kinds of allegations. XRP holders’ lawyer has come out to defend his links with Ripple and its executives. XRP proving to be an alternative? John Deaton, XRP holders’ lawyer in the Ripple <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawyer-calls-sec-an-innovation-killing-cesspool-of-corruption/" title="XRP Lawyer Calls SEC An “Innovation Killing Cesspool Of Corruption”"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawyer-calls-sec-an-innovation-killing-cesspool-of-corruption/">XRP Lawyer Calls SEC An “Innovation Killing Cesspool Of Corruption”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12153537/riple.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="XRP news case Ripple lawsuit XRP lawsuit Ripple Vs SEC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The lawsuit between the US SEC and Ripple is approaching its summary judgment. However, people linked with the case have been facing different kinds of allegations. XRP holders’ lawyer has come out to defend his links with Ripple and its executives.</p>
<h2>XRP proving to be an alternative?</h2>
<p>John Deaton, XRP holders’ lawyer in <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-deadline-whales-move-143-million-xrp/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">the Ripple lawsuit</a> mentioned that he doesn’t argue with the people who say that Ripple helped to create a secondary market by giving the token to people. He added that he doesn’t challenge them as most of the projects have done the same.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bitcoin maximalist Michael Saylor’s recent comments misrepresented the facts and theory. Deaton mentioned that Saylor claimed that Ripple and its executives have committed fraud and the XRP lawsuit against them involves Fraud.</p>
<p>He stated that the media houses like Foxbussines have called him a ‘no Ripple fan boy”.</p>
<p>He added that even if he believes that XRP is a shitcoin or the technology is inferior. However, it has proven to be a better layer 2 solution to the Bitcoin problem.</p>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s approach towards Ripple lawsuit</h2>
<p>XRP lawyer stated that the<a rel='nofollow'  rel="nofollow noopener" href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1601378285086068738" target="_blank"> SEC’s approach toward the crypto</a> and presenting the Ripple lawsuit is absolutely appalling. He called the SEC truly become an innovation killing cesspool of corruption.</p>
<p>He pointed out that after a 30 month long investigation, the commission didn’t charge fraud or even misrepresentation against Ripple or any other executive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawyer-calls-sec-an-innovation-killing-cesspool-of-corruption/">XRP Lawyer Calls SEC An “Innovation Killing Cesspool Of Corruption”</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12153537/riple.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worst Solana Tokens This Week: Chainlink, Terra Classic, Arweave Amongst The Coins That Plunged</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/worst-solana-tokens-this-week-chainlink-terra-classic-arweave-amongst-the-coins-that-plunged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shourya Jha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arweave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130811</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Worst Solana Tokens This Week: The overall prices of crypto tokens have been down today. Following this, the tokens in the Solana chain are also trading in negative. Tether has been in neither nor loss today, as well as in the last 7 days. Solana has dipped by 1.97%. Audius has dropped by 0.51%. Civic <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/worst-solana-tokens-this-week-chainlink-terra-classic-arweave-amongst-the-coins-that-plunged/" title="Worst Solana Tokens This Week: Chainlink, Terra Classic, Arweave Amongst The Coins That Plunged"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/worst-solana-tokens-this-week-chainlink-terra-classic-arweave-amongst-the-coins-that-plunged/">Worst Solana Tokens This Week: Chainlink, Terra Classic, Arweave Amongst The Coins That Plunged</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="900" height="500" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10184754/Solana-Could-Become-The-%E2%80%98Visa-Of-Crypto-Bank-Of-America-Strategist-Says.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Solana Tokens" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Worst Solana Tokens This Week:</strong> The overall prices of crypto <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/token/">tokens</a> have been down today. Following this, the tokens in the Solana chain are also trading in negative.</p>
<p>Tether has been in neither nor loss today, as well as in the last 7 days.</p>
<p>Solana has dipped by 1.97%. Audius has dropped by 0.51%. Civic has decreased by 0.48%.</p>
<h2>Chainlink (LINK)</h2>
<p>With a plunge of 8.06% in the last week, and of 2.56%, Chainlink stands as one of the worst-performing tokens. The <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/market-capitalization/">market cap</a> is at 3.882 billion USD. Trading volume is down by 6.65%. Each token costs 6.85 USD. <img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130815" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10185503/LINK_7D_graph_coinmarketcap-1.jpeg" alt="Worst Tokens This Week: LINK" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Terra Classic (LUNC)</h2>
<p>Terra Classic dips by 0.62% in the last 24 hours. In the week it has been slashed by 4.56%. The market cap is presently at 1.624 billion USD. Trading volume has dipped by 55.51%. Every token is at 0.0001709 USD.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130816" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10185559/LUNC_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-61.jpeg" alt="Worst Tokens This Week: LUNC" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Arweave (AR)</h2>
<p>Arweave plummets by 1.63% today and 3.92% in the week. Each token is selling at 8.98 USD. The market cap is currently at 300.37 million USD. Trading volume has seen a rise of 0.53%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130817" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10185655/AR_7D_graph_coinmarketcap.jpeg" alt="AR" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>As we enter the end of the year, the bearish market is still there. However, analysts think it might start to change as we enter another year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/worst-solana-tokens-this-week-chainlink-terra-classic-arweave-amongst-the-coins-that-plunged/">Worst Solana Tokens This Week: Chainlink, Terra Classic, Arweave Amongst The Coins That Plunged</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10184754/Solana-Could-Become-The-%E2%80%98Visa-Of-Crypto-Bank-Of-America-Strategist-Says.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey Denies Elon Musk’s Allegations Against Twitter</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/jack-dorsey-denies-elon-musks-allegations-against-twitter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Javed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 13:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=130806</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/jack-dorsey-denies-elon-musks-allegations-against-twitter/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10184337/Copy-of-Poster-Image-14.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Jack Dorsey Denies Elon Musk’s Allegations Against Twitter"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/jack-dorsey-denies-elon-musks-allegations-against-twitter/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10184337/Copy-of-Poster-Image-14.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Jack Dorsey Denies Elon Musk’s Allegations Against Twitter"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10184337/Copy-of-Poster-Image-14.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are You Using The World&#8217;s Most Common Passwords?</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/are-you-using-the-worlds-most-common-passwords-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 12:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=130787</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/are-you-using-the-worlds-most-common-passwords-2/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10173624/22222.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Are You Using The World&#8217;s Most Common Passwords?"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/are-you-using-the-worlds-most-common-passwords-2/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10173624/22222.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Are You Using The World&#8217;s Most Common Passwords?"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10173624/22222.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Lawsuit: Ripple, SEC Seeks Deadline; Whales Move 143 Million XRP</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-deadline-whales-move-143-million-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 12:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple vs SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC vs Ripple Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP vs SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130777</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP Lawsuit Updates: The legal battle between the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple is yet to get the most awaited Summary Judgment. However, the latest fillings show that both parties requested the court to set a deadline for sealing the Summary Judgment Materials. Ripple seeks deadline in XRP lawsuit James Filan reported <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-deadline-whales-move-143-million-xrp/" title="XRP Lawsuit: Ripple, SEC Seeks Deadline; Whales Move 143 Million XRP"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-deadline-whales-move-143-million-xrp/">XRP Lawsuit: Ripple, SEC Seeks Deadline; Whales Move 143 Million XRP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/16182409/SEC-VS-RIPPLE.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="SEC RIPPLE XRP Lawsuit xrp news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>XRP Lawsuit Updates:</strong> The legal battle between the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Ripple is yet to get the<a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-sec-holds-no-answers-for-ripples-argument-claims-counsel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> most awaited Summary Judgment</a>. However, the latest fillings show that both parties requested the court to set a deadline for sealing the Summary Judgment Materials.</p>
<h2>Ripple seeks deadline in XRP lawsuit</h2>
<p>James Filan reported that Ripple and the US SEC asked the district court to set a deadline of January 4, 2023, for sealing portions related to the briefs. If not then waive any objections to the court’s ruling on the parties’ sealing application.</p>
<p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/FilanLaw/status/1601295709688381440" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Ripple’s letter mentions</a> that the omnibus motions to seal the Parties are already due to be filed on December 22, 2022. It added that the parties will try to provide notice to all non parties whose confidential discovery documents will appear in the Summary Judgment materials. However, giving clarity regarding the sealing motion will give them an opportunity to redact those materials.</p>
<p>It added that the court earlier approved a similar process for addressing non-party sealing motions in relation to Daubert Motions.</p>
<h2>Are whales on an XRP buying spree?</h2>
<p>WhaleAlert reported that<a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1601365789096833024" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> 143 million XRP tokens</a> (worth approx $55 million) were moved to an unknown wallet. This move landed after both parties filed for deadlines in the XRP lawsuit. However, <a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-275-million-xrp-moved-amid-price-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">XRP prices have surged</a> over the past 30 days. This price jump has come amid the recent decline in the crypto market.</p>
<p>XRP is trading at an average price of $0.387, at the press time. However, its price has dropped by around 2% over the past 24 hours. Its 24 hour trading volume stands at $515 million.</p>
<p>Coingape reported that over<a href="https://coingape.com/xrp-news-over-4-billion-xrp-moved-as-ripple-awaits-summary-judgment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> 4 billion XRP tokens were moved</a> in multiple transactions from the Bittrex crypto exchange.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/xrp-lawsuit-ripple-sec-seeks-deadline-whales-move-143-million-xrp/">XRP Lawsuit: Ripple, SEC Seeks Deadline; Whales Move 143 Million XRP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/16182409/SEC-VS-RIPPLE.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Prices Today: Major Coins Trading In Red; Ethereum (ETH), Bitcoin (BTC) Plummets</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-prices-today-major-coins-trading-in-red-ethereum-eth-bitcoin-btc-plummets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shourya Jha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The major crypto tokens are back to trading in red today. After having a day of green charts and FTT boosting by 44%, the crypto prices has been a major disappointment today. Ethereum has fallen by 1.30%. Bitcoin falls by 0.53%. Pancake Swap plunges by 0.45%. Terra Classic decrease by 0.81%. FTX Token downwards by <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-prices-today-major-coins-trading-in-red-ethereum-eth-bitcoin-btc-plummets/" title="Crypto Prices Today: Major Coins Trading In Red; Ethereum (ETH), Bitcoin (BTC) Plummets"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-prices-today-major-coins-trading-in-red-ethereum-eth-bitcoin-btc-plummets/">Crypto Prices Today: Major Coins Trading In Red; Ethereum (ETH), Bitcoin (BTC) Plummets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10171726/bitcoin2.jpeg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Crypto Prices Today Bitcoin" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p>The major crypto <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/token/">tokens</a> are back to trading in red today. After having a day of green charts and FTT boosting by 44%, the crypto prices has been a major disappointment today.</p>
<p>Ethereum has fallen by 1.30%. Bitcoin falls by 0.53%. Pancake Swap plunges by 0.45%. Terra Classic decrease by 0.81%. FTX Token downwards by 12.02%. Shiba Inu is down by 0.90%.</p>
<p>Hooked Protocol has soared by 17.62%. Axie Infinity is up by 5.95%.</p>
<p>The market cap of global crypto market is currently at 854.08 billion USD, a decrease of 0.85% over the last day. Total market volume has gone down by 17.68% and stands at 31.05 billion USD.</p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>Crypto prices today for Ethereum has gone down by 1.30% and the market cap stands at 154.37 billion USD. Every token costs 1265.97 USD. Trading volume is down by 29.04%. <img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130789" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10172103/ETH_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-5.jpeg" alt="Crypto Prices Today: ETH" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Bitcoin (BTC)</h2>
<p>With a decrease of 0.53%, the market cap is 330.949 billion USD. BTC tokens are selling at 17,167.56 USD. Trading volume has seen a downfall of 17.14%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130790" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10172148/BTC_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-2.jpeg" alt="Crypto Prices Today: BTC" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Terra Classic (LUNC)</h2>
<p>A dip of 0.81% has taken Terra Classic tokens to 0.0001709 USD. The market cap is at 1.330 billion USD. Trading volume has decreased by 54.88%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130791" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10172230/LUNC_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-6.jpeg" alt="LUNC" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>FTX Token (FTT)</h2>
<p>With a massive spike yesterday, FTX Token has plummet by 12.02% and each coin costs 1.64 USD. The market cap is 538.41 million USD. Trading volume has increased by 16.37%.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-130792" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10172323/FTT_1D_graph_coinmarketcap-1.jpeg" alt="FTT" width="1858" height="800" />Source: coinmarketcap</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>It has been a hard year for the crypto prices, as the market had to deal with two major crash. The market still seems to be bearish. As we come closer to the end of the year, the change of year might pull up the prices a bit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-prices-today-major-coins-trading-in-red-ethereum-eth-bitcoin-btc-plummets/">Crypto Prices Today: Major Coins Trading In Red; Ethereum (ETH), Bitcoin (BTC) Plummets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10171726/bitcoin2.jpeg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snoop Dogg, Justin Bieber Face Lawsuit For Promoting BAYC</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/snoop-dogg-justin-bieber-face-lawsuit-for-promoting-bayc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Javed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=130743</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/snoop-dogg-justin-bieber-face-lawsuit-for-promoting-bayc/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10151620/Copy-of-Poster-Image-13.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Snoop Dogg, Justin Bieber Face Lawsuit For Promoting BAYC"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/snoop-dogg-justin-bieber-face-lawsuit-for-promoting-bayc/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10151620/Copy-of-Poster-Image-13.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Snoop Dogg, Justin Bieber Face Lawsuit For Promoting BAYC"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10151620/Copy-of-Poster-Image-13.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUNC News Live Updates Dec 10: Terraform Labs Believes Becoming Independent Can Benefit The Community</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/lunc-news-live-updates-dec-10-terraform-labs-believes-becoming-independent-can-benefit-the-community/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Classic]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LUNC News Updates Dec 10: Terra Classic Community currently votes on Proposal 11030 to separate from Terraform Labs (TFL) and Terra’s co-founder Do Kwon. Terra Classic developer group Terra Rebels to focus on Rebel Station with the proposal and works on Terra Station are managed by TerraCVita, with the help of validator Allnodes and TFL. <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-live-updates-dec-10-terraform-labs-believes-becoming-independent-can-benefit-the-community/" title="LUNC News Live Updates Dec 10: Terraform Labs Believes Becoming Independent Can Benefit The Community"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-live-updates-dec-10-terraform-labs-believes-becoming-independent-can-benefit-the-community/">LUNC News Live Updates Dec 10: Terraform Labs Believes Becoming Independent Can Benefit The Community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="675" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/13131623/LUNA-Shoots-10-After-Luna-Foundation-Raises-1-Billion-to.webp.webp" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Terra Classic lunc" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>LUNC News Updates Dec 10:</strong> Terra Classic Community currently votes on Proposal 11030 to separate from Terraform Labs (TFL) and Terra’s co-founder <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/do-kwon" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Do Kwon</a>. Terra Classic developer group Terra Rebels to focus on Rebel Station with the proposal and works on Terra Station are managed by TerraCVita, with the help of validator Allnodes and TFL.</p>
<p>Terra Classic price is moving sideways with the current price trading at $0.000171. The 24-hour low and high are $0.0001705 and $0.0001730, respectively.</p>
<h1><strong>LUNC News Updates Dec 10:</strong></h1>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/lunc-news-live-updates-dec-10-terraform-labs-believes-becoming-independent-can-benefit-the-community/">LUNC News Live Updates Dec 10: Terraform Labs Believes Becoming Independent Can Benefit The Community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/13131623/LUNA-Shoots-10-After-Luna-Foundation-Raises-1-Billion-to.webp.webp" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter To Auction Office Supplies In January</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/web-stories/twitter-to-set-auction-of-office-supplies-in-january/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Divya Sinha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 10:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?post_type=web-story&#038;p=130764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/twitter-to-set-auction-of-office-supplies-in-january/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10160522/13.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Twitter To Auction Office Supplies In January"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div class="wp-block-web-stories-embed alignnone">
			<a href="https://coingape.com/web-stories/twitter-to-set-auction-of-office-supplies-in-january/">
									<img
						src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10160522/13.jpg"
						width="360"
						height="600"
						alt="Twitter To Auction Office Supplies In January"
																			sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"
												loading="lazy"
						decoding="async"
					/>
								</a>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10160522/13.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Under Pressure As Another Whale Dumps Almost 10K BTC</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-under-pressure-as-another-whale-dumps-almost-10k-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Varinder Singh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 10:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130742</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) price struggles to rally above $17.5k as miners and whales continue to liquidate their BTC positions. The BTC price has failed to show any significant upside move and remains under pressure following the collapse of FTX. Bitcoin Whales Dumping Their BTC Holdings Whale Alert in a tweet on December 10 revealed that a <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-under-pressure-as-another-whale-dumps-almost-10k-btc/" title="Bitcoin Price Under Pressure As Another Whale Dumps Almost 10K BTC"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-under-pressure-as-another-whale-dumps-almost-10k-btc/">Bitcoin Price Under Pressure As Another Whale Dumps Almost 10K BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="676" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin Price Under Pressure As Another Whale Dumps Almost 10K BTC" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" srcset="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933.jpg 1200w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933-768x433.jpg 768w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933-678x381.jpg 678w, https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933-150x85.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /><p>Bitcoin (BTC) price struggles to rally above $17.5k as miners and <a href="https://coingape.com/glossary/whale-accumulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whales</a> continue to liquidate their BTC positions. The BTC price has failed to show any significant upside move and remains under pressure following the collapse of <a href="https://coingape.com/tag/ftx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a>.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Whales Dumping Their BTC Holdings</h2>
<p>Whale Alert in a <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1601295611168538626" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tweet</a> on December 10 revealed that a whale has transferred 9,901 BTC worth $170 million to crypto exchange Kraken.</p>
<p><a rel='nofollow'  href="https://bitinfocharts.com/bitcoin/address/bc1qxv55wuzz4qsfgss3uq2zwg5y88d7qv5hg67d2d" target="_blank" rel="noopener">On-chain data</a> reveals the Bitcoin whale purchased 9,901 BTC for $391.91 million on July 29, 2021. The BTCs remain unmoved since the date and the wallet has no other transactions. The whale has sold the Bitcoin holdings for a loss of $222 million.</p>
<figure id="attachment_130755" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-130755" style="width: 700px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class=" wp-image-130755" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/10150733/Bitcoin-Whales-Holding-1K-100K-BTCs.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Whales Holding 1K-100K BTCs" width="700" height="407" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-130755" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Whales Holding 1K-100K BTCs. Source: Santiment</figcaption></figure>
<p>Analyst <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1600823495981670400" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ali Martinez</a> has also shared that around 33 whales holding 1,000 to 100,000 <span class="link-complex-target">BTCs</span> have left the network. In fact, these whales sold or redistributed around 20,000 <span class="link-complex-target">BTC</span> in the last 96 hours. Now, there are only 2037 wallets holding 1,000 to 100,000 <span class="link-complex-target">BTCs.</span></p>
<p>However, <a rel='nofollow'  href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1600946173564502016" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Santiment</a> on-chain data platform tweeted that the supply of Bitcoin and Ethereum on crypto exchanges are now at a 4-year low. Thus, it indicates a lower sell-off risk.</p>
<p>As reported in a previous article, <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-btc-price-prediction-on-chain-data-indicates-whales-still-selling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">whales are still selling</a> their BTC holdings. Whales continued to reduce their Bitcoin holdings since June 2022 and sold nearly 367k BTC. Moreover, whales with 1k-10k BTC continued to liquidate their Bitcoin holdings during the <a href="https://coingape.com/slow-down-btc-mining-hamper-bitcoins-short-term-price/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">miner capitulation phase</a> until November. Therefore, traders must observe whales increasing their BTC holdings to confirm a Bitcoin rally.</p>
<figure id="attachment_130594" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-130594" style="width: 703px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class=" wp-image-130594" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09140428/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands.webp" alt="Bitcoin Spent Output Value Bands" width="703" height="436" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-130594" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Spent Output Value Bands. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<h2>BTC Price Risks Falling to $12.8K</h2>
<p>Analysts such as <a href="https://coingape.com/popular-analysts-predict-bitcoin-and-ethereum-prices-for-christmas/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Michael van de Poppe and “Wolf of the Wall Street” Jordan Belfort</a> believe Bitcoin can rally if it crosses $18k, suggesting $16.5k as a critical support level. However, the BTC price has failed to pass even $17.3k and on-chain data predicts <a href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-prediction-on-chain-data-analysts-predict-upside-level/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$18k is a strong resistance level</a>.</p>
<p>Moreover, miner capitulation and whales selling their BTC holdings indicate uncertainty. On-chain predicts that BTC price can bottom at $12.8k, the delta price for Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Also Read: <a href="https://coingape.com/ethereum-eth-price-prediction-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum (ETH) Price Key Metric At 4-Year Low Means Turnaround</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/bitcoin-price-under-pressure-as-another-whale-dumps-almost-10k-btc/">Bitcoin Price Under Pressure As Another Whale Dumps Almost 10K BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/12144007/Bitcoin-BTC-price--e1665934088933.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto News Live Updates Dec 10: Elon Musk Warns Fed Rate Hike; Crypto Market Declines</title>
		<link>https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-10-elon-musk-warns-fed-rate-hike-crypto-market-declines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ashish Kumar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 09:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coingape.com/?p=130734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto News Today Live Updates December and Latest News: (10 December 2022) The global digital asset market registered a marginal drop on Saturday. However, the crypto market saw a broad recovery yesterday. The cumulative market cap dropped by 0.54% over the past day. It now stands at $854.7 billion. The 24 hour trading volume is <a class="mh-excerpt-more" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-10-elon-musk-warns-fed-rate-hike-crypto-market-declines/" title="Crypto News Live Updates Dec 10: Elon Musk Warns Fed Rate Hike; Crypto Market Declines"></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-10-elon-musk-warns-fed-rate-hike-crypto-market-declines/">Crypto News Live Updates Dec 10: Elon Musk Warns Fed Rate Hike; Crypto Market Declines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<img width="1200" height="800" src="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/08113612/Bitcoin-BTC-crypto-news.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="Bitcoin BTC crypto news" decoding="async" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" loading="lazy" /><p><strong>Crypto News Today Live Updates December and Latest News: (10 December 2022)</strong> The global digital asset market registered a marginal drop on Saturday. However, the crypto market saw a broad recovery yesterday.</p>
<p>The cumulative market cap dropped by 0.54% over the past day. It now stands at $854.7 billion. The 24 hour trading volume is also down by 15% to stand at $31.8 billion.</p>
<h1>Crypto News Today Live Updates</h1>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com/crypto-news-live-updates-dec-10-elon-musk-warns-fed-rate-hike-crypto-market-declines/">Crypto News Live Updates Dec 10: Elon Musk Warns Fed Rate Hike; Crypto Market Declines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coingape.com">CoinGape</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content medium="image"  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://cdn.coingape.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/08113612/Bitcoin-BTC-crypto-news.jpg" width="460" height="230" />	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
