<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EMAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kim kardashian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
<p>Judge Fitzgerald reject arguments from Kim Kardashian and Paul Pierce's lawyers to dismiss the EMAX class-action lawsuit.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
<p>A California judge has ruled that Reality TV star and businesswoman Kim Kardashian posted false information on social media while promoting EthereumMax (EMAX). The ruling allows the plaintiffs to proceed with the case against the media personality, retired boxer Floyd Mayweather Jr., and NBA Hall of Famer Paul Pierce. Kardashian’s attorneys had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-ethereummax-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">moved to dismiss</a> the suit, claiming there was no evidence investors bought EMAX tokens based on her posts on Instagram.</p>
<p>Los Angeles District Judge Michael Fitzgerald rejected attorneys’ pleas to dismiss the case because Kardashian’s posts online contained “literally false” information. Judge Fitzgerald also said one such post contained misleading information, which suggested that EMAX tokens were scarce.</p>
<p>The judge also rejected similar arguments brought by Pierce’s legal team. However, Mayweather saw some respite as the ruling declared the boxer’s EMAX promotion simply expressed his belief. The judge also said Mayweather’s statements were “quintessential nonactionable puffery”.</p>
<p>Investors had accused the retired boxer of promoting the EMAX tokens at a Bitcoin conference in 2021. Although it was a Bitcoin event, Mayweather and his entourage arrived at the venue donning EMAX t-shirts.</p>
<h2>The Kim Kardashian and Mayweather EMAX Case</h2>
<p>In January last year, investors <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kardashian-mayweather-crypto-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> Kardashian, Pierce, and Mayweather for their involvement in EMAX promotions. According to the class-action suit, the named celebrities promoted EMAX and influenced fans and followers to buy the tokens.</p>
<p>The investors believe Kim Kardashian and other celebrities worked with EMAX to artificially spike the asset’s price. They were allegedly able to do this by deliberately posting “false or misleading statements”.</p>
<p>Between June 2021 and January 2022, EMAX crashed by about 97%. This irked investors who brought the class-action suit as they all believed it was a pump-and-dump scheme. The suit also claimed that the branding as “EthereumMax” was deliberately misleading because the project has no connection with Ethereum.</p>
<p>At the time, an EthereumMax spokesperson refuted the pump-and-dump claim. In an <a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/kim-kardashian-floyd-mayweather-ethereummax-emax-nft-scheme-1282801/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">email statement to RollingStone</a>, the spokesperson said the project is “one of the most transparent and communicative” in the crypto space. The person added that they “look forward to the truth coming out”.</p>
<h2>December’s Tentative Ruling</h2>
<p>Fitzgerald had issued a tentative ruling in favor of Kim Kardashian, Mayweather, and EMAX in December. In the ruling, Fitzgerald admitted that the case brings concerns to light about celebrities influencing “millions of undiscerning followers to buy snake oil with unprecedented ease and reach”. However, he tentatively dismissed the motion regardless. According to him, the plaintiff’s submitted facts were inadequate. Furthermore, Fitzgerald said investors must take necessary precautions before dumping funds into a project regardless of an advertiser’s misconduct. The recent rejection of the motion to dismiss the case is a turnaround from the tentative ruling.</p>
<p>In 2021, the UK’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) had <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-crypto-ad-uk-watchdog/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">criticized</a> Kardashian’s post. She was also fined by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) for failing to reveal the post was a paid advert. Kim Kardashian allegedly settled the case by paying a $1.26 million fine.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/">Kim Kardashian EMAX Case Proceeds as California Judge Rejects Motion to Dismiss</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/kim-kardashian-emax-case-proceeds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
<p>Crypto market prices have tumbled significantly since the news began to make rounds.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Altcoins like </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/solana/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solana</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (SOL), </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cardano</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (ADA), </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/matic-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polygon</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (MATIC) and many other tokens face the possibility of being </span><a href="https://beincrypto.com/robinhood-reviews-token-listings-sec-lawsuits-crypto-exchanges/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">delisted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> from </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/robinhood/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Robinhood Markets Inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: HOOD), after the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) charged Binance and </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinbase Global inc</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (NASDAQ: COIN) for trading unregistered securities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At present, Robinhood is taking another look at the digital assets offerings on its platform to &#8220;determine what, if any, actions to take”, according to Dan Gallagher, a one-time SEC Commissioner and the present Chief Legal Officer at Robinhood.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the lawsuit which was </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">filed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by the SEC against Binance, the regulator categorized BNB, BUSD, SOL, ADA, MATIC, FIL, ATOM, SAND, MANA, ALGO, AXS, and COTI as securities. Coinbase was not </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">left out</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> as the SEC also stated that SOL, ADA, MATIC, FIL, SAND, AXS, CHZ, FLOW, ICP, NEAR, VGX, DASH, and NEXO all fall under the securities class.</span></p>
<h2><b>Robinhood Tokens Scrutiny and Broad Crypto Market Reaction</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These lawsuits were filed simultaneously against the two prominent digital asset service providers. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unfortunately, the broad crypto industry has had to bear the brunt of these enforcement actions. Crypto market prices have </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-btc-crypto-sec-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tumbled</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> significantly since the news began to make rounds. A few hours after SEC indicted Binance, Bitcoin (BTC) price dipped by 5%, Ethereum (ETH) suffered a similar fate, and other altcoins like SOL, ADA, MATIC, and even Dogecoin (DOGE) also fell in terms of price.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dune Analytics data showed that Binance experienced huge outflows of up to $635 million after the lawsuit. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinbase shares value </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-tumble-sec-binance-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">fell</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by 10.3% and by the end of the trading day, it was down by 9%. Considering the huge effect on the crypto market, Edward Moya, a senior market analyst at foreign exchange Oanda mentioned that it was a reflection of investors&#8217; concerns over the U.S. regulatory crackdown on cryptocurrency. Investors have fears that in the long run, many digital assets would be categorized as securities.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, many crypto heavyweights have pledged support for the crypto exchanges against the SEC. Cardano boss Charles Hoskinson urged top crypto industry players to unite to combat the authoritarianism of the SEC and other regulatory agencies. This is not a far cry from what Coinbase was trying to achieve when it filed a lawsuit against SEC requesting that the regulator </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-regulatory-united-states-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">provide</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> clarity in its regulation framework for crypto.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“The SEC is talking out of both sides of its mouth, and it is wrong at each end. The Chair’s statements cannot provide fair notice of the obligations of regulated parties &#8211; that is the function of rulemaking, which Coinbase’s petition requests. But the SEC’s Chair undoubtedly can and does speak authoritatively for the agency he leads in describing its regulatory agenda,” Coinbase stated at the time.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking on the bright side, within the last 48 hours, the top three largest Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs): Uniswap v3 (Ethereum), Uniswap v3 (Arbitrum), and PancakeSwap v3 (BSC) have </span><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-crypto-crackdown-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400;">recorded</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a 444% jump in median trading volume, according to crypto data aggregator CoinGecko.</span></p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/">Robinhood Scrutinizing Tokens Designated as Securities by SEC</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/robinhood-tokens-securities-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ibukun Ogundare]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cftc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gopax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258191</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
<p>While Binance saw the acquisition of Gopax as a means of re-entering South Korea, it was also meant to be a turning point for the local trading platform.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
<p>The SEC’s lawsuit against <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has started affecting the company’s operations, particularly its acquisition of Gopax in South Korea. The US Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">filed</a> a case against Binance for violating securities law. According to the filing with the federal court in Washington, Binance mishandled investors and also misled both investors and regulators. The Commission also alleged that the exchange broke the rules by letting Americans trade in an unsecured and unprotected environment.</p>
<p>The Director of the SEC’s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, wrote in the filing that Zhao and the Binance entities “consciously chose” to flout the rules. He added that the company put its customers and investors at risk to maximize its profits. The SEC executive said Binance engaged in multiple unregistered offerings. Grewal continued, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While at the same time combining the functions of exchanges, brokers, dealers, and clearing agencies, the Binance platforms under Zhao’s control imposed outsized risks and conflicts of interest on investors.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance Faces Challenge with Gopax Acquisition</h2>
<p>Now, the legal case has become a hindrance to the business opportunity Binance has with Gopax. A South Korean <a href="https://m.newspim.com/news/view/20230607000608">report</a> revealed that the Financial Service Committee (FSC), is reviewing the Gopax acquisition by Binance. In light of the SEC allegations, the nation&#8217;s financial watchdog has decided to monitor the case as it progresses. Notably, Binance bought a majority stake in Gopax in February. However, the regulator has postponed the report and acceptance of the business change notification filed by Gopax concerning the Binance deal. The local crypto trading platform filed an executive change report on the 7th of March.</p>
<p>Apart from the US SEC accusations, Binance is also under the radar of the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a> sued the exchange in March for violating trading and derivative trading regulations and evading registration obligations. In addition, the company has a case with the US Prosecutors’ Office and the US Internal Revenue Service for breaching anti-money laundering laws.</p>
<p>The FSC finds it difficult to accept the report due to the alleged accusations from the SEC and further requests to seize all assets belonging to the US arm of Binance. Noting that the SEC trend cannot be dismissed, an FSC official said that “it is cautious to say that the report is being reviewed internally”.</p>
<p>While Binance saw the acquisition of Gopax as a means of re-entering South Korea, it was also meant to be a turning point for the local trading platform. Following the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange in November 2022, Gopax halted withdrawals of principal and interest payments from its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a> service GoFi. Thus, the Binance deal was supposed to reawaken the troubled exchange.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/">South Korea Regulator Delays Binance Acquisition of Gopax Due to SEC Lawsuit </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/south-korea-binance-gopax-sec/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sweat Economy to Launch Governance Vote to Decide Fate of 2B Tokens</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sweat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sweat economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SWEAT Token]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/">Sweat Economy to Launch Governance Vote to Decide Fate of 2B Tokens</a></p>
<p>The new governance requires at least 75,000 votes for the proposal to be either accepted or rejected.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/">Sweat Economy to Launch Governance Vote to Decide Fate of 2B Tokens</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/">Sweat Economy to Launch Governance Vote to Decide Fate of 2B Tokens</a></p>
<p>Sweat Economy, the label behind the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/sweatcoin-sweat-economy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sweatcoin</a> and Sweat Wallet apps, plans to roll out a new governance vote later today in the wallet app. By doing this, the Sweat community will be saddled with the responsibility of deciding what happens to the 2 billion Sweat tokens lying idle in inactive users&#8217; accounts.</p>
<p>Token holders can now participate in the decision-making process by the principle of one man, one vote, thereby democratizing the token&#8217;s future. The question of what should be done with the tokens has lingered for a very long time especially after no response was gotten following repeated prompts and reminders to users to activate their apps and claim their tokens.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the volume of tokens involved in this case makes the governance vote a crucial one. However, the project will still have to make sure that the voices of all its community members and token holders are heard, not considering the size of the holding. This is because the Sweat Economy is pushing to promote its commitment to making the decision-making process community-centric.</p>
<p>In September last year, Sweat Economy distributed about 4.7 billion of its Sweat tokens to 13.5M of its Sweatcoin users at the time. This happened about two weeks before the Move-to-Earn project <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/qredo-teams-pp-with-sweat-economy-on-crypto-custody/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">bagged</a> a crypto custody partnership deal with London-based decentralized digital asset management infrastructure Qredo. It turned out to be that a significant number of users did not activate their Wallet apps after the token generation and distribution.</p>
<p>Owing to this, up to 2 billion tokens were left unclaimed and locked up in a 24-month contract in inactive user accounts, representing approximately 13% of the total supply of the Sweat token.</p>
<h2>Sweat Economy Governance: Vote For or Against?</h2>
<p>The new governance requires at least 75,000 votes for the proposal to be either accepted or rejected. There is every likelihood that the volume of votes will exceed 75,000 as the previous vote attracted way over 150,000 participants. The Sweat Economy is even more positive about this possibility considering the bulk of Sweat tokens involved.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignnone" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sweat-economy-governance-vote-1.jpg" alt="Sweat Economy to Launch Governance Vote to Decide Fate of 2B Tokens" width="1024" height="576" /></p>
<p>The two options to be voted for or against are whether the 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens should be recovered and transferred back to the Sweat Treasury for maybe a potential future distribution or other uses that would also be decided via another round of votes, or the tokens should remain in the inactive users&#8217; accounts.</p>
<p>Every token holder has a fair chance of making their vote count and the polls will run for up to 7 days with the possibility of a 3-day extension depending on the influx of votes. So far, Sweat Economy has received feedback from holders indicating that the governance vote is a welcomed development.</p>
<p>On one hand, the Sweat Economy is preparing for its <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-september-us-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">launch</a> in the United States this September. This will facilitate Sweat Wallet installation among US residents. At the same time, existing users of the Sweatcoin app will receive their SWEAT token allocations in direct proportion to their current Sweatcoin stake.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/">Sweat Economy to Launch Governance Vote to Decide Fate of 2B Tokens</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sweat-economy-governance-vote/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HSBC CEO Promises Silicon Valley Bank UK Will Not Suspend Focus on Startups amid Expansion</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hsbc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silicon valley]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258158</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/">HSBC CEO Promises Silicon Valley Bank UK Will Not Suspend Focus on Startups amid Expansion</a></p>
<p>HSBC CEO has doused fears that Silicon Valley Bank UK will suspend or not adequately focus plans on helping startups.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/">HSBC CEO Promises Silicon Valley Bank UK Will Not Suspend Focus on Startups amid Expansion</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/">HSBC CEO Promises Silicon Valley Bank UK Will Not Suspend Focus on Startups amid Expansion</a></p>
<p>The CEO of HSBC UK has said that Silicon Valley Bank UK will continue its regular business of serving startups regardless of new ownership. Ian Stuart noted that Silicon Valley Bank will maintain its processes and business without disruption.</p>
<p>At the Money 20/20 fintech conference in Amsterdam, Stuart assured CNBC’s Arjun Kharpal of protecting Silicon Valley Bank. He said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are going to keep it ringfenced within our own ringfenced bank. It will have its own board, it will have its own risk policies. We are going to protect what it’s got today.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The HSBC CEO was responding to general anxiety about the takeover. Many worry that a traditional financial institution like HSBC is not in the best position to serve Silicon Valley Bank UK. The worry is specifically about HSBC financing small businesses and tech startups like Silicon Valley did.</p>
<p>Stuart has assured that customers will enjoy the same services without any difference. He stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our plan is we’ll take it from seed funding all the way through to IPO. Customers will never have to go outside of that network to meet their funding requirements.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, the CEO spoke on strategy. He said the plan is to “be global very, very quickly”, with infrastructure in Israel, the Middle East and Asia, the US, and the UK. According to a Sky News <a href="https://news.sky.com/story/hsbc-opts-for-innovation-in-rebranding-of-silicon-valley-bank-uk-12892645#:~:text=Sky%20News%20has%20learned%20that,the%20name%20HSBC%20Innovation%20Banking." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, HSBC will rebrand Silicon Valley Bank UK as “HSBC Innovation Banking”. The report states that HSBC will likely announce the new brand on June 12 as the London Tech Week kicks off.</p>
<h2>HSBC Acquired UK Arm of Silicon Valley Bank for 1 Pound</h2>
<p>HSBC Silicon Valley <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-svb-uk-subsidiary/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">acquired</a> Silicon Valley Bank UK following the Silicon Valley parent’s recent collapse. At the time of the official London Stock Exchange <a href="https://www.londonstockexchange.com/news-article/HSBA/hsbc-acquires-silicon-valley-bank-uk/15871682" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announcement</a>, Silicon Valley Bank UK had around £6.7 billion in deposits and about £5.5 billion in loans. The estimate for the bank’s tangible equity was £1.4 billion. In addition, the announcement said the bank had £88 million in profit before tax for the financial year ending December 31, 2022.</p>
<p>HSBC was one of a few institutions interested in Silicon Valley Bank UK. Global clearing organization Bank of London also sent an offer to the failed bank and submitted proposals to the Bank of England and the Treasury. Reportedly, SoftBank subsidiary OakNorth Bank was also interested in the acquisition, along with Abu Dhabi investment and holding company ADQ.</p>
<p>North Carolina-based First Citizens Bank acquired Silicon Valley Bank in the US following the collapse. A US Federal Deposit and Insurance Corporation (FDIC) <a href="https://www.fdic.gov/news/press-releases/2023/pr23023.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">statement</a> noted that First Citizens would also acquire all loans and deposits. The statement also said that the Silicon Valley Bank failure will cost the FDIC’s Deposit Insurance Fund (DIF) around $20 billion.</p>
<p>First Citizens planned to reopen at least 17 former Silicon Valley branches as First Citizens Bank and Trust Company.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/">HSBC CEO Promises Silicon Valley Bank UK Will Not Suspend Focus on Startups amid Expansion</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/hsbc-silicon-valley-bank-uk-startups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Remains Bullish on Bitcoin (BTC)</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arthur hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitmex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258177</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/">Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Remains Bullish on Bitcoin (BTC)</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin's strong bounce back despite the SEC lawsuits has made analysts optimist about the beginning of the next bull run. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/">Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Remains Bullish on Bitcoin (BTC)</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/">Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Remains Bullish on Bitcoin (BTC)</a></p>
<p>After facing strong selling pressure earlier this week, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has given a strong bounceback today moving closer to $27,000. As of press time, BTC is trading 3.2% up at a price of $26,603 and a market cap of $515 billion. The recent bounce back has created optimism among Bitcoin enthusiasts with analysts turning bullish on the crypto once again. Former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bitmex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BitMEX</a> CEO Arthur Hayes recently tweeted that it&#8217;s time to join the next bull run for Bitcoin.</p>
<p>&#8220;The wall of worry is being climbed, come with me on the $BTC bull market bus. We are still on struggle street, but the moon ain’t far away,&#8221; <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoHayes/status/1666232026054418432" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a> he.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, Bitcoin (BTC) and the broader crypto market came under major selling pressure following the SEC lawsuit on crypto exchange Binance. Soon after, crypto exchange Binance saw massive withdrawals on the platform, pushing the BTC price all the way under $26,000.</p>
<p>Today&#8217;s bounceback, however, brings interesting technical chart patterns into the picture. Popular crypto analyst Ali Martinez <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1666387288027168769" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The TD Sequential presents a buy signal on the hourly chart, which could see $BTC rebound to $27,000 &#8211; $27,300. Still, #BTC must avoid an hourly close below $26,360 because it could lead to a downswing to $25,800.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<div>
<dl id="attachment_258178">
<dt><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-BTC-Technical-chart.jpeg" alt="Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Remains Bullish on Bitcoin (BTC)" width="2256" height="1606" /></dt>
<dd>Photo: TradingView</dd>
</dl>
</div>
<p>Similarly, popular analyst Michael Van de Poppe <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1666383038651981824" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Great move of #Bitcoin, but you&#8217;d preferably want to see it hold above $26,100 to avoid a cascade. If $26,100 is lost, that&#8217;s the trigger that we&#8217;ll be losing the 200-Week MA on the Total Market Cap of #Crypto too.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Traders Liquidate Shorts, But the Dips</h2>
<p>The recent surge in the Bitcoin price and crypto market shows that investors are willing to look past the SEC&#8217;s regulatory actions on Binance and Coinbase. Amid the V-shaped recovery in the Bitcoin price, traders had to liquidate many short positions. On-chain data provider Santiment <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1666167622625558528" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reports</a> that&#8221;traders had many #liquidated #shorts today after showing some over-eagerness to bet against markets. The largest shorts in 3 months acted as rocket fuel as $BTC jumped back above $27k. We saw a similar price bounce when traders shorted on March 10th.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the investor&#8217;s interest in buying the dip shot up as the crypto prices corrected heavily. As the US SEC picks up the battle with the top two crypto trading platforms, it will be interesting to see what lies ahead.</p>
<p>The lawsuits&#8217; outcomes have the potential to establish a crucial precedent for cryptocurrencies. If the courts side with the SEC and classify numerous digital assets as securities, it could lead to a substantial transformation in cryptocurrency regulation, potentially granting the SEC authority over them.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/">Former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes Remains Bullish on Bitcoin (BTC)</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/former-bitmex-ceo-bitcoin-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US Says SEC Lawsuit Is Unjustified</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance us]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258175</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/">Binance.US Says SEC Lawsuit Is Unjustified</a></p>
<p>Many crypto exchanges including Binance believe that the SEC's requested relief will do more harm to investors than good. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/">Binance.US Says SEC Lawsuit Is Unjustified</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/">Binance.US Says SEC Lawsuit Is Unjustified</a></p>
<p>The United States arm of the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> exchange, Binance.US has <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/602764" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">responded</a> to the lawsuit filed against it by the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>).</p>
<p>According to Binance.US, the lawsuit is without any basis and therefore, the exchange is ready to go to court to refute all of the unwarranted accusations. In light of facts, the law at the time, as well as the SEC&#8217;s precedents, the exchange believes that the regulator&#8217;s complaint is unjustified.</p>
<p>At the same time, Binance claimed to be aware of the undue stress that the crypto market had been under following a rising trend of regulatory actions against crypto exchanges, hence the need to address it now.</p>
<p>The trading platform noted the series of lawsuits that the US regulator has filed against the likes of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase Global Inc</a> (NASDAQ: COIN), Gemini, and Kraken and after considering many of them including its recent indictment, the exchange concluded that the SEC may very well be restricting the digital assets industry.</p>
<p>At the same time, Binance.US says it is open to reaching a constructive compromise with the regulator, provided that Binance customers and their crypto assets are protected. Furthermore, the exchange reminded the public that it is one of the few exchanges that have been working tirelessly with the SEC for more than two years to ensure that a clear and realistic regulatory framework is upheld.</p>
<p>Many crypto exchanges including Binance opine that the SEC&#8217;s requested relief will do more harm to investors than good.</p>
<p>Precisely, it is presumed that investors will begin to seek a haven for their enterprises outside America seeing that the region is suffocating and stifling their mission to thrive. Conclusively, Binance.US is calling on the intervention of Congress in establishing bipartisan legislation for a sustainable and practicable crypto regulatory framework.</p>
<p>Without this bipartisan legislation, the US risks jeopardizing its position as a pioneer and innovator in the field of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>The SEC Lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase</h2>
<p>On Monday, the SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> Binance.US and its parent company in a U.S. federal court in Washington DC for violating securities laws. In addition, the SEC called out the exchange for mishandling investor funds as well as misleading investors and regulators. The SEC also accused the crypto exchange of flouting Know-Your-Customers (KYC) rules by letting Americans trade in an unsecured and unprotected environment.</p>
<p>“We allege that Zhao and the Binance entities not only knew the rules of the road, but they also consciously chose to evade them and put their customers and investors at risk – all in an effort to maximize their own profits,” Gurbir S. Grewal, Director of the SEC’s Division of Enforcement started in the filing.</p>
<p>This enforcement action, as well as the related lawsuit slammed against Coinbase caused the price of several crypto-linked assets including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-shares-tumble-sec-binance-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Coinbase shares</a> to fall significantly.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/">Binance.US Says SEC Lawsuit Is Unjustified</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-lawsuit-unjustified/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Is Security, Former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey Says</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jack dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/">Ethereum Is Security, Former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey Says</a></p>
<p>There are ongoing efforts to classify Ethereum. As of now, a final decision is yet to be reached regarding whether it should be considered a security or not. Considering the arguments, predicting the final outcome is challenging.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/">Ethereum Is Security, Former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey Says</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/">Ethereum Is Security, Former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey Says</a></p>
<p>With the recent noise about cryptocurrency regulation and events such as crypto exchanges being sued for offering unregistered securities, there have been varying views from experts and high-profile individuals about the state of some specific cryptocurrencies. One of them is a recent comment by <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/jack-dorsey/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jack Dorsey</a>, the former <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a> CEO, arguing that Ethereum is a security.</p>
<p>A Twitter user named Ali asked Jack if <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> is a security, and Jack <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1666078896327122946" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">responded</a> &#8220;Yes&#8221;. Many people reacted to his comment, many of whom were offended and disagreed with him. While many commented that his classification was irrelevant, many others referred to him as a clown.</p>
<p>Udi Wertheimer, a blockchain developer and consultant, reacted to Jack’s comment, calling him a clown. Jack responded to Udi’s tweet, asking him for more information about his opinions. Then Udi posted a 21-second video showing the SEC claiming in 2018 that Ethereum was already sufficiently decentralized not to be a security.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">clowns. <a href="https://t.co/S8AiJwuMem">pic.twitter.com/S8AiJwuMem</a></p>
<p>— Udi Wertheimer (@udiWertheimer) <a href="https://twitter.com/udiWertheimer/status/1666080703648284672?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Jack Dorsey’s Lack of Faith in the Ethereum Blockchain</h2>
<p>The tweet about Ethereum being a security came at a critical time in the crypto industry when the topic of crypto regulations and whether specific cryptos are securities or not is on the rise. This is also one of the reasons the particular tweet piqued people’s interest.</p>
<p>This is not the first time Jack has made comments that don’t align with Ethereum’s best interests. For a long time, it has been clear that Jack prefers Bitcoin and has no faith in the Ethereum project. He holds that Bitcoin will impact how money is exchanged and that the payment solution can transform the financial system by promoting fairness and equal opportunity.</p>
<p>The Square CEO has also criticized building projects on Ethereum. In a comment he sent as a reply to Deso Protocol&#8217;s tweet in 2022, he said developers building on Ethereum have at least one single point of failure, making the project unappealing to him.</p>
<h2>Uncertainty Still Surrounds Ethereum’s Classification</h2>
<p>The SEC has sued several cryptocurrency companies for failing to register certain cryptocurrencies, including Ethereum, as securities. Ongoing efforts still exist to assign a specific classification to Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies. No final decision has been made at this point, and no one can be sure of how it will end. It is possible that Ethereum will not be classified as a security, and thus the SEC will not be required to regulate it, or vice versa.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/">Ethereum Is Security, Former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey Says</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/ethereum-security-jack-dorsey/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stripe, Ripple, Blockchain.com, OpenSea Lead Way for Top 10 US Fintech Companies</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[staff writer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opensea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stripe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258167</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/">Stripe, Ripple, Blockchain.com, OpenSea Lead Way for Top 10 US Fintech Companies</a></p>
<p>Top crypto companies rank amongst the largest Fintech companies in America despite market challenges. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/">Stripe, Ripple, Blockchain.com, OpenSea Lead Way for Top 10 US Fintech Companies</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/">Stripe, Ripple, Blockchain.com, OpenSea Lead Way for Top 10 US Fintech Companies</a></p>
<p>Forbes has <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/emilymason/2023/06/06/the-10-biggest-fintech-companies-in-america-2023/?sh=2860ac3128c2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">released</a> its annual list of the top ten largest fintech companies in the US, providing insights into the dynamic landscape of the financial technology industry. However, this year&#8217;s list includes a disclaimer due to the market downturn&#8217;s impact on fintech valuations.</p>
<p>First on the list was payment processing giant Stripe. The crypto-friendly firm, founded by Irish brothers Patrick and John Collison, ranked first on the list despite experiencing a valuation decline from $95 billion recorded in 2021 to <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stripe-valued-50-billion-raise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">$50 billion</a> in March 2023. The company has been topping the chart since 2021.</p>
<p>The payment processor has played a pivotal role in facilitating online business transactions, processing a staggering $817 billion in transactions last year. Some of its high-end clients include ChatGPT creator OpenAI, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft</a>, and Ford.</p>
<p>Followed by Stripe is Chime, which emerged second on the list. The financial services firm has received $2.3 billion in financing, one of the criteria for the rankings, from venture capital firms such as Sequoia Capital and Menlo Ventures.</p>
<h2>Ripple Ranks the Third Largest Fintech Company in the US</h2>
<p>Blockchain payments infrastructure Ripple was third on the list, demonstrating resilience and innovation in the face of challenges.</p>
<p>The company faces one of the most prolonged <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ripple-eyes-ipo-as-xrp-lawsuit-draws-to-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">legal battles</a> in the history of crypto, with the United States regulator, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), over its XRP token. It recorded a valuation of $15 billion.</p>
<p>The payments firm was launched in 2012 by Chris Larsen, the executive chairman, and Brad Garlinghouse. According to reports, Ripple raised an undisclosed amount of funds in January this year.</p>
<p>Three years ago, Ripple earned a spot on the same Forbes list through fundraising and strategic partnerships. It raised around $200 million in a Series C funding round during the year&#8217;s final quarter.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ripple-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ripple</a> was followed by another crypto-focused company, Blockchain.com, taking the fourth position with a valuation of $14 billion. The firm operates as a digital asset trading platform, data hub, and wallet provider.</p>
<p>It allows users to self-custody their crypto assets and access multiple services within a single platform. With a presence in over 200 countries and support for 25 languages, Blockchain.com has gained recognition as a leading player in the crypto space.</p>
<h2>OpenSea Faces Competition with Blur</h2>
<p>OpenSea, a non-fungible token (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-non-fungible-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NFT</a>) marketplace, also made the list. The company ranked sixth on the Forbes list after Plaid, an American-based company that connects customers&#8217; data to other financial applications.</p>
<p>The NFT marketplace, launched in December 2017, is valued at around $13.3 billion. The valuation earned its founders, Devin Finzer and Alex Atallah, the title of NFT billionaires.</p>
<p>OpenSea experienced a highly successful year in 2022, generating a remarkable $472 million in revenue. The platform achieved this through a 2.5% transaction fee applied to a substantial trading volume of $18.8 billion. However, the company now faces increasing competition from emerging contenders such as Blur, which surpassed OpenSea as the dominant marketplace in terms of NFT trading volume earlier this year.</p>
<p>This shifting landscape presents OpenSea with the challenge of maintaining its position in the market amidst the rise of formidable rivals.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, other Fintech companies such as Brex, GoodLeap, Bolt, and Alchemy made the Forbes list with $12.3 billion, $12 billion, $11 billion, and $10.2 billion, respectively.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/">Stripe, Ripple, Blockchain.com, OpenSea Lead Way for Top 10 US Fintech Companies</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/top-10-us-fintech-companies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sequoia Capital Announces Upcoming Split amid Growing Brand Confusion and Other Reasons</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sequoia capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=258114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/">Sequoia Capital Announces Upcoming Split amid Growing Brand Confusion and Other Reasons</a></p>
<p>The move will help each business to build teams that have an intimate understanding of their local networks and industries.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/">Sequoia Capital Announces Upcoming Split amid Growing Brand Confusion and Other Reasons</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/">Sequoia Capital Announces Upcoming Split amid Growing Brand Confusion and Other Reasons</a></p>
<p>Venture capital (VC) firm Sequoia Capital has revealed its plans to split up into three distinct businesses. According to the announcement, the new businesses will focus on serving the United States, China, and the Asian markets, albeit separately.</p>
<h2>Sequoia Capital Cites Reasons for Upcoming Split</h2>
<p>Sequoia <a href="https://twitter.com/sequoia/status/1666029996455112704" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> plans for the three-way split on Tuesday, sharing numerous reasons behind the decision. One of those is to decentralize the backend operations of the company.</p>
<p>The move, according to a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/sequoia/status/1666029996455112704?t=KiLEg_rd3x5eM0FkB8nfhQ&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">post</a>, also seeks to address Sequoia&#8217;s growing brand confusion. But most importantly, it is a decision that has put into consideration the increasing complexities of global financing.</p>
<p>Therefore, each localized business will focus on its jurisdiction in the delivery of its services. The company believes that this move will greatly help each business to build teams that have an &#8220;intimate understanding of their local networks and industries&#8221;.</p>
<p>So, ultimately, the split spells that the US branch will continue to focus on North America-based dealings, while the Chinese branch serves China, and the India/SEA focuses on India and other Asian markets.</p>
<h2>US/China Relationship in View</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, it might be worth mentioning that the Sequoia split is coming at a time when the relationship between China and the US appears to be at its lowest. Recently, tensions rose between both sides when the US military released a clip on June 3. The clip showed a Chinese destroyer that nearly collided with a US warship. CNN later <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/04/asia/china-defense-minister-shangri-la-speech-intl-hnk/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> that China claims there was a &#8216;provocation&#8217; on the part of the US leading to the incident.</p>
<p>The most recent event is one of many events that have occurred in 2023. Recall the Chinese surveillance balloon that was discovered in February and also the close fly-by of a Chinese jet in May. These events continue to put a strain on the already edgy US/Chinese relationship.</p>
<p>But it remains unclear whether or not Sequoia’s impending split has anything to do with the relationship that is growing sour. Nonetheless, however, US and European arms will continue to operate under the Sequoia banner. The Chinese branch will retain its Chinese name which is translated to “HongShan” in the English language.  And lastly, the India and Southeast Asia arm will take up a new name and rebrand to “Peak XV Partners”.</p>
<p>According to Sequoia Capital,  all changes are expected to have taken effect by March 31, 2024.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on our website.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ark-invest-coinbase-shares-sec/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/">Sequoia Capital Announces Upcoming Split amid Growing Brand Confusion and Other Reasons</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/sequoia-capital-split-brand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4013 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1017358 metric#prefetches=192 metric#store-reads=20 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=199 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=100.80 metric#ms-cache=4.85 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2312 metric#ms-cache-ratio=4.8 -->