<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:47:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Story of the Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dow jones]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jpmorgan chase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq composite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stock market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
<p>US financial giants witnessed their shares slide as credit rating downgrades cast a shadow over the sector.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
<p>In a volatile trading session on Tuesday, stocks experienced a significant downturn as strain over the global economic outlook coupled with a decline in United States banking sector performance, exerted pressure on Wall Street.</p>
<h2>A Closer Look at Market Index Performance</h2>
<p>Reports <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/14/stock-market-today-live-updates.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reveal</a> that the stock market’s stumble was largely attributed to mounting concerns about the global economy, with China’s economic condition drawing particular attention.</p>
<p>These concerns resonated across the international financial landscape, impacting investor sentiment. As the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-dow-jones-industrial-average-index-djia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dow Jones Industrial Average</a> (INDEXDJX: .DJI) plummeted by 361.24 points, equivalent to a 1.02% drop, the prevailing unease was evident as its value is now pegged at 34,946.39.</p>
<p>Additionally, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500 Index</a> (INDEXSP: .INX) retreated by 1.16%, closing at 4,437.86 points. This marked a pivotal moment as the index fell below its 50-day moving average, a technical indicator that is often closely monitored by traders. Similarly, the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-nasdaq-composite-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Nasdaq Composite</a> (INDEXNASDAQ: .IXIC) experienced a decline, closing down by 1.14% at 13,631.05 points.</p>
<p>US financial giants also witnessed their shares slide as credit rating downgrades cast a shadow over the sector. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/jpmorgan-chase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: JPM) and <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/wells-fargo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wells Fargo &amp; Co</a> (NYSE: WFC) saw their shares dip by 2%, while <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bank-of-america/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of America Corp</a> (NYSE: BAC) shares declined by 3%. This move came after credit rating agency Fitch Ratings issued a warning that it might downgrade the credit ratings of several banks, including JPMorgan Chase.</p>
<p>The SPDR S&amp;P Regional Banking ETF (KBE) fell around 3% in trade on Tuesday. The drop followed remarks by Minneapolis Federal Reserve President Neel Kashkari, who pushed for stricter capital regulations. Kashkari expressed concern about potential vulnerabilities in the banking industry if inflation is not sufficiently controlled and interest rates are raised further.</p>
<h2>China’s Economic Data Deepens Global Strain</h2>
<p>The report further highlighted that global investor sentiment took another hit as China reported underwhelming economic data. China’s industrial production increased by 3.7% year on year in July, falling short of expectations. Additionally, retail sales growth was weaker than anticipated.</p>
<p>In response to these challenges, the People’s Bank of China (PBoC) unexpectedly lowered interest rates by 15 basis points to 2.5% from 2.65%. However, these measures failed to reassure investors and instead raised concerns about the struggling real estate market in China. The uncertainties surrounding China&#8217;s economic direction heightened market anxiety.</p>
<p>Against this backdrop of financial sector struggles and global economic concerns, earnings season for retailers commenced with a mix of results. <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/home-depot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Depot Inc</a> (NYSE: HD) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> earnings per share and revenue that exceeded analyst expectations, resulting in a little increase in its stock price.</p>
<p>Amidst the prevailing uncertainty, the July retail sales report in the United States revealed a silver lining. Retail sales increased by 0.7% month over month, beating economists’ expectations of a 0.4% increase.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/">Stocks Fall as Global Economic Worries Weigh on Wall Street</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stocks-fall-global-economic-worries-weigh/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinTech News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investors News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[denelle dixon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moneygram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stellar foundation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
<p>Stellar Development Foundation said that the investment in MoneyGram in growing its digital business, researching blockchain technology, and contributing in other ways. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
<p>On Tuesday, August 15, cross-border payments platform Stellar announced its decision of investing in the global money-transfer company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/moneygram/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">MoneyGram International</a>. By using money from its own treasury for investment, the Stellar Foundation becomes a minority holder in MoneyGram.</p>
<p>Stellar Development Foundation CEO and Executive Director Denelle Dixon called the new investing decision &#8220;an easy one&#8221;. &#8220;After years of getting to know the business and the teams, we are excited to take part in MGI’s next chapter. It’s been an awesome few years working together, and we are excited for what’s next!&#8221; she <a href="https://twitter.com/DenelleDixon/status/1691456351955025920" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>.</p>
<p>&#8220;Most importantly, it signifies a rededication from MoneyGram International, one of the world&#8217;s leading global financial technology, to becoming a digital-forward leader in fintech,&#8221; added Dixon. However, the Stellar Development Foundation hasn&#8217;t given enough details about the exact investment amount.</p>
<p>This investment allows SDF to support MGI&#8217;s efforts, especially in areas like growing its digital business, researching blockchain technology, and contributing to the various ways this fintech company helps people and businesses handle money worldwide. It&#8217;s also a significant commitment from MGI, a prominent global fintech, to embrace digital innovation and become a leader in the field.</p>
<h2>Stellar and MoneyGram Partnership</h2>
<p>The Stellar Development Foundation and MoneyGram started working together in 2021, but their collaboration on tools and technology goes back to 2019.</p>
<p>By November 2022, MoneyGram allowed users in the United States to buy, sell, and hold cryptocurrency using its mobile app. In July 2023, the company introduced a new service that lets people in Venezuela deposit funds into their accounts through its partnership with local bank Banesco.</p>
<p>Stellar&#8217;s goal is to use blockchain technology to make cross-border payments faster and more affordable. MoneyGram is one of the largest remittance companies in the United States, competing with <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/western-union/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Western Union</a>, Intermex, and Euronet.</p>
<p>Speaking to the crypto publication Decrypt, Stellar Development Foundation&#8217;s Director of Communications and Public Affairs Ellen Canale <a href="https://decrypt.co/152598/stellar-invests-in-moneygram-in-bid-to-become-a-digital-forward-leader-in-fintech" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Investment isn&#8217;t specific to any particular work&#8221; but because &#8220;we are confident in the organization, management, and board, and the company&#8217;s plans for the future focused on increasing MGI&#8217;s digital investment and bringing value to the under and unbanked through digital experiences.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Stellar Foundation has also been investing in other projects this year. Earlier in April, SDF <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-franklin-onchain-money-fund/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">invested</a> in Franklin OnChain US Government Money Fund.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/">Stellar Foundation Invests in MoneyGram in a Push for FinTech</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/stellar-invests-moneygram-fintech-push/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[electric vehicle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ev]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model s sedan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[model x suv]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tesla]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tsla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267084</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
<p>The latest decision is one of many attempts by Tesla to grow its sales by all means necessary.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/tesla/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tesla Inc</a> (NASDAQ: TSLA), an American automotive company, has introduced cheaper variants of some of its high-end electric vehicles (EVs) to the US market. According to a Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-introduces-new-model-s-x-cars-us-2023-08-15/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, the decision might be in line with the firm&#8217;s resolve to increase sales at a time when demand for expensive EVs has gone extremely low due to the high costs of borrowing.</p>
<p>To this end, Tesla has now launched more affordable versions of its Model S sedan and Model X SUV. But the new versions will come with shorter driving ranges.</p>
<p>For reference, the new S model has a top range of 320 miles. Whereas, the regular dual-motor and tri-motor Plaid versions offer up to 405 miles and 396 miles, respectively. Similarly, the range of the new X SUV model can go up to 269 miles, a significant downgrade from the 348 miles that its expensive variant offers.</p>
<p>However, the performance and range may just be all the difference that exists between the old and new versions. According to a Tesla sales representative, the new versions will have the same battery as the expensive ones. That is, those that cost $10,000 or more.</p>
<h2>Tesla Keen on Sales Growth</h2>
<p>The latest decision is one of many attempts by Tesla to grow its sales by all means necessary. Before the new launch, the firm <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-slashes-price-japan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">already cut down</a> on its vehicle prices in the US, China, and several other markets.</p>
<p>As further proof that Tesla might be prioritizing sales over profit margins at the moment, the company has also employed a strategy of offering incentives to reduce inventory.</p>
<p>Rollouts for the new variants will begin between September and October. But, according to an inside source, Tesla is not planning to improve the range and performance in the future.</p>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth though, the launch is expected to lessen Tesla&#8217;s operating income which has been growing worrisome recently. And, more importantly, it is also expected that the launch will help Tesla to increase its dwindling revenue as well.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/">Tesla Launches Cheaper Versions of Some of Its EVs in US as Demand Wanes</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tesla-cheaper-versions-model-s-x-suv/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum’s SEC Approval</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gary gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prometheum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267080</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
<p>Republican lawmakers have questioned whether the US SEC has assured enough security measures before granting Prometheum Inc. the license to operate as crypto broker. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
<p>Republican lawmakers at the US Congressional Committee overseeing the Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) are demanding an answer from SEC chair <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gary Gensler</a> over how Prometheum Inc secured a unique approval to operate as a crypto broker-dealer.</p>
<p>Led by Chair Patrick McHenry (R-N.C.), a group of 23 House Financial Services Committee lawmakers raised questions about how the recently revealed company managed to secure SEC registration as a special-purpose broker-dealer for digital assets. They also sought clarification on the factors that led to this decision and the timing of its conclusion, considering other applicants in the process.</p>
<p>Additionally, the lawmakers also sent a letter to the head of the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA). It&#8217;s an industry-funded group that enforces securities standards under the SEC&#8217;s watch. The letter noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The timing of the approval raises concerns that it was aimed at demonstrating that legislation is not needed because there is a workable regulatory framework for the custody of digital asset securities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s Special Treatment to Prometheum?</h2>
<p>The letters ask important questions about whether the SEC chose Prometheum as a prime example to support Gensler&#8217;s view that new laws aren&#8217;t necessary for regulating crypto in the US. This happened just as McHenry&#8217;s committee was preparing to send digital assets legislation to the House floor.</p>
<p>However, Prometheum&#8217;s leaders have said they&#8217;ve been following the registration process like any other company. Co-CEO Aaron Kaplan believes his company will show how to create a crypto platform that follows the rules properly. In a statement on Tuesday, August 15, the company said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Prometheum purpose-built its technology with the goal to develop a market infrastructure for digital asset securities that is compliant with the federal securities laws. This technology will serve as a building block for a compliant and orderly digital asset securities marketplace that protects investors and serves their best interests.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Lawmakers are also joining others in asking for more details about Prometheum&#8217;s sudden appearance in Washington. The company hasn&#8217;t started trading yet. Both Republicans and Democrats in the Senate and House have raised concerns about this, and Ritchie Torres, a Democrat on McHenry&#8217;s committee, has asked for the SEC to be investigated.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/">Republican Lawmakers Seek Answer from Gary Gensler over Prometheum&#8217;s SEC Approval</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/lawmakers-gary-gensler-prometheum-sec-approval/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Darya Rudz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editor's Choice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance buy-and-sell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance connect]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance sec lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
<p>Binance has confirmed the news, stating it would shift its focus to its main products and long-term goals.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has decided to close its buy-and-sell service Binance Connect amid challenges its provider faced with support for card payments. Starting from August 16, Binance Connect is no longer available.</p>
<p>Binance has confirmed the news, the announcement has also been revealed by BNB Chain-based platform Biswap in a tweet.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="474" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dear Biswappers,</p>
<p>The Biswap team keeps abreast of the latest DeFi news and aims to inform you right away.</p>
<p>After a thorough consideration, <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@binance</a> has made a difficult decision to disable <a href="https://twitter.com/Binance_Connect?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Binance_Connect</a> on 15 August due to its provider closing the supporting card payments… <a href="https://t.co/HcooyLn4sg">pic.twitter.com/HcooyLn4sg</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Biswap (@Biswap_Dex) <a href="https://twitter.com/Biswap_Dex/status/1691358029914996736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>As Binance has stated, it will shift its focus to its main products and long-term goals.</p>
<p>Binance representative commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We periodically review our products and services to ensure that our resources continue to be focused on core efforts that align with our long-term strategy. In the last six years, Binance has grown from being an exchange to a global blockchain ecosystem with multiple business lines. We consistently adapt and modify our business approach in response to changing market and user needs.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Launched in March 2022, Binance Connect (formerly Bitfinity) was connecting traditional finance to world-leading and emerging blockchains, transforming how businesses and people send and receive money around the world. Its aim was to create an open, financial world where people from all walks of life and businesses, big or small, can participate and realize their financial goals.</p>
<p>Serving as the official fiat-to-crypto payments provider for Binance, Binance Connect supported as many as 50 cryptocurrencies and major payment methods, including Visa and Mastercard. The service was also supposed to be the hub for the exchange’s <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-are-non-fungible-tokens-nfts/#:~:text=NFTs%20are%20created%20using%20blockchain,a%20token%20on%20the%20blockchain." target="_blank" rel="noopener">non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs) checkout solution. The feature was not added.</p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Legal Battles</h2>
<p>One of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchanges is currently facing challenges caused by regulatory scrutiny around its business. Earlier this year, Binance faced lawsuits filed by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CFTC</a>) accusing the company of misleading investors through opaque business practices. The violations included operating unregistered exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing agencies, misrepresenting trading controls and oversight on the Binance.US platform, as well as the unregistered offer and sale of securities. In total, SEC filed more than a dozen charges against Binance this year so far.</p>
<p>According to SEC, Binance has been manipulating its Know-Your-Customer (KYC) processes to conceal its US customer base and avoid regulatory oversight. Besides, the company has been accused of encouraging its US customers to use virtual private networks (VPNs) to hide their locations and bypass restrictions. Out of Binance’s 62 million global customers, only 25 million had submitted KYC documentation.</p>
<p>European regulators turned out to be not really welcoming as well. In June, Germany’s Federal Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin) reportedly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-german-license-denied-bafin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">denied</a> the Binance exchange’s application for a crypto custody license. Besides, Binance withdrew its application with the Financial Market Authority of Austria. Earlier this year, Binance also exited the Netherlands after failing to secure regulatory approval, as well as abandoned its Cyprus and UK registrations.</p>
<div id="gtx-trans" style="position: absolute; left: 773px; top: 1273.56px;">
<div class="gtx-trans-icon"></div>
</div>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/">Binance to Shut Down Its Buy-and-Sell Service Binance Connect</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-connect-shut-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk’s Platform X Slows Down Access to Facebook, Instagram, and Bluesky</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluesky]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elon musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[facebook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mark zuckerberg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[x]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267071</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Platform X Slows Down Access to Facebook, Instagram, and Bluesky</a></p>
<p>The targeted sites were subjected to a noticeable five-second delay.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Platform X Slows Down Access to Facebook, Instagram, and Bluesky</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Platform X Slows Down Access to Facebook, Instagram, and Bluesky</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/elon-musk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Elon Musk</a>&#8216;s social media platform X, formerly <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>, has stirred up a digital storm by intentionally slowing down access to certain websites, setting off debates about online power dynamics and user manipulation. The targeted sites, which include heavyweights like The New York Times, Instagram, Facebook, Bluesky, Threads, Reuters, and Substack, were subjected to a noticeable five-second delay when users tried to access links originating from X. The timing of the controversial move raised eyebrows, especially given Musk&#8217;s history of publicly expressing his disapproval of these platforms.</p>
<p>Slowing down traffic to specific websites raises critical questions about the role of platforms in shaping user experiences and the potential impact on the businesses being targeted. Even a minor delay can drastically affect user engagement and ultimately influence ad revenue for these platforms. Users have grown accustomed to near-instantaneous loading times, and such delays can lead to impatience and frustration.</p>
<h2>YouTube and Fox News Remain Unaffected</h2>
<p>On August 15, tech enthusiasts at Hackers News discovered that X had slowed down access to certain websites on Tuesday afternoon. Interestingly, the throttling strategy appears to selectively target websites that have faced Musk&#8217;s previous ire in the past.</p>
<p>According to the Washington Post, links to sites like Fox News, The Washington Post, and social media platforms such as Mastodon and YouTube remained unaffected. The move raises concerns about the ethics of using a platform to indirectly suppress competitors or platforms one disagrees with.</p>
<p>The former head of trust and safety at Twitter, Yoel Roth, chimed in on the matter, <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/yoyoel.com/post/3k4zcmly6wu2u" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">describing</a> the event as &#8220;one of those things that seem too crazy to be true, even for Twitter, until you see it inexplicably takes 5 seconds for Chrome to receive 650 bytes of data&#8221;.</p>
<p>According to him, this seemingly innocuous delay can have far-reaching implications, as research shows that even a 1-second delay can significantly impact user behavior, leading to higher bounce rates and less time spent on the site.</p>
<p>A touch of drama was added when <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/persons/mark-zuckerberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mark Zuckerberg</a>, CEO of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/meta/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Meta Platforms</a>, the conglomerate behind Facebook, Instagram, and Threads, <a href="https://www.threads.net/@zuck/post/Cv-EJEeLBHT/?igshid=MzRlODBiNWFlZA%3D%3D" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">responded</a> to a Threads post discussing the throttling with a contemplative &#8220;thinking face emoji&#8221;. The gesture comes amidst an ongoing feud between Musk and Zuckerberg, with Musk previously suggesting a real-life face-off in a cage match.</p>
<h2>X Restores Access to Affected Platforms</h2>
<p>Musk&#8217;s influence over X&#8217;s operations has manifested in the past, blocking links to competitors like Substack and Threads and removing The New York Times&#8217; verification ticker while labeling it as &#8220;propaganda&#8221;.</p>
<p>The platform has remained tight-lipped in response to the throttling controversy, maintaining a trend of non-responsiveness since Musk took over the company.</p>
<p>However, in a twist of events, X is gradually reversing the throttling tactics, with the delay in accessing news sites showing signs of improvement. According to the Post, the newly rebranded platform has completely restored the delay time to zero.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/">Elon Musk&#8217;s Platform X Slows Down Access to Facebook, Instagram, and Bluesky</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/x-access-facebook-instagram-bluesky/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AllianceBlock Announces Launch of Nexera Exchange </title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[allianceblock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nexera]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/">AllianceBlock Announces Launch of Nexera Exchange </a></p>
<p>AllianceBlock said the exchange is not just a platform but a treasure trove of DeFi features explicitly made for advanced trading strategies.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/">AllianceBlock Announces Launch of Nexera Exchange </a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/">AllianceBlock Announces Launch of Nexera Exchange </a></p>
<p><a href="https://allianceblock.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">AllianceBlock</a>, a blockchain agnostic platform designed to bridge the gap between the traditional finance (TradeFi) ecosystem and the world of decentralized finance (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-decentralized-finance-defi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">DeFi</a>) , has announced the launch of a new exchange dubbed <a href="https://nexera.exchange/">Nexera Exchange</a>. In a press release shared with Coinspeaker, the company said the exchange is on track to revolutionize how people trade cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The newly introduced exchange is an upgraded successor of AllianceBlock DEX, a platform designed to harness the power of Automated Market Maker (AMM) to &#8220;meet the demand of streamlined user interface&#8221;. Since its launch last year, the platform has gained recognition in the crypto community.</p>
<p>Building upon this success, AllianceBlock has launched Nexera Exchange to serve as an intermediary to the DEX protocol, making it more efficient and user-friendly.</p>
<p>While decentralized exchanges (DEXs) have grown in popularity, they sometimes lag behind their centralized counterparts in terms of user-friendliness. This is where Nexera Exchange steps in by incorporating an on-chain order book protocol to provide a new era of liquidity for various digital currencies and tokenized assets.</p>
<h2>Unleashing Liquidity with Uniswap Integration</h2>
<p>AllianceBlock said it has collaborated with Uniswap, a popular deFi marketplace based on the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> blockchain. Through this partnership, the company&#8217;s newly launched exchange will leverage Uniswap V3&#8217;s liquidity to enable it to provide limited orders that ensure competitive prices.</p>
<p>With the help of Uniswap, the exchange aims to become a hub for on-chain limited order aggregation, connecting liquidity from diverse, decentralized exchanges. The vision is set to empower traders with an unparalleled decentralized trading experience.</p>
<p>Nexera Exchange also plans to introduce a stability staking pool, which lets traders earn rewards while actively participating on the platform. By staking NXRA tokens, its native crypto, traders can partake in a share of the trading fees, turning trading into a rewarding endeavor.</p>
<h2>A Toolset of DeFi Wonders</h2>
<p>AllianceBlock said the exchange is not just a platform but a treasure trove of DeFi features explicitly made for advanced trading strategies.</p>
<p>These features open up new dimensions for traders, from stake-enabled on-chain order books to order-triggering matches, yield-optimized staked orders, and dynamic range order book provision.</p>
<p>Regarding safety, the company said it had equipped the exchange with quality security measures, including the KYC/AML procedures.</p>
<p>Nexera Exchange is also built to maintain compliance with regulations across its markets.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Nexera Exchange is primed to redefine crypto trading, offering advanced features, improved liquidity, and security measures that are set to shape the future of digital asset trading.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/">AllianceBlock Announces Launch of Nexera Exchange </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/allianceblock-launch-nexera/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Home Depot’s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[home depot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[home depot stock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[s&p 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
<p>Despite the favorable revenue surprise, Home Depot saw a moderated fiscal year earnings projection implying that the corporation remains cautious about the road ahead. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
<p>American retail giant <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/home-depot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Home Depot</a> (NYSE: HD) has once again demonstrated its financial resilience by surpassing Wall Street’s expectations for its Q2 2023 earnings. Despite a slight dip of 2% year-over-year sales, the company reported impressive results, reaffirming its position as a competitive player in the retail sector.</p>
<h2>Home Depot Beats Q2 2023 Earnings Expectation</h2>
<p>For the three-month period ending July 30, Home Depot <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/08/15/home-depot-hd-earnings-q2-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">reported</a> earnings per share of $4.65, outperforming the analysts’ consensus estimate of $4.45 per share. In addition, the company recorded revenue of $42.92 billion for the second quarter exceeding Wall Street&#8217;s projection of $42.23 billion.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Home Depot recorded a net income of $4.66 billion for the fiscal second quarter, translating to $4.65 per share. These figures represent a decline from last year’s results of $5.17 billion in net income and $5.05 per share.</p>
<p>While the decrease in net income and earnings per share might raise concerns, Home Depot’s recent financial report showcased a notable <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-fiscal-q4-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reversal</a> of fortune, as the company exceeded Wall Street&#8217;s revenue projections for the first time in three quarters.</p>
<p>The unexpected surge highlights Home Depot&#8217;s resilience in the face of economic challenges, reflecting its adaptability and responsiveness to evolving market dynamics.</p>
<h2>Navigating with Caution</h2>
<p>Despite the favorable revenue surprise, Home Depot saw a moderated fiscal year earnings projection implying that the corporation remains cautious about the road ahead. The retailer reiterated its forecast for sales and comparable sales to decline within a range of 2% to 5% when compared to the same period in the previous year.</p>
<p>Home Depot&#8217;s Chief Financial Officer, Richard McPhail, stated that consumer behavior remains cautious, particularly in terms of larger-ticket and discretionary purchasing. He mentioned that some homeowners made large purchases during the pandemic, while others are deferring such purchases because of rising interest rates.</p>
<p>McPhail also noted that some pandemic-induced dynamics are gradually reversing. Transportation expenses have decreased, and vendors are less likely to request price increases.</p>
<p>Home Depot’s challenges are compounded by a weakening housing market, which can impact home improvement spending. Additionally, the shift in consumer preferences towards spending more on services than goods is affecting the company’s performance.</p>
<p>The company is responding to these changing dynamics by adjusting its pricing strategies. McPhail explained that Home Depot is currently experiencing a period of “price settling,” characterized by adjustments to retail prices, including instances of lowering prices in various categories.</p>
<p>Addressing concerns about inflation, McPhail assured that the company does not anticipate significant inflation in the latter half of the year. He highlighted the typical Home Depot customer remains financially stable, partially due to substantial home equity gains during the pandemic.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the company’s shares have experienced a 4% increase year-to-date, which lags behind the broader <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-the-sp-500-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">S&amp;P 500</a>&#8216;s nearly 17% gain over the same period. As of Monday’s close, the company&#8217;s shares were trading at $329.95, a slight decline of less than 1%.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/">Home Depot&#8217;s Q2 2023 Earnings Surpass Expectations amid Sales Dip</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/home-depot-q2-2023-earnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe’s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funds & ETFs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jacobi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267039</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
<p>The Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF listing marks a significant achievement for the firm and the broader European crypto investment landscape.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
<p>Europe&#8217;s financial landscape is undergoing a significant change as Jacobi Asset Management company lists its first spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-an-exchange-traded-fund-etf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ETF</a>) on Euronext, a stock exchange platform based in Amsterdam. The move comes two years after the investment vehicle was approved by the Guernsey Financial Services Commission (GFSC) in October 2021. The fund, named the Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF, was initially planned for release last year. But the company turned back on the plans due to the market conditions and other negative news in the industry, including the catastrophic collapse of the Terra (LUNA) blockchain and the <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/ftx-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FTX</a> fiasco.</p>
<p>After months of postponement, Jacobi finally announced on August 15 that the Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) spot ETF is now available for trading on the stock exchange. The investment fund will be traded on Euronext under the ticker BCOIN. Investors are charged a 1.5% annual management fee.</p>
<h2>Europe Beats the US with the Launch of BCOIN</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230815404630/en" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a>, Fidelity Digital Assets, a subsidiary of the famous financial services company Fidelity Investments, will become the custodian of BCOIN. Similarly, Flow Traders has been authorized to serve as the official market maker for the fund, while Jane Street and DRW will serve as participants.</p>
<p>Regarding the fund&#8217;s benchmark, the FT Wilshire Bitcoin Blended Price Index, Jacobi said that Wilshire Indexes would provide the services with the REC solution created in collaboration with the digital asset platform Zumo.</p>
<p>With the listing of this investment vehicle in Amsterdam, Europe, the continent has emerged as the first region to introduce BTC investing opportunities for traditional corporate investors, beating the US and Asia.</p>
<p>&#8220;It is exciting to see Europe moving ahead of the US in opening up Bitcoin investing for institutional investors who want safe, secure access to the benefits of digital assets using familiar and regulated structures like our ETF,&#8221; said Martin Bednall, CEO of Jacobi Asset Management.</p>
<p>Despite multiple applications <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-spot-bitcoin-etf-applications/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">submitted</a> to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) over the years, none have been approved. Nonetheless, the tide may be shifting, with industry heavyweights like <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/blackrock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BlackRock</a> leading new applications designed to address concerns related to market manipulation.</p>
<h2>First Decarbonized Digital Asset Fund</h2>
<p>The Jacobi FT Wilshere Bitcoin ETF listing marks a significant achievement for the firm and the broader European crypto investment landscape. In a departure from exchange-traded notes (ETNs), this ETF introduces a fresh approach, offering investors direct ownership without the complexities associated with debt securities.</p>
<p>&#8220;Unlike other products in the European market, which are debt instruments, our fund owns the underlying asset directly. Jacobi is proud to be supported by Tier1 partners at the forefront of this digital asset market evolution while pioneering an innovative, environmentally sound solution for European investors,&#8221; Bednall continued.</p>
<p>The fund goes beyond technological innovation – it embraces sustainability. Aligned with Article 8 of the European Sustainable Finance Disclosure Regulation (SFDR), the ETF is hailed as the first decarbonized digital asset fund. The partnership with digital asset platform Zumo facilitates the integration of a Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution, ensuring institutional investors align with Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) objectives while participating in Bitcoin transactions.</p>
<p>As digital assets carve out a place within traditional finance, Jacobi&#8217;s debut as Europe&#8217;s first Bitcoin ETF showcases the region&#8217;s pioneering spirit in seizing transformative opportunities. By ushering in transparency, direct ownership, and sustainability considerations, the ETF marks a significant stride toward integrating digital assets into the heart of conventional financial systems.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/">Jacobi Asset Management Makes History with Europe&#8217;s First Bitcoin ETF Listing</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/jacobi-europe-first-bitcoin-etf/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tencent music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=267009</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
<p>Tencent Music entertainment noted that users are more willing to pay for the premium features. In Q2, the company registered 20% surge in the total paying users for its online music streaming service. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
<p>On Monday, August 15, Tencent Music Entertainment Group, China&#8217;s leading online music and entertainment platform, reported a surge in revenue for Q2 2023. The company&#8217;s total revenue, which stood at RMB7.29 billion (US$1.01 billion), surged by 5.5% from a year ago.</p>
<h2>Tencent Music in Q2 2023</h2>
<p>This growth specifically comes from the growth in the paying users on its Spotify-like music-streaming platform as well as the recovery in the advertising market. Following a period of cautious expenditure, businesses are beginning to witness a recovery, driven by indications of decreasing inflation and an improving consumer outlook for the remainder of the year.</p>
<p>Revenues from the music subscription represented a 37.2% year-over-year growth. The count of active paying users rose to 99.4 million, marking a 20.2% increase compared to the previous year and a growth of 5.0 million users from the previous quarter. Mr. Cussion Pang, Executive Chairman of Tencent Music Entertainment <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/tencent-music-entertainment-group-announces-second-quarter-2023-unaudited-financial-results-301900506.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">noted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are pleased to report a solid second quarter, supported by the continued strong growth of our online music services. As we continue driving the healthy development of China&#8217;s online music industry, we have seen users become increasingly accustomed and willing to pay for copyrighted music, whether for songs they want to listen to or for premium listening features they enjoy. This trend is evidenced by the all-time high paying ratio and ARPPU recorded by our online music services in the reported quarter. Such achievements led to revenues from online music services exceeding that of social entertainment services for the first time in our Company&#8217;s history. This marks a significant step along TME&#8217;s growth trajectory.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>TME Plans Further Expansion</h2>
<p>The company has been increasing its original content offerings to draw in more users and counter competition from platforms like Cloud Music owned by NetEase and ByteDance&#8217;s Douyin, a short-video sharing platform.</p>
<p>Mr. Cussion Pang, the Executive Chairman of TME, has stated that the company has initiated several service enhancement and risk control measures since the latter part of the second quarter of 2023. These measures aim at fostering a more music-centric live-streaming atmosphere.</p>
<p>While these actions are expected to exert pressure on revenues from social entertainment services in the latter half of 2023, potentially impacting total revenues for the year, Mr. Pang believes that these measures will ultimately lead to an optimized user experience and contribute to the company&#8217;s long-term business development.</p>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/business/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">business news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/ev-vinfast-nasdaq-spac/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/">Tencent Music Reports Surge in Q2 2023 Revenue as More Chinese Users Pay</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/tencent-music-q2-2023-revenue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4155 metric#misses=43 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1025121 metric#prefetches=203 metric#store-reads=22 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=210 metric#store-misses=4 metric#sql-queries=35 metric#ms-total=99.22 metric#ms-cache=4.97 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2070 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.0 -->