<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 21:06:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>NFT platform Recur shuts down less than 2 years after $50M financing round</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-platform-recur-shuts-down-less-than-2-years-after-50m-financing-round/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 21:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-platform-recur-shuts-down-less-than-2-years-after-50m-financing-round/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Recur announced the gradual wind down of its operations and functionality on August 18, 2023. All NFT activity will be disabled by November 16, with metadata migrated to IPFS. The startup had secured a $50 million series A funding round in 2021. Recur, an NFT startup that attracted over $50 million in its series A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-platform-recur-shuts-down-less-than-2-years-after-50m-financing-round/">NFT platform Recur shuts down less than 2 years after $50M financing round</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Recur announced the gradual wind down of its operations and functionality on August 18, 2023.</li>
<li dir="ltr">All NFT activity will be disabled by November 16, with metadata migrated to IPFS.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The startup had secured a $50 million series A funding round in 2021.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Recur, an NFT startup that attracted over $50 million in its series A financing round in 2021, is shutting down.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The platform <a href="https://support.recurforever.com/hc/en-us/articles/19685540105235" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">announced</a> the deprecation of its Web3 functionality on Friday, telling users that the gradual shut down will end with complete disabling of all metadata and migration to IPFS on November 22, 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Recur shut down timeline</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Details of the eventual closure indicate a timeline that began on August 18, 2023 with the disabling of RECUR-powered functionality including primary and secondary NFT sales. &nbsp;However, end users will still be able to withdraw <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/why-you-must-know-about-cryptocurrencies-to-understand-nfts/">NFTs</a> to on-chain wallets as well as cash out balances accumulated before August 31, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Starting November 9, 2023, Recur will disable NFT deposits and other functionality, including withdrawals and USDC cash outs, a week later.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Recur team, NFT metadata and graphical assets transitioned to IPFS will be accessible and retrievable.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">IPFS, short for InterPlanetary File System, is a peer-to-peer file sharing protocol that enables data retrieval without the need for the Recur platform. Users will also get the details on Filecoin&rsquo;s decentralized storage network, the startup announced.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recur&rsquo;s challenges and the turn of events come less than two years after the financing round, with this the latest NFT-focused startup to fold amid the effects of the prolonged crypto winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We want to extend our heartfelt thanks to each and every one of you for being an integral part of the RECUR community. It is with a deep sense of gratitude that we look back on the moments, both the triumphs and the challenges, that have shaped RECUR.</p>
<p>&mdash; RECUR (@RecurForever) <a href="https://twitter.com/RecurForever/status/1692633348454441054?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">In 2021, the startup <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/recur-announces-50m-series-a-raise-at-333m-valuation-301375145.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">raised $50 million</a> at a valuation of $333 million to become NFT&rsquo;s largest series A round. Metaverse-focused investment platform DIGITAL led the financing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Declines in NFT sales across the market have contributed to the downturn in fortune for Recur and other platforms, reflected by the dip in sales volume on Ethereum.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/nft-platform-recur-shuts-down-less-than-2-years-after-50m-financing-round/">NFT platform Recur shuts down less than 2 years after $50M financing round</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Memu token is thriving despite the painful crypto sell-off</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies plunged hard last week. This decline happened amid a sense of fear in the financial market. Shiba Memu token sale has gained steam as the developers raised over $2.1 million. Cryptocurrency prices had their worst performance this year as Bitcoin plunged from $29,000 to below $26,000. Most coins and tokens were&#160;deeply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/">Shiba Memu token is thriving despite the painful crypto sell-off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies plunged hard last week.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This decline happened amid a sense of fear in the financial market.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu token sale has gained steam as the developers raised over $2.1 million.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>Cryptocurrency prices</u></a> had their worst performance this year as Bitcoin plunged from $29,000 to below $26,000. Most coins and tokens were&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/over-a-billion-dollars-liquidated-in-cryptos-worst-day-since-ftx/"><u>deeply in the red</u></a> as demand waned and a sense of fear spread in the market. Despite this retreat, Shiba Memu&rsquo;s token sale continued, with the developers raising over $2.18 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why did cryptocurrencies slip?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">There are several reasons why most cryptocurrencies plunged last week. First, the coins dropped because of a potential shakeout. A shakeout refers to a situation where a financuial asset dips sharply and then resumes the bullish trend.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The most recent shakeout happened when Bitcoin fell from $25,000 to $19,000 and then resumed the bullish comeback to the year-to-date high of $32,000. It is still unclear whether the current decline was a shakeout or the start of a new bear run.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Second, Bitcoin dropped because of technical reasons.&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> formed a double-top pattern at $32,000. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually a bearish sign. Therefore, from these technicals, there is a likelihood that the coin will continue falling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Third, a sense of fear spread in the market as evidenced by the stock and bond market sell-off. Bond yields in most developed countries jumped, with US 10-year rising to 2012 highs and the 30-year reaching the 2007 highs. Bond yields move inversely to prices.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, cryptocurrency prices dropped because of the Chinese economy, which is going through the deepest slowdown in years. Data published last week showed that most parts of the economy like retail, industrial production, and fixed asset investments are slowing at a fast pace. China is still an integral part in the crypto industry, accounting for 20% of Binance volume.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is still thriving</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu, an upcoming cryptocurrency that combines aspects of meme coins and artificial intelligence, is thriving. Data available in its website shows that the developers have raised over $2.1 million from investors around the world. They have done that by raising over 68.1 million tokens in the past two months.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu&rsquo;s token sale is unique because the price of the token is raised every days. This means that investors who bought the token on the first day have seen their value jump sharply even without doing anything.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shiba Memu is thriving because of the industries that the developers are targeting. AI has become the fastest-growing industry this year, helping to push Nvidia&rsquo;s market cap to over $1 trillion. Similarly, meme coins have thrived, with some tokens like Pepe transforming some people into instant millionaires.</p>
<p>With the rising hype, there is a likelihood that the Shiba Memu price will also jump when it debuts in centralized and decentralized exchanges soon. You can buy the Shiba Memu token&nbsp;<a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>here</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/">Shiba Memu token is thriving despite the painful crypto sell-off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/shiba-memu-token-is-thriving-despite-the-painful-crypto-sell-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Master Key Finance to launch on BNB Chain</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/master-key-finance-to-launch-on-bnb-chain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chris Morris]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=150495</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Master Key Finance launch is scheduled for Aug. 23 at 1:00 PM CST (6:00 PM UTC).&#160; The Master Key Token (MKF) operates as a protocol on the BNB Chain, aiming to distribute wealth while addressing specific crypto domain gaps.&#160; In response to identified needs within the BNB Chain space, the objective is to foster confidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/master-key-finance-to-launch-on-bnb-chain/">Master Key Finance to launch on BNB Chain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Master Key Finance launch is scheduled for Aug. 23 at 1:00 PM CST (6:00 PM UTC).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Master Key Token (MKF) operates as a protocol on the BNB Chain, aiming to distribute wealth while addressing specific crypto domain gaps.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In response to identified needs within the BNB Chain space, the objective is to foster confidence in the project sector of the BNB Chain ecosystem.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The entity, which is veteran-owned and US-based, seeks to uphold values such as honor, courage, and commitment to both its stakeholders and technological advancements.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The team&rsquo;s foundation is truth, trust, and transparency. Collaborative efforts with regulatory authorities, such as the SEC, underscore a commitment to ensuring a secure environment within the BNB Chain.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_150507" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-150507" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-150507" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/masterkey-finance1.jpg" alt="masterkey finance 1" width="800" height="419"><figcaption id="caption-attachment-150507" class="wp-caption-text">masterkey finance 1</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Active Shilling contests are underway, offering participants the opportunity to win rewards, including a $350 prize and a spot within the MKF Presale Whitelist.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Details for participation can be accessed </span><a href="https://gleam.io/3e1sO/350-launch-give-away" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><span style="font-weight: 400">here</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Functionalities will be active upon launch, including Peer-to-Peer (P2P) trading. This feature allows buyers and sellers to determine transaction prices while mutually benefiting from reduced transfer taxes.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Master Key Finance (MKF) holders can earn rewards by staking their tokens on the platform. If a project featured on the portal does not have staking capabilities, token holders can stake with MKF to receive MKF tokens as a reward.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The portal allows Individuals to explore various opportunities and contribute to the MKF movement.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Allocation details for the ongoing sale are as follows:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Seed sale (Filled): 240 million tokens, priced at a rate of 1 BNB = 600,000 tokens. No tax applied, with a vesting period of 12 months (4 months post-launch). Minimum buy-in at 5 BNB, maximum allocation of 3 million tokens across 80 slots.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Private sale (95% filled): 80 million tokens, available at a rate of 1 BNB = 400,000 tokens. No tax is levied, and tokens are vested for six months. The minimum purchase is 5 BNB, while the maximum allocation is 2 million tokens over 40 slots.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Presale (90% filled): 280 million tokens, priced at a rate of 1 BNB = 350,000 tokens. No tax is applicable, and there is no vesting period. The minimum buy-in requirement is 1.0 BNB, with a maximum purchase limit of 5 BNB and a maximum allocation of 1.75 million tokens. The hard cap is set at 500 BNB, with a Soft Cap of 250 BNB.</span></li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_150508" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-150508" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-150508" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/masterkey-finance2.png" alt="masterkey finance2" width="800" height="450"><figcaption id="caption-attachment-150508" class="wp-caption-text">masterkey finance2</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Investors can join Master Keys and unlock your full crypto potential.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Their social coverage expands across various platforms, including Twitter, TikTok, Discord, Instagram, Medium, Rumble, Threads, and Facebook.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">You can find all the necessary links below.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><a href="https://linktr.ee/MKF_International" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400">https://linktr.ee/MKF_International</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/master-key-finance-to-launch-on-bnb-chain/">Master Key Finance to launch on BNB Chain</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Akash Network price soars as HSBC hikes Nvidia price target</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-soars-as-hsbc-hikes-nvidia-price-target/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-soars-as-hsbc-hikes-nvidia-price-target/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HSBC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-soars-as-hsbc-hikes-nvidia-price-target/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Akash Network price rose 6% to $1.48 at the time of writing and was 150% up in two weeks. The AI related cryptocurrency has outperformed amid strong forecasts for the AI sector. HSBC has reaffirmed the buy rating for Nvidia, with price target up from $600 to $780. Akash Network price rose 6% to $1.48 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-soars-as-hsbc-hikes-nvidia-price-target/">Akash Network price soars as HSBC hikes Nvidia price target</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Akash Network price rose 6% to $1.48 at the time of writing and was 150% up in two weeks.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The AI related cryptocurrency has outperformed amid strong forecasts for the AI sector.</li>
<li dir="ltr">HSBC has reaffirmed the buy rating for Nvidia, with price target up from $600 to $780.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Akash Network price rose 6% to $1.48 even as most major cap <a href="https://coinjournal.net/">cryptocurrencies</a> traded flat. Meanwhile, US stocks opened higher on Monday as the week began on a better note, with investor focus likely to be on Nvidia earnings and the Fed meeting at the Jackson Hole symposium.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ahead of that, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/hsbc/">HSBC</a> has hiked the price target for Nvidia shares, up from $600 to $780. Can this outlook be replicated across <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ai/">AI</a>-powered crypto tokens, like Akash Network?</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Strong demand for Nvidia&rsquo;s AI GPUs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A note by HSBC analyst Frank Lee reaffirmed the buy rating for the NVIDIA shares, with the bank&rsquo;s outlook pegged on earnings potential driven by an expected boom in AI. There&rsquo;s a lot of room for the company to grow in 2024 and 2025, Lee noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We continue to see strong demand that continues to outpace supply, especially with regard to AI GPU shipments. We believe this will continue to be the case going into FY25e especially as the market has better visibility over US CSP cloud 2024e CAPEX expectations by late 4Q23</em>,&rdquo; the analyst <a href="https://www.streetinsider.com/AI/NVIDIA+%28NVDA%29+PT+Raised+to+%24780+at+HSBC%2C+Still+room+for+upside/22066873.html" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">explained</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company&rsquo;s shares popped more than 4% in early trading to $451.53 as of 10:35 am ET. The HSBC price target gave it an 80% or so upside premarket.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Akash Network to benefit from AI boom?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">AI cryptocurrencies have in the past exploded on strong Nvidia earnings and revenue projections based on expected demand for artificial intelligence. As Nvidia&rsquo;s chips powering AI gains massive traction, analysts say crypto projects such as Akash Network could benefit from the resulting pivot.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Projects such as Render (RNDR), <a href="https://coinjournal.net/fetch-ai/">Fetch.ai</a> (FET) and Cortex (CTXC) could see significant traction. Today, Akash Network, a decentralised marketplace for cloud resources is outperforming the rest of AI tokens. The native token AKT is up more than 6% in the past 24 hours and 148% in the past two weeks to trade at $1.48.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Aiming to deliver the world&rsquo;s first decentralised AI Supercloud, Akash has seen several AI models successfully deployed on its Akash GPU Testnet. Nvidia GPUs have been tested on the network as projects seek to leverage AI in dApps.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While other factors could impact AKT price down the road, it appears marrying blockchain technology and AI could be a powerful driver of adoption. Revolutionising the decentralised physical infrastructure networks (dePINs) will likely underpin AKT price performance.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AKT price reached $1.77 on August 20, 2023, which is some distance off its all-time high of $8.07 reached in April 2021.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-soars-as-hsbc-hikes-nvidia-price-target/">Akash Network price soars as HSBC hikes Nvidia price target</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/akash-network-price-soars-as-hsbc-hikes-nvidia-price-target/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over a billion dollars liquidated in crypto’s worst day since FTX</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/over-a-billion-dollars-liquidated-in-cryptos-worst-day-since-ftx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/over-a-billion-dollars-liquidated-in-cryptos-worst-day-since-ftx/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Last week saw crypto suffered its worst 24 hours since FTX as over one billion dollars in derivatives were liquidated on Thursday Derivative volume outstrips the extremely low spot volume, with cascading liquidations having the potential to exacerbate price moves Volatility was sparked by sell-off in the bond market Developments re-affirm how vulnerable [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/over-a-billion-dollars-liquidated-in-cryptos-worst-day-since-ftx/">Over a billion dollars liquidated in crypto’s worst day since FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Last week saw crypto suffered its worst 24 hours since FTX as over one billion dollars in derivatives were liquidated on Thursday</li>
<li dir="ltr">Derivative volume outstrips the extremely low spot volume, with cascading liquidations having the potential to exacerbate price moves</li>
<li dir="ltr">Volatility was sparked by sell-off in the bond market</li>
<li dir="ltr">Developments re-affirm how vulnerable Bitcoin is in the short-term to the highly unusual macro climate&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Following an extended period of rest in the crypto markets, the beast re-awakened last week. Crypto markets plummeted late Thursday and early Friday, led as always by Bitcoin. The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency shed 7% in what amounted to the largest one-day drop since the spectacular <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/"><u>collapse of FTX</u></a> last November.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14776592">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The year 2023 has been characterised thus far by the unusual fact that crypto&rsquo;s rise has been slow and steady. Aside from a jump in March amid the regional bank crisis, Bitcoin has been perceptively devoid of the usual spikes and freefalls.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoin price displays this clearly in the next chart, as well as Friday&rsquo;s trip south.</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14777141">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">Digging further into last week&rsquo;s price drop shows that, remarkably, Bitcoin fell 8% in just ten minutes from 9:35 PM GMT on Thursday evening. Looking at data from Coinglass, this contributed to a surge of liquidations. All in all, over one billion dollars was liquidated in what amounted to the biggest day of liquidations since the FTX demise (anytime the phrase &ldquo;since FTX&rdquo; is used in crypto, it rarely spells good news).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/21/1692627832992-b8a9c594-995b-493e-956f-c8b1d0a825a2.jpg" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="174"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The flood of liquidations highlights how much greater the volume was in derivatives markets than spot, with the latter remaining extremely thin. Order books have been <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-market-participation-continues-to-dip/"><u>perceptibly shallow</u></a> ever since Alameda evaporated amid the FTX debacle (liquidity was thin even before then).&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What caused the sell off?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The underlying cause of the volatility was a sell-off in the bond market, with yields spiking to multi-year highs. Yields on long-term US government debt neared their highest level since 2007, UK 10-year gilts rose to their highest yield since 2008, and Germany&rsquo;s 10-year bund reached its highest yield since 2011.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Higher yields spell trouble for risk assets, as we are well aware by now, with Bitcoin sent tumbling amid the tightening monetary environment last year. The recent move was borne out of investors betting that high interest rates will persist for longer than previously anticipated, or further hikes may not be as improbable as previously expected.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The inverse relationship between Bitcoin and yields has been strong, demonstrated in the below chart. Hence, Bitcoin&rsquo;s drop is not surprising in the context of the developments in the bond market last week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14777202">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">The sell-off reaffirms how vulnerable Bitcoin is to a macro situation that continues to perplex &ndash; high but falling inflation, while high interest rates contrast with record-low unemployment and relatively resilient economic data.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Getting back to the derivatives market, the shift was further evident by looking at funding rates, with the Bitcoin OI-weighted funding rate dipping below -0.01% for the first time since March.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/21/1692627851311-90ea0609-3651-4a28-8dee-b281595357b4.jpg" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="177"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Finally, negative funding rates and freefaling open interest returned. It took a while, but volatility has returned.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What next for crypto?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">What this spells going forward is up for debate. Some analysts affirm this is a mere blip, a drop sparked by complacent overleverage following a period of calm that felt like forever. A slight increase in hawkish sentiment going forward won&rsquo;t ultimately change much, they argue, for an economy which seems increasingly ambitious about achieving a soft landing.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the other hand, some fear there could be a return to 2022-like conditions. While that may seem extreme, there is every change there is a recalibration away from the borderline-celebratory stance that interest rate hikes were complete and the soft landing was already guaranteed.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">If that were the case, this could mark the end of the bear market rally for crypto. Few assets are as sensitive to global liquidity as Bitcoin is, meaning a reversion towards the tightening seen last year would undoubtedly spell red candles on price charts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This would be getting ahead of oneself, however. The macro climate remains largely unprecedented and very challenging to predict. Even the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s language betrays this, with some notable see-sawing in recent meetings.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Last Wednesday, meeting minutes said that there are &ldquo;significant upside risks to inflation, which could require further tightening of monetary policy&rdquo;. Going back to the meeting in July, minutes say that the Fed believed inflation was falling and risks &ldquo;titled to the downside&rdquo;, with Jerome Powell asserting that &ldquo;given the resilience of the economy recently, (the Fed is) no longer forecasting a recession&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While these are not necessarily conflicting &ndash; one can have inflation and tightening without a recession, it is just quite difficult (but where we have been living for the last eighteen months) &ndash; it does highlight how uncertain the whole climate is.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin is again caught in the crossfire, a risk asset subject to the whims of the wider market as it grapples with this fast-changing environment.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/over-a-billion-dollars-liquidated-in-cryptos-worst-day-since-ftx/">Over a billion dollars liquidated in crypto’s worst day since FTX</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exclusive: Sharia-compliant Islamic Coin secures funding from Optic Capital</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/exclusive-sharia-compliant-islamic-coin-secures-funding-from-optic-capital/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/exclusive-sharia-compliant-islamic-coin-secures-funding-from-optic-capital/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Switzerland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/exclusive-sharia-compliant-islamic-coin-secures-funding-from-optic-capital/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Islamic Coin is a Sharia-compliant digital money project powered by the HAQQ blockchain. Optic Capital has made an investment of undisclosed amount in the project, whose ISLM token launches on September 1. Islamic Coin, the Shariah-compliant cryptocurrency, has secured funding from Web3 venture firm Optic Capital. The funding features an undisclosed amount, the Switzerland-based crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/exclusive-sharia-compliant-islamic-coin-secures-funding-from-optic-capital/">Exclusive: Sharia-compliant Islamic Coin secures funding from Optic Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Islamic Coin is a Sharia-compliant digital money project powered by the HAQQ blockchain.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Optic Capital has made an investment of undisclosed amount in the project, whose ISLM token launches on September 1.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://islamiccoin.net/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Islamic Coin</a>, the Shariah-compliant cryptocurrency, has secured funding from Web3 venture firm Optic Capital. The funding features an undisclosed amount, the Switzerland-based crypto project revealed via a press release exclusively shared with CoinJournal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Optic Capital has invested in leading crypto projects, including Polkadot, Chainlink and Compound.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Islamic Coin (ISLM) is the native token of HAQQ, the ethics-first L1 blockchain dedicated to creating a Shariah-compliant financial ecosystem. The crypto project was co-founded by UAE entrepreneurs Mohammed AlKaff AlHashmi and Hussein Al Meeza, and is gearing up for its official launch on September 1, 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Islamic Coin attracts global VCs</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With attention towards the platform growing rapidly since its inception, much of the highlights have been on key partnerships and strategic investments. A growing list of VCs and private capital continue to back it, largely due to what it could achieve in terms of global adoption.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Optic Capital&rsquo;s investment adds to this group of major venture capital firms and private funds that have backed the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;&ldquo;<em>Islamic Coins&rsquo; unique product market fit develops a path for a community of more than 1 billion potential new blockchain users. The project is highly differentiated, hard to copy, and elegantly solves a complex adoption problem. Once we understood the potential dynamics at play, for us, it seemed like an obvious platform to back</em>&rdquo;, said Optic Capital Managing Partner.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In July, Islamic Coin team announced it had raised $200 million from investors to bring its groundbreaking funding to $400 million. Funding participants now include Alpha Blue Ocean&rsquo;s ABO Digital, DF101, and Futurecraft Ventures. The project has also attracted funding from several high-net worth individuals (HNWIs).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Apart from funding, Islamic Coin has struck key partnerships across the globe. They include the recently announced integration with DDCAP Group, Holiday Swap and over 300 Islamic Banks. In the MENA region, the project has lined up 5 partnerships across Medical, Wellness, Immigration and the Travel sectors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Islamic Coin and HAQQ are also set to be Web3 and innovation partners of multiple companies associated with Dubai&rsquo;s ruling family.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Details on the HAQQ <a href="https://haqq.network/blog" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">website</a> also shows the network has integrated with Axelar, Sushi and Allnodes among other platforms.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/exclusive-sharia-compliant-islamic-coin-secures-funding-from-optic-capital/">Exclusive: Sharia-compliant Islamic Coin secures funding from Optic Capital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/exclusive-sharia-compliant-islamic-coin-secures-funding-from-optic-capital/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin price tumbled last week on SpaceX liquidating stash</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-tumbled-last-week-on-spacex-liquidating-stash/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-tumbled-last-week-on-spacex-liquidating-stash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 12:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-tumbled-last-week-on-spacex-liquidating-stash/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SpaceX&#8217;s Bitcoin liquidation triggered a massive drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price A double top pattern suggests more weakness might come The measured move hints at further downside into the $20k area Bitcoin price failed at the $30k level twice this year. After rallying from $16k, it formed a possible double top pattern that should worry investors. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-tumbled-last-week-on-spacex-liquidating-stash/">Bitcoin price tumbled last week on SpaceX liquidating stash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>SpaceX&rsquo;s Bitcoin liquidation triggered a massive drop in Bitcoin&rsquo;s price</li>
<li>A double top pattern suggests more weakness might come</li>
<li>The measured move hints at further downside into the $20k area</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin price failed at the $30k level twice this year. After rallying from $16k, it formed a possible double top pattern that should worry investors.</p>
<p>The latest sign of weakness came last week. News that Elon Musk&rsquo;s SpaceX liquidated its entire Bitcoin stash sent the price lower. More precisely, SpaceX sold Bitcoin worth $373 million.</p>
<p>It was one of the largest daily liquidations by volume in history. In just 20 minutes, Bitcoin price crashed by more than 7% on outflows bigger than during the FTX collapse.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/21/1692620000681-a5476a1c-558a-4608-930a-3034eaf8a26e.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="427"></p>
<p>SpaceX sold its Bitcoin holdings after Tesla did the same last year. More precisely, Tesla sold last year 75% of its Bitcoin holdings.</p>
<p>So what does it mean for Bitcoin price, and can the market bounce back?</p>
<h2>A double top pattern might have formed at $30k</h2>
<p>Since the start of the year, Bitcoin price have doubled. The rally was so powerful that it triggered a wave of enthusiasm among cryptocurrency investors.</p>
<p>But the failure to hold above $ 30k led to the formation of a possible double top pattern.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/21/1692620000728-ee7cc771-9f36-4201-b45d-e8470b86aabb.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="471"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTCUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Bitcoin chart by TradingView</a></p>
<p>A double top is a reversal pattern with a measured move equal to the distance from the top to the neckline, projected from the neckline. The chart above shows the two tops formed at the $30k area and the neckline at the $25k area.</p>
<p>Therefore, the measured move equals $5k and, if projected from the neckline, suggests that Bitcoin might see $20k sooner rather than later.</p>
<p>The only way for bulls to get back in control is for Bitcoin to break above the double top area (i.e., $30k). For now, however, the bias is bearish, and the focus is on a potential bearish breakout below the neckline.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-tumbled-last-week-on-spacex-liquidating-stash/">Bitcoin price tumbled last week on SpaceX liquidating stash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-price-tumbled-last-week-on-spacex-liquidating-stash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prediction markets tokens rise as other tokens dip: Gnosis, Augur price outlook</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/prediction-markets-tokens-rise-as-other-tokens-dip-gnosis-augur-price-outlook/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/prediction-markets-tokens-rise-as-other-tokens-dip-gnosis-augur-price-outlook/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/prediction-markets-tokens-rise-as-other-tokens-dip-gnosis-augur-price-outlook/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has suffered its worst weekly percentage loss since the collapse of FTX. Some of the factors behind the dip include reports of SpaceX selling its BTC holdings and the Chinese property giant Evergrande bankruptcy filing. Top prediction markets tokens have maintained a bullish trend amid the crypto meltdown. In what has caught most crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/prediction-markets-tokens-rise-as-other-tokens-dip-gnosis-augur-price-outlook/">Prediction markets tokens rise as other tokens dip: Gnosis, Augur price outlook</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Bitcoin has suffered its worst weekly percentage loss since the collapse of FTX.</li>
<li>Some of the factors behind the dip include reports of SpaceX selling its BTC holdings and the Chinese property giant Evergrande bankruptcy filing.</li>
<li>Top prediction markets tokens have maintained a bullish trend amid the crypto meltdown.</li>
</ul>
<p>In what has caught most crypto investors by surprise, the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> has decreased by 11.2% to about US$26k. Last week has been the worst week for Bitcoin (BTC) since <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/this-week-in-crypto-sbf-explained-ftxs-collapse-in-an-interview/">FTX&rsquo;s demise</a> in November 2022.</p>
<p>The market crash has not only affected BTC, seeing that the rest of the asset class has not fared any better. <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/">Ethereum (ETH)</a> fell by approximately 9.5% to $1.7K and Binance-coin (BNB) dropped by about 9.8% to $217, just to mention a few of the top cryptocurrencies by market capitalization.</p>
<p>While most of the top cryptocurrencies experienced a price dip, popular prediction markets tokens like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/gnosis/">Gnosis (GNO)</a>, SX Network (SX), Kleros (PNK), and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/augur/">Augur (REP)</a> registered significant gains. <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">Chancer (CHANCER)</a>, a new prediction markets token is also gaining traction as its token presale continues to gain traction.</p>
<h2>What caused the crypto market to drop?</h2>
<p>The price decrease was caused by a number of causes. They included speculation that SpaceX wrote down the value of its Bitcoin assets, the collapse of the Chinese real estate firm Evergrande, and rising yields in the US.</p>
<h3>SpaceX Bitcoin holdings</h3>
<p>The Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/behind-the-curtain-of-elon-musks-secretive-spacex-revenue-growth-and-rising-costs-2c828e2b">published a report</a> late last week stating that Elon Musk&rsquo;s space exploration company SpaceX marked down the value of the Bitcoin it had on its books by US$373 million for the years 2022 and 2021. The report claims that the business also sold a portion of the BTC it had at one point over the previous two years. The WSJ has identified documents that it claims offer uncommon insights into the business&rsquo;s finances.</p>
<p>However, the WSJ&rsquo;s assertions cannot be independently verified because SpaceX is a privately held corporation. Musk acknowledged that SpaceX did acquire Bitcoin during a panel appearance in 2021, but it is unclear how much or when the commodity was purchased.</p>
<h3>Evergrande bankruptcy&nbsp;</h3>
<p>In a disclosure made over the weekend, the Chinese real estate tycoon Evergrande filed for bankruptcy protection in the United States. The corporation reportedly took action to secure its assets while still trying to control its creditors.</p>
<p>Before proposing a comprehensive off-shore debt restructuring program in 2021, Evergrande experienced a public meltdown and went into default on its obligations. The business currently seems to be on life support.</p>
<p>Investors are worried that China&rsquo;s enormous real estate market may become contagious. Country Gardens and other significant developers are not paying their debts either, and the industry&mdash;which is thought to account for up to 30% of Chinese GDP&mdash;is in serious need of government assistance.</p>
<h3>US Treasury yields</h3>
<p>US Treasury yields are skyrocketing and pushing away investors from risky markets like the crypto market and toward saving. As the US Federal Reserve gradually increased rates throughout the previous year to reach a target rate of slightly over 5%, bond yields increased.</p>
<p>As strong US economic data keeps coming out, yields have increased this week in anticipation that rate rises will continue. Since 2011, the 30-year US Treasury yield has never been higher. Treasury bonds give a high, secure yield, which is detracting from the value of other asset types like shares and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Gnosis and Augur price prediction</h2>
<p>Gnosis has risen by 0.2% while <a href="https://coinjournal.net/augur/what-is-augur/">Augur</a> has registered a 1% surge after a bear week. In the past seven days, Gnosis dropped by 8.8% while Augur fell by 11.7%.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/21/1692615418036-f475f661-ac1a-42da-a2ad-d10664110755.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="299"><span class="fr-inner" style="background: transparent;position: relative"><em>Gnosis price daily chart</em></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p>Having bounced off the support at $97.60, the Gnosis (GNO) token is expected to test the resistance at $104.75. However, that depends on whether the current daily candlestick closes above the lower band line of the Bollinger Bands indicator.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 615px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/07/21/1692615496107-5ec41bbd-0e5e-4bad-bd62-487691bc2748.jpg" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="295"><span class="fr-inner" style="background: transparent;position: relative"><em>Augur price daily chart</em></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<p class="fr-img-space-wrap2">&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p>Augur, on the other hand, seems to have slid into consolidation after erasing most of the gains it made between July 19 and July 20. All eyes are on the support at $0.3246 and the resistance at $2.1844. If the REP price jumps above the upper Bollinger Bands line, it could test the $2.1844 resistance level and if it drops below the lower Bollinger Bands line, it could drop to the support at $0.3246.</p>
<p>The prediction markets tokens including Chancer, are expected to experience significant price gains as popular games including the English Premier League and the American MSL gather steam.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/prediction-markets-tokens-rise-as-other-tokens-dip-gnosis-augur-price-outlook/">Prediction markets tokens rise as other tokens dip: Gnosis, Augur price outlook</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/prediction-markets-tokens-rise-as-other-tokens-dip-gnosis-augur-price-outlook/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche unlocks $103M AVAX this week: What’s the price outlook?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-unlocks-103m-avax-this-week-whats-the-price-outlook/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-unlocks-103m-avax-this-week-whats-the-price-outlook/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-unlocks-103m-avax-this-week-whats-the-price-outlook/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche traded at $10.65, down 1.5% in the past 24 hours. The declines for AVAX, which has plummeted from highs near $16 in mid-July, come ahead of a $103 million token unlock. Token Unlocks shows Avalanche is set to unlock 9.54 million AVAX tokens on August 26. Avalanche is closer to unlocking a significant chunk [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-unlocks-103m-avax-this-week-whats-the-price-outlook/">Avalanche unlocks $103M AVAX this week: What’s the price outlook?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Avalanche traded at $10.65, down 1.5% in the past 24 hours.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The declines for AVAX, which has plummeted from highs near $16 in mid-July, come ahead of a $103 million token unlock.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Token Unlocks shows Avalanche is set to unlock 9.54 million AVAX tokens on August 26.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche/">Avalanche</a> is closer to unlocking a significant chunk of its native token AVAX, with this coming at a time a crypto sell-off has put pressure on prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With AVAX price down nearly 14% in the past week and over 25% in the last 30 days, the impending token unlock is definitely one to watch for Avalanche.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Avalanche will soon unlock AVAX worth $103</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Details on the platform&nbsp;<a href="https://token.unlocks.app/avalanche-2" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Token Unlocks</u></a> shows that the smart contracts platform is poised for a supply surge of 9.54 million AVAX tokens. That means over $103 million worth of AVAX tokens will soon be released into circulating supply. The event is scheduled for August 26 and will see the network add to its circulating supply by 2.77%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The planned unlock has earmarked tokens for various Avalanche ecosystem players. About 2.25 million tokens will go to strategic partners, roughly 1.67 million to foundations and 4.5 million to teams. Another 1.13 million AVAX is set to be released via airdrops.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche has so far unlocked 379.79 million AVAX tokens, representing 53%. Another 340 million, or about 47%, remains locked.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AVAX price outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The core Avalanche team could see this as an opportunity for ecosystem growth. However, traders are inclined to keenly watch the market as the new supply enters the market. This is due to the potential impact of such a massive release on short term price performance, especially as selling pressure creeps in.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AVAX was at $10.65, down 1.5% in the past 24 hours at 6 am ET on Monday. According to CoinGecko, the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s 24-hour trading volume stood at $88 million, up 12%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The token&rsquo;s value has traded lower since peaking near $16 in mid-July this year. DeFiLlama data&nbsp;<a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Avalanche" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>shows</u></a> the total value locked (TVL) in the Avalanche DeFi ecosystem has also shrunk, falling more than 10% in the past seven days to $544 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;and could face further downward pressure given the prospects of a volatile reaction to the unlock. Other market conditions might also come into play.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-unlocks-103m-avax-this-week-whats-the-price-outlook/">Avalanche unlocks $103M AVAX this week: What’s the price outlook?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/avalanche-unlocks-103m-avax-this-week-whats-the-price-outlook/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
