<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 06:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OKX Liquid Marketplace Launches &#8216;Nitro Spreads&#8217; Enabling One-Click Basis Trading for Institutional Clients</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-enabling-one-click-basis-trading-for-institutional-clients/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-enabling-one-click-basis-trading-for-institutional-clients/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 06:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144284</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, June 27th, 2023, Chainwire OKX, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today launched its new &#8216;Nitro Spreads&#8217; feature on its institutional Liquid Marketplace, an OTC, futures spreads and options liquidity network, allowing traders to make complex basis trades with simple one-click execution. Basis trading is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-enabling-one-click-basis-trading-for-institutional-clients/">OKX Liquid Marketplace Launches &#8216;Nitro Spreads&#8217; Enabling One-Click Basis Trading for Institutional Clients</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dubai, UAE, June 27th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OKX</a>, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today launched its new &lsquo;Nitro Spreads&rsquo; feature on its institutional <a href="https://www.okx.com/liquid-marketplace" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Liquid Marketplace</a>, an OTC, futures spreads and options liquidity network, allowing traders to make complex basis trades with simple one-click execution.</p>
<p>Basis trading is a strategy built around trading the difference between an asset&rsquo;s price on two separate markets, such as spot vs. futures, and can generate returns when executed properly. It typically requires both legs of the trade to be managed simultaneously, which can be cumbersome. OKX&rsquo;s Nitro Spreads automates this complex trade into one click, leveraging the platform&rsquo;s superior liquidity and low latency for maximum user benefit.</p>
<p>Nitro Spreads is also one of the only basis trading tools in the crypto market in which the two legs of the trade are executed via a central orderbook, eliminating leg risk between markets. Before execution, traders can also select a guaranteed spread for a trade, mitigating unexpected price slippage. Trades are then matched and settled immediately.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>OKX Global Chief Commercial Officer Lennix Lai said</strong>: &ldquo;In the current complex market environment, institutions demand reliability, predictable returns and genuine innovation when choosing a trading venue. This is especially true in basis trading, where precision is paramount. Nitro Spreads raises the bar for the industry for efficient basis trading, and we invite institutional traders everywhere to see how it can enhance their strategies and contribute to their success.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>A variety of basis trading strategies can be executed by institutional traders through Nitro Spreads&rsquo; easy-to-use interface. Institutional traders can employ popular delta one spread strategies like calendar spreads, future rolls and funding rate farming &ndash; all in an orderbook format.</p>
<p>The on-demand OKX Liquid Marketplace provides access to deep institutional liquidity and a number of crypto trading strategies, including futures spreads, large options block trades or spot OTC, to run at scale. In April, OKX <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/okx-liquid-marketplace-records-over-usd1-billion-in-institutional-trading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">announced</a> that the Liquid Marketplace exceeded USD1 billion in trading volume during the first three months of 2023.</p>
<h3><strong>About OKX</strong></h3>
<p>OKX is the second-largest global crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 ecosystem. Trusted by more than 50 million global users, OKX is known for being the fastest and most reliable crypto trading app for traders everywhere.</p>
<p>As a top partner of English Premier League champions Manchester City FC, McLaren Formula 1, Olympian Scotty James and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo, OKX aims to supercharge the fan experience with new engagement opportunities. OKX is also the top partner of the Tribeca Festival as part of an initiative to bring more creators into web3.</p>
<p>Beyond OKX&rsquo;s exchange, the OKX Wallet is the platform&rsquo;s latest offering for people looking to explore the world of NFTs and the metaverse while trading GameFi and DeFi tokens.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: <a href="https://www.okx.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>okx.com</u></a></p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p>THIS ANNOUNCEMENT IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE ANY INVESTMENT, TAX, OR LEGAL ADVICE, NOR SHOULD IT BE CONSIDERED AN OFFER TO PURCHASE, SELL, OR HOLD DIGITAL ASSETS. DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, INVOLVE A HIGH DEGREE OF RISK, CAN FLUCTUATE GREATLY, AND CAN EVEN BECOME WORTHLESS. OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AND WHETHER TRADING OR HOLDING DIGITAL ASSETS IS SUITABLE FOR YOU IN LIGHT OF YOUR FINANCIAL CONDITION. THE VALUE OF YOUR DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS. PLEASE CONSULT YOUR LEGAL/TAX/INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL FOR QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>Press<br>
media@okx.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-enabling-one-click-basis-trading-for-institutional-clients/">OKX Liquid Marketplace Launches &#8216;Nitro Spreads&#8217; Enabling One-Click Basis Trading for Institutional Clients</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-liquid-marketplace-launches-nitro-spreads-enabling-one-click-basis-trading-for-institutional-clients/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto resiliency continues as BTC holds above $30k, AltSignals raises $1M</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-resiliency-continues-as-btc-holds-above-30k-altsignals-raises-1m/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-resiliency-continues-as-btc-holds-above-30k-altsignals-raises-1m/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 06:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-resiliency-continues-as-btc-holds-above-30k-altsignals-raises-1m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AltSignals token has raised over $1 million as it nears its target. Bitcoin has held quite steady above $30,000 even as risks in the industry rise. Bitcoin price has held steady above the $30k level as the recent momentum wanes. It was trading at the important level of $30,230 on Tuesday, a few points below [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-resiliency-continues-as-btc-holds-above-30k-altsignals-raises-1m/">Crypto resiliency continues as BTC holds above $30k, AltSignals raises $1M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals token has raised over $1 million as it nears its target.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has held quite steady above $30,000 even as risks in the industry rise.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> price has held steady above the $30k level as the recent momentum wanes. It was trading at the important level of $30,230 on Tuesday, a few points below the year-to-date high of $31,413. Still, it remains about 21% above the lowest level in June and 95% above its 2022 low. At the same time, the first stage of the&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>AltSignals</u></a><strong>&nbsp;</strong>token sale is running out.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin is outperforming stocks</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin and many altcoins is outperforming American stocks and other assets this year even as regulatory risks continue. The coin has jumped by more than 80% in 2023, bringing its total market cap to over $587 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other financial assets have risen at a slower pace than crypto. For example, while gold price soared to an all-time high this year, it has only jumped by less than 10% this year. American indices like the Nasdaq 100 and S&amp;P 500 have risen by about 15% and 35%, respectively.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin has done well in a show of resilience considering that the crypto industry has gone through hell in the past few months. In May last year, Terra and its ecosystem crashed, leading to the collapse of other companies like Voyager Digital, Three Arrows, and Celsius.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In November, the industry experienced the collapse of FTX, a leading exchange that was valued at over $30 billion. Crypto investors lost over $8 billion following the collapse, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/ftx-insolvent-what-next-for-crypto/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And this year, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) decided to sue Coinbase and Binance, the two biggest players in the industry. The SEC made several allegations, including accusations that the two were offering unregulated products to American customers.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, the performance of Bitcoin is a reflection that cryptocurrencies are extremely resilient. In fact, Jerome Powell, the head of the Federal Reserve believes that Bitcoin has a lot of staying power.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">AltSignals token sale continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This resilience explains why several companies have managed to raise millions of dollars this year. Earlier this year, Metacade raised over $16 million from investors. Its developers are building a gaming platform that will compete with the likes of Decentraland and Sandbox.</p>
<p dir="ltr">AltSignals has raised over $1 million its highly successful token sale. As you can see&nbsp;<strong>here,&nbsp;</strong>the developers have sold 95.23% of all the available ASI tokens. They have raised over $1.028 million in the first stage of the sale. Each token is going for $0.015 and the developers will boost it by 25% in the next stage of the sale.</p>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, AltSignals is a company that hopes to use artificial intelligence to disrupt the financial services industry. The developers aim to improve its service by incorporating AI in its existing platform which is already profitable platform.</p>
<p>After the first phase, the developers will launch the second phase of the token sale. According to its&nbsp;<a href="https://token.altsignals.io/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong> the developers will then get to work ahead of the new AI platform launch. They will also list the token in key centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-resiliency-continues-as-btc-holds-above-30k-altsignals-raises-1m/">Crypto resiliency continues as BTC holds above $30k, AltSignals raises $1M</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-resiliency-continues-as-btc-holds-above-30k-altsignals-raises-1m/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget formally enters Turkey with a new website</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 21:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144239</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitget launched a dedicated website for Turkish users on Monday. Bitget Turkey features a Fiat Gateway that allows using TRY to trade. TokenInsight named it among the top 4 centralised exchanged in Q1. Bitget continues to execute on its commitment to expand globally. On Monday, the crypto exchange formally entered Turkey with a dedicated website [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/">Bitget formally enters Turkey with a new website</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitget launched a dedicated website for Turkish users on Monday.</li>
<li>Bitget Turkey features a Fiat Gateway that allows using TRY to trade.</li>
<li>TokenInsight named it among the top 4 centralised exchanged in Q1.</li>
</ul>
<p>Bitget continues to execute on its commitment to expand globally. On Monday, the crypto exchange formally entered Turkey with a dedicated website &ndash; Bitget TR.</p>
<h2>Turkey is a fast-growing crypto market</h2>
<p>Its new website aims at offering localized services to the crypto enthusiasts in Turkey. The transcontinental country is <a href="https://www.statista.com/outlook/dmo/fintech/digital-assets/cryptocurrencies/turkey#revenue" target="_blank" rel="noopener">rapidly growing</a> in terms of crypto adoption.</p>
<blockquote><p>The launch of Bitget TR enables us to provide localized, convenient, and compliant crypto services to users in Turkey.</p></blockquote>
<p>Last month, Bitget had successfully registered as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) in Poland (<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-registers-as-a-vasp-in-poland/">read more</a>). TokenInsight names it among the top four centralised exchanges in the first quarter of 2023.</p>
<p>Bitget now has a team of 1,300 across more than 60 countries and regions.</p>
<h2>Bitget TR comes with a Fiat Gateway</h2>
<p>More importantly, Bitget Turkey features a Fiat Gateway as well that enables local users to use TRY &ndash; the Turkish Lira to trade on the website.</p>
<p>The user-friendly platform allows Turkish users to easily make deposits or withdraw funds in their local currency. Gracy Chen, the Managing Director of Bitget said in a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/bitget-launches-localized-website-with-fiat-gateway-for-turkish-users-301862916.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">press release</a> today:</p>
<blockquote><p>We will continue to gain trust and recognition with the launch of more localized services in collaboration with local partners.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitget that has the legendary Lionel Messi as a partner continues to expand its footprint at a time when peers <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2023/jun/05/binance-sued-sec-cryptocurrency-accused-mishandling-funds" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/the-sec-strikes-again-first-binance-now-coinbase/">Coinbase</a> are facing intense scrutiny from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitget-formally-enters-turkey-bitget-tr/">Bitget formally enters Turkey with a new website</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hut 8 secures $50 million credit facility from Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hut 8 will have the option to draw $20 million and $15 million after the first tranche. The $50 million loan facility will mature one year after the first borrowing, and bear interest. CEO Jaime Leverton noted in a statement that the funds will give Hut 8 financial flexibility ahead of Bitcoin&#8217;s halving. Bitcoin mining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/">Hut 8 secures $50 million credit facility from Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Hut 8 will have the option to draw $20 million and $15 million after the first tranche.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The $50 million loan facility will mature one year after the first borrowing, and bear interest.</li>
<li dir="ltr">CEO Jaime Leverton noted in a statement that the funds will give Hut 8 financial flexibility ahead of Bitcoin&rsquo;s halving.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin-mining/">Bitcoin mining</a> company Hut 8 Mining has announced a $50 million loan facility secured from crypto exchange Coinbase&rsquo;s subsidiary Coinbase Credit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8 will use the funds to support its operations, including closing the deal for the merger with US-based miner Bitcoin Corp (USBTC).</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Financial flexibility</h2>
<p dir="ltr">According to details in a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/hut-8-announces-us50-million-credit-facility-301861407.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a> published on Monday, Hut 8 can access the loan facility in three tranches. The first, expected to be secured shortly is a term loan worth $15 million, and there are options for further drawings of $20 million and $15 million &ndash; the second of which will be a delayed draw term facility available one to two months later.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The mining platform will be able to tap into the third tranche of $15 million 15 business days after it closes its merger with USBTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>T</em><em>his credit facility gives us additional financial flexibility</em>,&rdquo; Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton commented. He noted that the loan will help the company maintain its dynamic Bitcoin treasury as the market edges closer to the next Bitcoin halving.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>All amounts borrowed under the Credit Facility will bear interest at a rate equal to (a) the greater of (i) the federal funds rate on the date of the applicable borrowing, and (ii) 3.25%, plus (b) 5.0%. The Credit Facility matures 364 days after the date of the first borrowing</em>,&rdquo; the company wrote in the press release.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The credit facility will mature 364 days after Hut 8&rsquo;s first borrowing and loan obligations are secured by the miner&rsquo;s Bitcoin held by Coinbase Custody.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Hut 8 stock was down 9% at the time of writing, although it remained more than 200% up in 2023 after rallying alongside cryptocurrencies. COIN shares were on the other hand trading at 2.3% higher on the day and 87% YTD.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/">Hut 8 secures $50 million credit facility from Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/hut-8-secures-50-million-credit-facility-from-coinbase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin’s correlation with Nasdaq 100 falls to 3-year low</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-down-to-3-year-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 17:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nasdaq]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-down-to-3-year-low/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s correlation with the Nasdaq 100 has fallen to just 3% in June, down from the overall 60% in 2022. BTC price has outperformed the stock index year-to-date and over the past year. Bitcoin price jumped to a year high last week after news of a spot Bitcoin ETF application by global asset manager BlackRock. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-down-to-3-year-low/">Bitcoin’s correlation with Nasdaq 100 falls to 3-year low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin&rsquo;s correlation with the Nasdaq 100 has fallen to just 3% in June, down from the overall 60% in 2022.</li>
<li dir="ltr">BTC price has outperformed the stock index year-to-date and over the past year.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price jumped to a year high last week after news of a spot Bitcoin ETF application by global asset manager BlackRock.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a>&rsquo;s correlation with tech stocks has declined sharply over the past few months, more so after the benchmark cryptocurrency&rsquo;s rally to a new year-to-date price this month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to an<a href="https://research.kaiko.com/insights/whats-driving-bitcoins-rally" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>analysis</u></a> published by market data research platform Kaiko released today, June 26, BTC has continued to break its correlation with the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/nasdaq/">Nasdaq</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kaiko researchers note that in June, Bitcoin&rsquo;s and the Nasdaq 100 trading trajectory diverged to currently sit at just 3% correlation.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin outperformed Nasdaq 100 in June</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The falling correlation, according to Kaiko, has been enhanced by the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s double digit gains in June.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In this, BTC outperformed the tech equities&rsquo; 3%. While the Nasdaq 100 has gained about 35% year-to-date, its managed only 22% in the past year. BTC on the other hand is up more than 108% YTD and over 72% over the past year, even with the sell-offs occasioned by the collapse of TerraUSD and FTX in 2022.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It&rsquo;s a performance that has seen the lockstep trading witnessed in the second half of last year shrink from 60%, the Kaiko analysts pointed out.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">CoinJournal analyst Dan Ashmore also recently looked at the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-nasdaq-100-and-bitcoin-correlation-has-faded/">fading correlation</a> between the top crypto asset and stocks, examining the whys.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BlackRock ETF news major bullish catalyst</h2>
<p dir="ltr">On current outlook, Bitcoin has outperformed traditional risk assets even after a negative sentiment permeated the market following the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regulatory actions against Binance and Coinbase. Earlier, BTC had performed much better as stocks floundered amid the banking sector turmoil.</p>
<p dir="ltr">And just this past week, as equities broke their winning streak on new macroeconomic fears, Bitcoin led the crypto market higher &ndash; fueled by news of BlackRock&rsquo;s ETF filing. BTC currently sits around $30,260, down 1% in the past 24 hours, but still up by over 15% in the past seven days.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CoinShares&rsquo; Chief Strategy Officer Meltem Demirors<a href="https://twitter.com/Melt_Dem/status/1673362112653975554" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;<u>notes</u></a> that together with BlackRock, companies with a combined $27 trillion in client assets are working to offer customers access to the crypto asset class.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ last week's <a href="https://twitter.com/BlackRock?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BlackRock</a> spot Bitcoin ETF filing was big news! </p>
<p>but, it's not the only story. many of the largest financial institutions in the US are actively working to provide access to Bitcoin and more.</p>
<p>a quick glance &ndash; $27 trillion of client assets here! <a href="https://t.co/azmHZmUL2a">pic.twitter.com/azmHZmUL2a</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Meltem Demirors (@Melt_Dem) <a href="https://twitter.com/Melt_Dem/status/1673362112653975554?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">But while the Blackrock-inspired ETF frenzy remains a key bullish catalyst, other metrics such as open interest suggest growing inflows and speculation. Bitcoin bulls holding above the psychological $30k level or bouncing from fresh retest below that could form the next leg for BTC price upside action.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As highlighted here, the $34k level is increasingly looking as the next major hurdle for BTC in the short term.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoins-correlation-with-nasdaq-100-down-to-3-year-low/">Bitcoin’s correlation with Nasdaq 100 falls to 3-year low</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance drops its license application in Austria</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Austria GmbH has revoked its license application as a virtual asset service provider from the Austrian Financial Market Authority (FMA). So far, Binance has withdrawn registration in the Netherlands and the United Kingdom. The only European countries where Binance is legally operating are France, Italy, Spain, Poland, Sweden, and Lithuania. Binance Austria GmbH, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/">Binance drops its license application in Austria</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Binance Austria GmbH has revoked its license application as a virtual asset service provider from the Austrian Financial Market Authority (FMA).</li>
<li>So far, Binance has withdrawn registration in the Netherlands and the United Kingdom.</li>
<li>The only European countries where Binance is legally operating are France, Italy, Spain, Poland, Sweden, and Lithuania.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> Austria GmbH, a wholly owned subsidiary of Binance, has cancelled its license registration from the Austrian Financial Market Authority (FMA) amid the increasing hitches stemming from the problems that Binance has had with financial authorities worldwide.</p>
<p>After facing increased regulatory <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/opinion-binance-sued-by-sec-an-inevitable-but-ominous-day-for-crypto/">obstacles from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</a> and in Europe, cryptocurrency exchange Binance has withdrawn its license applications in different European countries including the United Kingdom and the Netherlands as earlier reported <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-exchange-binance-announces-exit-from-the-dutch-market/">here</a>.</p>
<p>However, Binance is still legally registered to operate in Sweden, Italy, Spain, France, Poland, and Lithuania. Belgium&rsquo;s financial regulator, last week, also ordered Binance to cease all services in the country.</p>
<p>While responding to a prominent media outlet, a Binance spokesperson said:</p>
<p><em>&ldquo;We are unable to share details of our conversations with regulators, however, we remain committed to acting in compliance with our obligations wherever Binance operates. Our current focus in Europe is on ensuring that we will be in full compliance with the requirements of MiCA (Markets in Crypto Assets) when it is implemented at the end of next year.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2>Binance Austria GmbH</h2>
<p>Binance reportedly launched Binance Austria GmbH in 2022 with the aim of obtaining a license for the subsidiary.</p>
<p>However, the subsidiary is said to have had a hard time with the Austrian regulator leading to the decision to cut short its license application process in the wake of the global condemnation of the exchange.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/">Binance drops its license application in Austria</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-drops-its-license-application-in-austria/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chancer presale 35% sold out as top prediction markets tokens turn green</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-35-sold-out-as-top-prediction-markets-tokens-turn-green/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-35-sold-out-as-top-prediction-markets-tokens-turn-green/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-35-sold-out-as-top-prediction-markets-tokens-turn-green/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Chancer presale has raised $357,330.51 since launch. The presale seeks to raise $15 million in twelve stages. The price of the CHANCER token is expected to gradually rise through the twelve stages to $0.021. Top prediction markets tokens including TotemFi (TOTM), Gnosis (GNO), Augur (REP), Polkamarkets (POLK), PlotX (PLOT), and OptionRoom (ROOM) have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-35-sold-out-as-top-prediction-markets-tokens-turn-green/">Chancer presale 35% sold out as top prediction markets tokens turn green</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The Chancer presale has raised $357,330.51 since launch.</li>
<li>The presale seeks to raise $15 million in twelve stages.</li>
<li>The price of the CHANCER token is expected to gradually rise through the twelve stages to $0.021.</li>
</ul>
<p>Top prediction markets tokens including TotemFi (TOTM), Gnosis (GNO), <a href="https://coinjournal.net/augur/what-is-augur/">Augur</a> (REP), Polkamarkets (POLK), PlotX (PLOT), and OptionRoom (ROOM) have been trending in the last week. Polkamarkets (POLK) has gained the most at 9.56% in the last seven days, followed by Gnosis (GNO) and PlotX (PLOT) that has gained 9.25% and 6.77% respectively.</p>
<p>Well, while the prediction markets tokens are responding to the current bullish crypto market sentiment, a new predictions market token entrant, CHANCER, is making waves since its presale launch. CHANCER&rsquo;s parent platform is the world&rsquo;s first decentralized predictive market-making platform that is leveraging blockchain to decentralize betting.</p>
<h2>The decentralized prediction marker maker trailblazer</h2>
<p>The new betting platform, <a href="https://chancer.com/">Chancer</a>, aims to firmly place bettors in control of the betting markets. By allowing users to design their own betting markets, choose their own odds, and set their own rules, it has completely changed the betting industry.</p>
<p>The designers of Chancer, Adam and Paul Kelbie, are confident that the betting platform will fundamentally change the way people wager and unquestionably bring gambling back to life.</p>
<p>Chancer positions itself as a betting facilitator rather than a betting establishment by allowing betters to create peer-to-peer (P2P) bets. The types of bets that can be made by gamblers range from small, informal wagers among close friends to massive, viral bets involving thousands of gamblers, like picking the winner of the Best Director Oscar or forecasting the Champions League final score.</p>
<p>Additionally, Chancer accepts wagers on any prediction or event, not just sports, in contrast to the majority of bookmakers. Users of Chancer have total control over their wagers due to its decentralized nature.</p>
<p>The native token of Chancer, &ldquo;CHANCER,&rdquo; which is a Binance Smart Chain (BSC) token currently in the presale phase, is used for all bet payouts.</p>
<p>As a great incentive for different types of investors, Chancer&rsquo;s well-planned roadmap outlines a variety of product use cases for the CHANCER token after the presale.</p>
<p>Chancer&rsquo;s main goal is to achieve and maintain true decentralization. No one party can take over the network thanks to true decentralization. Users will be able to control decision-making in the platform&rsquo;s development and operation under quadratic governance thanks to the platform&rsquo;s proof of stake consensus mechanism.</p>
<h2>Investors confident in Chancer</h2>
<p>Investors are optimistic about the CHANCER token&rsquo;s value in addition to the betting platform&rsquo;s potential for greatness due to its novel approach to betting that uses blockchain to democratize market setting and management.</p>
<p>CHNACER is being sold for $0.01 in the first stage of the current presale. However, interested parties can only buy their CHANCER tokens with <a href="https://coinjournal.net/binance-coin/">BNB</a> or BUSD tokens.</p>
<p>The Chancer presale timelines state that the price of CHNACER is anticipated to keep increasing with each stage of the presale, reaching $0.021 in the final stage, stage 12 which according to the roadmap is expected to be concluded in Q2, 2023.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-35-sold-out-as-top-prediction-markets-tokens-turn-green/">Chancer presale 35% sold out as top prediction markets tokens turn green</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/chancer-presale-35-sold-out-as-top-prediction-markets-tokens-turn-green/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s why the Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price has just gone parabolic</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-has-just-gone-parabolic/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-has-just-gone-parabolic/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-has-just-gone-parabolic/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. The coin has surged by over 150% from the lowest level in May. This rally is being supported by the Bitcoin ETF applications. Bitcoin Cash price continued surging on Monday even as BTC and other cryptocurrencies moved sideways. The BCH [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-has-just-gone-parabolic/">Here’s why the Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price has just gone parabolic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The coin has surged by over 150% from the lowest level in May.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">This rally is being supported by the Bitcoin ETF applications.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/"><u>Bitcoin Cash</u></a> price continued surging on Monday even as BTC and other cryptocurrencies moved sideways. The BCH coin jumped to a high of $228.72, the highest level since May 14th of last year. In all, the coin has jumped by more than 150% from the lowest level in May, making it one of the top-performing cryptocurrencies in the world.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">BCH rally continues</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/"><u>Bitcoin</u></a> and other cryptocurrencies have been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. This rally is mostly because of the recent&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/"><u>crypto news</u></a><strong>.&nbsp;</strong>Companies like Blackrock, WisdomTree, and Invesco announced plans to launch their Bitcoin ETF. If this is accepted, it will likely help many institutional investors allocate funds to Bitcoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These ETF proposals do not impact Bitcoin Cash directly. However, analysts believe that these companies will file their Bitcoin Cash spot ETF proposals if the Bitcoin one is accepted. Bitcoin Cash, as with BTC, is seen as a commodity since it is a hard fork of Bitcoin itself.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other cryptocurrencies that could benefit in all this are Litecoin, Bitcoin SV, and Ethererum Classsic. There are concerns that Ethereum will be avoided because of its staking feature, which SEC believes contravenes securities law.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price also jumped after it became one of the four cryptocurrencies offered by EDX Markets, the new Fidelity, Schwab, and Citadel-backed&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/compare/best-cryptocurrency-exchanges/"><u>crypto exchange</u></a><strong>.&nbsp;</strong>The other cryptocurrencies offered by the exchange are Ethereum, Bitcoin, and Litecoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Further, Bitcoin Cash is doing well since it has a lower price than Bitcoin itself. The BTC and BCH ratio currently stands at 131, meaning that 1 Bitcoin is worth about 131 BCHs.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/26/1687795089463-3c5f9d41-797f-48d0-a81e-36c981660f2c.png" style="width: 511px;height: 248.687px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="511" height="248.687"></p>
<p dir="ltr">The 4H chart shows that the Bitcoin Cash price has been in a strong bullish trend in the past few days. It has jumped above the important resistance point at $124, the highest point on May 9th. The coin has moved sharply above the 25-day and 50-day moving averages (MA).</p>
<p dir="ltr">It has also invalidated the upper part of the double-top pattern at $221.10. This was an important level since it was the highest level last week. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved above the overbought level.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, there is a likelihood that the BCH price will continue rising as buyers target the next key resistance point at $250. A move below the double-top neckline at $184 will signal that there are more sellers left in the market.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How to buy Bitcoin Cash</h2>
<p dir="ltr"></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-has-just-gone-parabolic/">Here’s why the Bitcoin Cash (BCH) price has just gone parabolic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/heres-why-the-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-has-just-gone-parabolic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HSBC to offer Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs in Hong Kong</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/hsbc-to-offer-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etfs-in-hong-kong/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 15:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HSBC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/hsbc-to-offer-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etfs-in-hong-kong/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HSBC will offer access to three ETFs listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, including CSOP Bitcoin Futures ETF and CSOP Ethereum Futures ETF. The banking behemoth also launched a new service dubbed Virtual Asset Investor Education Center that offers educational and risk disclosure materials for customers. Customers will have to confirm the guidelines before [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hsbc-to-offer-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etfs-in-hong-kong/">HSBC to offer Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs in Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">HSBC will offer access to three ETFs listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, including CSOP Bitcoin Futures ETF and CSOP Ethereum Futures ETF.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The banking behemoth also launched a new service dubbed Virtual Asset Investor Education Center that offers educational and risk disclosure materials for customers.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Customers will have to confirm the guidelines before they are allowed to trade the listed ETFs.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">HSBC, the largest bank in Hong Kong, is offering cryptocurrency exchange traded funds (ETFs) to its clients, reports say.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Specifically, HSBC is allowing its customers to trade <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> and Ethereum ETFs listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange. The banking behemoth is now the first bank to offer clients access to crypto ETFs in Hong Kong, crypto journalist Colin Wu <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1673263927780859904" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a> early Monday.</p>
<p dir="ltr">HSBC will use the new offering to extend its users&rsquo; exposure to the crypto sector, a move that could see Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs be available to over millions of people using the bank&rsquo;s mobile app.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, Hong Kong lists three cryptocurrency ETFs: the CSOP Bitcoin Futures ETF, the CSOP Ethereum Futures ETF, and the Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">SCOOP: HSBC, the largest bank in Hong Kong, today allows its customers to buy and sell Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs listed on the Hong Kong exchange, and is also the first bank in Hong Kong to allow it. The move will expand local users&rsquo; exposure to cryptocurrencies in Hong Kong. <a href="https://t.co/vH0LieSVGw">pic.twitter.com/vH0LieSVGw</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1673263927780859904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">HSBC also reportedly launched a Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre, which provides access to educational materials and risk disclosures. Investors looking to buy and sell the listed ETFs will need to confirm they have read and understood the details before HSBC allows them to invest in any crypto-related products.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These products will be available via HSBC Hong Kong&rsquo;s Easy Invest app, Mobile banking app and online.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto ETFs news buoy BTC, altcoins</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Today&rsquo;s HSBC news follows recent reports that noted the Hong Kong Monetary Authority has asked major banks to offer financial services to crypto exchanges. This came after the Hong Kong securities watchdog allowed exchanges to begin offering crypto trading services to retail investors.</p>
<p dir="ltr">At the same time, the crypto ETFs space received a major boost when $9 trillion asset manager BlackRock filed for its first spot Bitcoin ETF from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Many other companies, including WisdomTree and Invesco have since followed suit. In the process, Bitcoin price rallied to a new year-to-date high above $31k as sentiment flipped bullish. Ethereum also traded higher, coming close to $1,930 last week.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/hsbc-to-offer-bitcoin-and-ethereum-etfs-in-hong-kong/">HSBC to offer Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs in Hong Kong</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
