<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>&lt;title&gt;</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<description>&lt;description&gt;</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:44:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.coinspeaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News | Coinspeaker</title>
	<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Eli Lilly Set to Close $2.4B Dice Therapeutics Acquisition to Treat Autoimmune Diseases</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deals News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dice therapeutics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eli lilly]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259599</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/">Eli Lilly Set to Close $2.4B Dice Therapeutics Acquisition to Treat Autoimmune Diseases</a></p>
<p>Eli Lilly will spend approximately $2.4 billion acquiring Dice Therapeutics to create more drugs for combating autoimmune diseases.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/">Eli Lilly Set to Close $2.4B Dice Therapeutics Acquisition to Treat Autoimmune Diseases</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/">Eli Lilly Set to Close $2.4B Dice Therapeutics Acquisition to Treat Autoimmune Diseases</a></p>
<p>American pharmaceutical company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/eli-lilly-and-company/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eli Lilly</a> has announced it is set to purchase biopharma company Dice Therapeutics. Eli Lilly hopes the $2.4 billion deal will help the company develop more drugs to treat immune diseases.</p>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lilly-to-acquire-dice-therapeutics-to-advance-innovation-in-immunology-301854537.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">press release</a> from both companies, Eli Lilly will buy all of Dice’s outstanding shares via a tender offer. Already approved by both boards of directors, the deal will price each share at $48, to a total of nearly $2.4 billion. The agreement also allows for a second-step merger for Eli Lilly to buy any Dice shares not included with the tender offer. The second step is subject to a successful closing of the tender offer, which depends on expected closing conditions, such as an official antitrust clearance.</p>
<h2>Terms of the Eli Lilly and Dice Deal</h2>
<p>The press release also states other terms of the agreement. For instance, the deal allows Eli Lilly to choose whether the agreement is an asset acquisition or a business merger. Furthermore, according to the agreement, the transaction will likely close in Q3 2023 as no financing conditions are required.</p>
<p>Speaking on the deal, Dice Therapeutics CEO Kevin Judice said the company is eager to have its products benefit from the resources Eli Lilly presents. Judice also said there is great potential as both companies embark on a “united quest for scientific innovation&#8221;.</p>
<p>For Eli Lilly’s executive vice president Patrik Jonsson, the partnership between both companies will considerably help people with related health challenges. Jonsson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“In combination with its novel technology and expertise in drug discovery, DICE’s talented workforce and passion for innovation will enhance our efforts to make life better for people living with devastating autoimmune diseases. We welcome DICE colleagues to Lilly and, together, we can tackle the challenges ahead in finding new treatments for patients with significant unmet medical needs.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Founded in 1876, Eli Lilly has developed medications and diagnostics that help treat several ailments, including cancer and diabetes. Its portfolio contains drugs that tackle disease in the areas of neurodegeneration, immunology, neuroscience, and cardiovascular disorders.</p>
<p>Common Eli Lilly drugs include Taltz and Olumiant. Last year, Taltz, a treatment for plaque psoriasis and psoriatic arthritis, brought Eli Lilly $2.48 billion. Olumiant, which treats rheumatoid arthritis, pulled sales worth $830.5 million in 2022 as well.</p>
<p>To grow its portfolio and expand offerings, Eli Lilly is already investing in artificial intelligence (AI). The company is also studying its benefits for drug discovery. <a href="https://africa.businessinsider.com/news/the-ceo-of-pharma-giant-eli-lilly-shares-3-ways-ai-could-transform-his-industry/448t52n" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Speaking to Business Insider</a>, Eli Lilly CEO David Ricks believes AI is “one of the most exciting technological moves” in a while. A spokesperson said the company is investing in machine learning and AI for several endeavors. Some of these include drug discovery, robotic-press automation, natural-language generation, and chatbots.</p>
<p>For drug discovery, Ricks also said AI will help Eli Lilly to automate specific mundane business processes. According to him, doing this would help to “augment human productivity”.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/">Eli Lilly Set to Close $2.4B Dice Therapeutics Acquisition to Treat Autoimmune Diseases</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/eli-lilly-2-4b-dice-therapeutics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Expands to Asia with Hub in Singapore: Strategic Move amidst Regulatory Challenges</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marco T. Lanz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cz]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/">Gemini Expands to Asia with Hub in Singapore: Strategic Move amidst Regulatory Challenges</a></p>
<p>Gemini highlighted their plans to diversify their customer base and reduce the dependence on the US market.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/">Gemini Expands to Asia with Hub in Singapore: Strategic Move amidst Regulatory Challenges</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/">Gemini Expands to Asia with Hub in Singapore: Strategic Move amidst Regulatory Challenges</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/gemini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Gemini</a>, the US-based exchange of the Winklevoss Twins, has announced its plans to establish a center in Singapore as part of its future expansion into the Asian market.</p>
<p>According to Gemini&#8217;s <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-announces-expansion-plans-in-apac" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a>, the company intends to hire over 100 employees in the next 12 months to capitalize on the growth potential of cryptocurrencies in the APAC (Asia-Pacific) market.</p>
<h2>Gemini Expanding to Singapore</h2>
<p>While Gemini has previously stated that it has no plans to abandon the US market, they have indicated, like other exchanges under attack by the SEC, their intentions to expand into other crypto-friendly countries due to regulatory uncertainty in the US.</p>
<p>As a result, Gemini is committed to &#8220;implementing its international vision for the future of the platform, aiming to unlock a new era of financial freedom&#8221;.</p>
<p>Gemini has not provided an official date for its expansion. However, they have highlighted their plans to diversify their customer base and reduce their dependence on the US market as the SEC intensifies regulations and lawsuits against cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<h2>Cryptocurrency Exchanges Face Uncertainty following SEC Attacks</h2>
<p>In early June, the SEC filed a <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">lawsuit</a> against Binance.US, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a>, and its CEO and founder, Changpeng &#8220;CZ&#8221; Zhao, alleging that they had violated US securities laws in order to enrich themselves with &#8220;billions of US dollars, putting investor assets at risk&#8221;.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the SEC issued an <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-market-crash-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">emergency order</a> requesting the freezing of the assets of Binance.US holding companies and the repatriation of assets to the country. However, both entities ultimately<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-us-sec-deal-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> reached an agreement</a> to avoid asset freezing in exchange for greater transparency and oversight. This represents a significant victory for Binance in its dispute against the SEC.</p>
<p>Similarly, Coinbase, which was <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">sued by the SEC</a> the day after Binance, for failing to register as a securities exchange, clearinghouse, and broker, despite providing those services to its clients. Additionally, regulators claimed that the exchange sold several unregistered securities on its platform.</p>
<p>Like Binance, Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coinbase-sec-answers-court-order/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">responded to the SEC&#8217;s attack</a> by urging regulators to clearly address the regulatory issues surrounding cryptocurrencies considered as securities, a matter they have not wanted or known how to respond to until now.</p>
<p>Therefore, Gemini&#8217;s expansion reflects the company&#8217;s determination to seek opportunities beyond the United States, where the crypto industry is welcomed rather than suppressed by a few power-hungry individuals.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/">Gemini Expands to Asia with Hub in Singapore: Strategic Move amidst Regulatory Challenges</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/gemini-asia-singapore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Denounces Entity Registered in UK, Issues Cease and Desist</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259541</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/">Binance Denounces Entity Registered in UK, Issues Cease and Desist</a></p>
<p>Binance has confirmed it is not affiliated with a supposed branch in the UK after a Reddit post shared the exchange's alleged UK address.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/">Binance Denounces Entity Registered in UK, Issues Cease and Desist</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/">Binance Denounces Entity Registered in UK, Issues Cease and Desist</a></p>
<p>Major crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> announced that it issued a cease and desist order to Binance Ltd in the UK. In a <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1671091589286973440?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">tweet</a> from Binance’s official account, the exchange said the referenced company has no business with the company.</p>
<p>The Binance tweet was in response to a Reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Buttcoin/comments/14dkyia/the_billion_dollar_crypto_company_binance_has_a/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">post</a> brought to Twitter, stating that the Binance office in the UK is a “utility closet”. The post includes a picture of the supposed address in Mildenhall, a small town in Suffolk County. Refuting any affiliations with the company or the location in the picture, Binance described the entity as “a scam company &#8211; not affiliated with Binance in any way”.</p>
<p>According to the UK’s company registrar, Companies House, Binance Ltd at that address shares the same small nondescript building with <a href="https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/advanced-search/get-results?companyNameIncludes=&amp;companyNameExcludes=&amp;registeredOfficeAddress=82A+James+Carter+Road%2C+Mildenhall&amp;incorporationFromDay=&amp;incorporationFromMonth=&amp;incorporationFromYear=&amp;incorporationToDay=&amp;incorporationToMonth=&amp;incorporationToYear=&amp;status=active&amp;sicCodes=&amp;dissolvedFromDay=&amp;dissolvedFromMonth=&amp;dissolvedFromYear=&amp;dissolvedToDay=&amp;dissolvedToMonth=&amp;dissolvedToYear=" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">more than 2,400 companies</a>. Companies House records show that the firm registered at the address is OfficeServe, a firm that provides a physical address for interested companies.</p>
<h2>Binance Issues Cease and Desist to Scam Entities in the United Kingdom and Nigeria</h2>
<p>The UK cease and desist is the second one Binance has announced this week. On Sunday, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1670369403223900160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1670369403223900160%7Ctwgr%5E190e7c86f85755bea457d2aa57f2dcf479a53e57%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fnairametrics.com%2F2023%2F06%2F18%2Fbinance-ceo-declares-binance-nigeria-limited-a-scam-entity%2F" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">said</a> the exchange has issued a cease and desist to Binance Nigeria Limited. The issuance immediately requires the Nigerian entity to stop all activities purporting any association with the exchange.</p>
<p>Binance announced a cease and desist only a few days after the Nigerian Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-nigeria-illegal-crypto-exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">declared</a> Binance Nigeria an illegal entity. The SEC <a href="https://sec.gov.ng/circular-on-the-activities-of-binance-nigeria-limited/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ordered</a> Binance Nigeria Limited to “stop soliciting Nigerian investors in any form whatsoever”. The SEC’s publication also warns the Nigerian public about the dangers of investing in cryptocurrencies, describing them as “extremely risky”.</p>
<p>In February 2021, the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) <a href="https://www.premiumtimesng.com/business/440826-updated-cbn-orders-nigerian-banks-to-close-cryptocurrency-accounts.html?tztc=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">directed</a> financial institutions to stop facilitating crypto transactions. In a letter sent to the country’s Deposit Money Banks (DMBs), Non-Financial Institutions (NBFIs), and other financial institutions (OFIs), the CBN also directed the institutions to immediately close all accounts owned by persons or entities conducting crypto transactions.</p>
<p>About a month later, CBN Deputy Governor Adamu Lamtek clarified the crypto ban. According to him, the CBN’s directive did not outrightly ban crypto trading and transactions. The order was to keep crypto activities away from the banking sector.</p>
<h2>Binance UK Cancels FCA Permissions</h2>
<p>Binance Markets Limited (BML), a UK subsidiary of the Binance exchange, has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-withdraws-request-fca-uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">withdrawn</a> its registration with the country’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). According to an official FCA <a href="https://register.fca.org.uk/s/firm?id=001b000000nojfNAAQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener">publication</a>, BML can “no longer provide regulated activities and products”. In another <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/news/news-stories/consumer-warning-binance-markets-limited-and-binance-group" target="_blank" rel="noopener">update</a>, the FCA clarified that:</p>
<blockquote><p>“No other entity in the Binance Group holds any form of UK authorisation, registration or licence to conduct regulated activity in the UK.”</p></blockquote>
<p>BML launched in June 2020 following Binance’s acquisition of a firm called EddieUK. At the time, Binance acquired the firm to enter the UK market and launch Binance.UK, similar to Binance.US.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/">Binance Denounces Entity Registered in UK, Issues Cease and Desist</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-denounces-entity-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Backed by Fidelity and Citadel Securities Starts Operations in US</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin etf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blackrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[citadel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[edx markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fidelity investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nasdaq]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/">Crypto Exchange Backed by Fidelity and Citadel Securities Starts Operations in US</a></p>
<p>EDX Markets plans to step into the crypto space just when the regulatory developments are quite hot and the US SEC has been cracking hard on crypto firms. </p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/">Crypto Exchange Backed by Fidelity and Citadel Securities Starts Operations in US</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/">Crypto Exchange Backed by Fidelity and Citadel Securities Starts Operations in US</a></p>
<p>The cryptocurrency landscape in America seems to be undergoing a seismic shift, and it&#8217;s still too early to say whether it is for the good or the bad. As per the latest <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/crypto-exchange-backed-by-citadel-securities-fidelity-schwab-starts-operations-597f6d46" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> from Wall Street Journal, crypto exchange EDX Markets is planning to start operations in the US.</p>
<p>Interestingly, crypto exchange EDX Markets is backed by some of the top financial giants such as Fidelity Investments, Citadel Securities, and Charles Schwab. As the cryptocurrency exchange steps into the market, it is wary of all the troubles at crypto exchange FTX and Binance, that unfolded over the last year.</p>
<p>The scope of the operations for EDX Markets is still not clear, however, the WSJ report notes that the crypto exchange won&#8217;t directly serve individual customers or handle customers&#8217; digital assets.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, EDX Markets partnered with Paxos Standard for offering custodial solutions. As we know, Paxos is regulated by NYDFS and shall put all EDXM customer assets in a bankruptcy-remote trust. Back then, EDX Markets CEOJamil Nazarali said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With compliance and security as key differentiators of EDXM’s offering, we are thrilled to partner with Paxos to deliver the gold standard in digital asset custody services to our investors. With Paxos’ best-in-class solutions along with MEMX’s technology powering the exchange, EDXM now has all the tools to make institutional-grade digital asset trading available to investors for the first time.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>America&#8217;s Changing Crypto Landscape</h2>
<p>The recent developments show that despite the strong regulatory action by the US SEC, big market players are still keen to enter the crypto space. Earlier this month, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed lawsuits against two of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges &#8211; Binance and Coinbase &#8211; in a move to tighten its grip[ over the crypto space.</p>
<p>However, a week after, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager BlackRock filed for a spot Bitcoin ETF dubbed the iShares Bitcoin Trust. Interestingly, BlackRock has chosen Coinbase as its custodial partner despite the SEC lawsuit.</p>
<p>BlackRock and Nasdaq have made an agreement to share information about trading, clearing, and identifying customers. This shows that BlackRock is taking a careful approach to overcoming regulatory challenges and gaining approval for its application. It&#8217;s an important step in bringing together traditional finance and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that Coinbase&#8217;s involvement in BlackRock&#8217;s application highlights the close relationship between traditional financial institutions, regulators, and cryptocurrency platforms. This reflects a larger trend of merging the traditional finance industry with the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Reports suggest that Fidelity Investments will be making a similar move. This shows that big players are still interested in crypto. Thus, crypto in America is not dying anytime soon. Dawn Fitzpatrick, CEO of Soros Fund Management, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Crypto is here to stay. What has happened is clearly a setback. But right now I actually think it is a huge opportunity for the incumbent financial firms to actually take the lead.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Other crypto news can be found <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/">Crypto Exchange Backed by Fidelity and Citadel Securities Starts Operations in US</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/crypto-exchange-fidelity-citadel-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deutsche Bank Seek BaFin License to Provide Crypto Custody Services</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benjamin Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bafin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto custody]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deutsche bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/">Deutsche Bank Seek BaFin License to Provide Crypto Custody Services</a></p>
<p>Deutsche Bank’s application for regulatory approval is a positive step toward the development of a regulatory framework for digital asset custody services in Germany.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/">Deutsche Bank Seek BaFin License to Provide Crypto Custody Services</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/">Deutsche Bank Seek BaFin License to Provide Crypto Custody Services</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/deutsche-bank/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Deutsche Bank AG</a> (ETR: DBK), one of the leading financial institutions in the world, is seeking regulatory approval from Germany’s financial market regulator, BaFin, to operate a custody service for crypto assets, including cryptocurrencies. Interestingly, this move is a significant step towards the banks’ entry into the digital asset space, which has been gaining traction in recent years.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-20/deutsche-bank-applies-for-digital-asset-license-amid-growth-push" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a>, David Lynne, head of Deutsche Bank’s commercial banking unit, mentioned the bank’s application during a conference. Per the report, the custody service would allow Deutsche Bank to store and manage digital assets on behalf of its clients.</p>
<p>Digital assets, such as cryptocurrencies, are becoming increasingly popular as a store of value and a means of payment. However, the lack of a secure and reliable custody solution has been a major hurdle for institutional investors looking to enter the digital asset space.</p>
<p>As such, Deutsche Bank’s entry into the digital asset custody space would provide a much-needed solution for institutional investors, who require a secure and reliable way to store and manage their digital assets. Meanwhile, the bank’s reputation for security and reliability makes it an ideal candidate to provide such a service, although the bank must comply with strict regulatory requirements to ensure the safety of its clients’ digital assets.</p>
<h2>Deutsche Bank Steps into the Crypto Space</h2>
<p>Undoubtedly, Deutsche Bank’s application for regulatory approval is also a positive step toward the development of a regulatory framework for digital asset custody services in Germany.</p>
<p>Recall that the Frankfurt-headquartered bank has been making plans to enter into the crypto industry since 2020, but never decided on a timeline. In February, its asset management arm decided to explore the<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-invest-crypto-companies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> option of investing</a> in two German-based crypto companies as part of its growth strategy.</p>
<p>Notably, the bank’s entry into the digital asset space could also encourage other financial institutions to follow suit, which could help further legitimize the digital asset industry and promote its adoption.</p>
<p>Aside from Deutsche Bank, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/bny-mellon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bank of New York Mellon Corp</a> (NYSE: BK), America’s oldest bank has <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bny-mellon-crypto-custody-services/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">extended</a> its custody services to cryptocurrencies. Interestingly, BNY Mellon is the first bank to use one platform to offer custody for both traditional and crypto holdings. This means that the banks can now hold digital assets, including <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bitcoin</a> (BTC), <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ethereum</a> (ETH), and the like on behalf of their customers.</p>
<p>The move has also showed the health in Deutsche Bank’s business prospects. Amid the crisis that ravaged the industry earlier in the year, the German bank <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-q1-2023-results/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">posted</a> a net profit of 1.158 billion euros, or $1.28 billion in its Q1 2023 earnings report which ended on March 31, continuing an 11th straight quarterly profit. Also, its first-quarter revenue came in at 7.7 billion euros, up from the 7.33 billion euros reported during the same period in 2022.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/">Deutsche Bank Seek BaFin License to Provide Crypto Custody Services</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/deutsche-bank-bafin-license-%d1%81rypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Announces Co-Founder Eddie Wu Set to Replace Daniel Zhang as CEO</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tolu Ajiboye]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alibaba]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[daniel zhang]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jack ma]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/">Alibaba Announces Co-Founder Eddie Wu Set to Replace Daniel Zhang as CEO</a></p>
<p>According to Alibaba, Eddie Wu will take over from Daniel Zhang as CEO, to allow Zhang focus on the company's Cloud intelligence business.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/">Alibaba Announces Co-Founder Eddie Wu Set to Replace Daniel Zhang as CEO</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/">Alibaba Announces Co-Founder Eddie Wu Set to Replace Daniel Zhang as CEO</a></p>
<p>Chinese multinational tech company <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/alibaba-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Alibaba Group Holding Limited</a> (HKG: 9988) has announced that co-founder Eddie Wu will take over the CEO position from Daniel Zhang. The company made the surprise announcement, intended to allow Zhang to concentrate on Alibaba Cloud.</p>
<p>In an internal memo sent to staff, current CEO Zhang touched on the need to focus completely on the company’s Cloud business. He said that cloud computing is an integral part of today’s tech landscape, especially as the AI boom continues:</p>
<blockquote><p>“As everyone is well aware, the development of core technologies such as cloud computing, big data and AI will lead to a tremendous transformation of our society and is of utmost strategic significance.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Since Alibaba’s inception, Wu has taken on more than a few roles at the Chinese tech giant. He was the company’s first tech head and later was Alipay and Taobao’s chief technology officer. Wu also founded venture capital firm Vision Plus Capital, which invests in startups focused on digital health care and advanced tech.</p>
<p>The management restructuring will also promote current executive vice chairman and co-founder Joseph Tsai to chairman. The execs will resume their new roles on September 10.</p>
<h2>New Alibaba CEO and Management Restructuring</h2>
<p>In March, Alibaba <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-split-6-groups-ipo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> it would split the company into 6 units. The announcement was quickly considered pivotal by the general market, especially as Alibaba specified that each unit could pursue an independent IPO. In a <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/Alibaba-to-split-into-6-companies-pursue-IPOs-in-major-shakeup" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">statement</a>, Zhang said the split would provide the much-needed focus each arm of the business needs. He also said it would help with decision-making, allowing each group to respond independently to changes in the market.</p>
<p>Other units besides the Cloud Intelligence Group are Taobao Tmall Commerce Group, Global Digital Commerce Group, and the Local Services Group. The list also includes Cainiao Smart Logistics and the Digital Media and Entertainment Group. Following a complete spinoff, each unit would have independent boards of directors and CEOs.</p>
<p>Alibaba stock responded to the announcement, climbing over 9% in US pre-market trading.</p>
<p>Speaking on ensuring undivided attention to the company’s cloud business, Zhang added in the internal memo:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Cloud Intelligence Group is now full speed ahead on its spin-off plans and we are approaching a crucial stage of the process, so it is the right time for me to dedicate my full attention and time to the business.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Zhang has been Alibaba&#8217;s CEO since co-founder Jack Ma stepped down in 2015.</p>
<h2>Company Layoff</h2>
<p>Last month, Coinspeaker <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-cloud-layoff-spinoff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">reported</a> that Alibaba plans to reduce its staff count by 7%. According to unnamed sources, the company conceived the move in preparation for spinning off Alibaba’s cloud division. Alibaba has already begun notifying affected staff and compensating them with severance packages. In addition, there are unconfirmed plans that the company will transfer some staff to other divisions of the company. As of March, Alibaba’s total headcount was more than 235,000.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/">Alibaba Announces Co-Founder Eddie Wu Set to Replace Daniel Zhang as CEO</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/alibaba-co-founder-eddie-wu-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Moves $3 Billion Worth of BTC to New Address</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance cold wallet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc balance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changpeng zhao]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof-of-Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[securities and exchange commission]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259467</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/">Binance Moves $3 Billion Worth of BTC to New Address</a></p>
<p>Despite the large amounts being removed, data suggests that Binance remains the exchange with the largest BTC balance.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/">Binance Moves $3 Billion Worth of BTC to New Address</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/">Binance Moves $3 Billion Worth of BTC to New Address</a></p>
<p>Top crypto exchange <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> has <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1670723088802283520" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">shared</a> its recent move which saw it transfer massive amounts of Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) to a new blockchain address. According to the crypto firm, it recently moved at least nine figures worth of BTC but assures users of the safety of their funds. Per Binance, the funds are now safely tucked away in cold storage.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, analytic firm Blockchain.com has also run a check on the new cold storage. This was done to verify Binance&#8217;s claims. According to Blockchain.com <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/addresses/btc/1Pzaqw98PeRfyHypfqyEgg5yycJRsENrE7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, the said address received 15,000 BTC, in the early hours of Monday. That is worth around $402 million as of press time. The analytic firm also found another transaction where 117,000 BTC was transferred from one of Binance&#8217;s old cold wallet addresses to a new one. The single transaction is worth over 3 billion dollars.</p>
<p>Further confirming Blockchain.com&#8217;s data, a similar analytic firm Bitinfocharts <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/bitcoin/wallet/Binance-coldwallet" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">says</a> that a total of 130,000 BTC left Binance’s cold wallet on Monday.</p>
<p>Despite the large amounts being removed, Coinglass data suggests that Binance remains the exchange with the largest BTC balance. As of publication, its BTC balance stands at 510,425, while the closest exchange is Coinbase Pro with 486,568 BTC.</p>
<h2>Is Trouble Looming for the Binance Exchange?</h2>
<p>Recently, there has been one issue or the other with the exchange, thereby raising concerns among users and all stakeholders. Firstly, the exchange is currently being <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/sec-sues-binance-securities-rules/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sued</a> by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for violating United States securities laws.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there have been claims that Binance&#8217;s proof of reserves is questionable. After FTX collapsed in November 2022, the exchange felt the need to publish its reserve report. This was necessary to allay the fears of its users. As it turned out, however, the December report where it claimed that its user funds were 101% backed, is also now being questioned. More so, since the company that carried out the audit has also forward to distance itself from anything crypto-related.</p>
<p>Lastly, Reuters also reported in May that Binance may have been mixing user deposits with corporate funds within its bank accounts at the now-defunct Silvergate Bank and Signature Bank. However, the exchange has since responded to the claims. In its counterclaim, Binance insists the deposits in question were moved to convert them into BUSD stablecoins inside user accounts.</p>
<p>Generally, there is an air of uncertainty in and around the Binance exchange for now. However, the exchange alongside its CEO Changpeng Zhao, has a track record of making it out of the tunnels.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/">Binance Moves $3 Billion Worth of BTC to New Address</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/binance-3b-btc-new-address/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance’s BNB Smart Chain Unveils Scalability Solution opBNB Powered by Optimism</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Bhushan Akolkar]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bsc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opbnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/">Binance&#8217;s BNB Smart Chain Unveils Scalability Solution opBNB Powered by Optimism</a></p>
<p>The combination of BSC's strong ability and opBNB's dedicated new features will make data access easier.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/">Binance&#8217;s BNB Smart Chain Unveils Scalability Solution opBNB Powered by Optimism</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/">Binance&#8217;s BNB Smart Chain Unveils Scalability Solution opBNB Powered by Optimism</a></p>
<p>In a major announcement on Monday, June 19, Binance-founded Layer-1 blockchain platform BNB Smart Chain (BSC) <a href="https://www.bnbchain.org/en/blog/introducing-opbnb-unleashing-a-new-era-of-scalability/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">introduced</a> a new scalability solution opBNB, with the goal of offering a seamless experience for users, developers, and projects on BSC.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Binance</a> unveiled the testnet on the very same day inviting testnet validators and dApp builders to try their hands. They noted that opBNB will address the scalability requirements for the mass adoption of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Powered by Optimism&#8217;s OP Stack, opBNB is also an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatible layer 2 chain. The role of Optimistic Rollups is to make things easier on the main chain by doing transactions outside of it. They only put the important transaction data on the main chain. This helps increase how much the system can handle by grouping many transactions together before sending them to the main chain.</p>
<p>The combination of BSC&#8217;s strong ability and opBNB&#8217;s dedicated new features will make data access easier. It will also improve the cache system while adjusting the submission process algorithm. Additionally, it will allow simultaneous operations while allowing opBNB to push the gas limit to a massive 100M. This would be a massive jump from Optimism&#8217;s 30M gas limit.</p>
<p>With all these new features at work, opBNB will be able to handle 4000 transactions per second while keeping the average transaction cost under 0.005 USD.</p>
<h2>Benefits of opBNB</h2>
<p>BSC&#8217;s opBNB solution provides developers access to a robust EVM-compatible platform thereby allowing the creation of open systems. The opBNB team has helped make the Optimism Stack better, which makes it easier for developers to bring their applications to BSC.</p>
<p>This means more people can use their apps. It also improves the speed and lowers the cost of transactions, making things better for users. Projects that had trouble before because of too many transactions can now do well with opBNB&#8217;s improved scalability. Some of the other benefits include:</p>
<ul>
<li>EVM Compatibility: Being EVM-compatible, developers who know how to use Ethereum can easily use opBNB too. They can move or add their apps from Ethereum to BSC without much trouble. This means they can reach more people and have more resources to work with. They can use the good things from both Ethereum and BNB Smart Chain.</li>
<li>Security and Trust: opBNB takes security seriously by using a fraud-proving scheme. This makes sure that all transactions done off-chain are real and trustworthy. It gives developers and users more trust and confidence. Also, the transparency and verifiability of transactions on opBNB make the app environment safer and better for everyone.</li>
<li>Future Proof: opBNB provides a flexible framework for developers to adapt, innovate, and grow in the evolving blockchain space. It is a strategic choice for the future, enabling developers to easily add new features and experiment with innovative ideas.</li>
<li>Rich Ecosystem Integration: opBNB is more than just a layer 2 solution. It is seamlessly integrated into the thriving BSC ecosystem, offering developers and projects a chance to engage with a diverse range of tokens and projects. This includes popular options like BNB, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/tether/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">USDT</a>, and upcoming ERC20 tokens supported on opBNB.</li>
</ul>
<p>Read other <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/news/crypto/blockchain-news/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">blockchain-related news</a> on Coinspeaker.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/">Binance&#8217;s BNB Smart Chain Unveils Scalability Solution opBNB Powered by Optimism</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bnb-smart-chain-opbnb/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Surges Past 50% amid Crackdown on Altcoins</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mayowa Adebajo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin btc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bnb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc dominance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btcusd]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paxos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sec]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/">Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Surges Past 50% amid Crackdown on Altcoins</a></p>
<p>The market capitalization of the flagship cryptocurrency recently hit levels greater than that of all other cryptocurrencies combined.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/">Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Surges Past 50% amid Crackdown on Altcoins</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/">Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Surges Past 50% amid Crackdown on Altcoins</a></p>
<p>Bitcoin (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/coins/bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">BTC</a>) has had some difficult runs recently, but maybe its market dominance was never in doubt. This follows after the market capitalization of the flagship cryptocurrency recently hit levels greater than that of all other cryptocurrencies combined.</p>
<p>According to TradingView <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTC.D/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">data</a>, Bitcoin dominance surpassed 50% on Monday, in what was its first attempt in over 2 years. Since the BTC price headed for the rocks following China&#8217;s ban in May 2021, the closest BTC dominance came to 50% was in June 2022. That was just before the entire market plummeted again on the news of persistent inflation.</p>
<h2>Here&#8217;s What May Be Helping Bitcoin Dominance</h2>
<p>For what it&#8217;s worth, Bitcoin dominance represents the ratio of BTC&#8217;s market cap to that of the entire crypto market. However, many have faulted the metric for including stablecoins within its calculations. They argue that BTC&#8217;s true market share is not well represented by that calculation since stablecoins are arguably just dollars trading on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, even the so-called stablecoins have had a tough year so far. In February, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEC</a>) ordered Paxos to stop issuing BUSD. More recently, top altcoins such as Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC) have also suffered significant losses. This follows after the SEC <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/us-sec-coinbase-unregistered-exchange/">filed a lawsuit</a> against Coinbase alleging that all three coins are unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Similarly, the regulator also slammed Binance with a lawsuit that claimed that the exchange’s native token BNB is a security. News of the suit, expectedly, has also meant that the BNB token has plunged no less than 20% in the ongoing month alone. It might be worth noting, however, that BNB holds a significant share of the crypto market. It is the fourth largest crypto by market cap.</p>
<p>With serious regulatory pressure on all sides, stablecoins have had billions of dollars wiped off their combined market capitalization. And as a result, BTC once again rules the crypto market convincingly.</p>
<p>Perhaps, there may even be room for more dominance. Last Tuesday, MicroStrategy&#8217;s Michael Saylor <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1668681012115546120?t=YkwyNPSANvzAOG1QTLBLRg&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">predicted</a> that Bitcoin dominance will eventually rise above 80% as time goes on. That is if regulators can maintain the momentum at which they currently clamp down on other digital assets.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/">Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Surges Past 50% amid Crackdown on Altcoins</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/bitcoin-dominance-crackdown-altcoins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Ride-Hailing Giant Grab Plans First Massive Layoffs since Pandemic</title>
		<link>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chimamanda U. Martha]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grab]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[microsofft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[salesforce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.coinspeaker.com/?p=259502</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/">Singapore Ride-Hailing Giant Grab Plans First Massive Layoffs since Pandemic</a></p>
<p>Despite expressing positive revenue projections for 2023 and accelerating its profitability timeline in February, Grab is now planning a fresh round of layoffs.</p>
<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/">Singapore Ride-Hailing Giant Grab Plans First Massive Layoffs since Pandemic</a></p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com">Coinspeaker</a><br />
<a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/">Singapore Ride-Hailing Giant Grab Plans First Massive Layoffs since Pandemic</a></p>
<p>Grab Holdings, a Singapore-based ride-hailing and food delivery company, is gearing up for its largest round of layoffs since the pandemic, according to a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-20/singapore-s-grab-plans-biggest-round-of-job-cuts-since-pandemic?sref=y3YMCJ4e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">report</a> by Bloomberg on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Sources familiar with the matter stated that the company would officially announce the planned job cuts this week, which is expected to surpass the previous 5% reduction in 2020, affecting up to 360 employees. At the time, Grab attributed the downsizing to the economic repercussions of the pandemic.</p>
<p>Despite expressing positive revenue projections for 2023 and accelerating its profitability timeline in February, the ride-hailing giant Grab is now planning a fresh round of layoffs. The company predicted its revenue for this year to range between $2.20 billion and $2.30 billion.</p>
<h2>Fresh Layoffs by Grab: A Change of Heart</h2>
<p>Last September, the Singapore-based firm stated that it had no plans for extensive layoffs despite the challenging market conditions. However, in December of the same year, Grab had a change of heart, contradicting its earlier statement.</p>
<p>In a letter to employees, Grab&#8217;s CEO Anthony Tan informed the staff of a freeze on most hiring, pay raises for senior managers, and implemented cost-saving measures such as reduced travel and expense budgets.</p>
<p>According to Grab&#8217;s latest annual report, the company had a workforce of 11,934 employees as of the end of 2022. However, it remains unclear how many of these staff members will be impacted by the upcoming job cuts.</p>
<p>As one of the leading Asian tech companies, Grab went public in 2021 through a merger with a special purpose acquisition company (<a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/guides/what-is-special-purpose-acquisition-company-spac/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SPAC</a>) called Altimeter. The transaction raised a gross profit of $4.5 billion, making it the biggest public US market debut by a Southeast Asian firm.</p>
<p>Since then, the company has expanded its operations across Thailand and Indonesia, providing customers with a wide range of services, including ride-hailing and food delivery.</p>
<h2>Not the First</h2>
<p>With its planned downsizing, Grab joins a number of <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/tech-companies-job-cuts-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">tech companies</a> that have been forced to slash their workforce due to poor market sentiments.</p>
<p>In January, e-commerce giant Amazon <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/amazon-additional-9000-layoff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">announced</a> its plans to reduce its global headcount. The company revealed its intention to wind down three UK warehouses and seven delivery stations, impacting more than 1,200 workers. Shortly after, Amazon conducted a second round of layoffs, affecting 9,000 employees.</p>
<p>That same month, another tech firm, Salesforce, also joined the trend, <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/salesforce-workforce-pandemic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">dismissing</a> 10% of its staff. While sharing his reflections on the series of events leading up to this crucial moment, the company&#8217;s CEO Marc Benioff blamed the job cuts on overstaffing and the post-pandemic effects.</p>
<p>Other companies, such as <a href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/organizations/microsoft-corporation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Corporation</a> and Alphabet, Google&#8217;s parent company, have also implemented workforce reductions. The planned layoffs at Microsoft affected up to 10,000 employees from its cloud service business. On the other hand, Alphabet dismissed around 6% of its global workforce, impacting up to 12,000 workers.</p>
<p>These layoffs reflect the challenges technology companies face, grappling with economic uncertainties and changing market dynamics brought on by the pandemic.</p>
<a class="infinscroll_next_page_link" style="display:none" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/etherscan-analyze-smart-contract-ai-code-reader/" rel="prev">next</a><p><a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/">Singapore Ride-Hailing Giant Grab Plans First Massive Layoffs since Pandemic</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.coinspeaker.com/grab-massive-layoffs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss><!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=4194 metric#misses=41 metric#hit-ratio=99.0 metric#bytes=1043622 metric#prefetches=208 metric#store-reads=19 metric#store-writes=2 metric#store-hits=214 metric#store-misses=2 metric#sql-queries=34 metric#ms-total=94.58 metric#ms-cache=5.17 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2587 metric#ms-cache-ratio=5.5 -->