<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 19:08:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Labs incubation program season 6 opens as AltSignals presale hits 96.71%</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-incubation-program-season-6-opens-as-altsignals-presale-hits-96-71/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-incubation-program-season-6-opens-as-altsignals-presale-hits-96-71/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 19:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-incubation-program-season-6-opens-as-altsignals-presale-hits-96-71/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Binance Labs has started accepting Season 6 Incubation Program applications for Web3 innovation. The incubation program offers tailored resources and mentoring for startups. At the same time, the first stage of AltSignals presale has hit 96.71%. The sixth season of Binance Labs&#8217; prestigious Incubation Program is now accepting applications. The program&#8217;s goal is to promote [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-incubation-program-season-6-opens-as-altsignals-presale-hits-96-71/">Binance Labs incubation program season 6 opens as AltSignals presale hits 96.71%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>Binance Labs has started accepting Season 6 Incubation Program applications for Web3 innovation.</li>
<li>The incubation program offers tailored resources and mentoring for startups.</li>
<li>At the same time, the first stage of AltSignals presale has hit 96.71%.</li>
</ul>
<p>The sixth season of Binance Labs&rsquo; prestigious Incubation Program is now <a href="https://twitter.com/BinanceLabs/status/1674736149024378881?s=20">accepting applications</a>. The program&rsquo;s goal is to promote innovation in the Web3 industry, a rapidly expanding field at the vanguard of the digital revolution.</p>
<p>The sixth season of the Binance Labs Incubation program opens at a time when the exiting crypto-based AI project <a href="https://token.altsignals.io/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news">AltSignals</a> is running the presale of its native token ASI.</p>
<p>The track record of Binance Labs in accelerating startups is strong. Over 900 applications were submitted for the program&rsquo;s previous season. After a thorough review process, 12 project teams were chosen. These teams represented a range of industries, including infrastructure, security, and decentralized finance (DeFi).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Out of the 12, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/exchanges/binance/">Binance</a> invested in five standout project teams, demonstrating the enormous potential and talent that the program unearths.</p>
<h2>AltSignals&rsquo; crypto-based AI project</h2>
<p>With the creation of a completely new trading stack powered by artificial intelligence, AltSignals is embracing the potential of generative AI through its upcoming platform ActualizeAI which uses blockchain technology and AI to create the highest calibre trading intelligence available online.</p>
<p>For a number of reasons, AltSignals is already hailed as one of the cryptocurrency platforms with a very promising future. It was launched in 2017 and it has developed to support a community of more than 50,000 users, all of whom benefit from the platform&rsquo;s patented AltAlgoTM trading indicator tool that boasts an exceptional success rate of 64% on average.</p>
<p>AltSignals is utilizing the immense potential of AI to create its ActualizeAI trading stack in an effort to raise this rate to over 80%. As it readies for the launch of its AI platform, AltSignals is currently conducting the presale of its cryptocurrency, ASI.</p>
<p>The ActualizeAI combines a number of cutting-edge generative AI capabilities to provide a remarkably potent all-in-one solution for enabling profitable decision-making. The tool uses machine learning algorithms to apply rules-based logic to understand how markets function. Natural language processing (NLP) also uses trader sentiment analysis while speeding up learning. This improves output quality, frequency, and volume, offering a reliable and flexible solution for trading insights.</p>
<p>To help members benefit from the best buy and sell prices, ActualizeAI uses reinforcement learning to automatically balance the risk/reward ratio on all trades. This helps to remove emotions from the decision-making process. Users benefit from the most recent information available thanks to a system that is constantly learning and enhancing the calibre of its trading signals.</p>
<h2>Binance&rsquo;s incubation program tailored for Web3</h2>
<p>The three-month program is specifically designed to meet the changing needs of founders in this fast-paced sector. Its educational program is totally dedicated to creating Web3 startups. The program&rsquo;s resources are encouraged to be used by founders as they develop their concepts and iterate on their products.</p>
<p>One-on-one mentoring sessions and access to fireside chats with business luminaries, including the founders of portfolio companies from Binance and Binance Labs, are included in this special opportunity.</p>
<p>Additionally, for its Incubation Program, Binance Labs is looking for startups in particular fields of interest. Infrastructure, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/defi/">Decentralized Finance (DeFi)</a>, and the Application Layer are some of these areas. Numerous sub-areas, including MEV, ZK Proofs, Layer 2 Scaling, Lending &amp; Borrowing, Perpetuals &amp; Derivatives, Investing, AI-Powered DApps, Web 2.5 DApps, Analytics, and SocialFi, are included within these sectors.</p>
<p>By concentrating on these regions, Binance Labs aims to sponsor the most promising and innovative Web3 projects.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-incubation-program-season-6-opens-as-altsignals-presale-hits-96-71/">Binance Labs incubation program season 6 opens as AltSignals presale hits 96.71%</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/binance-labs-incubation-program-season-6-opens-as-altsignals-presale-hits-96-71/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EOS price lags as Bitcoin Cash, Litecoin soar</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/eos-price-lags-as-bitcoin-cash-litecoin-soar/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/eos-price-lags-as-bitcoin-cash-litecoin-soar/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 19:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/eos-price-lags-as-bitcoin-cash-litecoin-soar/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EOS price is down 13% year-to-date even as LTC and BCH have turned extremely bullish. The broader market outlook is bullish and that could help EOS target recent peak. EOS traded at $0.77 at the time of writing, about 10% up after a brief dip to $0.70.&#160; EOS price is currently trading near $0.77 after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/eos-price-lags-as-bitcoin-cash-litecoin-soar/">EOS price lags as Bitcoin Cash, Litecoin soar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">EOS price is down 13% year-to-date even as LTC and BCH have turned extremely bullish.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The broader market outlook is bullish and that could help EOS target recent peak.</li>
<li dir="ltr">EOS traded at $0.77 at the time of writing, about 10% up after a brief dip to $0.70.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/eos/">EOS price</a> is currently trading near $0.77 after briefly falling to $0.70 on a move replicated across the broader crypto market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the coin is still hovering below June highs, and is down 15% in the past 30 days. EOS is also way off its year-to-date peak, with the performance contrasting with some of the oldest altcoins as seen over the last few weeks.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Could news about EOS EVM provide positive vibes that can spur bulls higher? Probably, and it&rsquo;s what bulls need &ndash; upside impetus sparked by increased network activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Games and dapps coming to EOS EVM &#128526;</p>
<p>&mdash; Yves La Rose (@BigBeardSamurai) <a href="https://twitter.com/BigBeardSamurai/status/1674833138277662728?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">EOS price amid crypto market outlook</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Coins like Litecoin (LTC) and Bitcoin Cash (BCH) have been on a tear lately, outperforming even the benchmark crypto Bitcoin (BTC) that has had an impressive first half of 2023 with 83% year-to-date gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">On the other hand, we have EOS that has remained largely wedged in negative territory since the breakdown from around $2 in September last year. The downturn from $1.34 in March gradually saw EOS/USD reach $0.60 in mid-June and see bulls down 13% YTD even after recent gains.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The coin&rsquo;s performance has been punctuated by the dips occasioned by SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance, which had Bitcoin retreating sharply from the $30k area earlier this month. While the spot ETF wave sparked by asset manager giant BlackRock has had EOS bounce higher, the overall technical setup is bearish.</p>
<p dir="ltr">EOS price might yet also see fresh sell-off as bankrupt crypto lender Celsius begins to sell or convert altcoins into BTC and ETH. [<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">Read more</a>].</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/eos-price-lags-as-bitcoin-cash-litecoin-soar/">EOS price lags as Bitcoin Cash, Litecoin soar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/eos-price-lags-as-bitcoin-cash-litecoin-soar/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) bounces strongly as bulls brush off brief retreat</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-bounces-strongly-as-bulls-brush-off-brief-retreat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-bounces-strongly-as-bulls-brush-off-brief-retreat/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin price bounced strongly to see bulls hit a 14-month high near $110. LTC last traded at these prices in April 2022, and could hit new multi-year highs as the Litecoin halving approaches. Prices fell to $84 earlier in the day after markets reacted negatively to news about spot Bitcoin ETfs. Litecoin is still poised [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-bounces-strongly-as-bulls-brush-off-brief-retreat/">Litecoin (LTC) bounces strongly as bulls brush off brief retreat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Litecoin price bounced strongly to see bulls hit a 14-month high near $110.</li>
<li dir="ltr">LTC last traded at these prices in April 2022, and could hit new multi-year highs as the Litecoin halving approaches.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Prices fell to $84 earlier in the day after markets reacted negatively to news about spot Bitcoin ETfs.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/litecoin/">Litecoin</a> is still poised for more upside action after an enforced breather pushed LTC back to lows of $84 on Friday.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A strong rebound for LTC in the last few minutes had buyers eyeing $110, even as the cryptocurrency reached its highest level since early April 2022.</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688145077796-1c9f9c9d-ed78-4589-8a92-f59902c298c0.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="270"><span class="fr-inner">Litecoin price on the daily chart. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.tradingview.com/x/1G4BuULw/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TradingView</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<h2 class="fr-img-space-wrap2">What happened to the LTC price today?</h2>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin had surged to highs of $103 earlier in the day as bulls looked to breach a level last reached in mid-February.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, the momentum was briefly halted as the broader market reacted to a news report that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had provided feedback on recently filed spot Bitcoin ETFs indicating the filings were &ldquo;inadequate.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As reported <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/">here</a>, Bitcoin briefly fell below $30k as the market reaction injected sell-off pressure. But there has been some kind of swift rebound for BTC as buyers rode on the details of the &ldquo;quick&rdquo; feedback from the SEC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BlackRock, Fidelity and other asset managers that recently submitted applications for a spot Bitcoin ETF will need to refile with the SEC. Specifically, they have to clearly point out which spot crypto exchange provider they have a market surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) with.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">LTC price bullish ahead of halving</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Litecoin&rsquo;s positive outlook is down to a key fundamental factor &ndash; the network&rsquo;s upcoming halving will only be days away now as July begins. The <a href="https://www.litecoinhalving.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">countdown</a> to the halving shows that the highly anticipated event is expected at block 2,520,000 on August 2, 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The network&rsquo;s third halving, after 2015 and 2019, will see block reward reduced from 12.5 LTC to 6.25 LTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Amid the exuberance about potential price growth, hashrate recently rose to its all-time high of 958.36 TH/s. CoinWarz data <a href="https://www.coinwarz.com/mining/litecoin/hashrate-chart" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">indicates</a> the milestone was reached on June 28, 2023 at block 2,499,942.</p>
<p dir="ltr">With price near $110 and the halving event around the corner, LTC price could rise to $200 pre-halving. Post-halving, it&rsquo;s the all-time high of $410 that could be a nice target for bulls.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/litecoin-ltc-bounces-strongly-as-bulls-brush-off-brief-retreat/">Litecoin (LTC) bounces strongly as bulls brush off brief retreat</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court allows Celsius to sell altcoins for BTC, ETH starting July 1</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CEL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bankruptcy Judge Martin Glenn of the US Southern District Court of New York on Friday ordered that bankrupt crypto lender Celsius can begin to sell or convert altcoins to Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH). The price of CEL, the native Celsius Network token, rose sharply on Friday, trading above $0.15 with 33% gains in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">Court allows Celsius to sell altcoins for BTC, ETH starting July 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Bankruptcy Judge Martin Glenn of the US Southern District Court of New York on Friday ordered that bankrupt crypto lender <a href="https://coinjournal.net/celsius/">Celsius</a> can begin to sell or convert altcoins to Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The price of CEL, the native Celsius Network token, rose sharply on Friday, trading above $0.15 with 33% gains in the past 24 hours.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Celsius can sell altcoins for BTC, ETH from July 1</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The liquidating of the said altcoins comes ahead of a planned distribution of assets to creditors and will start on or after July 1, the judge <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ordered</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>The Debtors, in consultation with the advisors to the Committee, may sell or convert any non-BTC and non-ETH cryptocurrency, crypto tokens, or other cryptocurrency assets other than such tokens that are associated with Withhold or Custody accounts (collectively, the &ldquo;Altcoins&rdquo;) to BTC or ETH commencing on or after July 1, 2023</em>,&rdquo; reads part of the ruling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Celsius is expected to use &ldquo;commercially reasonable efforts to maximize the value of the Altcoins to be sold or converted to BTC or ETH.&rdquo; However, with the SEC having recently alleged some of the altcoins held by the crypto lender as securities, the sales are expected to comply with the &ldquo;applicable exemptions to the US securities laws.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Among the tokens the US regulator recently highlighted as securities in its cases against Binance and Coinbase include Cardano (ADA), Polygon (MATIC) and Near (NEAR). Celsius holds these and other alts such as Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC) and Chainlink (LINK).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The tokens have recently traded higher alongside the broader crypto market and it remains to be seen what impact, if any, the offloading will have on prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here are the Celsius alts FWIW, these will be sold and the proceeds used to buy BTC and ETH. <a href="https://t.co/Bp7MWUhstB">https://t.co/Bp7MWUhstB</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Hal Press (@NorthRockLP) <a href="https://twitter.com/NorthRockLP/status/1674792909449879552?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Celsius filed for bankruptcy in July 2022 after pausing customer withdrawals amid crypto contagion from the collapse of Terra and Three Arrows Capital.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to court documents, the company has been in dialogue with the SEC and state regulators as it looked to update its restructuring plan to only distribute crypto to creditors in bitcoin and ether.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/">Court allows Celsius to sell altcoins for BTC, ETH starting July 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/court-allows-celsius-to-sell-altcoins-for-btc-eth-starting-july-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Bitcoin dominance measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative cryptocurrency sector market cap It is currently at 58%, the highest mark since April 2021 Market dynamics are changing as institutions consider Bitcoin, while rest of crypto market still struggles amid tight monetary policy environment Regulatory clampdown has also declared [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/">Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin dominance measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative cryptocurrency sector market cap</li>
<li dir="ltr">It is currently at 58%, the highest mark since April 2021</li>
<li dir="ltr">Market dynamics are changing as institutions consider Bitcoin, while rest of crypto market still struggles amid tight monetary policy environment</li>
<li dir="ltr">Regulatory clampdown has also declared many tokens as securities, while Bitcoin appears to be carving out its own niche&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">The Bitcoin market is never boring.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Having said that, the year 2023 has (thus far at least) has not thrown up mayhem on the scale of what we saw in past years. In 2022, Bitcoin freefell as the world transitioned to tight monetary policy, while scandals such as the Terra collapse and the staggering deception at FTX coming to light. This came after the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021, when crypto surged into mainstream consciousness, Bitcoin printing dizzying gains and inspiring dinner table conversation around the globe as to what this mysterious Internet money was all about.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So, 2023 cannot match the scale of that drama. But there is something very intriguing happening to the market dynamics of Bitcoin, at least relative to other cryptocurrencies. Bitcoin dominance, which measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative market cap of all cryptocurrencies, is at its highest level in over two years, at 52%. In other words, 52% of the cryptocurrency market cap, currently at $1.18 trillion, is Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<h2><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688118673827-71a712e7-acd0-4d3b-8651-836d1ad218d0.png" style="width: 600px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="600" height="284">Dominance fell in the years 2020 and 2021</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The above chart shows that Bitcoin opened the year 2020 with a dominance of about 70%. Over the course of the next 365 days, it bounced around a bit and trickled down to the high 50s. However, it was the final quarter of 2020 when Bitcoin began to make serious moves, rising from $10,000 to $28,000. In this time period, the dominance ratio rose from 59% back to 70%, where it closed at, approximately the same dominance ratio it opened the year at twelve months earlier. &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The following year, 2021, saw altcoins catch up. Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance plunged like a stone, falling quicker than it ever had before. The wider cryptocurrency market exploded as stimulus cheques, lockdown-driven Robinhood trading and basement-level interest rates pushed capital into anything and everything remotely connected to a blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The total cryptocurrency market cap touched $3 trillion in November 2021, while Bitcoin&rsquo;s market cap peaked at $1.28 trillion. Bitcoin dominance, therefore, was down to 43%. However, the worst inflation crisis since the 1970s forced central banks into one of the fastest rate hiking cycles in recent memory, following years of zero (or even negative in some cases) rates.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">        </p><div class="flourish-embed flourish-map" data-src="visualisation/14292455">
            <script src="https://public.flourish.studio/resources/embed.js"></script>
        </div>
    
<p dir="ltr">For risk assets, this spelled trouble. And make no mistake, the entire crypto market is as far out on the risk spectrum as it gets. Capital flooded out of the space as rates continued rising, inflation got hotter, and several nefarious scandals struck the crypto sector (looking at you, Do Kwon, Sam Bankman-Fried and Alex Mashinsky). &nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Which brings us to now. While inflation peaked in Q4 last year, the macro climate is still uncertain. Employment is tight, the economy is still hot and inflation, while dropping, is well north of the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s 2% target. In Europe, inflation is even hotter (and don&rsquo;t even ask about the UK, if that still counts as Europe anyway).&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In crypto, however, something is changing. Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance has risen and appears to be in an uptrend again. It is currently up to 58%, the highest mark since April 2021. On the one hand, this is typical of what we have seen in the past: money begins to flow into Bitcoin after a prolonged and seismic pullback (2022), seeing dominance rise before it eventually filters into altcoins and the rest of the market catches up.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, there are two points to counter why this time could be different, and may give pause for thought to those assuming that altcoins will follow this time around. The first is, well, obvious: past cycles aren&rsquo;t indicative of future ones, and this is especially true for Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The asset was only launched in 2009, and it is only in the last five years that it has traded with any sort of reasonable liquidity (although even at that, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/very-few-bitcoins-are-actually-moving-but-the-liquidity-picture-could-change-soon/"><u>it&rsquo;s thin</u></a>). It would be foolish to put too much weight into previous years, therefore, especially as its entire existence has, until last year, coincided with a remarkable bull market in the wider economy. This is Bitcoin, and crypto&rsquo;s, first rodeo in a high-interest rate environment, so all bets are off.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">But aside from that blindingly obvious caveat, there is more evidence to suggest that there may have been a structural shift with regard to the market in the last six months, or something that may change the dominance trend going forward. What I am referring to is regulation and, more recently, institutional moves.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulatory clampdown in the US has been brutal for the crypto sector, with a number of tokens being confirmed as securities by the SEC in recent times, including Solana, Polygon, Cosmos, BNB and Cardano. Bitcoin, on the other hand, appears to be carving out its own niche. Or, as Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong said when discussing the lawsuit levelled against his exchange by the SEC, &ldquo;we kind of got this information from the SEC that, well actually, everything other than Bitcoin is a security&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, it feels foolish to declare this rise in dominance over the past few months as temporary. If anything, it is surprising that it has not risen more, although a lot of this regulatory trouble may have been priced in already, while the biggest non-Bitcoin token, Ether, seems to have evaded the dreaded security label thus far.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, there is also the reality of what has been happening on the institutional side in recent weeks. Blackrock and Fidelity, two of the world&rsquo;s largest asset managers, have both filed for spot ETFs. These are Bitcoin ETFs, not crypto ETFs.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In a sector where regulation is so hazy and the intimidation factor of actually buying physical Bitcoin is so high (the reality is that wallets and seed phrases are not ideal for new users or institutional funds, no matter how seductive the promise of self-custody is), this could do wonders for liquidity &ndash; one of the big factors holding Bitcoin back right now. It may also assuage concern around the lack of transparency and reliability of centralised exchanges, as institutions can simply bypass actors like Binance and go straight towards a (regulated) Bitcoin ETF. Of course, these ETFs are not approved yet, but we are a hell of a lot closer to a Bitcoin ETF than any other sort of crypto ETF.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The macro climate is still uncertain: inflation may have peaked but is still elevated, and with monetary policy notoriously operating with a lag, the full pain of a Fed rate north of 5% has yet to be felt. There are numerous challenges still to come. The regulatory crackdown could worsen, while who knows what is going behind the scenes at some of these crypto companies. But it feels undeniable that as bad as things are for crypto, Bitcoin has its head and shoulders above the rest of the gang.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">With all this in mind, the rising dominance makes sense. And while I have no idea what happens next (at the end of the day, <em>crypto is going to crypto</em>), I certainly see nothing that would make me confident that Bitcoin dominance, which is now at a two-year high, is bound to inevitably retreat soon.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/">Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner Of Manchester City In Expansion Of Partnership</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=144709</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club&#8217;s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement. As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left sleeve of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/">OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner Of Manchester City In Expansion Of Partnership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club&rsquo;s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement.</p>
<p>As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left sleeve of both the men&rsquo;s and women&rsquo;s first team playing kits and will retain its position on the left sleeve of the first team training kits, in addition to appearing across further digital and physical club assets.</p>
<p>OKX&rsquo;s partnership with Manchester City began in March 2022, first expanding in July 2022 to become the Club&rsquo;s Official Training Kit Partner for the 2022/23 season. To date, the partnership has helped introduce the brand to millions of football fans around the world through innovative Web3 experiences like the <a href="https://www.okx.com/activities/okxcollectivemetaverse" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OKX Collective</a>, through which fans can get up-close-and-personal with Manchester City players and OKX Ambassadors such as Jack Grealish and Alex Greenwood.</p>
<p>The partnership expansion was unveiled at an exclusive reveal at the Etihad Stadium featuring City Football Group Chief Executive Officer Ferran Soriano and OKX Global Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique. As part of the event, the sleeve was unveiled in a &lsquo;virtual reveal&rsquo; with a hero video featuring player avatars. Manchester City legend Ga&euml;l Clichy was also in attendance for a media Q&amp;A.</p>
<p>In a session moderated by Manchester City presenter <a href="https://www.mancity.com/wnrh/natalie-pike" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Natalie Pike</a>, Rafique and Soriano spoke about OKX&rsquo;s vision of reaching City fans around the world through the partnership. They also discussed the role Web3 technology can play in fan engagement, especially when it comes to designing engaging, immersive experiences for fans.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Ferran Soriano, Chief Executive Officer at City Football Group, said:</strong> &ldquo;We are very proud to have OKX represented on the sleeve of the Manchester City shirt. Both OKX and Manchester City are leading companies driven by a passion for innovation. We have already seen great Web3 experiences designed by OKX for Manchester City&rsquo;s global fan base and there will be many more to come. This is a very exciting partnership.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p><strong>Haider Rafique, CMO at OKX, said:</strong> &ldquo;The journey with the Man City team has been incredible. Manchester City was our first official global brand partnership and in just a year and a half we have come a long way. We always intended to integrate with the sport and help the Club lead on leaning into Web3. Fast forward fifteen months, we now have a metaverse, an NFT initiative and a number of other new projects that we are excited about.</p></blockquote>
<p>The sleeve partnership brings us closer to City fans across the globe, and we look forward to collaborating to create unique, exciting and innovative engagements through Web3 technology. As the Club&rsquo;s Official Cryptocurrency Exchange Partner, fans can expect amazing things every time they interact with OKX.&rdquo;</p>
<h3>About OKX</h3>
<p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of trading and Web3. Its leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Proof of Reserves</a> on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit:<a href="http://okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"> okx.com</a></p>
<h3 class="ql-align-justify">About Manchester City Football Club</h3>
<p>Manchester City FC is an English Premier League club initially founded in 1880 as St Mark&rsquo;s West Gorton. It officially became Manchester City FC in 1894 and has since then gone onto win the UEFA Champions League, European Cup Winners&rsquo; Cup, nine League Championship titles, seven FA Cups and eight League Cups. Manchester City FC is one of 13 clubs comprising the City Football Group.</p>
<p>Under manager Pep Guardiola, one of the most highly-decorated managers in world football, the Club plays its domestic and UEFA Champions League home fixtures at the Etihad Stadium, a spectacular 53,500 seat arena that City has called home since 2003. Today, the stadium sits on the wider Etihad Campus, which also encompasses the City Football Academy, a state-of-the-art performance training and youth development facility located in the heart of East Manchester. Featuring a 7,000-capacity Academy Stadium, the City Football Academy is also where Manchester City Women&rsquo;s Football Club and the Elite Development Squad train on a daily basis and play their competitive home games.</p>
<p>Disclaimer</p>
<p>OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AS THE VALUE OF YOUR ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS.</p>
<h3>Contact</h3>
<p>Media, media@okx.com, 0788118718</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/">OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner Of Manchester City In Expansion Of Partnership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin briefly falls below $30k as SEC says spot Bitcoin ETF filings are inadequate</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price reacted sharply to news that the SEC had said Bitcoin ETFs filings were inadequate. The SEC had reportedly returned the filed documents to BlackRock, Fidelity. However, BTC recovered above $30k as more details emerged. Bitcoin briefly crashed to below $30k within minutes on Friday as the US Securities and Exchnage Commission (SEC) reportedly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/">Bitcoin briefly falls below $30k as SEC says spot Bitcoin ETF filings are inadequate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin price reacted sharply to news that the SEC had said Bitcoin ETFs filings were inadequate.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The SEC had reportedly returned the filed documents to BlackRock, Fidelity.</li>
<li dir="ltr">However, BTC recovered above $30k as more details emerged.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> briefly crashed to below $30k within minutes on Friday as the US Securities and Exchnage Commission (SEC) reportedly told Nasdaq and the Cboe that recently filed spot Bicoin ETFs by BlackRock, Fidelity and other Wall Street giants were &ldquo;not clear and comprehensive.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulator has reportedly returned the spot ETF documents.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The markets reaction to the initial <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate-390336e8" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">news</a> by the Wall Street Journal was swift, with Bitcoin falling to $29,790 and Ethereum below $1,840.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">According to WSJ, the U.S. SEC stated that the filing of spot bitcoin ETFs was insufficient, and regulators told Nasdaq that recent filings by companies such as BlackRock and Fidelity were not clear and comprehensive.  The SEC returned the documents.  <a href="https://t.co/HK75jdB3ks">https://t.co/HK75jdB3ks</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1674778074557337601?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">&nbsp;&ldquo;<em>A</em><em>ffected by the news, the market crashed within 30 minutes. BTC once fell by more than 5% to below $30,000, ETH fell by more than 4%, and BCH and COMP, which had a large increase today, fell by more than 10%. &nbsp;Coinglass data shows that in the past 1 hour, the liquidation of the entire network exceeded 84 million US dollars</em>,&rdquo; Blockchain news reporter Colin Wu tweeted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, as it was reported that BlackRock and other asset managers only had to refile their applications correctly, Bitcoin moved back above $30k. Crypto analyst Will Clemente <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1674778064708935680" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">noted</a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Think the market is overreacting here, seems like the "denial" is just a technicality and Blackrock/Fidelity just have to refile naming Coinbase as the exchange that they have a "surveillance-sharing agreement" with</p>
<p>&mdash; Will Clemente (@WClementeIII) <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1674778064708935680?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-briefly-falls-below-30k-as-sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate/">Bitcoin briefly falls below $30k as SEC says spot Bitcoin ETF filings are inadequate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash has skyrocketed to a 14-month high above $320, hitting highs of $326 on Coinbase. BCH upside momentum has increased since Wall Street-backed EDX listed the coin alongside BTC, ETH and LTC. A spike in volume on South Korea exchange Upbit helped push CBH price higher on Friday. Bitcoin Cash rallied to its highest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/">Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin Cash has skyrocketed to a 14-month high above $320, hitting highs of $326 on Coinbase.</li>
<li>BCH upside momentum has increased since Wall Street-backed EDX listed the coin alongside BTC, ETH and LTC.</li>
<li>A spike in volume on South Korea exchange Upbit helped push CBH price higher on Friday.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin-cash/">Bitcoin Cash</a> rallied to its highest price in 14 months on Friday morning, trading at highs of $326 on US-based crypto exchange Coinbase.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Why is BCH price rallying today?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bitcoin Cash had stagnated below $165 since dipping below the level in June last year. However, with Bitcoin rallying to above $31k amid bullish sentiment buoyed by BlackRock&rsquo;s spot ETF filing, BCH roared to a <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-price-hits-1-year-high-as-bch-soars-72-this-week/">one-year high</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The bulls have been relentless since, with price crossing the psychological $300 mark today with more than 30% gains in 24 hours. The cryptocurrency has rallied nearly 200% over the past two weeks, and is now in the green by 110% over the past year.</p>
<p dir="ltr">It is notable that the price of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bch/">BCH</a> had raced to a new year high last week after EDX Markets, a new crypto exchange backed by major Wall Street companies including Fidelity and Charles Schwab, listed Bitcoin Cash. EDX only lists three other coins &ndash; BTC, ETH and LTC.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Enthusiasm across the BCH community from this listing has added to the upside momentum. On Friday, the positive outlook on the cryptocurrency&rsquo;s potential saw volume spike on a leading South Korea-based crypto platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As crypto markets bid to hold onto the positive sentiment, Bitcoin Cash appears to be getting some extra leg from South Korea. Over the past 24 hours, the BCH/KRW pair on crypto exchange Upbit rose to $557 million, more than thrice the volume of BTC/KRW and nearly 6x greater than BCH/USD.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Data from CoinGecko shows daily trading volume across all exchanges has increased 165% in the past 24 hours to over $2.4 billion. As IntoTheBlock <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1674432186660057092">points out</a>, BCH volume rose to above $750 million on Thursday, a one-year high.</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/2 Bitcoin Cash (BCH) soars 70% in a week, riding high on its recent inclusion on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/EDX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#EDX</a>, the Citadel Securities-Backed Crypto Exchange. Yesterday saw the highest volume of BCH transacted in a year, exceeding a staggering $750M.&#128279; <a href="https://t.co/1qZbEChogW">https://t.co/1qZbEChogW</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BitcoinCash?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BitcoinCash</a> <a href="https://t.co/OEOYG61sQR">pic.twitter.com/OEOYG61sQR</a></p>
<p>&mdash; IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1674432186660057092?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/">Bitcoin Cash jumps to 14-month high amid South Korea volume spike</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-cash-jumps-to-14-month-high-amid-south-korea-volume-spike/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana technical analysis update  can it jump to $40?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mircea Vasiu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana rallied in 2023 but failed to break above the horizontal resistance A bullish case remains valid unless the price moves below the 2022 lows If it breaks above horizontal resistance, Solana may trade above $40 Cryptocurrency investors must be thrilled with the 2023 price action. After all, Bitcoin bounced from last year&#8217;s lows, triggering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/">Solana technical analysis update  can it jump to $40?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Solana rallied in 2023 but failed to break above the horizontal resistance</li>
<li>A bullish case remains valid unless the price moves below the 2022 lows</li>
<li>If it breaks above horizontal resistance, Solana may trade above $40</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p>Cryptocurrency investors must be thrilled with the 2023 price action. After all, Bitcoin bounced from last year&rsquo;s lows, triggering a similar move in other major cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Solana followed suit.</p>
<p>The price more than doubled this year, rising from $10 to over $25 in what appeared to be a clear bullish breakout.</p>
<p>However, after trading above $26 in January, the market failed to build on the bullish trend. Instead, a consolidation started, bringing doubts to bullish traders.</p>
<p>The best way to clear such doubts is to look at the bigger picture. As the chart below shows, it is difficult to build a bullish case while the market holds below horizontal resistance.</p>
<p>However, the 2022 lows remain in place, so one can build a bullish scenario as long as the market does not dip below those lows.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/30/1688128168792-a49e9d0f-ca7e-491c-b8fb-341615b6e752.jpg" style="width: 1800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="1800" height="487"></p>
<p><a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/SOLUSD/?exchange=CRYPTO" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Solana chart by TradingView</a></p>
<h2>A break above horizontal resistance should trigger more gains</h2>
<p>Solana&rsquo;s price remains bearish while below horizontal resistance. However, a break above it implies more strength ahead.</p>
<p>That is especially true if the US dollar&rsquo;s weakness resumes. So far in 2023, the dollar traded with a mixed tone.</p>
<p>But as the Fed is on pause, renewed weakness will bode well for cryptocurrencies and for Solana.</p>
<p>A daily close above horizontal resistance opens the gates for a move above $40. If the Fed believes that the US inflation data follows the right path, the dollar should weaken in the year&rsquo;s second half.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/">Solana technical analysis update  can it jump to $40?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/solana-technical-analysis-update-can-it-jump-to-40/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
