<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 20:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin network hash rate hit a record high in May</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-network-hash-rate-record-high-may/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 20:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=142004</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin network activity climbed for the fifth month straight. Mining difficulty and transaction fee also climbed in May. The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency lost about 8.0% last month. Bitcoin may have lost about 8.0% last month on macro uncertainty but the network activity remained incredibly strong. JPMorgan analyst expects a slowdown in hash rate In May, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-network-hash-rate-record-high-may/">Bitcoin network hash rate hit a record high in May</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Bitcoin network activity climbed for the fifth month straight.</li>
<li>Mining difficulty and transaction fee also climbed in May.</li>
<li>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency lost about 8.0% last month.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> may have lost about 8.0% last month on macro uncertainty but the network activity remained incredibly strong.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan analyst expects a slowdown in hash rate</h2>
<p>In May, the daily network <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/hash-rate-6746261" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hash rate</a> &ndash; a closely followed metric that indicates network&rsquo;s health climbed to a record high. It was the fifth consecutive month of increase for the said indicator.</p>
<p>Simply put, larger the hash rate, the more secure is the network. Nonetheless, Reginald Smith &ndash; a JPMorgan analyst said in a note on Friday:</p>
<blockquote><p>Our sense is that network hash rate growth could slow over the coming months (possibly lagging BTC price appreciation) as funding available rack space is hard to come by.</p></blockquote>
<p>In terms of market cap, the 13 U.S. listed miners that JPMorgan tracks noted an aggregate increase of 5.0% last month to $6.7 billion.</p>
<h2>Mining difficulty and transaction fee also increased</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-does-mining-difficulty-mean/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mining difficulty</a> &ndash; another metric that typically moves in tandem with the Bitcoin hash rate &ndash; also climbed to a record high in May.</p>
<p>Recent data confirmed the crypto transaction fee to have increased last month as well. JPMorgan&rsquo;s Smith also said in his research note:</p>
<blockquote><p>Transaction fees spiked to over 5 Bitcoin per block mined in early May, which should drive modest C2Q23 earnings upside for the industry at large.</p></blockquote>
<p>In recent weeks, though, Bitcoin transaction fees have returned close to its historic average of about 0.5 BTC per block mined. Last week, JPMorgan <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/31/jpmorgan-reveals-900-billion-gold-based-implied-bitcoin-price-alongside-an-ethereum-upgrade-prediction-warning/?sh=62cd1f1d2010" target="_blank" rel="noopener">said</a> Bitcoin should be trading at $45,000.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-network-hash-rate-record-high-may/">Bitcoin network hash rate hit a record high in May</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CRUX Unveils a Thrilling Journey: Game Development, CEX Listing, and a Marketing Evolution</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>$CRUX, the new blockchain-powered gaming and financial platform, is proud to announce aims to revolutionize the crypto gaming industry and pave the way for exciting new milestones. They started to establish themselfs as a driving force in the gaming and blockchain space, building through bear market and with massive potential. At its core, CRUX offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/">CRUX Unveils a Thrilling Journey: Game Development, CEX Listing, and a Marketing Evolution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">$CRUX, the new blockchain-powered gaming and financial platform, is proud to announce aims to revolutionize the crypto gaming industry and pave the way for exciting new milestones. They started to establish themselfs as a driving force in the gaming and blockchain space, building through bear market and with massive potential.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685719079363-d9a6aeb2-0df4-4b03-b8be-154f1d0855ee.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="331"></p>
<p dir="ltr">At its core, CRUX offers a captivating gaming ecosystem that seamlessly integrates with its native token, CRUX (CRUX). They provide a play-to-earn (P2E) experience where players can unleash their skills, navigate challenges, and unlock real-world value. The immersive survival MMORPG game allows players to venture into a post-apocalyptic world, where they fight against relentless undead enemies and compete for survival in a resource-scarce environment all worth $CRUX that is tradeable for real value and money.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition to the game, CRUX offers a comprehensive financial platform that harnesses the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning technologies. Traders and investors can access real-time market analysis, social sentiment analysis, and on-chain data, enabling them to make well-informed decisions and capitalize on opportunities in the crypto market.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685719030295-1a29c3c5-f31f-44ce-b44c-327a0d22db18.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="340"></p>
<p dir="ltr">Exciting new milestones lie ahead for CRUX, with a key focus on expanding its reach and creating more value for its community. One of the most highly anticipated milestones is the upcoming listing on a major centralized exchange (CEX), which will significantly enhance accessibility and liquidity for the CRUX token. The CEX listing will empower users to seamlessly trade CRUX on a trusted and established platform, further fueling the growth and adoption of the ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Another critical area of development for CRUX is the continuous enhancement of its game. The team is dedicated to delivering engaging gameplay experiences, expanding the world, introducing new features, and fostering a vibrant community of players. By incorporating player feedback and leveraging cutting-edge technologies, CRUX aims to establish its game as a benchmark for immersive and rewarding gaming experiences in the crypto space.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CRUX recognizes the importance of strategic marketing initiatives to bolster its presence and drive user adoption. As the volume of CRUX transactions and the ecosystem&rsquo;s growth continue to surge, their smart contract allows them to gather even more funds for marketing due to a 4% fee on every transaction. On the tokenomics side, $CRUX has an 8% fee on every transaction, where 4% goes to marketing, 2% to liquidity, and 2% back to holders. These initiatives further strengthen the CRUX brand, attract new users, and expand its global community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Our upcoming CEX listing, coupled with ongoing game development and targeted marketing initiatives, will solidify CRUX&rsquo;s position as a leader in the crypto gaming industry,&rdquo; says Rodrigo, CEO of CRUX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">CRUX remains steadfast in its long-term vision of building a dynamic and interconnected metaverse powered by blockchain technology. By creating a seamless and immersive gaming experience while providing real-world value through the CRUX token, the platform aims to revolutionize the gaming and financial industries.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Their demo version of the game is out already and available on CRUX website.<br>Here&rsquo;s also a short gameplay of the alpha version:</p>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yKlM2DZaG1I" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yKlM2DZaG1I</u></a></p>
<p dir="ltr">To stay updated on CRUX&rsquo;s latest news, milestones, and developments, visit the official website at<a href="http://www.cruxcryptos.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>www.cruxcryptos.com</u></a>. Join the vibrant CRUX community on Telegram at<a href="https://t.me/CRUX_CRYPTOS" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>https://t.me/CRUX_CRYPTOS</u></a> for engaging discussions and insights.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">About CRUX</h2>
<p>CRUX is a community-driven blockchain platform that combines gaming and finance to deliver a unique and rewarding experience. With its survival MMORPG game and advanced financial platform powered by AI and machine learning, CRUX is reshaping the crypto gaming industry. The CRUX token (CRUX) serves as the utility token within the ecosystem, facilitating in-game transactions, empowering the financial platform, and rewarding users. For more information, visit<a href="http://www.cruxcryptos.com/" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"> <u>www.cruxcryptos.com</u></a>.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crux-unveils-a-thrilling-journey-game-development-cex-listing-and-a-marketing-evolution/">CRUX Unveils a Thrilling Journey: Game Development, CEX Listing, and a Marketing Evolution</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How a frog-themed token shapes Ethereum gas fees in 2023</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/how-a-frog-themed-token-shapes-ethereum-gas-fees-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/how-a-frog-themed-token-shapes-ethereum-gas-fees-in-2023/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We all know the cryptocurrency world is attached to memes and entertainment. From the Dogecoin meme coin that got the interest of Elon Musk to the Shiba Inu cryptocurrency that tried overcoming it, memes are catchy and thriving in the crypto market. Most of them are built within the Ethereum ecosystem, as the community is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-a-frog-themed-token-shapes-ethereum-gas-fees-in-2023/">How a frog-themed token shapes Ethereum gas fees in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">We all know the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/">cryptocurrency world</a> is attached to memes and entertainment. From the Dogecoin meme coin that got the interest of Elon Musk to the Shiba Inu cryptocurrency that tried overcoming it, memes are catchy and thriving in the crypto market. Most of them are built within the Ethereum ecosystem, as the community is one of the most united, so if you&rsquo;re looking for the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/how-to-buy/ethereum" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>best way to buy Ethereum,</u></a> you&rsquo;ve got plenty of support.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The latest and funniest coin is Pepe, which reached the crypto sector after becoming a famous meme a few years ago. The cartoon-based drawing is used as a mood for almost any emotion, so Matt Furie used Ethereum to launch the Pepe coin. The creator aims to increase the popularity of meme coins.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, what makes this cryptocurrency unique, and why does it influence Ethereum <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-are-gas-fees-in-crypto/">gas</a> prices?&nbsp;</p>
<div class="fr-img-space-wrap"><span class="fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib fr-draggable" style="width: 800px"><span class="fr-img-wrap">
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685714664580-d1634535-b598-4ff2-b826-1ce04b504d3d.jpg" style="width: 800px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="800" height="307"><span class="fr-inner">An image showing the Ethereum coin symbol. Source:&nbsp;<a href="https://pixabay.com/ro/illustrations/ethereum-de-aur-cripto-criptomoned%c4%83-7084736/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Pixabay</a></span></p>
<p></p></span></span>
<h2 class="fr-img-space-wrap2">What&rsquo;s so special about Pepe?</h2>
</div>
<p dir="ltr">The deflationary meme coin is unique as it enhances the meme culture spread among communities similar to cryptocurrency. However, the currency offers something only a few cryptocurrencies do: rewarding long-term stakers and incentivizing holders for longer periods to increase the chances of the coin&rsquo;s success. At the same time, the no-tax policy encourages holders to boost Pepe since a wider audience can access and use it.</p>
<p>The burning method of Pepe is also unique because, despite the 420,690,000,000,000-maximum supply, a portion of the coins are frequently removed from circulation to maintain scarcity and help users commit to the project.</p>
<p>Pepe is secured through the Ethereum blockchain by the PoS consensus mechanism, where decentralized validators stake ETH to secure the network and process transactions.</p>
<h2>What&rsquo;s the deal with Pepe and Ethereum gas fees?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The pepecoin has surged in popularity since its launch in April. This caused the median gas price to increase to more than 50% in the last 12 months, reaching 150 gwei (one gwei is a billionth of an ether). The demand for pepecoin has changed the network drastically, affecting even liquidity pools. It has been disclosed that Pepecoin transactions have burned around $10 million of gas since the launch.</p>
<p>Although similar meme coins have seen this success in the past market capitalization, such as CHAD and DINO, this time, things are different. While <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum</a> is fighting to lower gas prices, the increased demand for a particular cryptocurrency is against the upgrade efforts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The latest Ethereum update, Shanghai, is supposed to contribute to diminished gas fees as it gets more difficult for miners and investors to get ether. At the same time, as the network struggles with scalability, a suddenly increasing number of transactions usually leads to network congestion.</p>
<h2>How does Ethereum mitigate challenges?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The latest completed update on Ethereum was Shanghai, whose primary purpose was to allow users to withdraw their staked ether. The next target is to address scaling concerns to make transactions faster and cheaper, considering Ethereum&rsquo;s high fees.</p>
<p>At the same time, developers will benefit from lower costs through the EIP-3855 and EIP-3860 updates in an effort to encourage activity on the blockchain regarding creating DApps. Many other minor updates will contribute to lowering gas fees while maintaining network productivity.</p>
<h2>Why should Ethereum gas fees remain low?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Gas prices are usually affected by network congestion and the complexity of actions made on the blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Although Ethereum created the EIP-1559 program to make fees more predictable and help investors not be hit by sudden price changes, when a coin increases in demand, it&rsquo;s challenging to keep the base fee at a decent limit. And gas fees can&rsquo;t be considerably lowered because they&rsquo;re used to compensate stakers for their efforts to maintain the network, which is essential for providing data security.</p>
<p>However, gas prices have become so high that many people prefer to stop mining or investing, as the cost overtakes the profit, which is the case for such a prominent cryptocurrency and network. Besides the updates mitigating smaller costs, there are some ways for users to minimize fees and save money.</p>
<h2>Are meme coins important? Or safe to invest in?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Regardless of the coin type on the blockchain, keeping lower gas fees and maximizing transactional time will win over any other feature. However, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-is-blockchain/">blockchains</a> should be used for various cryptocurrencies to truly put them to work, which is why discussing the importance of meme coins is necessary.</p>
<p>The blockchain sector is all about communities and groups of people with similar interests who put their efforts into gaining cryptocurrencies and increasing the value of the ones they invest in.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meme coins help build these communities easier, as memes always bring people together for entertainment. Since there&rsquo;s already one formed, it&rsquo;s easier for the crypto sector to be linked with something with a base. That&rsquo;s because this type of community also takes the initiative to keep the audience engaged and interested in the common purpose of the network. That&rsquo;s why Ethereum has one of the strongest communities, whose interests include developing the ecosystem, bringing more updates, and offering support to beginners and users interested in investing.</p>
<p>Still, when investing in meme coins, certain dangers are linked to their stability. Let&rsquo;s take the example of Doge, whose popularity drastically increased after Elon Musk tweeted about it a few times. However, the coin doesn&rsquo;t necessarily hold a significant purpose during regular times.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Like in the case of Pepe, who&rsquo;s just starting to become viral as a cryptocurrency, the risk of holding this coin is that it can increase in value overnight and then drop down dramatically in the following hours, and so on. Its value depends on the hype from social media created by its holders. After that, we can&rsquo;t say that Pepe or another meme coin will have the same course as Bitcoin or Ethereum, which underwent different challenges over the years and remained reliable.</p>
<h2>Bottom line</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Pepe the Frog is a famous meme recently introduced in the blockchain sector as a cryptocurrency. Its value surged so drastically that it led to increased gas fees, an issue for which Ethereum is taking action now.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/how-a-frog-themed-token-shapes-ethereum-gas-fees-in-2023/">How a frog-themed token shapes Ethereum gas fees in 2023</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRX now live on Ethereum via the BitTorrent Bridge</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/trx-now-live-on-ethereum-via-the-bittorrent-bridge/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/trx-now-live-on-ethereum-via-the-bittorrent-bridge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/trx-now-live-on-ethereum-via-the-bittorrent-bridge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tron founder Justin Sun has announced that TRX is now accessible on Ethereum. According to Sun, Tron will leverage the BitTorrent Bridge, which provides a chain-agnostic asset transfer solution, to bring TRX to Ethereum. The price of TRX rose slightly following the news, trading around $0.076 on Friday morning. Tron&#8216;s native token TRX is now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/trx-now-live-on-ethereum-via-the-bittorrent-bridge/">TRX now live on Ethereum via the BitTorrent Bridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Tron founder Justin Sun has announced that TRX is now accessible on Ethereum.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to Sun, Tron will leverage the BitTorrent Bridge, which provides a chain-agnostic asset transfer solution, to bring TRX to Ethereum.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The price of TRX rose slightly following the news, trading around $0.076 on Friday morning.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/tron/">Tron</a>&lsquo;s native token TRX is now fully accessible on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/ethereum/">Ethereum</a>, the world&rsquo;s largest proof-of-stake network.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Tron founder Justin Sun said on Friday that the cryptocurrency had expanded its reach by going live on Ethereum.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Tron&rsquo;s live on Ethereum via BitTorrent Bridge</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Tron&rsquo;s expansion onto the leading altcoin network leverages the BitTorrent Bridge, Sun <a href="https://twitter.com/justinsuntron/status/1664582616098705409" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">tweeted</a>. In his announcement, Sun provided the contract address that has TRX fully accessible across the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">BitTorrent Bridge is a chain-agnostic, decentralized asset transfer solution offering a faster and easier way to move assets between EVM-compatible chains and Tron. TRX going live on Ethereum via the BitTorrent Bridge will boost the asset&rsquo;s liquidity and help increase Tron&rsquo;s overall growth within the DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Currently, Tron ranks as the second-largest chain in terms of total value locked (TVL), with data from <a href="https://defillama.com/chains" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DeFiLlama</a> showing a total of $5.6 billion worth of assets locked in 22 protocols. However, this pales in comparison to TVL on Ethereum &ndash; which is currently at over $27 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But with 22 protocols leveraging the Tron network, data shows its way off competitors including BNB Smart Chain (606), Polygon (425) and Arbitrum (346).</p>
<p dir="ltr">TRX traded around $0.076 on Friday morning, with the price up 2.2% in the past 24 hours. Meanwhile, Ethereum&rsquo;s ETH was perched near $1,900, up just over 1%.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/trx-now-live-on-ethereum-via-the-bittorrent-bridge/">TRX now live on Ethereum via the BitTorrent Bridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/trx-now-live-on-ethereum-via-the-bittorrent-bridge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto price predictions: Sui, Jasmy, Avalanche (AVAX)</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-sui-jasmy-avalanche-avax/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-sui-jasmy-avalanche-avax/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-sui-jasmy-avalanche-avax/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sui Blockchain made headlines by partnering with RedBull Racing. Jasmy has formed a rising wedge pattern on the hourly chart. AVAX has formed a double-bottom pattern. Cryptocurrency prices remained in a consolidation mode this week even after the US Congress voted for a bipartisan bill to avert a government default. They also wavered as volume [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-sui-jasmy-avalanche-avax/">Crypto price predictions: Sui, Jasmy, Avalanche (AVAX)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Sui Blockchain made headlines by partnering with RedBull Racing.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Jasmy has formed a rising wedge pattern on the hourly chart.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">AVAX has formed a double-bottom pattern.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/price/"><u>Cryptocurrency prices</u></a> remained in a consolidation mode this week even after the US Congress voted for a bipartisan bill to avert a government default. They also wavered as volume of coins traded in centralized and decentralized exchanges (DEX) fell. Bitcoin is still hovering at the key point at $27,100 while Ethereum has been stuck below $2,000. In this article, we will highlight some of the most notable cryptocurrencies this week like Jasmy, Avalanche, and SUI.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Sui price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sui is a new blockchain project that aims to become the best alternative to layer-1 networks like Avalanche and Ethereum. This week, the coin plunged to a low of $0.90, which was sharply lower than its all-time high of $1.1140.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The biggest news was that the company was partnering with RedBull Racing, the leading Formula 1 team. This partnership will see the logo pasted in the Formula 1 cars. Sui Blockchain will also roll out several digital experiences for the team, as we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/sui-blockchain-partners-with-formula-ones-oracle-red-bull-racing-team/"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is an important partnership but investors should take it with a grain of salt. In the past, blockchains that partnered with Formula 1 teams like&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/tezos"><u>Tezos</u></a> and Velas did not outperform the market.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The hourly chart shows that the token has rebounded after the new agreement. It still remains below the 25-period and 50-period moving averages. Therefore, I suspect that the token will resume the bearish trend during the weekend as investors assess the Red Bull partnership. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.9090, this week&rsquo;s low.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685710952835-70b3415f-2f98-46fb-ad32-6d77a75caf4b.png" style="width: 517px;height: 251.174px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="517" height="251.174"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy SUI</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Jasmy price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr">JasmyCoin is a small but well-known Japanese cryptocurrency that is seen as Japan&rsquo;s version of&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin"><u>Bitcoin</u></a>. Like other cryptocurrencies, the token plunged to a low of $0.0044 as interest in cryptocurrencies waned. It has now pared back some of the recent losses and jumped by about 4% from the lowest point this month.</p>
<p dir="ltr">These gains could be limited since the coin has formed a rising wedge pattern. In price action analysis, this pattern is usually a bearish sign. And the wedge pattern is nearing its confluence level. It has also formed an inverted cup and handle pattern. Therefore, I supect that the coin will have a bearish breakout as sellers target the next key support at $0.0044, the lowest point in June.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685710952985-a8957eb2-040d-4c1a-9b5c-f8673dec2957.png" style="width: 550px;height: 267.667px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="550" height="267.667"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Jasmy</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    Binance.US</h3>

    <p>Binance.US provides secure and reliable access to the world&rsquo;s most popular cryptocurrencies, with some of the lowest fees in the industry.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/binance-us-crypto?guid=MTQxNzM5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy JASMY with Binance.US today            </a>
    </p><h3>
    Swapzone</h3>

    <p>Swapzone is a crypto exchange aggregator that operates as a gateway between the cryptocurrency community and exchange services. Swapzone aims to provide a convenient interface, safe user flow, and crystal-clear data for users to find the best exchange rates among the whole cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/swapzone-crypto?guid=MTQxNzM5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy JASMY with Swapzone today            </a>
    </p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Avalanche price prediction</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/avalanche/"><u>Avalanche</u></a> price dropped to an important support level at $13.8 this week as cryptocurrencies retreated. It then bounced back as Trader Joe&rsquo;s JOE token roared back. On the 4H chart, it seems like the coin has formed a small double-bottom pattern whose neckline is at $15. However, the coin remains below the 50-period and 100-period moving averages.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, because of the double-bottom pattern, AVAX price will likely continue rising as buyers target the neckline of the double-bottom pattern at $15. This price is about 4.50% above the current level.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/05/02/1685710952796-c7c84eee-f464-475f-bd8b-5aa54216f789.png" style="width: 693px;height: 337.26px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="693" height="337.26"></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">How to buy Avalanche</h3>
<p dir="ltr"></p><h3>
    eToro</h3>

    <p>eToro offers a wide range of cryptos, such as Bitcoin, XRP and others, alongside crypto/fiat and crypto/crypto pairs. eToro users can connect with, learn from, and copy or get copied by other users.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/etoro-crypto?guid=MTQxNzM5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=1&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy AVAX with eToro today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptoasset investing is unregulated in some EU countries. No consumer protection. Your capital is at risk." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p><h3>
    Public</h3>

    <p>Public is an investing platform that allows you to invest stocks, ETFs, crypto, and alternative assets like fine art and collectibles&mdash;all in one place.</p>

<p>
    <a href="/visit/public-crypto?guid=MTQxNzM5&amp;component=simple-table&amp;language=en&amp;country=US&amp;position=2&amp;totalPositions=2" rel="noopener nofollow sponsored">
                    Buy AVAX with Public today            </a>
            <button class="flex items-center mt-2 text-sm text-gray-600 focus:o-outline-none" data-tooltip="Cryptocurrency execution and custody services are provided by Apex Crypto LLC (NMLS ID 1828849) through a software licensing agreement between Apex Crypto LLC and Public Crypto LLC. Crypto trading on Public platforms is served by Public Crypto LLC and offered through APEX Crypto. Please ensure that you fully understand the risks involved before trading." aria-expanded="false">
            <span class="border-b border-gray-600 border-dotted">Disclaimer</span>
            <span class="ml-1">
                <svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 512 512" class="w-3 h-3">
                    <path fill="currentColor" d="M256 40c118.621 0 216 96.075 216 216 0 119.291-96.61 216-216 216-119.244 0-216-96.562-216-216 0-119.203 96.602-216 216-216m0-32C119.043 8 8 119.083 8 256c0 136.997 111.043 248 248 248s248-111.003 248-248C504 119.083 392.957 8 256 8zm-36 344h12V232h-12c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12h48c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v140h12c6.627 0 12 5.373 12 12v8c0 6.627-5.373 12-12 12h-72c-6.627 0-12-5.373-12-12v-8c0-6.627 5.373-12 12-12zm36-240c-17.673 0-32 14.327-32 32s14.327 32 32 32 32-14.327 32-32-14.327-32-32-32z"></path>
                </svg>
            </span>
        </button>
    </p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-sui-jasmy-avalanche-avax/">Crypto price predictions: Sui, Jasmy, Avalanche (AVAX)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-price-predictions-sui-jasmy-avalanche-avax/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DPAT Raises Private Funding To Enhance Web3.0 Ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 11:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=141729</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Accra, Ghana, June 2nd, 2023, Chainwire DPAT, the first Web3 crowdsourcing platform designed to connect investors with real estate and infrastructure opportunities in major African cities, has announced the launch of its highly anticipated updated roadmap and revamped website. Positioning itself as a bridge to new emerging economies, the Ethereum-backed Web3 investment platform is set [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/">DPAT Raises Private Funding To Enhance Web3.0 Ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Accra, Ghana, June 2nd, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://dpatoken.io/?utm_source=syndicated&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=private_funding&amp;utm_id=dpat" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><strong>DPAT</strong></a><strong>, the first Web3 </strong>crowdsourcing platform designed to connect investors with real estate and infrastructure opportunities in major African cities, has announced the launch of its highly anticipated updated roadmap and revamped website.</p>
<p>Positioning itself as a bridge to new emerging economies, the Ethereum-backed Web3 investment platform is set to attract investors, crypto advocates, and entrepreneurs alike by offering a say in what gets built, by whom and for who in markets where they believe success is only lacking the right type of funding.</p>
<p>The road map for the Direct Property Africa Token (DPAT) project demonstrates its scope and endurance. Initially, focusing on 15 cities in 12 countries to establish systems, processes, and legal precedent. The project team will reinvest the funds received to support the ongoing development of custom solutions such as a seamless marketplace checkout and simple developer onboarding processes.</p>
<blockquote><p>Project Lead for DPAT, Mustafa A said: &ldquo;The feedback from our community matters to us, and we have taken that into account. We continue to build applications with the end user in mind and revamping our website and processes to provide an enhanced user experience is a sign of things to come.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>Beyond the new website built to make it easier to navigate and access project information, the marketplace will help developers smoothly list their projects and engage with their community by offering rewards and equity-based NFTs to swiftly raise capital at prices that are competitive with banks and other traditional lenders. To further show its support to the African real estate industry, DPAT will work closely with agents and developers in project cities to increase knowledge, simplicity and security through implementation and integration of Web3 technology to digitise and update current business models.</p>
<p>The project is currently in its presale phase and shortly after completion in August, Direct Property Africa will roll out the NFT crowdsourcing marketplace and increase its core team. DPAT will initially launch on Uniswap and list on tier 1 centralized exchanges a few weeks later. With an ambitious road map, DPAT is on track to disrupt how developers finance projects and the community access African assets. All while showcasing a different side and image of the continent.</p>
<h2><strong>About Direct Property Africa Token (DPAT)</strong></h2>
<p>Direct Property Africa is a Web3 real estate and infrastructure ecosystem including a crowdsourcing marketplace for local developers to raise funding for projects in major African cities like Cape Town, Lagos and Accra with fractional ownership using asset-backed equity NFTs. DPAT is the utility token of the Direct Property Africa ecosystem offering rewards and privileges to holders.</p>
<p>Learn more about Direct Property Africa Token at <a href="https://dpatoken.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://dpatoken.io/</a></p>
<p>Join the conversation on DPATs <a href="https://discord.gg/u2dgVqUYun" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a>, <a href="https://t.me/dpatokencommunity" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> and follow on <a href="https://twitter.com/dpatoken" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> for latest project updates.</p>
<h2>Contact</h2>
<p>Mr Dan Costea, Direct Property Africa Token (DPAT), marketing@dpatoken.io</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/">DPAT Raises Private Funding To Enhance Web3.0 Ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What does Binance leaving Canada mean for the crypto industry?</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-binance-leaving-crypto-mean-for-the-crypto-industry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dan Ashmore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Opinion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-binance-leaving-crypto-mean-for-the-crypto-industry/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Takeaways Binance has become the latest crypto company to depart Canada amid regulatory concerns Canada is a small market but US regulators have also clamped down severely&#160; The move by Binance amplifies the growing concern within the industry that crypto will have no choice but to move offshore Another week, another story of regulatory [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-binance-leaving-crypto-mean-for-the-crypto-industry/">What does Binance leaving Canada mean for the crypto industry?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr">Key Takeaways</h2>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Binance has become the latest crypto company to depart Canada amid regulatory concerns</li>
<li dir="ltr">Canada is a small market but US regulators have also clamped down severely&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">The move by Binance amplifies the growing concern within the industry that crypto will have no choice but to move offshore</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<p dir="ltr">Another week, another story of regulatory woes for the cryptocurrency industry. The world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange by volume, Binance, announced Friday that it was fleeing Canada off the back of regulatory changes in the nation.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;Unfortunately, new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits provided to crypto exchanges makes the Canada market no longer tenable for Binance at this time.&rdquo;, the company said in a statement on Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Unfortunately, today we are announcing that Binance will be joining other prominent crypto businesses in proactively withdrawing from the Canadian marketplace.</p>
<p>We would like to thank those regulators who worked with us collaboratively to address the needs of Canadian users.&hellip;</p>
<p>&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1657099651210969088?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">As the tweet also notes, Canada held &ldquo;sentimental value for us as the home country of our founder (CEO Changpeng Zhao)&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance may be the biggest, but it is not the first crypto firm to abandon the Canadian market. In February, the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) published new expectations around the registration of crypto platforms in the country, specifically around the requirement to file preregistration undertakings.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This has proved a problem. Fellow exchange OKX withdrew from the Canadian market within a month. The decentralised exchange dYdX soon followed, and last month Paxos, who formerly issued the Binance-branded stablecoin BUSD, did the same. Now, it is Binance&rsquo;s turn.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">US regulators will be watching</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Pulling out of the Canadian market should not be a big issue in itself. As Binance says in its tweet, the nation represents a &ldquo;small market&rdquo;. The population of Canada is approximately 38 million, slightly less than the US state of California.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Nonetheless, the developments are concerning as they come amid a broader regulatory clampdown in the US. South of the border in the US, the crypto industry is at war with regulators, and Canada&rsquo;s unaccommodating stance won&rsquo;t help things.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Binance itself is already under pressure via multiple investigations and complaints in the US. The most notable is a civil enforcement action <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8680-23"><u>filed</u></a> by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, alleging that Binance and its subsidiaries operate through &ldquo;an intentionally opaque common enterprise&rdquo;, with accusations including the failure &ldquo;to implement basic compliance procedures designed to prevent and detect terrorist financing and money laundering&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">SEC tighten screw</h2>
<p dir="ltr">This is only part of an intense regulatory crackdown in the US. Coinbase and the SEC have been engaged in an ongoing war of words, the former threatening last week to use the UAE as an international hub amid the growing hostility in the US. The exchange has repeatedly lamented what it perceives as a lack of regulatory clarity by lawmakers.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;It is important for regulators to set policy and THEN enforce it. Not start with enforcement before there are clear rules&rdquo;, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong tweeted last week.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">
</p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Met with the SEC today. We&rsquo;ll continue pushing for a clear rule book in the U.S. for crypto regs.</p>
<p>The U.S. can&rsquo;t afford to fall behind on this important technology to update the financial system.</p>
<p>Also important for regulators to set policy and THEN enforce it. Not start with&hellip; <a href="https://t.co/EaPD7wDbSx">pic.twitter.com/EaPD7wDbSx</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Brian Armstrong &#128737;&#65039; (@brian_armstrong) <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1649465612987449344?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Chairman of the SEC, Gary Gensler, clapped back this week. He asserted in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k-ueNvNwcnI"><u>speech</u></a> at the Financial Markets Conference in Atlanta that &ldquo;the rules have already been published&rdquo;. He added that &ldquo;there&rsquo;s nothing about a new technology (such as crypto) that makes it non-consistent with the public polices that congress has laid out&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The comments follow a <a href="https://docs.house.gov/meetings/BA/BA00/20230418/115751/HHRG-118-BA00-Wstate-GenslerG-20230418.pdf"><u>testimony</u></a> in April before the House of Representatives Committee on Financial Services that slammed the crypto sector for mass non-compliance.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr"><em>&ldquo;Crypto intermediaries&mdash;whether they call themselves centralised or decentralised&mdash;often provide an amalgam of services that typically are separated from each other in the rest of the securities markets: exchange functions, broker-dealer functions, custodial and clearing functions, and lending functions. The commingling of the various functions within crypto intermediaries creates inherent conflicts of interest and risks for investors&mdash;risks and conflicts the Commission does not allow in any other marketplace.&rdquo;</em></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">What happens next for crypto?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, while Binance abandoning the relatively small Canadian market may not be the biggest blow in isolation, industry participants should worry about what this signals going forward. It amounts to just the latest regulatory blow in North America, and it feels like the industry is very much being pushed overseas.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">While cryptocurrency is technology and can theoretically operate anywhere, the fact of the matter is that the US is the biggest financial market in the world, and pushing firms abroad &ndash; and making it far more inconvenient for customers to access the blockchain world &ndash; cannot be good for the space.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Blockchain is often advertised as a way to circumvent the traditional finance world. As seductive as that sounds for some, it is also the reason it is landing itself in hot water with authorities (unsurprisingly). Additionally, while branches of crypto may offer a more censorship-resistant, smoother way to shift money around and store wealth, people still need to access it from the fiat world in the first place. They also need to repeatedly bridge between the two to withdraw money, because the world is still paying for food, water, housing and every other good and service in fiat. This is why restricting crypto exchanges and other onboarding avenues in the US is a big problem for the industry&rsquo;s hopes of establishing itself in the mainstream.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So the argument that crypto can brush aside these regulatory issues, or seamlessly move abroad without impact, may be missing the point. The continued crackdown from regulators in North America is becoming a crisis for the crypto industry. Canada&rsquo;s expulsion of Binance is just the latest story highlighting that fact.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/what-does-binance-leaving-crypto-mean-for-the-crypto-industry/">What does Binance leaving Canada mean for the crypto industry?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pink Moon Studios Reveals &#8216;KMON: World of Kogaea&#8217; Pioneering a New Era in Web3 Open-World Gaming</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/pink-moon-studios-reveals-kmon-world-of-kogaea-pioneering-a-new-era-in-web3-open-world-gaming/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/pink-moon-studios-reveals-kmon-world-of-kogaea-pioneering-a-new-era-in-web3-open-world-gaming/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 07:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=141671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 2nd, 2023, Chainwire Pink Moon Studios, a leading innovator in the Web3 gaming industry, is thrilled to announce the launch of their latest sensation, &#8220;KMON: World of Kogaea.&#8221; This immersive 3D open-world game, available initially to Kryptomon NFT holders, underscores Pink Moon Studios&#8217; expertise in crafting groundbreaking NFT metaverse games, harnessing the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pink-moon-studios-reveals-kmon-world-of-kogaea-pioneering-a-new-era-in-web3-open-world-gaming/">Pink Moon Studios Reveals &#8216;KMON: World of Kogaea&#8217; Pioneering a New Era in Web3 Open-World Gaming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Singapore, Singapore, June 2nd, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Pink Moon Studios, a leading innovator in the Web3 gaming industry, is thrilled to announce the launch of their latest sensation, &ldquo;<a href="https://www.kryptomon.co/world" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">KMON: World of Kogaea</a>.&rdquo; This immersive 3D open-world game, available initially to Kryptomon NFT holders, underscores Pink Moon Studios&rsquo; expertise in crafting groundbreaking NFT metaverse games, harnessing the power of state-of-the-art Web3 gaming technologies.</p>
<h2>Unveiling Pink Moon Shards: Ultra-Exclusive NFT Rewards for &ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo; Players</h2>
<p>Pink Moon Studios has orchestrated a series of immersive campaign activities to celebrate the game&rsquo;s launch. Foremost among these is the introduction of the &ldquo;Pink Moon Shards,&rdquo; unique tokens crafted using ERC-1125 blockchain technology that will be only available by completing the quests players will be given in World of Kogaea during the Early-Community Preview events. Exclusive to the game&rsquo;s Early-Community Preview launch events, these shards will serve as tradable NFTs, bringing unprecedented rewards to the players.</p>
<p>The Pink Moon Shards present a unique opportunity for players to later interact during the game&rsquo;s official release with the &ldquo;KMON Forge,&rdquo; Pink Moon&rsquo;s pioneering on-chain crafting system. This system allows players to craft limited-edition NFTs that can&rsquo;t be found elsewhere in the game, offering holding players significant advantages throughout the KMON Game Saga. Following the game&rsquo;s official release, the shards will be airdropped into the players&rsquo; wallets based on their performance and event participation.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/w70iSY1_1685625220DdrzjiVv5a.jpeg"></p>
<blockquote><p>Brian Bento, the Chief Product Officer at Pink Moon Studios, shares his enthusiasm: &ldquo;The launch of our initial community tech preview for &lsquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rsquo; is a monumental event we&rsquo;ve eagerly awaited. It&rsquo;s an invitation to our players to be the first to experience this new massive world we&rsquo;ve brought to life. The unveiling of the exclusive Pink Moon Shards is equally exciting. These unique tokens represent a pioneering approach to in-game rewards, enhancing our players&rsquo; experience while enriching our gaming ecosystem. I&rsquo;m ecstatic about what we&rsquo;re bringing to the world of Web3 gaming, and I can&rsquo;t wait to see our players dive into the captivating world of Kogaea to see what we have in store for them in the future.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to the exclusive shards, Pink Moon Studios will launch a vibrant community campaign spanning various social media platforms, in which participants will get an opportunity to win free Kryptomon NFTs for completing a few simple steps, providing a compelling incentive for players to engage in the celebration of the game&rsquo;s official release. More information about the campaign can be found on the <a href="https://www.kryptomon.co/world" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">official website of KMON World of Kogaea</a>.</p>
<h2>Meet the Creators: Exclusive Live Streaming Event</h2>
<p>To commemorate this exciting release, Pink Moon Studios will host an exclusive live-streaming event where the community can meet the team behind &ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo;. The creators will step into the world they&rsquo;ve designed, exploring and experiencing it alongside community members while providing insights about the game&rsquo;s creation and its unique Web3 gaming mechanics. This exclusive streaming event, which will feature Pink Moon Studios&rsquo; CEO Umberto Canessa Cerchi and other leadership members, will take place during the launch week. The exact date and time of the event will be announced in the next few days on the company&rsquo;s official <a href="https://www.facebook.com/KryptomonTeam" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://discord.gg/kryptomon" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Discord</a>, and <a href="https://t.me/kryptomonofficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a> channels.</p>
<h2>Revolutionizing the Gaming Industry with KMON Games</h2>
<p>Since its inception, Pink Moon Studios has been at the forefront of innovation in the gaming landscape with its KMON Game Saga, all powered by the transformative potential of blockchain technology. This dynamic gaming universe allows players to breed, train, and battle with their NFT Kryptomon, forging unique digital companions.</p>
<p>The long-awaited &ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo; is a ground-breaking Web3 blockchain-enabled game that plunges players into an extraordinary 3D open-world metaverse experience, seamlessly integrating with the other two KMON games &ldquo;Genesis&rdquo;, its 2D casual training and battling game, and &ldquo;Pink Moon&rdquo;, the company&rsquo;s AR treasure-hunt game. &ldquo;World of Kogaea&rdquo; offers players a multifaceted interaction with their Kryptomon NFTs across multiple platforms, propelling the gaming experience to unprecedented levels.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fjXTUN2oCXI?showinfo=0"></iframe></p>
<p>The &ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo; launch is a testament to Pink Moon Studios&rsquo; robust capabilities and achievements in the Web3 gaming industry. As the world of blockchain technology continues to evolve, the gaming experiences offered by innovators like Pink Moon Studios promise to ascend to even more impressive heights. Umberto Canessa Cerchi, the CEO of Pink Moon Studios, expressed his excitement about the launch: &ldquo;The unveiling of &ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo; marks a significant milestone for Pink Moon Studios and the Web3 gaming industry. This revolutionary game underscores our commitment to leveraging the power of blockchain technology and our groundbreaking Web3 gaming technologies to redefine the gaming landscape.&rdquo;</p>
<h2>Riding the Wave of Remarkable Success</h2>
<p>Pink Moon Studios has already demonstrated significant success, amassing a noteworthy $11.4 million in two funding rounds and fostering a dedicated community of almost 450,000 members across various social platforms. This achievement reflects the company&rsquo;s commitment to creating immersive gaming experiences and has drawn the attention of industry-leading partners, including Binance NFT, Crypto.com NFT, and others. Already during its first seven months of existence, Pink Moon Studios has generated over $18M in Kryptomon NFT transaction volumes alone, demonstrating its ability to fascinate the gaming community.</p>
<p>Beyond funding and partnerships, Pink Moon Studios&rsquo; relentless pursuit of innovation has led to the development of path-breaking technologies. These include the unique &ldquo;Diamond Contract&rdquo; and the on-chain &ldquo;NFT Forging System,&rdquo; allowing players to engage with their Kryptomon innovatively, fostering a unique digital bond.</p>
<p>Additionally, introducing its crypto and non-crypto user-friendly &ldquo;Trainer Hub&rdquo; and &ldquo;KMarket&rdquo; NFT marketplace has revolutionized how players buy and sell blockchain-based assets, providing seamless transactions without prior crypto knowledge or a crypto wallet.</p>
<h2>The Dawn of a New Era in Gaming</h2>
<p>The debut of &ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo; marks the beginning of an exciting new chapter in gaming, promising even more thrilling, immersive, and engaging experiences. As Pink Moon Studios continues to redefine the gaming industry with its unique blend of cutting-edge technology and inventive gameplay, it&rsquo;s well-positioned to become a trendsetter in the rapidly evolving world of digital entertainment.</p>
<p>&ldquo;KMON: World of Kogaea&rdquo; is just the beginning, and the gaming community eagerly awaits the new waves of innovation that Pink Moon Studios is set to bring in the years to come. The future is certainly promising for Pink Moon Studios as they continue their journey, redefining the gaming landscape and delivering unparalleled experiences to players around the globe.</p>
<h2>About Pink Moon Studios</h2>
<p>Pink Moon Studios, initially known as Kryptomon, is a cutting-edge technology company established in 2021, specializing in pioneering Web3 gaming solutions. Composed of a vibrant team of experienced developers and entrepreneurs, they harness the power of blockchain technology, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and augmented reality (AR) to reshape the gaming industry. Offering a suite of innovative services including the Diamond Contract, NFT Forging, Phygital NFTs, and the AR NFT Hunt, Pink Moon Studio aims to create immersive, engaging, and innovative gaming experiences that transcend traditional gaming boundaries. In addition to gaming innovation, Pink Moon Studio is deeply committed to social responsibility and environmental sustainability, indicating their dedication to driving positive change in the world. Their vision is not only to revolutionize gaming but also to foster a more responsible and sustainable future for the industry.</p>
<h2>Contact</h2>
<p>Chief Business Development Officer, Tomer Warschauer Nuni, Pink Moon Studios, tomer@pink-moon.studio, &#8237;+1 (347) 527-9811&#8236;</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/pink-moon-studios-reveals-kmon-world-of-kogaea-pioneering-a-new-era-in-web3-open-world-gaming/">Pink Moon Studios Reveals &#8216;KMON: World of Kogaea&#8217; Pioneering a New Era in Web3 Open-World Gaming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/pink-moon-studios-reveals-kmon-world-of-kogaea-pioneering-a-new-era-in-web3-open-world-gaming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Proposes Industry-First BRC-30 Token Standard to Enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 Token Staking</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 22:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=141624</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SAN FRANCISCO, UNITED STATES, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire With BRC-30, OKX Wallet users will soon be able to stake BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin to earn passive income on their digital assets OKX, a leading Web3 company, today introduced its proposal for a new, open-source BRC-30 protocol that enables staking of BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking/">OKX Proposes Industry-First BRC-30 Token Standard to Enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 Token Staking</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>SAN FRANCISCO, UNITED STATES, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>With BRC-30, OKX Wallet users will soon be able to stake BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin to earn passive income on their digital assets</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=djN5tl1YI3n-fgTWNjU7Z11yepNupe6FKFK4tQmjr7XwkwLirt8TEFQ2dB0PtrVpgZeYXCDddJTNW8IJtF-s0Hln-4JR3B2BKPx3ypDGiTLrafMbQNP4m3SMhGBgO88-Lu-FKAfyfI8U3Qe1BA5sW37WfBkxNJGLXYk4S28SQtYWlrjc7xX0nB3XQ2ay-_hV" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>OKX</u></a>, a leading Web3 company, today introduced its <a href="https://www.okx.com/web3/build/docs/bitcoin-ecosystem/brc30-proposal" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">proposal</a> for a new, open-source BRC-30 protocol that enables staking of BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin in order to earn BRC-30 tokens. The protocol is open-source and available for all developers to build upon.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.okx.com/web3" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">OKX Wallet</a> will add support for the BRC-30 standard according to the protocol, enabling users to earn passive income by staking BRC-20 tokens or Bitcoin on <a href="https://www.okx.com/web3/earn" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Web3 Earn</a> without actively trading. This complements the existing range of curated DeFi earning products already available through the platform.</p>
<p>The introduction of BRC-30 and its staking functionalities is driven by OKX&rsquo;s goal to provide users with additional opportunities to participate in the Bitcoin ecosystem and earn passive income.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>OKX Chief Innovation Officer Jason Lau said</strong>: &ldquo;We&rsquo;re thrilled to have proposed and pioneered the BRC-30 standard to enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 token staking. With the OKX Wallet soon to incorporate BRC-30 support, users will be able to access Bitcoin staking and earn opportunities across multiple-chains. With the Bitcoin ecosystem seeing an explosion of new development, we&rsquo;re proud to work with developers and projects across the community to contribute to the growth of the wider ecosystem.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>
<p>OKX is a longstanding supporter of Bitcoin, having integrated the Lightning Network to its centralized exchange over two years ago. OKX Wallet is also the first multi-chain wallet to support BRC-20 trading with the launch of its Ordinals Marketplace, as well as the viewing and transfer of Bitcoin Ordinals.</p>
<p><strong>About OKX</strong></p>
<p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace, DEX and Web3 Earn.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX believes in challenging the status quo. The company recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, <a href="https://www.okx.com/learn/okx-launches-global-brand-campaign-the-system-needs-a-rewrite" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u>The System Needs a Rewrite</u></a>, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit:<a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=-97bDo6UkGkXWr9xvBuJ5zVdJXbyZKLDWnhnnDg7_IQpUAN5tZv82wcT9F7y5bztE8uXJtidgjX1_SHT2X-kNzJ1prvtanGeldPPReOWhzBE9T9aa9KURUdDtN3tO2aTSl0Db3UzVwRMr4_viG01aJZzsc5ygl3enkd54vGvswg9h2CADbDyTnY6_ktSNlc0_EiWVSHFCslZtg_qG2gsAhNKNH4hJF4bYQRf-WvPSCQ=" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"><u> okx.com</u></a></p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p>THIS ANNOUNCEMENT IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE ANY INVESTMENT, TAX, OR LEGAL ADVICE, NOR SHOULD IT BE CONSIDERED AN OFFER TO PURCHASE, SELL, OR HOLD DIGITAL ASSETS. DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, INVOLVE A HIGH DEGREE OF RISK, CAN FLUCTUATE GREATLY, AND CAN EVEN BECOME WORTHLESS. OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AND WHETHER TRADING OR HOLDING DIGITAL ASSETS IS SUITABLE FOR YOU IN LIGHT OF YOUR FINANCIAL CONDITION. THE VALUE OF YOUR DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS. OKX IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH ANY PARTICULAR DEFI PROTOCOL, MAKES NO WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR UNDERTAKINGS RELATING TO ANY DEFI PROTOCOL&rsquo;S OFFERINGS, AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSS OR OTHER DAMAGE ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF ANY DEFI PROTOCOL. OKX WALLET IS AN AGGREGATOR; ALL DISPLAYED ESTIMATED RETURN RATES ARE PROVIDED BY THE DEFI PROTOCOL, AND ARE NOT GUARANTEED NOR INDICATIVE OF FUTURE RETURNS. PLEASE CONDUCT YOUR OWN DUE DILIGENCE BEFORE INVESTING IN ANY DEFI PROTOCOL. PLEASE CONSULT YOUR LEGAL/TAX/INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL FOR QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>OKX, media@okx.com</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking/">OKX Proposes Industry-First BRC-30 Token Standard to Enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 Token Staking</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
