<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<atom:link href="https://coinjournal.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your home of the best & latest crypto news. Most recent news & guidance about Bitcoin, Ethereum, mining, cryptocurrency prices, and more.]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 19:27:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://coinjournal.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/apple-touch-icon.png</url>
	<title><![CDATA[CoinJournal: Latest Bitcoin, Ethereum & Crypto News]]></title>
	<link>https://coinjournal.net/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin supply in loss at 68% after BTC price drop from $31k local top</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-supply-in-loss-at-68-after-btc-price-drop-from-31k-local-top/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 19:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-supply-in-loss-at-68-after-btc-price-drop-from-31k-local-top/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin supply in loss has risen to 68%, with 6.67 million BTC under water water at current spot price. Indeed, on-chain data shows 2.71 million BTC has fallen into loss as Bitcoin price dropped from the $31k local top. With sell-side risk ratio approaching its all-time lows, Glassnode analyst James Check says BTC could see [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-supply-in-loss-at-68-after-btc-price-drop-from-31k-local-top/">Bitcoin supply in loss at 68% after BTC price drop from $31k local top</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Bitcoin supply in loss has risen to 68%, with 6.67 million BTC under water water at current spot price.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Indeed, on-chain data shows 2.71 million BTC has fallen into loss as Bitcoin price dropped from the $31k local top.</li>
<li dir="ltr">With sell-side risk ratio approaching its all-time lows, Glassnode analyst James Check says BTC could see a big move to either side.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin&rsquo;s price</a> has dropped about 14.6% since rejecting at the local top of $30.9k, and the result has been a sharp rise in the total amount of supply in loss.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The leading cryptocurrency&rsquo;s current spot price is around $26.4k, after the week was spent in a tight range below the key resistance level of $27.6k. Although Bitcoin retested levels above $28k multiple times this month, the drawdown below $27k has bulls staring at a potential dip to support at $25k or lower.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But even as this outlook materializes, about 2.71 million BTC has drifted underwater. The BTC supply in loss, according to data <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1662113823547879425" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">shared</a> by on-chain analytics platform Glassnode, is equivalent to about 14% of the benchmark crypto&rsquo;s circulating supply.</p>
<p>&ldquo;<em>This raises the total supply in loss across the aforementioned period from 3.96M to 6.67M BTC, a 68.4% increase</em>,&rdquo; Glassnode noted.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">$45k or $20k? Analysts weigh in on BTC price movement</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Earlier this week, Glassnode lead analyst James Check said Bitcoin could see a &ldquo;big move&rdquo; in coming weeks amid seller exhaustion. Pointing to on-chain-data, Check <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-on-chain-metric-suggests-big-move-is-incoming-expert-says/">explained</a>:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>Bitcoin Sell-side Risk ratio is approaching all-time lows. This indicates that investors are reluctant to spend coins which are in profit, or loss within the current price range. This usually occurs when sellers are exhausted on both sides, suggesting big moves are coming</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">On Wednesday, JPMorgan lead strategist Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou said Bitcoin could rise 25% in the next 12 months. In a note to clients, Panigirtzoglou highlighted the price of gold rallying to a new multi-year high above $2k as the potential lead for BTC to hit $45k.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the analyst, Bitcoin and gold have often traded in sync. Bitcoin&rsquo;s upcoming halving will also play a role in ticking up prices of the digital asset. Recently, analysts at Standard Chartered predicted a 70% gain for BTC price, outlining the $100k as a target.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/bitcoin-supply-in-loss-at-68-after-btc-price-drop-from-31k-local-top/">Bitcoin supply in loss at 68% after BTC price drop from $31k local top</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Neighbor Alice and ELLE: a Groundbreaking Collaboration for an Unprecedented Web3 Gaming Experience</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/my-neighbor-alice-and-elle-a-groundbreaking-collaboration-for-an-unprecedented-web3-gaming-experience/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/my-neighbor-alice-and-elle-a-groundbreaking-collaboration-for-an-unprecedented-web3-gaming-experience/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>STOCKHOLM-&#8211; MAY 25, 2023&#160;&#8211; In a landmark partnership, My Neighbor Alice (MNA)&#160;has teamed up with the iconic brand ELLE to create a unique and immersive gaming experience that showcases the best of both worlds. This collaboration is set to demonstrate MNA&#8217;s ability to integrate brands successfully into its gaming universe in preparation for more partnerships [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/my-neighbor-alice-and-elle-a-groundbreaking-collaboration-for-an-unprecedented-web3-gaming-experience/">My Neighbor Alice and ELLE: a Groundbreaking Collaboration for an Unprecedented Web3 Gaming Experience</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr"><strong>STOCKHOLM-&ndash; MAY 25, 2023&nbsp;</strong>&ndash; In a landmark partnership, <a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>My Neighbor Alice (MNA)&nbsp;</u></a>has teamed up with the iconic brand <a href="https://elleboutique.com/france/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>ELLE</u></a> to create a unique and immersive gaming experience that showcases the best of both worlds. This collaboration is set to demonstrate MNA&rsquo;s ability to integrate brands successfully into its gaming universe in preparation for more partnerships in the future.</p>
<p dir="ltr">This collaboration aims to merge the distinct brand values of My Neighbor Alice and ELLE, providing players with a high-quality experience that seamlessly combines fashion, lifestyle, and gaming. ELLE will be incorporated into the game as a neighbor, with plots in each active region: Rusty Pikes and Tourney Wolds in Medieval Plains, Pioneer Point, Shaded Headland, and Gloomy Gulch in Nature&rsquo;s Rest. Players will find each ELLE plot conveniently located near the Town Hub of their respective region.</p>
<p>To encourage player engagement, quests have been designed to allow gamers to acquire exclusive ELLE-branded items customized with an Alice twist. These quests will be integrated into the existing game quest system, accessible to players at the ELLE Caf&eacute;, a unique building placed within the ELLE plot.</p>
<p>Adding to the excitement, this partnership will introduce two limited ELLE Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) collections: the Mots d&rsquo;Amour and the Wonder Collection, inspired by the real-life collections. The former will be available for purchase in the OpenSea marketplace, while the latter can only be obtained by crafting in the game. These items will be rewarded in NFTs, making them valuable to any player&rsquo;s in-game inventory. The collaboration will result in three distinct collections: Rare, Epic, and Legendary.</p>
<p>The Rare Collection consists of 23 unique clothing items. The Epic Collection is a limited edition, featuring only 4 unique clothing items and The Legendary Collection is the most exclusive, featuring full-suit NFTs.</p>
<p>In addition to the NFTs included in the boxes, buyers can receive free exclusive NFTs through the airdrop system. If you want to learn more about this sale, we tell you all about it <a href="https://myneighboralice.medium.com/my-neighbor-alice-elle-nft-sale-on-opensea-binance-discover-more-about-the-coming-drops-73a31f12320c" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>here</u></a>. Also, the collection will be available on <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/mots-d-amour-rare-ed/drop" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Opensea</u></a> or <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/nft/collection/MOTS-D'AMOUR-Rare-Ed.-712965386265505792?isBack=1?utm_source=nft-share&amp;utm_medium=share&amp;utm_campaign=MyNeighborAlice&amp;ref=40465521" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>Binance</u></a> if you want to check it out!</p>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/26/1685114853538-a61cbd5a-9a7f-4e25-8948-422ecc2ff4fd.jpg" style="width: 700px" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="700" height="345"></p>
<p>This pioneering collaboration between My Neighbor Alice and ELLE will create an unparalleled gaming experience for players as they navigate the beautifully crafted world of My Neighbor Alice and engage with the stylish offerings from ELLE.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Keep an eye out for the upcoming launch of this exceptional partnership that promises to revolutionize the way brands and games interact. If you&rsquo;re interested in learning more about the collaboration, check out the article on Elle&rsquo;s website here.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Discord: <a href="https://discord.gg/myneighboralice" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://discord.gg/myneighboralice</u></a>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/MyNeighborAlice" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://t.me/MyNeighborAlice</u></a>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Telegram Announcement: <a href="https://t.me/AliceAnnouncements" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://t.me/AliceAnnouncements</u></a>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/MyNeighborAlice" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://twitter.com/MyNeighborAlice</u></a>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/my-neighbor-alice/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"><u>https://www.linkedin.com/company/my-neighbor-alice/</u></a></p>
<p></p>
<h2 dir="ltr">About My Neighbor Alice</h2>
<p dir="ltr">My Neighbor Alice is a groundbreaking multiplayer builder game being built on Chromia&rsquo;s Blockchain that offers an engaging and accessible experience on a charming virtual island. Integrating Blockchain technology allows players to own and trade virtual assets (NFTs). The game&rsquo;s marketplace enables players to buy, sell, and trade these NFTs, creating a dynamic and player-driven virtual economy. Players can earn rewards, monetize their creations, and engage in community events, fostering a sense of ownership and collaboration. With different strategic partnerships, MNA underscores the project&rsquo;s dedication to promoting NFT ownership, encouraging a more engaging and interactive gaming community. My Neighbor Alice represents the future of gaming, combining virtual reality, blockchain, and decentralized finance to redefine how we interact with virtual worlds.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/my-neighbor-alice-and-elle-a-groundbreaking-collaboration-for-an-unprecedented-web3-gaming-experience/">My Neighbor Alice and ELLE: a Groundbreaking Collaboration for an Unprecedented Web3 Gaming Experience</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MCADE price prediction ahead of the Metacade Lite launch</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-price-prediction-ahead-of-the-metacade-lite-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-price-prediction-ahead-of-the-metacade-lite-launch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Metacade community is only counting days to the launch of the much anticipated Metacade Lite. MCADE price has started responding to the hype on the upcoming Metacade Lite launch. At press time, MCADE was trading at $0.02229, up 5.44% in the last 24 hours. Metacade is gearing up for releasing its Metacade Lite version [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-price-prediction-ahead-of-the-metacade-lite-launch/">MCADE price prediction ahead of the Metacade Lite launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="decimal_type">
<li>The Metacade community is only counting days to the launch of the much anticipated Metacade Lite.</li>
<li>MCADE price has started responding to the hype on the upcoming Metacade Lite launch.</li>
<li>At press time, MCADE was trading at $0.02229, up 5.44% in the last 24 hours.</li>
</ul>
<p>Metacade is gearing up for releasing its Metacade Lite version to the public soon, details of which can be confirmed in the recent <a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/1tz16w_Hqro?feature=share">AMA held on 24 May 2023</a>.</p>
<p>As the CEO of Metacade embarks on AMAs to explain the current status of the project, it is important to point out that the project hit all the milestones set in its roadmap for Q1, 2023. The team is currently working to hit the targets set for this quarter including the launch of the Create2Earn platform that will allow users to sample the game-changing gaming experience that comes with Metacade&rsquo;s unique approach to play-to-earn (P2E).</p>
<h2>What is Metacade and what does it offer?</h2>
<p><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=coinjournal&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=price_prediction">Metacade </a>is a blockchain gaming platform that aims to become the largest Web3 gaming arcade.</p>
<p>At its core, Metacade aims to offer gamers, investors, and developers access to a decentralized gaming hub, complete with the biggest collection of different play-to-earn (P2E) arcade games. It also plans to allow the integration of multiple earning mechanisms for ecosystem players.</p>
<p>The platform also has a utility ERC-20 token, the MCADE token, which is used to pay rewards in the ecosystem and help platform users access services and opportunities including staking and DeFi. In the future according to the project&rsquo;s roadmap, MCADE holders will also play a pivotal role in running the project by getting voting rights on governance proposals.</p>
<h2>For how long will MCADE maintain the current bullish trend?</h2>
<p>The crypto markets are expected to enter a new bullish cycle after a gruelling bear market, it is possible that MCADE could lead the charge within the GameFi and Web3 ecosystem. Seemingly, the crypto market has been on a short bearish pullback after what was a very splendid market recovery for the year that saw the likes of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/what-is-bitcoin/">Bitcoin&nbsp;</a>and <a href="https://coinjournal.net/ethereum/what-is-ethereum/">Ethereum&nbsp;</a>recover 70% and 55% respectively.</p>
<p>The recent developments including the recent <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/axs-price-soars-as-axie-infinity-game-launches-on-the-app-store/">Axie Infinity&rsquo;s debut on the Apple App Store</a>, and the reaffirmation by the Japan-based gaming giant Square Enix that it is committed to blockchain and Web3 gaming could help spark new GameFi demand and adoption.</p>
<p>In addition to the developments within the GameFi space, the MCADE token is also likely to benefit from the Metagrants programme that incentivises developers to increase the creation and deployment of games on the platform. However, MCADE&rsquo;s future is also dependent on the easing of the macro headwinds including inflation to help the crypto market grow.</p>
<p>Jamie Douglas of Bloomberg Intelligence recently said that <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">Bitcoin price</a> could shoot to $18,000 if only 1% of the global bond market value moved to Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Taking all these into consideration including the upcoming Metacade Lite launch that is likely to spur increased interest in Metacade and its native token, the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/metacade/">MCADE price</a> is projected to sustain the current Bull Run and possibly hit $0.045 by the end of the month.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/mcade-price-prediction-ahead-of-the-metacade-lite-launch/">MCADE price prediction ahead of the Metacade Lite launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GamStop &#038; Crypto: fostering responsible gambling for a sustainable ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/gamstop-crypto-fostering-responsible-gambling-for-a-sustainable-ecosystem/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Thuo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Policy and Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/gamstop-crypto-fostering-responsible-gambling-for-a-sustainable-ecosystem/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>GamStop was created in the United Kingdom to help gamblers get free help when they need it. A lot of gamblers gambling at casino sites not on GamStop in the UK are using crypto. Besides GamStop, there are other responsible gambling tools like GamBan and BetBlocker. Crypto gambling is slowly immerging as a new trend. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamstop-crypto-fostering-responsible-gambling-for-a-sustainable-ecosystem/">GamStop &amp; Crypto: fostering responsible gambling for a sustainable ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>GamStop was created in the United Kingdom to help gamblers get free help when they need it.</li>
<li>A lot of gamblers gambling at casino sites not on GamStop in the UK are using crypto.</li>
<li>Besides GamStop, there are other responsible gambling tools like GamBan and BetBlocker.</li>
</ul>
<p>Crypto gambling is slowly immerging as a new trend. Almost 420 million people in the world use cryptocurrency and many of them love to gamble, meaning many of them would prefer crypto gambling.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, crypto gamblers need to play responsibly. Tools like GamStop can help the <a href="https://coinjournal.net/casinos/">crypto casino</a> ecosystem and make it sustainable.</p>
<h2>GamStop &ndash; popular responsible gambling tool</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/26/1685109294879-4f5e5531-81af-41c7-a327-4d2f684c49af.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="343"></p>
<p>There are dozens of responsible gambling tools and their number is growing. One of these tools, GamStop, has become a choice for many crypto gamblers. But what is it?</p>
<p>For starters, GamStop is not GameStop. These are two completely different platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p>GamStop was created in the United Kingdom to help gamblers get a free type of help when they need it. People create accounts on GamStop to ensure they only gamble on UKGC-licensed casinos and betting sites. It ensures they cannot play on unlicensed casinos and sites and the ban can last as long as you want it to last up to 5 years after which you can remove the ban or prolong it once again and again.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The main benefits are a bit obvious. Gamblers can enjoy safer gambling, period. They can use a free tool to get professional help whenever they need it. Players can also get additional help if their condition is a bit more demanding. All of these things make the gambling ecosystem possible and stable!</p>
<p>There is one issue though. Players can bypass GamStop! It is possible to play at non-GamStop casinos, which are sites that are not controlled by UK or UKGC.</p>
<h2>Correlation between crypto gambling and casinos not on GamStop</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/26/1685109491283-9fb1fc6e-fbd0-4302-9fd1-2f02d03c2c95.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="344"></p>
<p>A lot of gamblers gambling at <a href="https://www.nongamstopbets.com/casinos-not-on-gamstop/">casino sites not on GamStop</a> in the UK have <a href="https://coinjournal.net/cryptocurrencies/invest/">invested in crypto</a>. They will continue to use it and they adore this idea. See, these people don&rsquo;t like the limitations UKGC has set. They want and need freedom while playing. Non-GamStop casinos offer just that.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Using crypto means players can get even bigger bonuses, stay anonymous, and do so much more that are not a thing at UKGC sites.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are some issues we must mention. For instance, these casinos are not heavily regulated like UKGC sites which means that some of them can be problematic. Sites of this kind also don&rsquo;t invest in security as massive UK casinos do.&nbsp;</p>
<p>All of this suggests one simple thing. Responsible gambling tools are even more important at non-GamStop casinos. We can say that they are essential and something you should use in 100% of cases. These tools can keep you safe when nothing else will work.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Other responsible gambling tools in addition to GamStop</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/26/1685109741540-0cf7d444-80eb-4f53-a480-bb4aec63e928.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="615" height="343"></p>
<p>Today when more and more people try to <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-65610851">equate cryptocurrencies with gambling</a>, it is important to show that there are already available tools that can cover all the requests. If you think that GamStop is the only tool of this kind, you are wrong.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a matter of fact, users have a lot of additional options they can use at any given moment. All of these methods, options or apps if you like have one thing they are designed to do. They can be used alongside GamStop and help a player completely. What this means is that GamStop will cover UKGC sites and another tool will cover all the rest. This combo can make gambling online extremely safe and secure. Anyway, let&rsquo;s see the most common options you can use.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>GamBan</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>GamBan comes in the form of an app. You can get it on computers and smartphones if you like. The app is not free. But you will get a 7-day free trial you can use to check out the app and see how it works.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The idea is simple. Once installed, the app will block access to gambling and betting websites. You are done. Additionally, <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamban-blocks-crypto-platforms-will-gamstop-take-actions/">GamStop started blocking crypto platforms</a> and it constantly expands its database. There is no way you can remove the app and continue playing and this makes GamStop so effective.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>BetBlocker</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Betblocker is one of the free apps (for this purpose of course) that is rare today. You can install it right now and set it all up in 2 minutes. Then you will see that over 85.000 gambling sites are not available any longer. Once the time frame you have selected expires, you can remove the app and play again.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>NetNanny</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>This is probably the oldest app of this kind. It was developed in the 90s. Then, it was developed for parental controls which some people used. In the 2000s it added functionality to block gambling and betting sites.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Netnanny works on all operating systems and it is very effective. Try it and you will see why some people have been using it for years.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Empowering crypto users and ensuring a sustainable gambling ecosystem</h2>
<p>Using GamStop or some other tools we have listed here is needed, especially if you like playing at crypto casinos. These are all tools that can help you when you need help the most. At the same time, these can help you control your gambling desires more so you can play in a clever way.</p>
<p>When using these tools and when you invest some time into learning all about responsible gambling, you can make this form of fun special. You can play and don&rsquo;t have to worry about gambling addiction or anything similar.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another benefit of all this is that the gambling ecosystem will become sustainable. There won&rsquo;t be a lot of people who have issues while playing, meaning that the whole ecosystem will flourish. Without these tools and responsible gambling, all of this will be much harder and maybe even impossible.&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Responsible gambling tools are one thing we all need. These can make any form of gambling better and safer. therefore, it is important to <a href="https://www.irishcentral.com/gamstop-role-promoting-responsible-gambling-ireland">promote them properly</a> around the world and adopt the available tools with different topics.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Although all players may want to consider these at some point, crypto gamblers simply must. They are in an ecosystem that is still relatively new, so using all the help they can is important.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/gamstop-crypto-fostering-responsible-gambling-for-a-sustainable-ecosystem/">GamStop &amp; Crypto: fostering responsible gambling for a sustainable ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire &#160;]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Labuan, Malaysia, May 26th, 2023, Chainwire Cerus Markets is thrilled to announce an exciting update to its leverage options for non-crypto instruments. Effective immediately, Cerus Markets clients can enjoy leverage of up to 400:1 for Forex, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks trading. This increase in leverage options allows traders to make the most of their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/">Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Labuan, Malaysia, May 26th, 2023, Chainwire</strong></p>
<p>Cerus Markets is thrilled to announce an exciting update to its leverage options for non-crypto instruments. Effective immediately, Cerus Markets clients can enjoy <strong>leverage of up to 400:1</strong> for Forex, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks trading.</p>
<p>This increase in leverage options allows traders to make the most of their investments, providing greater market exposure and the potential for higher returns. By offering increased leverage options for non-crypto instruments, Cerus Markets aims to provide clients with even more opportunities to capitalize on market movements.</p>
<p>At Cerus Markets, the company prides itself on its commitment to providing clients with the best possible trading experience. This update is just one example of the company&rsquo;s dedication to ensuring that clients have access to the best tools and trading conditions.</p>
<p><strong>About Cerus Markets</strong></p>
<p>Established in 2022, Cerus Markets Limited is a multi-asset broker authorized and regulated by the Labuan Financial Service Authority, Malaysia. With a focus on innovation, Cerus offers unique crypto derivative products that allow clients to trade over 200 instruments paired with cryptocurrencies. Alongside crypto derivatives, Cerus provides trading opportunities in FX, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks.</p>
<p>Cerus Markets believes in empowering traders of all levels with easy and affordable access to the market. The trading platform stands out from traditional brokers by not charging entry fees and allowing trading of a wide range of digital assets starting from just $50, with leverage up to 400:1.</p>
<p>Moreover, traders can benefit from a <strong>100% deposit matching bonus</strong>, doubling the amount of their first deposit and further enhancing their trading experience.</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://cerusmarkets.com/?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">cerusmarkets.com</a> to learn more about Cerus Markets and its offerings.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/cerusmarkets/?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Instagram</a> l <a href="https://twitter.com/CerusMarkets?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Twitter</a> l <a href="https://t.me/cerusmarkets_official?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Telegram</a></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><strong>Marketing Director at Cerus Markets</strong><br>
<strong>Veronica Imasheva</strong><br>
<strong>marketing@cerusmarkets.com</strong></p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/">Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metacade price and the debt ceiling impasse opportunity</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crispus Nyaga]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Credit rating agencies are watching the ongoing debt ceiling debate in Washington. Fitch placed the US into a rating watch negative area. The debt ceiling crisis is creating a good buying opportunity. Metacade (MCADE), like other cryptocurrencies and stocks, has come under intense pressure as the debt ceiling crisis has escalated. The token was trading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/">Metacade price and the debt ceiling impasse opportunity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Credit rating agencies are watching the ongoing debt ceiling debate in Washington.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">Fitch placed the US into a rating watch negative area.</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr">The debt ceiling crisis is creating a good buying opportunity.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://metacade.co/en?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=invezz&amp;utm_term=internal&amp;utm_content=current_news"><u>Metacade</u></a> (MCADE), like other cryptocurrencies and stocks, has come under intense pressure as the debt ceiling crisis has escalated. The token was trading at $0.022, which was much lower than its all-time high of $0.046. Other cryptocurrencies have also been in the red. Bitcoin has retreated from the year-to-date high of $31,000 to below $27,000.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Debt ceiling crisis opportunity</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade price has not retreated because of its bad fundamentals. Instead, it has dropped because of the ongoing risk-off sentiment among market participants. This is evidenced by the fact that the US dollar index has surged to the highest level in more than a month. The closely watched VIX index has also jumped by double-digits.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The main concern is that the American government will default on its debt obligations in June if Democrats and Republicans fail to reach an agreement. Recent reports show that talks between the two negotiators have hit a wall. As a result, Fitch, a major rating agency announced that it was placing the US in a rating watch negative area. The report said:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;The brinkmanship over the debt ceiling, failure of the U.S. authorities to meaningfully tackle medium-term fiscal challenges that will lead to rising budget deficits and a growing debt burden signal downside risks to U.S. creditworthiness.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">I believe that the debt ceiling issue is creating a good opportunity for investors to buy the dip in key financial assets like Metacade and stocks. For one, odds are that the US will not default since the two sides will reach an agreement.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Janet Yellen, the head of the Treasury, has said that the US will run out of money on June 1. This means that there are still six weeks to reach an agreement. Historically, including in 2011, these deals are reached in the last day.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">A common saying in the market recommends buying when other people are fearful. This is a strategy that has worked well in the past crises. For example, it worked well when the Covid-19 pandemic was starting. Also, investors who bought the dip during the Global Financial Crisis made strong profits over the years.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade fundamentals are strong</h2>
<p dir="ltr">For starters, Metacade is a new blockchain project that raised over $16 million in a token sale. The developers are building a gaming product that is expected to be much better than existing products like Axie Infinity and Decentraland.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Metacade&rsquo;s&nbsp;<a href="https://metacade.co/whitepaper.pdf"><u>white paper</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>the developers are now working on the game, which will be launched in the next few months. At the same time, they are working to have the token listed by leading exchanges. As we wrote&nbsp;<a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-prediction-one-day-to-mexc-global-listing/"><u>here</u></a><strong>,&nbsp;</strong>it has already been listed by MEXC and BitMart.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Metacade has strong fundamentals since it is in an industry that is expected to grow in the next few years. A reccnt&nbsp;<a href="https://www.marketsandmarkets.com/Market-Reports/blockchain-gaming-market-167926225.html"><u>study</u></a> estimates that blockchain games made over $4.6 billion in 2022 and that the volume will jump to over $65 billion by 2027. I believe that Metacade will have a market share in this industry.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Metacade price prediction</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://media.igms.io/2023/04/25/1684994533941-e94bc508-631b-448f-babd-4b946a2c83cd.png" class="fr-fic fr-dib" width="528" height="318"></p>
<p dir="ltr">On the hourly chart, we see that Metacade price has moved sideways in the past few days. This price action is the same as that of other cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://coinjournal.net/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a>, ethereum, and solana. The coin has moved slightly above the ascending trendline that is shown in black. It has also jumped above the 25-day moving average while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has moved above the neutral point.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Therefore, I suspect that MCADE price will continue consolidating and then make a bullish breakout later this month. If this happens, the next level to watch will be at $0.024. A move above that level will bring the resistance at $0.30 into view.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/metacade-price-and-the-debt-ceiling-impasse-opportunity/">Metacade price and the debt ceiling impasse opportunity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain.com CEO explains what a U.S. default could mean for cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-com-ceo-us-default-cryptocurrencies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wajeeh Khan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/?p=140690</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain.com CEO says debt default will initially hit crypto. Peter Smith expects 2024 to be a strong year for cryptocurrencies. He made the comments today at the 2023 Qatar Economic Forum. In the short-term, cryptocurrencies will likely take a hit if the United States indeed ends up in its first-ever debt default, says Peter Smith [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-com-ceo-us-default-cryptocurrencies/">Blockchain.com CEO explains what a U.S. default could mean for cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Blockchain.com CEO says debt default will initially hit crypto.</li>
<li>Peter Smith expects 2024 to be a strong year for cryptocurrencies.</li>
<li>He made the comments today at the 2023 Qatar Economic Forum.</li>
</ul>
<p>In the short-term, cryptocurrencies will likely take a hit if the United States indeed ends up in its first-ever debt default, says Peter Smith &ndash; the Chief Executive of Blockchain.com.</p>
<h2>Smith expects a quick recovery though</h2>
<p>Interestingly, though, he does not expect that weakness to last for long. Smith&rsquo;s medium to long-term outlook on the market remains positive as ever.</p>
<blockquote><p>On a long horizon, these are probably good for crypto &hellip; if the U.S. government defaults, we&rsquo;ll see a quick pullback and then a very strong push upward in the crypto market.</p></blockquote>
<p>He also confirmed today that the crypto exchange was considering expanding its small Middle Eastern Office in the United Arab Emirates.</p>
<p>It is also noteworthy that House Speaker Kevin McCarthy <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/white-house-republicans-seek-close-us-debt-ceiling-deal-deadline-nears-2023-05-25/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">expressed confidence</a> this morning that Republicans will reach a deal with the White House on debt ceiling in time.</p>
<h2>2024 could be a high year for crypto</h2>
<p>Also on Thursday, CEO Peter Smith forecast 2024 to be a very strong year for the crypto space.</p>
<p>His view is based on a pattern that this market seems to follow &ndash; 2021 was a high year, 2022 was a major correction, 2023 is recovery, and the next year will be of exponential growth again. Speaking at the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-05-25/blockchain-com-ceo-on-cryptocurrency-moves" target="_blank" rel="noopener">2023 Qatar Economic Forum</a>, he added:</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the crypto market is going to be much bigger in the future than it is today. I expect the market to be positive for the next twelve to eighteen months.</p></blockquote>
<p>Remember that the total supply of <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/bitcoin/">bitcoin</a> is scheduled to <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/bitcoin-halving-4843769" target="_blank" rel="noopener">halve</a> in April of 2024 &ndash; an event known to benefit the crypto market at large.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/blockchain-com-ceo-us-default-cryptocurrencies/">Blockchain.com CEO explains what a U.S. default could mean for cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto casinos: revolutionizing payouts, privacy and fairness</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency has transformed the casino withdrawal process. Crypto casinos are leveraging the power of blockchain tecchnology and cryptocurrencies to prioritize user privacy.&#160; Cryptographic algorithms and smart contracts are helping ensure provably fair gaming. In recent years, the world of online gambling has undergone a profound transformation with the advent of crypto casinos. These innovative platforms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/">Crypto casinos: revolutionizing payouts, privacy and fairness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Cryptocurrency has transformed the casino withdrawal process.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto casinos are leveraging the power of blockchain tecchnology and cryptocurrencies to prioritize user privacy.&nbsp;</li>
<li dir="ltr">Cryptographic algorithms and smart contracts are helping ensure provably fair gaming.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">In recent years, the world of online gambling has undergone a profound transformation with the advent of crypto casinos. These innovative platforms have brought about a wave of change, revolutionizing the way payouts are processed, privacy is upheld and fairness is ensured in the realm of online gaming.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">How cryptocurrency transforms the casino withdrawal process</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Traditional online casinos often present challenges when it comes to the speed and security of withdrawals, leaving players frustrated with lengthy processing times and potential vulnerabilities. However, with the rise of crypto casinos, players can now experience a seamless and efficient withdrawal process. <a href="https://zamsino.com/crypto/casinos/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Zamsino&rsquo;s research</a> on crypto technology in online casinos has shed light on the transformative potential of crypto technology, highlighting its ability to revolutionize payments.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">By leveraging blockchain technology, transactions are conducted directly between the player and the casino, eliminating the need for intermediaries and reducing the processing time significantly. The decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies ensures that funds are securely transferred, providing players with peace of mind and prompt access to their winnings.&nbsp;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The anonymity features of crypto casinos</h2>
<p dir="ltr">At the core of crypto casinos lies a paramount focus on privacy, offering players an unprecedented level of anonymity in their gambling activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Unlike traditional online casinos that often require personal information for registration and transactions, crypto casinos leverage the power of cryptocurrencies to prioritize user privacy. By using pseudonymous transactions through blockchain technology, players can enjoy a heightened sense of confidentiality. Personal details are not linked to the transactions, shielding players from potential privacy breaches and identity theft.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The anonymity <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/blockchain/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">features of crypto</a> casinos empower individuals to gamble without the fear of their personal information being compromised, providing a safe and discreet environment for online gaming.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">The role of blockchain technology in ensuring provably fair gaming</h2>
<p dir="ltr">With the emergence of blockchain technology, the concept of fairness in online gaming has been redefined, leading to the advent of provably fair gaming in crypto casinos. Traditional online casinos have often faced skepticism regarding the fairness of their games, leaving players uncertain about the integrity of their outcomes. However, blockchain technology has introduced a groundbreaking solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Through cryptographic algorithms and smart contracts, players can independently verify the randomness and fairness of each game&rsquo;s outcome.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Transparent and immutable records stored on the blockchain provide an auditable trail, ensuring that the casino cannot manipulate the results. This innovative approach has instilled a new level of trust among players, allowing them to engage in online gambling with confidence.</p>
<p dir="ltr">By leveraging the power of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, crypto casinos have emerged as a secure, transparent and decentralized alternative to traditional online casinos</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/crypto-casinos-revolutionizing-payouts-privacy-and-fairness/">Crypto casinos: revolutionizing payouts, privacy and fairness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle launches its euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche</title>
		<link>https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/</link>
					<comments>https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Benson Toti]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The euro-backed stablecoin will bring more liquidity to the Avalanche network, Circle said in a press release. Developers using USDC can now easily integrate Euro Coin. Wallets that support Euro Coin on Avalanche include Coinbase Wallet and MetaMask. Circle, the issuer of the USDC, has launched its other fiat-backed stablecoin Euro Coin on Avalanche, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/">Circle launches its euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li dir="ltr">The euro-backed stablecoin will bring more liquidity to the Avalanche network, Circle said in a press release.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Developers using USDC can now easily integrate Euro Coin.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Wallets that support Euro Coin on Avalanche include Coinbase Wallet and MetaMask.</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Circle, the issuer of the USDC, has launched its other fiat-backed <a href="https://coinjournal.net/learn/what-are-stablecoins/">stablecoin</a> Euro Coin on <a href="https://coinjournal.net/news/tag/avalanche/">Avalanche</a>, a smart contracts enabled layer-1 blockchain.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Avalanche&rsquo;s AVAX, currently trading at around $14.05, is the 17th largest cryptocurrency with a market cap of $4.7 billion.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Euro liquidity comes to Avalanche</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Circle says it expects Euro Coin&rsquo;s launch on Avalanche will be the first in a series that&rsquo;s set to see the euro-backed stablecoin bring multi-chain euro liquidity to developers and ecosystem users around the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Deployment on Avalanche also means apps that support USDC will easily integrate Euro Coin, the digital technology firm said in a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/circle-takes-euro-coin-multi-chain-with-launch-on-avalanche-301834001.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">press release</a>.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>When we first introduced Euro Coin on Ethereum last year, we wanted anyone with an internet connection to have access to the euro across borders and time zones</em>,&rdquo; said Joao Reginatto, VP of Product at Circle. He added:</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>By launching Euro Coin on Avalanche&rsquo;s fast and efficient platform, we can help developers and their users experience near-instant, more cost effective financial transactions and unlock new possibilities for payments, remittances and 24/7 FX</em>.&rdquo;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Ava Labs VP of Business Development John Nahas said having the euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche opens up the blockchain network to new possibilities for developers and other users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">&ldquo;<em>We continue to see great adoption and volume behind Circle&rsquo;s USDC, and expect great feedback and usage of Euro Coin on Avalanche. DeFi continues to expand into a multi-currency, cross-border environment &ndash; delivering a trusted and fully reserved euro stablecoin like Euro Coin will greatly accelerate the adoption of instant payments and remittances to a much larger swath of the world</em>,&rdquo; Nahas noted.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Circle, apps and wallets that support the stablecoin on Avalanche include Coinbase Wallet, MetaMask, BENQI, Cables, Core, and Curve.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Circle Account holders access to Euro Coin liquidity on the Avalanche platform, with support for trading or lending in crypto capital markets available. Euro Coin can also be held in custody, or used for payments.</p>

<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/">Circle launches its euro-backed stablecoin on Avalanche</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://coinjournal.net">CoinJournal</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://coinjournal.net/news/circle-launches-its-euro-backed-stablecoin-on-avalanche/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
