<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Blockchain.com Obtains Regulatory Approval in Singapore</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-com-obtains-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264962</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The new license enables Blockchain.com to provide digital token payment services to institutional and accredited investors.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading cryptocurrency exchange Blockchain.com received a payment institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This marks the company&#8217;s second license in the city-state after the in-principle approval secured in September 2022.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265097" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg" alt="blockchain_com_singapore_license" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Blockchain.com </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/blockchaincom-receives-major-payment-institution-license-from-monetary-authority-of-singapore-301895088.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that its recently-obtained authorization in Singapore follows the entity&#8217;s strategy to comply with regulators in every region where it conducts business.</span></li>
<li>The team behind the exchange said the Asian city-state has emerged as a &#8220;profitable trading hub&#8221; focused on global institutional and accredited investor clients.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Over 90 percent of the group&#8217;s institutional and accredited investors business is in Singapore,&#8221; Rakesh Madamanchi &#8211; Blockchain.com&#8217;s head of institutional compliance and Singapore operations revealed. </span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another reason why the marketplace views Singapore as a key area is because it serves as its Southeast Asia headquarters. Commenting on the regulatory approval was also CEO Peter Smith:</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are thrilled to receive this license that will allow Blockchain.com to bring our industry-leading products and services to Singapore, we commend the Monetary Authority of Singapore on its transparent regulatory process that prioritizes crypto industry oversight while allowing innovation to thrive.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Multiple cryptocurrency exchanges and firms have recently focused on Singapore due to the city-state&#8217;s comprehensive regulations. </span></li>
<li><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-eyes-uae-expansion-amid-us-uncertainty-crypto-com-gets-mpi-license-in-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto.com</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Circle, Paxos, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-receives-in-principle-singapore-payments-license-us-crypto-exodus-continues/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ripple</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> are some organizations that have secured authorization there over the past several months. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-com-obtains-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/" rel="nofollow">Blockchain.com Obtains Regulatory Approval in Singapore</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody&#8217;s Mulls Downgrades For Top U.S. Banks Citing Funding Risks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/moodys-mulls-downgrades-for-top-u-s-banks-citing-funding-risks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265195</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The agency says top banks are facing weaker profits and reduced availability of CRE credit.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Big Three credit rating agency Moody’s has downgraded numerous regional banks in the United States due to weak earnings last quarter and sizable unrealized losses, according to the firm’s Monday note.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, banking giants including Bank of New York Mellon (BK.N), US Bancorp (USB.N), State Street (STT.N) and Truist Financial (TFC.N) have been placed on review for potential downgrades.</p>
<h2>Stress in the Banking Sector</h2>
<p>As reported by <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/moodys-downgrades-10-us-banks-warns-possible-cuts-others-2023-08-08/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Reuters</a></em> on Tuesday, Moody’s note highlighted “profitability pressures” at many banks that are expected to hinder their ability to generate further capital. Banks downgraded by the firm include M&amp;T Bank (MTB.N), Pinnacle Financial Partners (PNFP.O), Prosperity Bank, and BOK Financial Corp (BOKF.O).</p>
<p>Meanwhile, high exposure to commercial real estate (CRE) poses a significant risk due to the nation’s high-interest rate environment. Last month, the Federal Reserve <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-loses-30k-as-us-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-another-25bps-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">rose</a> its benchmark rate to between 5.25% and 5.5% – its highest level since January 2001.</p>
<p>&#8220;This comes as a mild U.S. recession is on the horizon for early 2024 and asset quality looks set to decline, with particular risks in some banks’ commercial real estate portfolios,” the note added.</p>
<p>According to Federal Reserve survey data from last week, U.S. banks reported both weaker loan demand and tighter credit standards in Q2.</p>
<p>The U.S. banking sector has already been plagued by a crisis of confidence this year, with Silvergate Bank, Signature Bank, and Silicon Valley Bank collectively collapsing in March. The latter fell as customers rushed for the exits when the bank reported that it had realized a $1.8 billion loss on its long-term bond portfolio.</p>
<p>Indeed, Moody’s warned that U.S. banks sitting on high unrealized losses face similar risks related to a crisis of confidence, especially given today’s high-interest rate environment.</p>
<h2>Government Gets Downgraded</h2>
<p>High rates are part of what has prompted Fitch Ratings – another top-rated agency – to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fitch-us-ratings-downgrade-is-fine-for-bitcoin-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">downgrade</a> the U.S. government&#8217;s credit to AA+ as of last month, away from the upper echelon shared with international competitors.</p>
<p>Given the country’s high debt-to-GDP ratio, the agency noted that the country would start struggling to manage growing interest payments as it rolled over existing debt at a higher borrowing rate.</p>
<p>The government’s annual interest payments have skyrocketed since last year and now approach $1 trillion. Mike Novogratz, CEO of Galaxy Digital, has told followers to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/novogratz-advises-investors-to-buy-bitcoin-as-federal-interest-payments-skyrocket/" data-wpel-link="internal">buy Bitcoin</a> in response.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/moodys-mulls-downgrades-for-top-u-s-banks-citing-funding-risks/" rel="nofollow">Moody&#8217;s Mulls Downgrades For Top U.S. Banks Citing Funding Risks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle&#8217;s Jeremy Allaire Estimates Majority of USDC Adoption Originates Beyond US Borders</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circles-jeremy-allaire-estimates-majority-of-usdc-adoption-originates-beyond-us-borders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264980</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Circle_Banks.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Circle_Banks.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Circle is directing its attention to international markets where there is a rising trend in adoption.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stablecoin issuer Circle is a US-based company, and 70% of its USDC adoption originates from non-US regions.</p>
<p>According to the estimations of Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire, some of the fastest growing areas are emerging and developing markets, which are not in the country that has been facing severe regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<h2>Not Fixated on US</h2>
<p>Allaire took to X (formerly Twitter) to <a href="https://twitter.com/jerallaire/status/1688672056898928640" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reveal</a> observing &#8220;strong progress&#8221; across Asia, LATAM, and Africa, highlighting the demand for &#8220;safe, transparent digital dollars.&#8221;</p>
<p>Circle isn&#8217;t the only company that has demonstrated not being particularly fixated on the US ecosystem. In fact, Tether&#8217;s chief technology officer, Paolo Ardoino, also echoed a similar sentiment when he earlier revealed the stablecoin company&#8217;s aim to position USDT as &#8220;a safe tool for emerging markets and developing countries, a life-life for many communities that are suffering from a heavy devaluation of their national currencies.&#8221;</p>
<p>Allaire&#8217;s remarks coincide with a reduction in the supply of the USDC stablecoin since the start of 2023 as a result of diminishing demand and a rise in redemptions. With redemptions surpassing issuance, concerns over USDC&#8217;s liquidity surfaced again. The Circle CEO also <a href="https://twitter.com/jerallaire/status/1688667728737959937" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">addressed</a> the situation and confirmed issuing $5 billion worth of USDC and redeeming $6.6 billion worth of USDC.</p>
<p>Doubling down on Circle&#8217;s expansion, Allaire revealed that the stablecoin issuer company was actively collaborating with several reputable financial institutions across key global regions.</p>
<h2>Shift in Stablecoin Landscape</h2>
<p>USDC has had a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-usdc-outflows-surpassed-10b-since-svb-collapse-tether-dominance-rises/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">rocky start</a> shedding over 43% since the beginning of the year. The stablecoin, however, held up its market cap above $26 billion over the past few weeks following a brief slump below the level. This is despite Binance selling a significant chunk of the token, as recently revealed by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong.</p>
<p>The unexpected <a href="https://protos.com/brian-armstrong-revealed-binance-sold-all-its-usdc-in-coinbase-earnings-call/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">comment</a> by the exec came during Coinbase&#8217;s second-quarter earnings, during which he said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Binance actually moved some of their funds from USDC into another stablecoin. I think the data we have in the last six or seven weeks, I believe, that the USDC market cap is up net of that. And so that’s an important data point.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>A lookout for a different stablecoin follows the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-regulator-reportedly-stops-paxos-from-issuing-busd-but-is-it-just-fud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">order</a> to stop issuing the dollar-pegged BUSD stablecoin. Binance shifted its focus to TrueUSD (TUSD) as a solution for its stablecoin requirements. But TUSD lost its peg, and its issuance ceased by June 10th.</p>
<p>The rise of FDUSD, on the other hand, caught the attention of Tether&#8217;s Ardoino, who observed that USDT faced downward pressure, and its primary competitor, USDC, which is experienced significant redemptions instead of gaining from such a situation.</p>
<p>The change in the stablecoin landscape is further validated by this week&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of PYUSD by global payments giant PayPal.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-jeremy-allaire-estimates-majority-of-usdc-adoption-originates-beyond-us-borders/" rel="nofollow">Circle&#8217;s Jeremy Allaire Estimates Majority of USDC Adoption Originates Beyond US Borders</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lazarus Group Spent Six Months Trying to Penetrate CoinsPaid Systems for Weaknesses: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lazarus-group-spent-six-months-trying-to-penetrate-coinspaid-systems-for-weaknesses-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264729</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CoinsPaid said that blockchain scoring proved ineffective against money laundering of stolen funds. 
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Estonian crypto-payments service provider CoinsPaid found that the notorious hacking group Lazarus spent six months tracking and studying the platform before finally attacking on July 22nd.</p>
<p>ConsPaid collaborated with cybersecurity firm Match Systems to track the perpetrators&#8217; steps minute by minute, as well as identify what services and platforms were used to launder the funds. In a press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the platform said that Lazarus Group spent half a year trying to infiltrate the CoinsPaid systems and find vulnerabilities.</p>
<h2>Orchestrating $37.3M Theft</h2>
<p>Since March, CoinsPaid revealed having been hit by constant unsuccessful attacks of various kinds, ranging from social engineering to DDos and BruteForce. During the same period, key engineers of the company were approached by an entity purporting to be a Ukrainian crypto-processing startup presenting a set of technical infrastructure-related inquiries. This interaction was corroborated by three key developers within CoinsPaid.</p>
<p>In April and May, CoinsPaid encountered four significant assaults targeting its systems which sought unauthorized access to the accounts belonging to both the company&#8217;s employees as well as its clients. The spam and phishing activities against the team members were constant and highly aggressive, the press release stated.</p>
<p>The following month of June and July witnessed the orchestration of a malicious campaign that involved a combination of bribing and fictitious employment offers, all directed at crucial personnel within the company.</p>
<p>The attacker launched a meticulously planned and executed assault against the CoinsPaid infrastructure and applications on July 7th. The attack, which unfolded between 20:48 and 21:42, demonstrated an unprecedented surge in network activity, recording an engagement of over 150,000 distinct IP addresses.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265133" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover.jpg" alt="hacker_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hacker_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Tracing the Attack</h2>
<p>The primary objective of the culprits was to deceive a key staff member into installing software, enabling them to establish remote control over a computer by infiltrating and accessing CoinsPaid&#8217;s internal systems. Despite six months of unsuccessful attempts, the attackers eventually managed to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinspaid-suspects-north-koreas-lazarus-group-of-orchestrating-37-3m-theft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">breach</a> its infrastructure on July 22nd which resulted in the loss of $37.5 million.</p>
<p>The attackers used highly sophisticated and vigorous social engineering techniques to gain access to an employee&#8217;s computer. Recruiters from crypto companies reached out to CoinsPaid employees via LinkedIn and various Messengers, offering enticingly high salaries.</p>
<p>After one of its employees responded to a job offer posing to be Crypto.com, they received a test assignment that required the installation of an application with malicious code. Upon opening the test task, the employee&#8217;s profiles and keys were stolen from the computer to set up a connection with CoinsPaid&#8217;s infrastructure.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The access enabled the hackers to create authorized requests to withdraw funds from CoinsPaid hot wallets. But the perpetrators were not able to breach the hot wallets and acquire private keys to access funds directly. </span></p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Internal security measures triggered the alarm system and allowed us to swiftly stop the malicious activity and throw the hackers out of the company&#8217;s perimeter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>CoinsPaid further stated that despite crypto companies complying with the KYC measures and using blockchain risk scoring systems to detect suspicious activity, the perpetrators still managed to launder the stolen funds successfully.</p>
<p>The company pointed fingers at the Lazarus group since the hackers used similar tactics in the Atomic Wallet <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hacked-largest-victim-reportedly-lost-2-8m-usdt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">heist</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lazarus-group-spent-six-months-trying-to-penetrate-coinspaid-systems-for-weaknesses-report/" rel="nofollow">Lazarus Group Spent Six Months Trying to Penetrate CoinsPaid Systems for Weaknesses: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cypher Protocol Exploited, Will the Hacker Return the Funds? Details</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cypher-protocol-exploited-will-the-hacker-return-the-funds-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265135</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hacker_steal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hacker_steal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The team has paused operations until the million-dollar exploit can be patched.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cypher Protocol, a Solana-based futures DEX, has been forced to pause its smart contract in the wake of an exploit that resulted in a loss of more than $1 million.</p>
<h2>The Why</h2>
<p>Late last night, Cypher’s devs announced that they had suffered a “security incident”, resulting in the need to pause their smart contract until a post-mortem was carried out. An appeal to the hacker was also made, promising a discussion on the next steps should the bad actor care to reply.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Cypher has has experienced an exploit/security incident. The smart contract has been frozen.</p>
<p>The team is currently working with individuals and investigating</p>
<p>To the hacker: We are writing to see whether you would be open to speaking with us about any potential next steps.</p>
<p>— cypher ©&#xfe0f; (@cypher_protocol) <a href="https://twitter.com/cypher_protocol/status/1688641036476731393?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The exchange’s mission, which is proudly stated in Cypher Protocol’s Twitter bio, was also cause for mirth.</p>
<p>However, the irony doesn’t stop there. It turns out that the hack <a href="https://twitter.com/mtndao/status/1687917521247363072" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">occurred</a> during mtnDAO, a hackathon co-hosted by Cypher Protocol and Marginfi, another Solana-based project.</p>
<p>It appears we have a winner – although not by popular vote.</p>
<p>The exploit drained over 38k SOL tokens and more than 123k USDC, adding up to a total of $1,035,203 in ill-begotten gains.</p>
<p>In a rather perplexing move for the hacker, Binance and KuCoin were chosen for <a href="https://solscan.io/tx/4ZqYRfvPePGLpZCb6t1iq7gNMUwsrkcQoSAiDHq9gEYUve9t3b598Qf63uErtaoB1onScKf7VcmM3u8qVbAd3XK6" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">cashing</a> out. By choosing big exchanges with robust cybersecurity teams instead of the well-known crypto mixer route, the hacker runs a much bigger risk of being caught. However, it’s also possible that the exploit was carried out as an impromptu addition to the hackathon. If the funds are meant to be returned, anonymity may not matter to the exploiter as much.</p>
<p>Alternatively, the attack may have been carried out by someone in a country who does not cooperate with Western law enforcement, in which case ease of access to liquidity provided by big CEXs may be the only thing that matters.</p>
<h2>Reaching Out Via NFTs.</h2>
<p>Since the attack, users have been reaching out to the hacker by sending NFTs with brisk messages to the address involved.</p>
<p>Some of these messages are simple <a href="https://solscan.io/token/BhgF2oFyy3TDdMqK2XchMS2Q76TsdRw9ZhnMErdkEPRi" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">appeals to morality</a>.</p>
<p><em>&#8220;Seriously though, you used Binance and KuCoin to fund and to try and get 30k out. People will find you. Please do the right thing and give the rest back.”</em></p>
<p>However, other users opted for a terser “<em>Give it</em> <a href="https://solscan.io/token/BhgF2oFyy3TDdMqK2XchMS2Q76TsdRw9ZhnMErdkEPRi" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><em>back</em></a>,<em> you sh*tlord</em>”.</p>
<p>Although the size of the exploit is dwarfed by previous <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thousands-of-wallets-compromised-in-ongoing-solana-based-hack/" data-wpel-link="internal">attacks</a> on the Solana network, a hack of this size can be a sink-or-swim deal for smaller projects like Cypher Protocol. It remains to be seen what the devs uncover about the attack and if a recovery is possible.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cypher-protocol-exploited-will-the-hacker-return-the-funds-details/" rel="nofollow">Cypher Protocol Exploited, Will the Hacker Return the Funds? Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitsamp Not For Sale: Exec Confirms Fundraise Plans for International Expansion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitsamp-not-for-sale-exec-confirms-fundraise-plans-for-international-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitstamp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265037</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/jean_bitstamp_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/jean_bitstamp_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitstamp is currently and exclusively prioritiizing raising through strategic investors to accelerate its operations.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitstamp &#8211; the world&#8217;s longest-running cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; is currently engaged in discussions to secure new capital to ramp up its operations. The revelation was made by Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux, Bitstamp&#8217;s global chief executive officer.</p>
<p>Besides focusing on raising capital to expand the services to retail and institutional crypto clients, Bitstamp also plans on diving into the derivatives space.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-188551" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux.jpg" alt="Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jean-Baptiste-Graftieaux-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Bitstamp Fundraise</h2>
<p>The fundraising process was initiated in late June, with Michael Novogratz’s Galaxy Digital Holdings acting as an adviser. Bitstamp plans to deploy the funds for operations such as rolling out derivatives trading in Europe next year. The crypto exchange will also focus on expanding its operation across several markets in Asia, as well as in the UK.</p>
<p>Graftieaux was <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-in-talks-to-raise-funds-for-expansion-ceo-says-1.1956129" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">quoted</a> saying,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Bitstamp is not for sale, and we are not actively looking to sell the company. Our current and exclusive priority is to raise money through strategic investors to accelerate Bitstamp’s growth by providing new products and services to retail and institutional crypto customers.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitstamp was founded in 2011 and emerged as a European-centric substitute to the once-dominant Bitcoin exchange, Mt. Gox. Currently, it is ranked as the seventh-largest exchange globally, boasting a trading volume of around $126 million. It is based in Slovenia, with its headquarters situated in London, England.</p>
<p>The latest development comes a few months after the San Francisco-based blockchain firm Ripple was reported to have acquired a minority stake in the crypto exchange in the first quarter of 2023. The deal was advised upon by Galaxy Digital.</p>
<h2>French Foray</h2>
<p>Bitstamp secured an operational license from France&#8217;s top financial regulatory body, the Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF), this February and became part of a roster of cryptocurrency platforms permitted to provide products and services to the local user base.</p>
<p>The Luxembourg-based company had previously acquired licenses in other European nations, including registration as a virtual asset service provider (VASP) in Italy a year back. It was also authorized by the Spanish financial watchdogs in November.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitsamp-not-for-sale-exec-confirms-fundraise-plans-for-international-expansion/" rel="nofollow">Bitsamp Not For Sale: Exec Confirms Fundraise Plans for International Expansion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mahjong Meta Unveils Revolutionary Web3 Esports Platform, Official Launch on August 7th</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mahjong-meta-unveils-revolutionary-web3-esports-platform-official-launch-on-august-7th/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265172</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/20230804-020815_1691493687QmKsp5SKSa.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/20230804-020815_1691493687QmKsp5SKSa.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Hong Kong, Hong Kong, August 8th, 2023] Mahjong Meta, the web3 Riichi Mahjong esports platform, is excited to announce the official launch of its highly anticipated game on August 7th. After a successful two-month Open Beta test that captured the hearts of mahjong enthusiasts, the platform is set to revolutionize the mahjong [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Hong Kong, Hong Kong, August 8th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Mahjong Meta, the web3 Riichi Mahjong esports platform, is excited to announce the official launch of its highly anticipated game on August 7th. After a successful two-month Open Beta test that captured the hearts of mahjong enthusiasts, the platform is set to revolutionize the mahjong gaming experience on-chain with its immersive and decentralized gaming experience.</p>
<p>In Mahjong Meta, players can not only participate in various matches such as Ranking, Tournaments, or Playgrounds with other real players, but they can also deploy their pets, known as &#8220;Tama,&#8221; equipped with customized AI strategies for automatic mahjong battles. This feature has greatly reduced the barrier for new mahjong players and Web3 users, making the gaming experience more accessible and enjoyable.</p>
<p>During the Open Beta period, Mahjong Meta attracted over 15,000 players who collectively participated in more than 490,000 matches, showcasing the game&#8217;s immense popularity and potential in the crypto-gaming world. The integration of web3 ownership economics, innovative AI-based gameplay, and stylish graphic design proved to be a winning combination, setting the stage for an extraordinary gaming experience.</p>
<p>Additionally, during the Beta phase, Mahjong Meta introduced 0xMahjong and 0xTama NFTs, with a total trading volume on Opensea approaching 500ETH, further highlighting the growing interest and confidence from the community.</p>
<p>The game&#8217;s initial success at this stage can be attributed to its experienced core team, which comprises professionals from renowned gaming companies like Tencent, NetEase, Lilith, etc. Inspired by the ancient classic and beloved game Mahjong, which continues to be popular among over 600 million players worldwide, Brice, the game designer of Mahjong Meta, reveals that the idea of the game comes from the inherent mathematical beauty of Riichi Mahjong, blending strategy and probability, along with its enduring appeal in strategy, social engagement, gameplay deduction, and cultural significance. Mahjong Meta embraces the &#8220;Play to Own &amp; Skill to Earn&#8221; philosophy, aiming to establish a blockchain-based Riichi Mahjong esports community and a Mahjong-themed gaming park, co-built with players and supported by asset ownership through blockchain and token-based economy.</p>
<p>The concept of Mahjong Meta, current development progress, and the platform&#8217;s immense potential have attracted significant investments from prominent venture capital firms. Dragonfly and Folius led the funding round, underscoring their belief in Mahjong Meta&#8217;s vision and potential in the gaming industry. Other notable investors include Meteorite Labs, Find Satoshi Lab, Parallel Ventures, and Emoote. The accumulated investment exceeds $12 million.</p>
<p>Upon its official launch on August 7th, Mahjong Meta unveiled all game-related features, including Ranking, Tama Master, Friends Room, and all NFT markets including Mahjong House, Tama, Fashion, Furniture, etc., offering players a more immersive game-fi experience within the ecosystem. In conjunction with the launch, Mahjong Meta will also offer additional community rewards with its vault system and additional referral rewards for players, encouraging more Mahjong enthusiasts to participate in this exciting gaming experience.</p>
<p>Join Mahjong Meta now as the game sets a new standard for Mahjong gaming, leveraging ownership economy from Web3 to create a real Meta for Mahjong players.</p>
<p><strong>About Mahjong Meta</strong></p>
<p>Mahjong Meta is a game created by former Tencent and Netease employees. With the game, they intend to nurture a community of mahjong lovers while offering a stable and secure game environment. Mahjong fans may now test their talents in novel gameplay modes and compete for potential rewards at stake.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/0xMJM" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://mjmeta.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a> | <a href="https://discord.gg/mjmeta" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DC</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mahjong-meta-unveils-revolutionary-web3-esports-platform-official-launch-on-august-7th/" rel="nofollow">Mahjong Meta Unveils Revolutionary Web3 Esports Platform, Official Launch on August 7th</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pro-XRP Lawyer Willing to Bet Big on Ripple v. SEC Case Appeal</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-willing-to-bet-big-on-ripple-v-sec-case-appeal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265153</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/secvripple_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/secvripple_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[John Deaton says he's willing to bet a lot of money on the outcome of the SEC's appeal against the recent ruling in the Ripple case.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pro-XRP lawyer John Deaton has said he’s willing to wager on the outcome of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s appeal against a recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/history-in-the-making-with-ripple-scoring-massive-win-in-court-in-xrp-security-case-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruling</a> that determined Ripple’s XRP token is not a security under certain circumstances.</p>
<ul>
<li>Deaton, the founder, and host of CryptoLaw, remarked in a post on X (formerly Twitter) while supporting the view of fellow lawyer and crypto enthusiast Bill Morgan, who claimed the judge in the SEC vs XRP case had not erred in her decision.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Excellent <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> explaining that Torres didn’t make a distinction between the different sales out of thin air. She took each type of sale CHOSEN and DEFINED by the SEC and applied the Howey test. I’m willing to bet significant funds she doesn’t get reversed on appeal. <a href="https://t.co/5jAfwusrng" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/5jAfwusrng</a></p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1688309749610168320?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>According to Deaton, Judge Analisa Torres, who presided over the XRP case, applied the Howey Test on each SEC charge against Ripple before delivering her verdict. For that reason, Deaton is willing to bet “significant funds” against the SEC, getting a reversal of the judgment if it appeals.</li>
<li>Deaton’s confidence is in stark contrast to other members of the crypto community who may have been rattled by the decision of another judge presiding over a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-rejects-terraforms-attempt-to-capitalize-on-ripple-precedent-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">case</a> the SEC has brought against Terraform Labs and its founder, Do Kwon.</li>
<li>Terraform and Do Kwon had tried to use the findings in the XRP case to get charges against them dropped. However, Judge Jed Rakoff faulted Judge Torres’ reasoning, stating that the Howey Test does not distinguish between buyers.</li>
<li>Rakoff’s comment led many in the crypto space to speculate that Judge Torres’ decision may get squashed on appeal, which the SEC has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-xrp-in-trouble-again-sec-signals-appeal-in-ripple-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">signaled</a> it plans to file.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pro-xrp-lawyer-willing-to-bet-big-on-ripple-v-sec-case-appeal/" rel="nofollow">Pro-XRP Lawyer Willing to Bet Big on Ripple v. SEC Case Appeal</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla&#8217;s Master of Coin Resigns as CFO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/teslas-master-of-coin-resigns-as-cfo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265035</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/tesla_cfo_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/tesla_cfo_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CAO Vaibhav Taneja will replace "Master of Coin" Kirkhorn as Tesla's new CFO.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Zachary Kirkhorn, who served as chief financial officer at Tesla, stepped down after staying in the position for the last four and a half years. He will remain part of the company until the end of 2023 to help transition the new CFO.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kirkhorn earned the nickname &#8220;Master of Coin&#8221; in 2021, shortly after the electric vehicle giant splashed the waters with its whopping $1.5 billion bitcoin purchase. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Changes in Tesla&#8217;s Management Team</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kirkhorn (who joined Tesla in 2010) will be succeeded by the chief accounting officer Vaibhav Taneja. The former CFO </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/zachkirkhorn_this-morning-tesla-announced-that-ive-stepped-activity-7094302559581954050-ROjP/?trk=public_profile_post_view" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">confirmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the news on his LinkedIn profile, saying his journey at the firm has been a &#8220;special experience.&#8221; He also thanked all his colleagues, including CEO Elon Musk, for their support over the years.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Being a part of this company is a special experience, and I&#8217;m extremely proud of the work we&#8217;ve done together since I joined over 13 years ago. As I shift my responsibilities to support this transition, I want to thank the talented, passionate, and hard-working employees at Tesla, who have accomplished things many thought not possible.</span></p>
<p>I also want to thank Elon for his leadership and optimism, which has inspired so many people,&#8221; he stated.</p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_265078" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265078" style="width: 711px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Zachary-Kirkhorn.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-265078" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Zachary-Kirkhorn.jpg" alt="Zachary Kirkhorn" width="711" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Zachary-Kirkhorn.jpg 929w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Zachary-Kirkhorn-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Zachary-Kirkhorn-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Zachary-Kirkhorn-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 711px) 100vw, 711px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265078" class="wp-caption-text">Zachary Kirkhorn, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kirkhorn did not disclose the reasons behind his departure nor what his next step will be. Apart from managing the financial policies of Tesla through challenging times such as the COVID-19 crisis, he will be remembered by his nickname &#8220;Master of Coin.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He earned that informal title shortly after the EV behemoth </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/breaking-tesla-bought-1-5-billion-of-bitcoin-btc-skyrockets-to-new-ath/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">bought</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $1.5 billion worth of bitcoin in 2021 and displayed intentions to accept the asset as a payment method. Musk, on the other hand, was named &#8220;Technoking.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">What Happened to Tesla&#8217;s BTC Bet?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company kept its stash untouched for approximately a year and a half before selling 75% of it in July last year. However, Musk </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-reveals-the-reason-why-tesla-sold-75-of-its-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">explained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the move was not prompted because Tesla does not believe in the primary cryptocurrency anymore but because it had to cover record production costs in China.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm has not sold any of its BTC possessions since then and remains one of the largest corporate holders of the leading digital asset. It has 10,725 BTC, equaling around $315 million (calculated at current rates).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides that, Tesla </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/tesla-starts-accepting-bitcoin-payments-btc-price-spikes-1000-immediately/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accepted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the asset as a payment option for its vehicles in March 2021. Shortly after, though, it suspended that offering out of concern over the &#8220;rapidly increasing use of fossil fuels for bitcoin mining.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/teslas-master-of-coin-resigns-as-cfo/" rel="nofollow">Tesla&#8217;s Master of Coin Resigns as CFO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Whales Accumulate Heavily Below $0.30: Details</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-whales-accumulate-heavily-below-0-30-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265085</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The accumulation comes in the wake of growing DeFi activity on the network. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano whales are seizing the opportunity of price inaction to rake in more tokens. One particular cohort of ADA holders has accumulated back to their highest level not seen in nearly a year as the current value of the crypto-asset struggles below the $0.30 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265145" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover.jpg" alt="cardano_whale_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cardano_whale_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p>According to the crypto-analytic platform, Santiment, whales and sharks holding between 100K-10M ADA have accumulated back to their highest level since September 2022. It was also observed that Cardano&#8217;s on-chain transaction volume was rising nearly every week for the past six months.</p>
<ul>
<li>ADA&#8217;s performance, so far, has been underwhelming. The crypto being dragged into court battles by the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) further reversed any potential upside moves.</li>
<li>However, the continued <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1688789040815075328" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">accumulation</a> depicts that investors are bullish about ADA&#8217;s price action even as it was trapped within the range of $0.35-$0.26 for the past several weeks.</li>
<li>On the DeFi side of things, Cardano registered notable growth with its total value locked (TVL) rising by nearly 10% quarter-over-quarter and climbing beyond $151 million.</li>
<li>The layer-1 smart contract platform&#8217;s year-to-date TVL also surged by almost 200%, propelling it from the 34th to the 21st position among all networks in 2023.</li>
<li>Cardano&#8217;s average daily dapp transactions also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-records-impressive-49-qoq-growth-in-dapp-transactions-10-rise-in-tvl-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">increased</a> by 49.0% increase from the previous quarter in Q2, retaining an average of 57,900 daily transactions, according to Messari’s report titled &#8216;State of Cardano.&#8217;</li>
<li>The transaction activity on the network also surged during the period by approximately 2% QoQ from 67,500 to 68,800.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-whales-accumulate-heavily-below-0-30-details/" rel="nofollow">Cardano (ADA) Whales Accumulate Heavily Below $0.30: Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
