<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Russian Central Bank Readies ‘Real-world’ CBDC Pilot – Digital Ruble Launch Imminent?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-readies-real-world-cbdc-pilot-digital-ruble-launch-imminent.htm</link><description>The Russian Central Bank could begin “real-world” tests on the digital ruble next month after parliament approved a key piece of CBDC legislation. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Interfax, the State Duma voted in favor of adopting the bill at a third reading this week. &lt;br /&gt;
This means the main clauses of the bill are set to pass into national law on August 1, 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
At the end of March, the Central Bank announced that it was ready to conduct a pilot with “real” digital ruble tokens....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-readies-real-world-cbdc-pilot-digital-ruble-launch-imminent.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Central Bank Readies ‘Real-world’ CBDC Pilot – Digital Ruble Launch Imminent?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-central-bank-readies-real-world-cbdc-pilot-digital-ruble-launch-imminent.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119465/317591/rus-1207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="821975"/></item><item><title>Lawyer Says Argentina Should Bin Dollarization Plans, Adopt BTC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lawyer-says-argentina-should-bin-dollarization-plans-adopt-btc.htm</link><description>A prominent Argentine lawyer has told a leading presidential candidate to bin his dollarization plans in favor of a Bitcoin (BTC) adoption drive. &lt;br /&gt;
The comments were directed at Javier Milei, a right-wing political leader who has been described as a populist by some commentators. &lt;br /&gt;
Milei has previously spoken out in favor of Bitcoin, and was last year embroiled in a crypto-related controversy....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lawyer-says-argentina-should-bin-dollarization-plans-adopt-btc.htm"&gt;Read More: Lawyer Says Argentina Should Bin Dollarization Plans, Adopt BTC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lawyer-says-argentina-should-bin-dollarization-plans-adopt-btc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119391/317469/arg-1107.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="876631"/></item><item><title>New Tool Allows Bitcoin Holders to Store Private Keys as Colors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-tool-allows-bitcoin-holders-store-private-keys-as-colors.htm</link><description>One of the challenges crypto investors face is the issue of asset loss. Sometimes, scammers steal users’ assets when they access their private keys.  &lt;br /&gt;
Other times, the government can seize an investor's crypto assets when flagging them for illegal transactions or other cases unrelated to crypto.  &lt;br /&gt;
But all these issues are about to change with an introduction of a new Bitcoin tool. Users no longer need to use word and alphanumeric characters as private keys. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-tool-allows-bitcoin-holders-store-private-keys-as-colors.htm"&gt;Read More: New Tool Allows Bitcoin Holders to Store Private Keys as Colors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-tool-allows-bitcoin-holders-store-private-keys-as-colors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119476/317635/bitcoin-gd7c63a073-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="450348"/></item><item><title>Google Play Embraces Digital Assets &amp; NFTs: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/google-play-embraces-digital-assets-nfts-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>In an unprecedented move, Google Play, the popular Andriod app and game marketplace, has announced policy changes to allow the integration of digital assets such as non-fungible tokens (NFTs) into its platform. &lt;br /&gt;
Google Play Group Product Manager, Joseph Mills, unveiled the policy shift on Wednesday via a blog post. &lt;br /&gt;
In it, he underlined that the move will usher in a new era of enriched user experiences and novel forms of user content....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/google-play-embraces-digital-assets-nfts-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Google Play Embraces Digital Assets &amp; NFTs: What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Google</category><category>Google play</category><category>Digital Assets</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Play To Earn Games</category><category>P2E</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/google-play-embraces-digital-assets-nfts-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119475/317632/google.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="992629"/></item><item><title>IMF Highlights Climate Change and DAOs as Major Threats to the Marshall Islands</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/imf-highlights-climate-change-daos-as-major-threats-marshall-islands.htm</link><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) has identified climate change and decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) as potential threats to the Republic of Marshall Islands. Therefore, the IMF urges reforms in light of these challenges. &lt;br /&gt;
On July 9, the IMF published its disclosure titled "Republic of the Marshall Islands: Concluding Statement of the 2023 Article IV Consultation Mission" following the completion of its annual consultation with the Republic of the Marshall Islands (RMI)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/imf-highlights-climate-change-daos-as-major-threats-marshall-islands.htm"&gt;Read More: IMF Highlights Climate Change and DAOs as Major Threats to the Marshall Islands&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>IMF</category><category>DAO</category><category>Marshall Islands</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/imf-highlights-climate-change-daos-as-major-threats-marshall-islands.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119467/317624/getpaidstock-com-64af06ef55c23.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="100535"/></item><item><title>AI Coins Pump as Elon Musk Launches ChatGPT Competitor – Where Next for RNDR, FET and AGIX?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-coins-pump-as-elon-musk-launches-chatgpt-competitor-where-next-for-rndr-fet-agix.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrencies that boast a strong artificial intelligence (AI)-linked use case, such as Render Network (RNDR), SingularityNET (AGIX) and Fetch.ai (FET) have seen a pump on Wednesday amid positive AI news. &lt;br /&gt;
Twitter, Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announced on Wednesday that he had launched a new generative AI start-up called xAI....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-coins-pump-as-elon-musk-launches-chatgpt-competitor-where-next-for-rndr-fet-agix.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Coins Pump as Elon Musk Launches ChatGPT Competitor – Where Next for RNDR, FET and AGIX?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Render Network</category><category>RNDR</category><category>SingularityNET</category><category>AGIX</category><category>Fetch.ai</category><category>FET</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>AI</category><category>Elon Musk</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-coins-pump-as-elon-musk-launches-chatgpt-competitor-where-next-for-rndr-fet-agix.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119472/317613/ai.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="36563"/></item><item><title>FTT Price Pumps, Dumps as FTX Claims Portal Opens, Then Becomes Unavailable</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftt-price-pumps-dumps-as-ftx-claims-portal-opens-then-becomes-unavailable.htm</link><description>FTT saw a massive 26% pump from the $1.40s to the $1.80 area on Tuesday in a matter of minutes, before pulling back under $1.60 on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
FTT is the utility token of the now defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX that is currently going through a lengthy, arduous bankruptcy process in wake of its collapse last November. &lt;br /&gt;
The token pumped on Tuesday on reports across social media that FTX had launched its online claims portal at claims.ftx.com....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftt-price-pumps-dumps-as-ftx-claims-portal-opens-then-becomes-unavailable.htm"&gt;Read More: FTT Price Pumps, Dumps as FTX Claims Portal Opens, Then Becomes Unavailable&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTT</category><category>FTX</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>Thug Life Token</category><category>THUG</category><category>Mr Hankey Coin</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftt-price-pumps-dumps-as-ftx-claims-portal-opens-then-becomes-unavailable.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119468/317599/ftt.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="360928"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Core Inflation Data is Released – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-core-inflation-data-released-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Bitcoin is steady at around $30,600, reflecting a nearly 0.50% increase on Wednesday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The consumer price index saw a 0.2% rise in June, marking a 3% increase from a year ago, the lowest level since March 2021.  &lt;br /&gt;
With the release of US core inflation data, investors are evaluating the potential impact on Bitcoin's price. The question arises: is it the right time to buy? &lt;br /&gt;
Let's find out. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-core-inflation-data-released-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Core Inflation Data is Released – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-core-inflation-data-released-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119438/317595/12.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482642"/></item><item><title>Crypto Investment Firm Paradigm Challenges SEC's Jurisdiction in Bittrex Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-investment-firm-paradigm-challenges-secs-jurisdiction-bittrex-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Prominent crypto investment firm Paradigm has challenged the US Securities and Exchange Commission's authority to regulate secondary markets for crypto assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The company has filed an amicus brief in the SEC's case against cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex, challenging the regulator's attempt to expand its jurisdiction over crypto secondary markets, Paradigm's special counsel Rodrigo Seira said in a recent statement....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-investment-firm-paradigm-challenges-secs-jurisdiction-bittrex-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Investment Firm Paradigm Challenges SEC's Jurisdiction in Bittrex Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Paradigm</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bittrex</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-investment-firm-paradigm-challenges-secs-jurisdiction-bittrex-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119461/317584/bittrex-media-library-ori.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="80519"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 July – Conflux, SingularityNET, Fetch.ai</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-july-conflux-singularitynet-fetchai.htm</link><description>Despite softer-than-expected US headline and core inflation numbers for June, which weighed heavily on the US dollar and US yields whilst also pushing up US equity markets as Fed tightening bets ease, crypto markets have failed to rally. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last near $30,500 and ether (ETH) was last in the upper $1,800s. &lt;br /&gt;
Over all market cap was last broadly unchanged in the $1.19 trillion region....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-july-conflux-singularitynet-fetchai.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 July – Conflux, SingularityNET, Fetch.ai&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Conflux</category><category>CFX</category><category>SingularityNET</category><category>AGIX</category><category>Fetch.ai</category><category>FET</category><category>AI coin</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-july-conflux-singularitynet-fetchai.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119460/317581/bestcrypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Here's How This PEPE Price Trade Made a Crypto Millionaire</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/heres-how-pepe-price-trade-made-crypto-millionaire.htm</link><description>Pepe Coin, the Pepe the Frog-themed meme coin that exploded back in April, made near instant millionaires. &lt;br /&gt;
What was so amazing it that many millionaires were created despite only putting very small initial investments into the $PEPE token. &lt;br /&gt;
For example, a Twitter user going by the name of lyx.eth highlighted back in April how one wallet beginning with 0xAf235 made nearly $1 million at the time with a minuscule initial $27 investment in Pepe. &lt;br /&gt;
That was then....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/heres-how-pepe-price-trade-made-crypto-millionaire.htm"&gt;Read More: Here's How This PEPE Price Trade Made a Crypto Millionaire&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Pepe</category><category>South Park</category><category>Mr Hankey Coin</category><category>Shit Coin</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/heres-how-pepe-price-trade-made-crypto-millionaire.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119458/317572/pepethefrog.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4136604"/></item><item><title>Former CFTC Chair: Crypto Regulations Must Not Wait for Litigation, Standards Needed Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-cftc-chair-crypto-regulations-must-not-wait-for-litigation-standards-needed-today.htm</link><description>A crackdown on the crypto industry in the US should not wait for litigation in courts to conclude, but instead move forward with temporary restraints while the courts do their work, a former regulator has said. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking with CNBC on Monday, Timothy Massad, former chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) said that enforcing current laws is no longer enough to reign in crypto, and that new “standards” are needed....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-cftc-chair-crypto-regulations-must-not-wait-for-litigation-standards-needed-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Former CFTC Chair: Crypto Regulations Must Not Wait for Litigation, Standards Needed Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-cftc-chair-crypto-regulations-must-not-wait-for-litigation-standards-needed-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119441/317547/timothy-massad.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="522290"/></item><item><title>Mr Hankey Meme Coin Goes Viral as South Park-Related Tokens Take Off – Here's How to Buy Early</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mr-hankey-meme-coin-goes-viral-as-south-park-related-tokens-take-off-heres-how-to-buy-early.htm</link><description>A brand-new meme coin themed on South Park’s Mr Hankey, a sentient, jolly piece of feces and the cartoon’s former Christmas deity, has been going viral in the last few days. &lt;br /&gt;
Mr Hankey Coin, which is proudly marketing itself as the crypto industry’s best shitcoin, is launching a stealth presale in just over one day’s time. &lt;br /&gt;
And ahead of the event, the project has been going viral across social media....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mr-hankey-meme-coin-goes-viral-as-south-park-related-tokens-take-off-heres-how-to-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Mr Hankey Meme Coin Goes Viral as South Park-Related Tokens Take Off – Here's How to Buy Early&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Mr Hankey Coin</category><category>Shitcoin</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mr-hankey-meme-coin-goes-viral-as-south-park-related-tokens-take-off-heres-how-to-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119452/317564/mr-hankey-web.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="341188"/></item><item><title>Singapore's Investment Conglomerate Temasek Drops Crypto Investment Plans Citing Regulatory Uncertainties</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapores-investment-conglomerate-temasek-drops-crypto-investment-plans-citing-regulatory-uncertainties.htm</link><description>Singaporean investment conglomerate Temasek has decided to drop its plans to invest in crypto exchanges, due to regulatory uncertainties. &lt;br /&gt;
In an interview with CNBC, Temasek’s Chief Investment Officer Rohit Sipahimalani revealed the bitter experience of writing down its entire $275 million investment in the now-bankrupt crypto exchange FTX. &lt;br /&gt;
As a result, and with unclear regulations and market conditions, Temasek is not currently looking to invest in crypto-related firms, he said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/singapores-investment-conglomerate-temasek-drops-crypto-investment-plans-citing-regulatory-uncertainties.htm"&gt;Read More: Singapore's Investment Conglomerate Temasek Drops Crypto Investment Plans Citing Regulatory Uncertainties&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapores-investment-conglomerate-temasek-drops-crypto-investment-plans-citing-regulatory-uncertainties.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119445/317557/pexels-kin-pastor-777059.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="3366194"/></item><item><title>EU Regulators Issue Stablecoin Guidance, Calls For Compliance Ahead Of MiCA</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-regulators-issue-stablecoin-guidance-calls-for-compliance-ahead-of-mica.htm</link><description>Financial regulators within the European Union (EU) have urged stablecoin issuers alongside other industry participants to adopt the guidelines set out in Markets In Crypto Assets Regulation (MiCA). &lt;br /&gt;
MiCA is the first comprehensive digital asset regulatory framework that covers exchanges, assets, and stablecoins amongst others. Billed to come into effect in June 2024, authorities have advised market players to begin preparations to ensure compliance. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-regulators-issue-stablecoin-guidance-calls-for-compliance-ahead-of-mica.htm"&gt;Read More: EU Regulators Issue Stablecoin Guidance, Calls For Compliance Ahead Of MiCA&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>EU</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Regulators</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-regulators-issue-stablecoin-guidance-calls-for-compliance-ahead-of-mica.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119443/317554/flags-g49974bacd-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="136266"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Investor Tim Draper Still Bullish on Bitcoin, Foresees $250,000 Price in the Future – Here's the Timeline</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-investor-tim-draper-still-bullish-bitcoin-foresees-250000-price-future-heres-timeline.htm</link><description>Billionaire venture capitalist Tim Draper is standing by his Bitcoin (BTC) price prediction of $250,000 per coin - but he’s pushed it forward to 2025. &lt;br /&gt;
“When Bitcoin was $4000, I predicted it would reach $250k (60X) by now,” tweeted Draper at the end of last month. The asset traded for roughly $30,400 at the time, and has remained mostly flat since. “I guess we have to wait a little longer, (maybe 2 years) but engineers are hard at work,” he added. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-investor-tim-draper-still-bullish-bitcoin-foresees-250000-price-future-heres-timeline.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Investor Tim Draper Still Bullish on Bitcoin, Foresees $250,000 Price in the Future – Here's the Timeline&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-investor-tim-draper-still-bullish-bitcoin-foresees-250000-price-future-heres-timeline.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119437/317544/tim-draper-media-library-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="53941"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Celsius Sues StakeHound Over $150M in Assets, US Finance Committee Asks Crypto Industry for Opinions, Russia's Duma Passes Digital Ruble Bill, Stablecoins are 'Existential Threat to Policy Sovereignty'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-celsius-sues-stakehound-over-150m-in-assets-us-finance-committee-asks-crypto-industry-for-opinions-russias-duma-passes-digital-ruble-bill-stablecoins-are-existential-threat-to-policy-sovereignty.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-celsius-sues-stakehound-over-150m-in-assets-us-finance-committee-asks-crypto-industry-for-opinions-russias-duma-passes-digital-ruble-bill-stablecoins-are-existential-threat-to-policy-sovereignty.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Celsius Sues StakeHound Over $150M in Assets, US Finance Committee Asks Crypto Industry for Opinions, Russia's Duma Passes Digital Ruble Bill, Stablecoins are 'Existential Threat to Policy Sovereignty'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Legal</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Regulation</category><category>USA</category><category>Tax</category><category>South Korea</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Russia</category><category>India</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Investment</category><category>NFT</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Polkadot</category><category>Celsius</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-celsius-sues-stakehound-over-150m-in-assets-us-finance-committee-asks-crypto-industry-for-opinions-russias-duma-passes-digital-ruble-bill-stablecoins-are-existential-threat-to-policy-sovereignty.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119403/317528/adobestock-timon-1-media-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="69784"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Pumps Up 18%, and AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Approaches $2.9 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-pumps-up-18-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-approaches-29-million-1.htm</link><description>Solana's native token, $SOL, is signaling positive market sentiment and has rallied above the $18 resistance zone. &lt;br /&gt;
Based on data from CoinMarketCap, the digital asset has experienced a remarkable 18% increase over the past few days as it hovers at a $22 price mark.  &lt;br /&gt;
This surge has generated a bullish sentiment and sparked enthusiasm among cryptocurrency traders....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-pumps-up-18-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-approaches-29-million-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Pumps Up 18%, and AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Approaches $2.9 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-pumps-up-18-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-approaches-29-million-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119428/317537/solana.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="572774"/></item><item><title>EU ‘Understands the Benefits of Having One Crypto Market’, Says Blocktrade CEO Christian Niedermüller</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-understands-benefits-of-having-one-crypto-market-says-blocktrade-ceo-christian-niedermuller.htm</link><description>The EU's comprehensive work on regulating the industry will provide numerous benefits to crypto companies and their customers, argued Christian Niedermüller, CEO of the fully regulated crypto platform Blocktrade, in an interview with Cryptonews. &lt;br /&gt;
However, it will also create certain difficulties that are bound to affect crypto firms - specifically, in terms of costs of compliance and reporting. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-understands-benefits-of-having-one-crypto-market-says-blocktrade-ceo-christian-niedermuller.htm"&gt;Read More: EU ‘Understands the Benefits of Having One Crypto Market’, Says Blocktrade CEO Christian Niedermüller&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Blocktrade</category><category>EU</category><category>European Union</category><category>Europe</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Estonia</category><category>Circle</category><category>USA</category><category>SEC</category><category>Gaming</category><category>Staking</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-understands-benefits-of-having-one-crypto-market-says-blocktrade-ceo-christian-niedermuller.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/116298/312153/screenshot-2023-06-08-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="133223"/></item><item><title>South Korea To Require Firms To Disclose Crypto Holdings Starting 2024</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korea-require-firms-disclose-crypto-holdings-starting-2024.htm</link><description>South Korean firms that hold or issue cryptocurrencies will be required to disclose information about their transactions to the financial regulator starting next year. &lt;br /&gt;
The Financial Services Commission (FSC) of South Korea announced Tuesday that domestic companies that engage with crypto will have to provide complete disclosure under the new accounting rules set to take effect starting January 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korea-require-firms-disclose-crypto-holdings-starting-2024.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korea To Require Firms To Disclose Crypto Holdings Starting 2024&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korea-require-firms-disclose-crypto-holdings-starting-2024.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119424/317535/south-korea.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99472"/></item></channel></rss>
