<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Payments App Strike Adds Support for Tether&#8217;s USDT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-payments-app-strike-adds-support-for-tethers-usdt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 23:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251804</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tether_Strike.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tether_Strike.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The alliance aims to pave the way for greater adoption. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Strike &#8211; a Bitcoin payments company and remittance app &#8211; announced the integration of the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin, Tether&#8217;s USDT.</p>
<p>The latest move comes on the heels of Strike&#8217;s expansion into 65 additional countries and USDT-supported new app design, which was announced at Bitcoin 2023.</p>
<h2>Strike-Tether Integration</h2>
<p>The integration aims to address key challenges hindering the widespread acceptance of the industry, including the volatility aspect of crypto-assets.</p>
<p>As such, combining the stability and utility of USDT with Strike&#8217;s payment solutions is expected to serve as a &#8220;reliable bridge&#8221; between the crypto world and traditional financial systems while minimizing exposure to price fluctuations.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-usdt-to-be-integrated-onto-strike-leading-global-money-app/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> on Monday, Tether said users will gain the ability to convert their digital assets into fiat currency swiftly with its stablecoin as an intermediary and, in the process, overcome &#8220;liquidity challenges that have previously hindered adoption.&#8221;</p>
<p>Following the development, Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino commented,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to announce the integration of Tether (USD₮) with Strike. This is a pivotal moment for the cryptocurrency industry as it signifies the growing acceptance and recognition of stablecoins as a reliable and efficient digital payment solution.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The exec further added that the collaboration will boost the widespread adoption of digital currencies, &#8220;driving innovation and creating a more inclusive financial ecosystem for all.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Strike Expansion</h2>
<p>Strike <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wallet-strike-expands-support-to-3-billion-people-targets-global-south/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the expansion of its app to more than 65 countries from the current base of the United States and El Salvador, ramping up its total addressable market to almost 3 billion people. The new <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wallet-strike-expands-support-to-3-billion-people-targets-global-south/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">inexhaustive</a> list of 47 supported countries includes Bhutan, Brazil, Ecuador, Guatemala, Honduras, Kenya, New Zealand, Paraguay, and Uganda, alongside formerly announced expansions like Argentina, Nigeria, Kenya, and Ghana.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-integrates-lightning-with-point-of-sale-giant-clover/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnered</a> with fintech giant Fiserv to integrate Bitcoin&#8217;s lightning network with the point-of-sale terminal provider Clover.</p>
<p>The digital payments platform also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-announces-integration-with-shopify-to-facilitate-bitcoin-payments-via-lightning-network/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">integrated</a> with e-commerce giant Shopify in a bid to enable merchants to accept Bitcoin payments as US dollars seamlessly last November.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-payments-app-strike-adds-support-for-tethers-usdt/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Payments App Strike Adds Support for Tether&#8217;s USDT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Delays Plans for Controversial &#8220;Recover&#8221; Service, Announces Open-Source Roadmap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-delays-plans-for-controversial-recover-service-announces-open-source-roadmap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 22:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252060</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/ledger-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/ledger-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ledger will open-source its “clarified version” of Ledger Recover, but still cannot fully open-source its wallet firmware.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto hardware wallet provider Ledger will delay plans to launch its private key recovery service after receiving major backlash following its announcement last week. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The controversy – which rose questions about the safety and trustworthiness of Ledger devices more broadly – has inspired the company to accelerate its open-sourcing roadmap. </span></p>
<h2>Ledger’s Apology</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier began by issuing a public apology letter on Tuesday for the way Ledger’s “Recover” service was initially communicated to the public. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Our unintentional communication mistake took everyone by surprise and affected our customers’ ability to accurately understand Ledger Recover,” said Gauthier. “We never meant to surprise you.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger Recover, announced last week, is an upcoming paid subscription service for Ledger Nano X users that gives them a way to recover their crypto in case they lose both their device and paper-backup seed phrase. At a technical level, it involves breaking up a user’s private key into three encrypted “shards”, and storing each shard with Ledger, Coincover, and another third party. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The service was widely </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-under-fire-for-allegedly-exposing-user-seed-phrases/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">criticized</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for exposing that Ledger could potentially take users&#8217; private keys from their devices with a malicious firmware update. Concerns swelled later that week when Ledger Support </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-responds-to-customer-fears-on-wallet-safety-but-deletes-confusing-tweet/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">claimed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> (in a now-deleted tweet) that customers have always “trusted” Ledger not to release such malicious code “whether you knew it or not.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M3VjQUcyZSY" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">podcast episode</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> of </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400">What Bitcoin Did </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400">posted on Monday, Gauthier also stated that Ledger’s custodians could be forced to forfeit a customer’s private key shards if subpoenaed by a government. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ledger CEO, Pascal Gauthier, explains that Ledger Recover would give the state the ability to recover your <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> private keys in the event of a subpoena. <a href="https://t.co/KWaXcgtMqr" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/KWaXcgtMqr</a></p>
<p>&mdash; The ₿itcoin Therapist (@TheBTCTherapist) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheBTCTherapist/status/1660677064700178436?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger still plans to go forward with a “clarified version” of Ledger Recover in the future, which will answer most of the community&#8217;s expressed “sticking points.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The main concerns that you expressed are around transparency, censorship resistance, and security,” said Gauthier. “I think we’ve done a good job to address all of your concerns.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>The Open-Source Roadmap</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger CTO Charles Guillemet <a href="https://twitter.com/P3b7_/status/1661012196397305859" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">detailed</a> how the company would open-source more of its software going forward as a commitment to maximal transparency. “Open-source” code refers to code that is publicly viewable and verifiable.</p>
<p><img src="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Fw0X4lpaAAYj_Bp?format=jpg&amp;name=900x900" alt="Image" /><br />
</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The firm recently open-sourced its cryptography library, and will soon release its Ledger Recover whitepaper, allowing anyone to “audit the cryptographic protocols and enable people to build their own shards backup provider.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger plans to “gradually” open source most of its operating system, but still cannot fully open-source its firmware due to IP agreements with the manufacturers of its smartcard chips, which fend off hostile attackers with physical access to the device. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Open sourcing has always been at the core of our roadmap, and recent events emphasize the importance of accelerating our initiative to bring greater verifiability to everything we do at Ledger,” concluded the CTO. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-delays-plans-for-controversial-recover-service-announces-open-source-roadmap/" rel="nofollow">Ledger Delays Plans for Controversial &#8220;Recover&#8221; Service, Announces Open-Source Roadmap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitPay Integrates Brave Wallet Amid &#8216;Strong Interest&#8217; From Major Retailers, Brands</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitpay-integrates-brave-wallet-amid-strong-interest-from-major-retailers-brands/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitPay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251925</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BitPay_Brave.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BitPay_Brave.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BitPay revealed that it has processed more than $1 million in BTC payments over Lightning since supporting Lightning payments last year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin payment service provider &#8211; Bitpay &#8211; announced the integration of Brave Wallet into its payment protocol allowing crypto wallet users to make payments straight from the privacy browser.</p>
<p>According to the official press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, users of Brave Wallet will be able to shop with crypto at thousands of top merchants online and in-store, such as Newegg, APMEX, PacSun, AMC Theatres, and airBaltic.</p>
<p>Commenting on the development, BitPay CEO Stephen Pai said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;BitPay applauds Brave’s adoption of the BitPay Protocol. With the hard work and dedication of the Brave team, we are able to promote payment quality online and in-store for both customers and merchants wanting to leverage the benefits of crypto payments.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The latest development comes a month after the famous American fashion brand Ralph Lauren partnered with BitPay to accept Bitcoin payments at its new Miami Design District store.</p>
<h2>Crypto Payment Surge in Bear Market</h2>
<p>Litecoin and Bitcoin Lightning Network payments are showing impressive growth on BitPay&#8217;s platform this year. While speaking with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the chief executive of the Atlanta-based payment processor revealed that Litecoin continued to make up about a quarter of BitPay transactions.</p>
<p>Despite an ongoing bear market, BitPay recorded a notable uptick in crypto payments in 2022. This trend appears to have continued in recent months as well. Pair observed a strong interest in accepting crypto payments by major retailers and brands, especially high-end brands, even during market turmoil.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The crypto community is a passionate group that has shown time and time again that they are serious about spending their crypto, and the top brands and retailers are noticing.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The company has processed over $1 million in BTC payments over Lightning since adding support for Bitcoin LN payments in April 2022.</p>
<h2>BitPay Merchant Transaction Unaffected By Memecoin Craze</h2>
<p>The ordinals craze was viewed as a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-capitalizing-on-ordinals-hype-daily-revenue-hit-5-year-high-at-17m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">blessing</a> by the BTC miners as revenues shot up massively. But the spike in transactions of Ethereum-type tokens and NFT-like &#8220;inscriptions&#8221; drove average fees to as high as $30 on May 8 and 9 &#8211; levels not seen in the last two years &#8211; thereby adding to network congestion.</p>
<p>This increased Bitcoin network activity caused some surging miner fees for BitPay customers as well. However, the merchant transactions were largely unaffected, Pair said in a statement.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitpay-integrates-brave-wallet-amid-strong-interest-from-major-retailers-brands/" rel="nofollow">BitPay Integrates Brave Wallet Amid &#8216;Strong Interest&#8217; From Major Retailers, Brands</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Responds to Reuters Claims About Mixing User Funds</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-responds-to-reuters-claims-about-mixing-user-funds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252055</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/myths_facts_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/myths_facts_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance blasted Reuters for a “weak” article related to how customers’ dollar deposits were handled between its accounts.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A Reuters report on Tuesday suggested that Binance – the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange – comingled billions of dollars worth of customer assets with its corporate revenue in 2020 and 2021, obscuring the whereabouts of their money. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance’s Chief Communications Officer Patrick Hillmann responded by calling the story “weak” and xenophobic but admitted that Binance has had “regulatory shortcomings” in the past.</span></p>
<h2>Reuters’ Claims</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The initial Reuters </span><a href="https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/crypto-binance-money/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> cited multiple anonymous sources familiar with the matter, one of whom had “direct knowledge of Binance’s group finances.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The source claimed that comingling happened “almost daily” in accounts Binance held with Silvergate – a now collapsed crypto-supportive bank that’s been </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-regulators-launch-official-probe-into-silvergate-ftx-dealings/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">investigated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for helping the bankrupt FTX exchange comingle funds with Alameda Research.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance told Reuters that none of the funds within its Silvergate accounts were “customer deposits,” but rather funds used to purchase BUSD, Binance’s native dollar-pegged stablecoin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, throughout 2021, the exchange’s website represented dollar transfers to its platform as “deposits” that would be “credited” to their accounts as BUSD, creating potential confusion about regulatory safeguards around those transfers.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Paxos – the issuer behind BUSD – was forced to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-will-happen-to-binance-if-sec-manages-to-kill-busd/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">stop issuing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> new stablecoin tokens in February after receiving a Wells Notice from US regulators. </span></p>
<h2>Binance’s Response</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1660987014626287617" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, Binance’s Hillman asserted that customers were explicitly told on the website that their “deposits” would be used to purchase BUSD.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The comms officer also called out one of Reuters’ qualifying statements that it found “no evidence” Binance clients had lost any money, which he considered a “transparent attempt to protect themselves from a libel suit.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We’ve been very public about where the company had regulatory shortcomings in the past, there’s no reason for a respected news outlet like Reuters, to continue making stuff up,” he said.  </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hillman went on to accuse Reuters of implicit “xenophobia” for frequently mentioning CEO Changpeng Zhao’s Chinese ethnicity. The executive has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-is-not-a-chinese-company-declares-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">clarified</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in the past that Binance is not a Chinese company and that he’s been a Canadian citizen since the age of 12. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-responds-to-reuters-claims-about-mixing-user-funds/" rel="nofollow">Binance Responds to Reuters Claims About Mixing User Funds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court Dismisses $8M Pig Butchering Lawsuit Against Binance</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/court-dismisses-8m-pig-butchering-lawsuit-against-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 20:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251924</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Judge Mazzant dismissed the claims because Binance and its American affiliate were prohibited from operating in Texas.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A United States Court has granted a motion to dismiss a lawsuit alleging Binance&#8217;s involvement in a pig butchering scam that stole roughly $8 million from its victim.</p>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://assets.bwbx.io/documents/users/iqjWHBFdfxIU/rvg8sVwxegEU/v0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a> with the U.S. District Court for the Eastern District of Texas, Judge Amos Mazzant granted Binance&#8217;s motion to dismiss the case for lack of personal jurisdiction and the plaintiff&#8217;s failure to state a claim.</p>
<h2>An $8M Pig Butchering Scam</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-doj-confiscates-112-million-worth-of-crypto-linked-to-pig-butchering-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">A pig butchering scam</a> involves criminals luring victims into financial investments by building digital romantic relationships to gain their trust. Initially, the scheme mostly solicits modest investments to bolster the victims&#8217; confidence before seeking large funds.</p>
<p>The plaintiff, a Texas woman named Divya Gadasalli, was promised romance and financial prosperity on the popular online dating site Tinder by the scammer Jerry Bulasa. Gadasalli believed she had a romantic connection with Bulasa and began to invest through him, as he claimed to be a successful crypto investor.</p>
<p>Gadasalli then invested more than $8 million within a year. Despite Bulasa&#8217;s claims that the assets had grown to roughly $10 million, she could not withdraw any funds from her account.</p>
<p>In March 2022, after many excuses from Bulasa over Gadasalli&#8217;s inability to withdraw, she filed a lawsuit against him and his accomplices, Dong Lian and Danyun Lin, mentioning several entities, including Binance and crypto exchange Poloniex as the defendants.</p>
<h2>Lack of Personal Jurisdiction</h2>
<p>Binance filed a motion to dismiss the charges in June 2022 for lack of personal jurisdiction and failure to state a claim, but Gadasalli opposed the motion less than a month later.</p>
<p>The Texas woman argued that Binance was involved in the scheme as it provided exchange services to the scammer. She insisted that Binance and Binance.US were the same entity as customers used virtual private networks (VPNs) to access the services.</p>
<p>However, Judge Mazzant ruled that Gadasalli could not produce proof of Binance&#8217;s involvement in the fraud as the exchange and its American subsidiary were banned from operating in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/texas-regulator-issues-a-cease-and-desist-order-against-scammers-impersonating-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">Texas</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Pending before the Court is Defendant Binance Holdings Ltd.&#8217;s Motion to Dismiss the Amended Complaint for Lack of Personal Jurisdiction and Failure to State a Claim (Dkt. #32). Having considered the motion, the pleadings, and the relevant law, the Court finds that the motion should be GRANTED,&#8221; the judge said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/court-dismisses-8m-pig-butchering-lawsuit-against-binance/" rel="nofollow">Court Dismisses $8M Pig Butchering Lawsuit Against Binance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Crypto’s Regulatory Uncertainty By Design? Michael Saylor Answers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-cryptos-regulatory-uncertainty-by-design-michael-saylor-answers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252027</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here’s what regulators believe about the crypto industry, according to Michael Saylor. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Michael Saylor – Executive Chairman of the Bitcoin-bullish software company MicroStrategy – spoke at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami regarding the trajectory of Bitcoin adoption as a Treasury Reserve asset, and its place next to crypto in the US regulatory perimeter. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The former CEO addressed whether the so-called “lack of clarity” surrounding crypto regulation in the United States is “by design,” and how regulatory agencies actually view digital assets. </span></p>
<h2>What the SEC Doesn’t Like, According to Saylor</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Onzd5QxKaGQ&amp;ab_channel=KitcoNEWS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with Kitco NEWS published on Monday, Saylor said that he believes regulators are opposed to stablecoins effectively allowing billions of US dollars to circulate in “dark pools,” thus evading the controls of the banking system and sanctions. “Stablecoins are a problem for them, and I don’t think they’re going to change their view,” he said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">He also believes regulators have already concluded that most crypto tokens are unregistered securities that are being manipulated by their issuers, who have not released proper disclosures about those assets. This would align with the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chairman-is-only-willing-to-call-bitcoin-a-commodity/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">view</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> of Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chairman Gary Gensler, who has only shown a public willingness to label Bitcoin as a commodity. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The meltdown of FTX was a catalytic event that caused the regulators to decide that crypto exchanges, crypto securities, and cryptocurrencies that imitate the dollar are not really consistent with a stable world financial system,” said Saylor. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The US government has launched a multi-front attack on the crypto industry since FTX fell apart, including the SEC’s $30 million fine against Kraken in February, and Wells Notice against Coinbase for a similar product in April. Coinbase responded by compelling the SEC to respond to its request for clearer crypto regulations, which the SEC now wishes to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-moves-to-block-coinbases-request-for-clarification-in-court-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">strike down</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<h2>What’s Stopping Bitcoin Adoption?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Bitcoin itself doesn’t face the same types of regulatory threats, Saylor notes that there are still milestones to overcome on its way to larger institutional adoption. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">One is a matter of </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylors-wish-for-bitcoin-accounting-changes-has-arrived/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">accounting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">: Bitcoin is currently transitioning from using an “indefinite intangible” to a “fair value” accounting framework, which will let companies holding BTC on their balance sheets mark their crypto investment gains – not just their losses. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Another hurdle is related to “crypto confusion,” with companies conflating Bitcoin with the rest of the crypto market. “A lot of people had a hard time distinguishing between Bitcoin and FTX, and FTT token, and Terra, and Luna token, and all these other crypto assets,” explained Saylor.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, Saylor believes Bitcoin will benefit once regulators “clean up” the crypto industry. “Until that’s resolved… I think there are a lot of conservative investors that just stand off and wait.”</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-cryptos-regulatory-uncertainty-by-design-michael-saylor-answers/" rel="nofollow">Is Crypto’s Regulatory Uncertainty By Design? Michael Saylor Answers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Increasingly Being Used as &#8216;Buy-and-Hold&#8217; Asset: Bitfinex Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-increasingly-being-used-as-buy-and-hold-asset-bitfinex-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251934</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BitcoinHODL.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BitcoinHODL.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite short-term price volatility, key stakeholders continue to remain invested in Bitcoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin turned higher this week, recording a modest 2% gain. While the largest crypto asset continues to languish below several key levels, the holders&#8217; accumulation over the past several weeks suggests that it is &#8220;increasingly being used as a buy-and-hold asset.'&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>According to Bitfinex&#8217;s latest <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitfinex-Alpha-55.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, over 68.45% of the total supply, amounting to 13.27 million of the 19.4 million BTC in existence, have not moved in over a year.</li>
<li>This growing trend of investors holding strongly demonstrates a changing attitude towards Bitcoin ownership.</li>
<li>Another important indicator that underlined the prevailing trend of long-term accumulation is the number of &#8216;Wholecoiner&#8217; addresses crossing the one million mark this week.</li>
<li>These Wholecoiners can be defined as entities or individuals possessing at least one entire BTC and constitute a substantial segment of the Bitcoin community.</li>
<li>Data indicates that these investors have been gradually amassing since mid-2021, and there has been almost no notable reversal in the upward trajectory of 1-BTC wallets ever since.</li>
<li>The trend became even more pronounced in 2022 as the market plunged, and this cohort saw a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wholecoiners-reached-ath-above-1-million-amid-bear-market/" data-wpel-link="internal">20% increase</a> as a result.</li>
<li>Reiterating its previous <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-long-term-metrics-resemble-early-stages-from-previous-bull-markets-bitfinex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">analysis</a> that Bitcoin could be in the early stages of a bull market, Bitfinex added,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Despite the current market downturn, long-term Bitcoin holders remain undeterred. The increasing trend of long-term holding, coupled with the rise of Wholecoiners and the benefit to miners from increased transaction fees, paints a picture of a resilient Bitcoin ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-increasingly-being-used-as-buy-and-hold-asset-bitfinex-report/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Increasingly Being Used as &#8216;Buy-and-Hold&#8217; Asset: Bitfinex Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Are the Critical Levels for BTC in the Immediate Term (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/these-are-the-critical-levels-for-btc-in-the-immediate-term-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251947</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[For the past two weeks, Bitcoin has maintained its range-bound price movement. However, there are several indicators pointing toward an imminent breakout. Technical Analysis By Edris The Daily Chart The price has been consolidating within a narrow range on the daily timeframe for the last 7 days. This consolidation follows the market&#8217;s downward rejection at [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the past two weeks, Bitcoin has maintained its range-bound price movement. However, there are several indicators pointing toward an imminent breakout.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The price has been consolidating within a narrow range on the daily timeframe for the last 7 days. This consolidation follows the market&#8217;s downward rejection at the $30K resistance level and the subsequent breakdown of the 50-day moving average of around $29K.</p>
<p>Currently, the expected bearish target for the price is the $25K support level. However, there is a possibility that the price may first retest the 50-day moving average before continuing its decline toward $25K.</p>
<p>The RSI is also showing an upward trend and is approaching the 50% threshold, indicating a potential pullback toward the 50-day moving average or perhaps even another retest of the $30K resistance level in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that the latter scenario would likely invalidate the former, and a bullish breakout above the $30K level would then be more likely in this case.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251956" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251956" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251956 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2305231" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-23-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251956" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The 4-hour chart presents an intriguing situation. Currently, the price is undergoing a retest of both the $27,500 level and the upper boundary of a small bearish flag. If it faces another rejection, there is a strong likelihood of a decline towards the lower boundary of a larger channel and the $25K support level.</p>
<p>On the contrary, a breakout above this area would potentially result in a push out of the larger channel, followed by a subsequent retest of the $30K level in the near future.</p>
<p>Additionally, the RSI on this timeframe indicates bullish momentum with values above 50%, further enhancing the likelihood of the bullish scenario unfolding.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251955" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251955" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251955 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_chart_2305232" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-23-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251955" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>The graph below illustrates the Bitcoin Active Addresses metric, a 30-day moving average, alongside the BTC price since the bear market of 2017. This metric serves as an indicator of market demand. During bull runs, the demand for Bitcoin rises, leading to an increase in active addresses. Conversely, during bearish market phases, interest in the industry wanes, resulting in a decline in the active addresses metric.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s recent behavior resembles its price action at the beginning of the 2019 bull market. However, after a period of consolidation, the metric began an upward trend simultaneously with a bullish mid-term rally in price, indicating growing demand for Bitcoin. This phase can be referred to as the early stage of the 2019 bull run, preceding the main stage in which active addresses experienced a sustained surge.</p>
<p>A similar pattern is unfolding currently as the metric continues to soar alongside Bitcoin&#8217;s upward movement. Based on the graph, it can be inferred that Bitcoin is potentially entering the early stage of its next bull run. Nevertheless, remaining aware of market risks and volatility during these periods is crucial.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251954" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251954" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251954 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_active_adresses_chart_2305231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251954" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-are-the-critical-levels-for-btc-in-the-immediate-term-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">These Are the Critical Levels for BTC in the Immediate Term (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is the Dogecoin Price Dead? AiDoge Meme Coin Raises $12 Million, Ecoterra $4 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-the-dogecoin-price-dead-aidoge-meme-coin-raises-12-million-ecoterra-4-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251977</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGE-dead-CryptoPotato-1200x780-1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGE-dead-CryptoPotato-1200x780-1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the crypto market continues to exhibit high levels of volatility, the stagnant performance of Dogecoin ($DOGE) has left some investors wondering if the coin’s glory days are behind it. The $DOGE price continues to be trapped below the $0.075 level – and hasn&#8217;t shown any significant bullish momentum since mid-April. Meanwhile, new market entrants [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the crypto market continues to exhibit high levels of volatility, the stagnant performance of Dogecoin ($DOGE) has left some investors wondering if the coin’s glory days are behind it.</p>
<p>The $DOGE price continues to be trapped below the $0.075 level – and hasn&#8217;t shown any significant bullish momentum since mid-April.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, new market entrants <a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AiDoge ($AI)</a> and <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra ($ECOTERRA)</a> are attracting substantial attention and funding – suggesting they could be the next captivating prospects for investors to monitor.</p>
<h2><strong>Dogecoin Continues to Trade Sideways – Is a Price Drop Imminent?</strong></h2>
<p>Despite retaining its status as the world&#8217;s largest meme coin, according to<a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/memes/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> CoinMarketCap</a>, Dogecoin hasn’t been immune to the bearish investor sentiment over the past month.</p>
<p>Following an impressive 18% price surge in mid-April, $DOGE has been on a sustained downtrend and now trades 23% lower than those highs.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, $DOGE is hovering around the $0.075 region, which acted as resistance over the past two weeks.</p>
<p>Adding to the concerns of Dogecoin holders is the current stagnant state of the token&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>The days of substantial bullish or bearish swings on the daily timeframe seem to be a thing of the past, as they are now replaced by minor fluctuations – an indication of diminished trading volume.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251979" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="268" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This development might shock many in the crypto community, given that<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> CoinGecko</a> reports that 80% of users still &#8220;feel good&#8221; about Dogecoin&#8217;s prospects.</p>
<p>Despite this positive sentiment, it hasn’t translated into price gains – and it looks like the only way is down for $DOGE.</p>
<p>Looking at the price chart, a worrying sign is emerging for $DOGE bulls – a bear flag on the daily timeframe. This pattern usually forms immediately before a sharp drop, reminiscent of the situation in late April.</p>
<p>If $DOGE were to break to the downside, the likely target would be $0.065, a level that held as support on March 10. This would represent an 11.37% drop from today&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Adding more confluence to the bear hypothesis is that $DOGE now trades comfortably below the 20-day and 50-day EMAs – suggesting that Dogecoin fans may be in for a challenging few weeks ahead.</p>
<h2><strong>AiDoge&#8217;s Presale Makes Waves with a Whopping $12 Million Raised</strong></h2>
<p>As the bearish signs around Dogecoin show no signs of abating, a fresh and innovative player is emerging on the horizon.</p>
<p>This player is <a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AiDoge ($AI)</a> – a new meme coin that fuses artificial intelligence with the viral appeal of meme culture.</p>
<p>In an impressive feat of early-stage success, AiDoge has raised a staggering $12 million during its presale phase – catching the attention of both investors and the wider crypto community.</p>
<p>This significant fundraising milestone speaks volumes about AiDoge’s potential and underscores the rapid growth of the project’s community – as evidenced by over 18,400 people joining the official<a href="https://t.me/AiDogeCryptoOfficial" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p>Much of the buzz around AiDoge is driven by the project&#8217;s unique use cases, which dovetail effectively with its meme-style design.</p>
<p>As outlined in AiDoge&#8217;s whitepaper, the flagship use cases will be the trailblazing &#8220;meme generator,&#8221; built on the Ethereum blockchain. Using this generator, users can easily create hilarious memes using text-based prompts – mirroring the approach used by ChatGPT.</p>
<p>AiDoge&#8217;s meme generator will be trained on massive datasets and leverage advanced artificial intelligence algorithms to ensure all created images are viral-ready.</p>
<p>If that wasn&#8217;t enough, users can earn $AI, AiDoge&#8217;s native ERC-20 token, by uploading their created memes to the &#8220;public wall,&#8221; where other community members can upvote or downvote them.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, AiDoge is in Stage 17 of its 20-stage presale, meaning would-be investors only have a limited time remaining to purchase $AI tokens at a discount relative to the planned exchange listing price.</p>
<p>Ultimately, as AiDoge prepares to transition out of this presale phase, it appears that the project&#8217;s groundbreaking setup has caught the crypto community&#8217;s attention – making it an exciting time to be an $AI holder.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2><strong>Investor Enthusiasm Surges for Green Crypto Ecoterra, Raising Over $4 Million</strong></h2>
<p>Another cryptocurrency that’s making waves while Dogecoin struggles is Ecoterra ($ECOTERRA).</p>
<p>Unlike Dogecoin and AiDoge, Ecoterra isn’t a meme coin. Instead, it’s an Ethereum-based ecosystem where users can earn rewards for taking decisive action in the fight against climate change.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra’s presale</a> phase has been a resounding success since it commenced and has just breached the $4 million milestone during Stage 7.</p>
<p>This presale is nearing its conclusion, with only two stages remaining before the $ECOTERRA token is listed on crypto exchanges for $0.01.</p>
<p>Ecoterra&#8217;s pioneering &#8220;Recycle2Earn&#8221; app is the key driver of token demand. According to the project&#8217;s whitepaper, this app will reward users with $ECOTERRA tokens whenever they recycle using a Reverse Vending Machine (RVM).</p>
<p>Naturally, this incentivizes users to recycle more and contribute to environmental sustainability.</p>
<p>Additionally, Ecoterra’s ecosystem will also feature a carbon offset marketplace, a recycled materials marketplace, and even an “Impact Profile.” The latter feature will allow individuals and businesses to publicly showcase their commitment to eco-friendly practices.</p>
<p>Due to Ecoterra’s holistic approach, the project is expected to play an important role in the global effort to counter climate change in the coming years.</p>
<p>This gives investors a unique opportunity to be involved at the ground level – making it a compelling investment proposition for those who want to add an eco-friendly twist to their crypto portfolios.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-the-dogecoin-price-dead-aidoge-meme-coin-raises-12-million-ecoterra-4-million/" rel="nofollow">Is the Dogecoin Price Dead? AiDoge Meme Coin Raises $12 Million, Ecoterra $4 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ScalingX’s The Hunt For X Demo Day: A Resounding Success</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/scalingxs-the-hunt-for-x-demo-day-a-resounding-success/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251948</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] ScalingX, in partnership with distinguished sponsors ARPA and AELF, has concluded its highly successful and impactful event, The Hunt For X Demo Day. This exclusive event brought together visionary developers and innovators, providing them with a unique platform to delve into the boundless possibilities of Zero-Knowledge Proofing (ZKP) technology [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://scalingx.xyz/#/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ScalingX</a>, in partnership with distinguished sponsors <a href="https://www.arpanetwork.io/en-US" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ARPA</a> and <a href="https://aelf.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AELF</a>, has concluded its highly successful and impactful event, The Hunt For X Demo Day. This exclusive event brought together visionary developers and innovators, providing them with a unique platform to delve into the boundless possibilities of Zero-Knowledge Proofing (ZKP) technology and Random Number Generation (RNG) as groundbreaking solutions for scaling blockchain networks. The event not only fostered exploration but also extended crucial support and momentum to the ongoing development efforts in this dynamic field.</p>
<p>Advancing Web3 innovation and development necessitates an organized endeavor to foster and attract top talent while mobilizing resources and infrastructure for sustained growth and success in this ever-evolving industry. Hence, the ZK hackathon showcased various challenges that aimed to explore diverse facets of ZKP technology and its applications in the Web3 ecosystem. Participants had the chance to demonstrate their abilities and make meaningful contributions to the development of privacy-centric technologies in the blockchain space.</p>
<p>The Hunt For X Demo Day gathered various venture capital firms like LongHash Ventures, OP Crypto, Waterdrip Capital, M-Ventures, Sharding Capital, Fracton Ventures, Web3.com Ventures, and Temasek-backed Superscrypt. Additionally, prominent media outlets like PANews, Techub.news, Coinlive, and several developer communities also joined us for the event. Among the 77 remarkable projects that submitted applications, 15 were chosen to participate in the Demo Day.</p>
<p>Here is a compilation of 15 exceptional projects, presented in random order, that exhibit excellent quality.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251951" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX2.jpg" alt="ScalingX2" width="670" height="2048" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX2.jpg 670w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX2-98x300.jpg 98w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX2-335x1024.jpg 335w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ScalingX2-16x50.jpg 16w" sizes="(max-width: 670px) 100vw, 670px" /></a></p>
<p>Should you express interest in any of the featured projects and desire to learn more about them, we encourage you to check out the Demo Day recap on ScalingX’s Official Youtube channel.</p>
<p>Once again, ScalingX would like to express sincere congratulations to all the projects that were chosen to participate in the Demo Day, as well as the esteemed judges and mentors for their invaluable contributions. The triumph of &#8220;The Hunt for X&#8221; ZK Hackathon on the Buidlbox platform underscores the increasing significance and interest in ZKP technology within the Web3 ecosystem. ScalingX is steadfast in its dedication to nurturing the adoption and advancement of this technology.</p>
<h2>About ScalingX</h2>
<p>ScalingX is a global accelerator across Singapore, Hong Kong and San Francisco dedicated to the development of Web3 and blockchain technologies, with a focus on Zero-Knowledge Proof (ZKP) technology. Our goal is to advance the adoption of blockchain technology around the world through investments. We support early-stage Web3 startups by helping them with talent recruitment, networking, fundraising, project incubation, PR and branding, community building, and more. We are fully committed to building a more scalable, transparent, secure, and decentralized network of tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/scalingxs-the-hunt-for-x-demo-day-a-resounding-success/" rel="nofollow">ScalingX’s The Hunt For X Demo Day: A Resounding Success</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
