<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:33:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SEC Targets Crypto Auditors Seeking Greater Scrutiny</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-targets-crypto-auditors-seeking-greater-scrutiny/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229967</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/TheSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/TheSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In its ongoing war against crypto, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has now turned its sights on auditing firms and their reports.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC is stepping up its scrutiny of crypto auditors as it continues to wage war against the digital asset industry.</p>
<p>In the latest in a recent torrent of anti-crypto articles, the Wall Street Journal has <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-heightening-scrutiny-of-auditors-crypto-work-11671681693" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reported</a> that there will be more dissection of the work that audit firms are doing for crypto companies.</p>
<p>According to the financial regulator, there is concern that investors may be getting a false sense of security from these crypto audits. Paul Munter, the SEC’s acting chief accountant, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re warning investors to be very wary of some of the claims that are being made by crypto companies.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The SEC has long claimed to be operating in the interests of investors, but its effort to crack down on the crypto industry by enforcement appears to be doing more harm than good. Munter even alluded to this, adding, “If we find fact patterns that we think are troublesome, we will consider a referral to the division of enforcement.”</p>
<h2>SEC: Don’t Trust The Audits</h2>
<p>Furthermore, many crypto companies are based offshore, so do not come under the SEC’s jurisdiction. However, they are still keen to provide audits and proof of reserves to settle jittery customers and investors.</p>
<p>Last week the auditing firm Mazars that reported on Binance’s reserves <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-and-crypto-com-auditor-mazars-group-pauzes-work-with-crypto-clients/" data-wpel-link="internal">paused all further work</a> for crypto clients, citing increased scrutiny.</p>
<p>Earlier this week, Binance.US chief Brian Shroder <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/if-people-withdrew-everything-from-binance-us-we-would-still-have-millions-in-assets-ceo-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">assured customers</a> that his exchange is prepared to process every last withdrawal and that assets are fully backed.</p>
<p>The SEC has become concerned about these proof of reserve reports as many are lacking in additional financial details, the report added. The SEC lawyer continued to advise investors not to pay too much attention to these audits:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Investors should not place too much confidence in the mere fact a company says it’s got a proof of reserves from an audit firm.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In late November, auditing firms <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/auditing-firms-elevate-crypto-clients-to-high-risk-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">elevated crypto clients</a> to high risk following the collapse of FTX.</p>
<h2>No Winning With The SEC</h2>
<p>It seems that crypto companies can’t win when it comes to American regulators. They get jumped on for not being audited, and they get jumped on again when they produce proof of reserve reports.</p>
<p>It is unlikely the SEC will quit until the industry is quashed or converted into traditional finance and banking.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-targets-crypto-auditors-seeking-greater-scrutiny/" rel="nofollow">SEC Targets Crypto Auditors Seeking Greater Scrutiny</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter Integrates Live Market Charts for Bitcoin and Ether</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-integrates-live-market-charts-for-bitcoin-and-ether/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229804</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Twitter_BlueSky.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Twitter_BlueSky.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Twitter users can now check the prices of bitcoin and ether by typing BTC or ETH on the platform's search tab.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Twitter introduced a new cryptocurrency feature on its platform that allows users to check the current price of bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The graphics display the logo of the market tracking site Trading View and a link directing to Robinhood. It remains unknown whether those two were somehow involved with the new feature.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Twitter&#8217;s Latest Crypto Move</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Users of the social media platform can now track the USD valuation of the two largest cryptocurrencies by market cap &#8211; bitcoin and ether &#8211; by typing the assets&#8217; names or their tickers on the search tap. The </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/TwitterBusiness/status/1605651865818914816" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">feature</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> also shows their fluctuations compared to the previous day.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The price charts are an addition to the existing &#8220;$Cashtags&#8221; option that displays the prices of numerous ETFs or leading stocks. Twitter&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Elon Musk &#8211; praised his team for designing the integration.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">One of many product improvements coming to financial Twitter!</p>
<p>Nice work by Twitter team. <a href="https://t.co/CKLH8OtDDW" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/CKLH8OtDDW</a></p>
<p>— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1605738005813084165?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 22, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While bitcoin and ether are the only supported digital currencies as of the moment, Twitter plans to &#8220;refine&#8221; its user experience and include additional assets in the &#8220;coming weeks.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The price graphics show Trading View&#8217;s logo and direct to a Robinhood link, suggesting that the social media giant could have partnered with those organizations. None of them have confirmed such collaboration yet. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A New CEO Coming?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the improvements and amendments, many users seem to oppose the new way Twitter has been managed. Roughly 10 million people voted for Elon Musk to step down from the role of a CEO in a recent poll that he initiated. Around 7.5 million wished he could stay in charge of the platform.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entrepreneur <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-is-looking-for-a-new-foolish-enough-twitter-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> he will abide by the results and look for &#8220;someone foolish enough&#8221; to swap him at the helm. Once appointing a new chief executive, Musk plans to manage software and server teams within Twitter. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Several prominent individuals, including Binance&#8217;s boss &#8211; Changpeng Zhao &#8211; insisted the South African is the best fit for the role. The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange has previously financially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-binance-invested-500-million-in-elon-musks-twitter-deal/" data-wpel-link="internal">backed</a> Musk&#8217;s multi-billion acquisition of Twitter, believing that Tesla&#8217;s CEO could eliminate bots and spam comments on the platform.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-integrates-live-market-charts-for-bitcoin-and-ether/" rel="nofollow">Twitter Integrates Live Market Charts for Bitcoin and Ether</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Completed the Blockfolio Deal Mainly in FTT Tokens: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-completed-the-blockfolio-deal-mainly-in-ftt-tokens-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 23:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229857</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/blockfolio_ftx_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/blockfolio_ftx_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FTX has supposedly financed 94% of its Blockfolio acquisition deal in FTT tokens.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX reportedly paid 94% of the $84 million purchase of a majority stake in Blockfolio in FTT tokens. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The coin played a leading role in the platform&#8217;s crash last month. CZ said Binance plans to dump its entire FTT stash (23 million tokens worth over $580 million at the time) amid rising worries about the over-exposure of FTX and Alameda towards the former&#8217;s native asset.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">New Data on the Blockfolio Deal</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a recent Bloomberg </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/ftx-paid-for-blockfolio-deal-mostly-in-ftt-token-it-invented-1.1862375" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, FTX acquired a majority stake in the trading platform Blockfolio in 2020 using almost entirely FTT tokens (the native asset of the bankrupt exchange). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sources previously disclosed that the former crypto behemoth financed the agreement with a mixture of digital currencies, cash, and equities, without providing accurate information. Initial reports suggested FTX </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-derivatives-exchange-ftx-acquires-blockfolio-for-150-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">spent</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $150 million to finalize the deal.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Established in 2014, Blockfolio became one of the leading firms in its field, amassing nearly six million customers in the following years. It shook hands with the notorious FTX to add a retail trading experience for its users and later took the name of the exchange.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For its part, the platform&#8217;s native token was in the spotlight last month after Binance </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftt-drops-10-after-binance-dumps-its-entire-stash-of-23-million-ftx-tokens/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> it will sell </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">its entire FTT holdings (worth $584 million at the beginning of November). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The move triggered a wave of customer withdrawals and FTX could not honor those requests. The exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-alameda-file-for-bankruptcy-sbf-resigns-as-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for bankruptcy protection several days later, owing billions of dollars to investors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The negative event had a devastating effect on FTT&#8217;s price. The token is currently trading at around $0.87 (nearly 99% down compared to its peak in September 2021).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC Views FTT as Security</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sec.gov/litigation/complaints/2022/comp-pr2022-234.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that FTT should be considered an &#8220;illiquid crypto asset security that was issued by FTX and provided to Alameda at no cost.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency further maintained that the bankrupt exchange had used profits from the asset&#8217;s sale to boost the development, business operations, and marketing of its brand. At the same time, it lured consumers that its token is an &#8220;investment&#8221; with great potential.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The FTT materials made clear that FTX&#8217;s core management team&#8217;s efforts would drive the growth and ultimate </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">success of FTX. The whitepaper also advertised that certain features gave FTX an advantage over competing platforms, including industry-leading risk management systems and its liquidation engine model,&#8221; the Commission stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SEC Chairman Gary Gensler has previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chairman-is-only-willing-to-call-bitcoin-a-commodity/" data-wpel-link="internal">outlined</a> that bitcoin is the only cryptocurrency that could classify as a commodity. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-completed-the-blockfolio-deal-mainly-in-ftt-tokens-report/" rel="nofollow">FTX Completed the Blockfolio Deal Mainly in FTT Tokens: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Things to Watch to Identify Bitcoin&#8217;s Breaking Point: DataDash</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3-things-to-watch-to-identify-bitcoins-breaking-point-datadash/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 22:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229950</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/bitcoin_chop_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/bitcoin_chop_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's 200 DMA and WMA show worrying signs for bulls, according to a veteran analyst.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">DataDash founder a veteran crypto analyst Nicholas Merten predicts more pain ahead for Bitcoin’s price based on a combination of technical indicators and macroeconomic pressures. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The analyst referenced price charts for three different assets to back up his claim: BTC, ETH, and AAPL. </span></p>
<h2>Where Bitcoin’s Price Will Crumble</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a video </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cu1RaRjThLY&amp;ab_channel=DataDash" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">published</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Wednesday, Merten began by pointing out how Bitcoin remains suspended well below its 200-week moving averages (WMA) and 200-day moving averages (DMA). The former has historically been a long-standing price floor for Bitcoin but flipped from a line of support into resistance for the first time ever in 2022. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The fact that we are well suspended and not even coming up to re-test those 200 day, as well as the 200 week [averages], is a big worrying sign,” said Merten. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Secondly, the relief rallies Bitcoin has managed to muster from its new lows throughout 2022 have “continued to get weaker and weaker.” This indicates that Bitcoin bulls “aren’t showing up to the plate” as they once did, which could signal a major capitulation wave to come. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Market order flow has also been negative week after week – meaning traders are continuing to sell and “take the best available price.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The industry is going through its biggest restructuring since the Mt. Gox hack back in 2014 and 2015,” said Merten. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As for Bitcoin’s “breaking point,” the analyst suggested that the asset could experience a “major capitulation event” if its price plummets below its 2022 low of around $15,600.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ethereum, he said, is also still at “highly suspended levels.” Merten predicted that a break on its 200 DMA against Bitcoin could place a “50% correction in the cards.”</span></p>
<h2>The Macro Picture</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Moving into the broader equities market, Merten highlighted the monthly chart for Apple stock, where he identified signs of fading momentum from its years-long uptrend. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Like Bitcoin, the chart’s 200 DMA and WMA both show signs of a bearish reversal. Merten suggested that Apple, alongside other major tech companies like Amazon, could possibly deviate below their 200 WMAs for the first time since the dot com bubble.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Macroeconomic pressures from rising interest rates have helped culminate in the failures of multiple crypto companies in 2022, as Bitcoin’s price fell over 75% from its highs in November 2021. With the fall of </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Sam Bankman-Fried</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">’s FTX empire, Merten expects that more companies are yet to “unravel” with “uncertainty” already growing around </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/analyst-confirms-gbtcs-633k-bitcoin-claim-despite-grayscales-reluctance-to-share-proof-of-reserves/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Grayscale</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, CryptoCom, and Binance. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“While I’m not here to spew unnecessary FUD… there are still things being unraveled,” he said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-things-to-watch-to-identify-bitcoins-breaking-point-datadash/" rel="nofollow">3 Things to Watch to Identify Bitcoin&#8217;s Breaking Point: DataDash</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter McCormack Vs Craig Wright: CSW Has Not Established He is Satoshi</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/peter-mccormack-vs-craig-wright-csw-has-not-established-he-is-satoshi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin SV (BSV) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Craig Wright]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229815</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/CraigWright.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/CraigWright.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The judgment clarifies Craig Wright has not established that he is the inventor of Bitcoin - Satoshi Nakamoto. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the final trial between Bitcoin proponent Peter McCormack and computer scientist Craig Steven Wright (CSW), UK High Court Judge Martin Chamberlain ruled that the former should pay a fine of $1.1 million.</p>
<p>According to the court <a href="https://www.judiciary.uk/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Wright-v-McCormack-Final-Judgment-for-Hand-Down.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">document</a>, McCormack failed to prove that he was telling the truth when he labeled Wright a fraud. However, Judge Chamberlain said that the legal proceedings have not established that Wright is Satoshi.</p>
<ul>
<li>The scientist then contested that McCormack should pay the majority of the costs for legal proceedings but finally agreed to the settlement mentioned above.</li>
<li>The judge did not grant Wright&#8217;s request for an injunction against McCormack repeating these claims. His permission to appeal the decision was also refused.</li>
<li>Shedding light on the final judgment in the case, McCormack <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterMcCormack/status/1605579038369538049" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweeted</a>,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The final judgment in my case against CSW has been handed down. It is not a very good judgment for Craig but ultimately a very expensive one for me. The stress of the last four years can&#8217;t be understated, it has had a significant impact on me and my family.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The development comes four months after Wright was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/craig-wright-awarded-1-for-the-defamation-lawsuit-against-peter-mccormack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">awarded</a> £1 in damages against McCormack. The former was found to have put forward &#8220;false evidence.&#8221;</li>
<li>The legal battle stemmed from a 2019 discussion broadcasted on YouTube which shows McCormack calling Wright a liar and a fraud and dismissing his claims of being Satoshi.</li>
<li>The BSV creator, on the other hand, reciprocated with a lawsuit claiming that such publications were defamatory and caused him financial damage after his invitation to speak at various events and conferences was withdrawn.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-mccormack-vs-craig-wright-csw-has-not-established-he-is-satoshi/" rel="nofollow">Peter McCormack Vs Craig Wright: CSW Has Not Established He is Satoshi</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Released on a $250M Bail, Can Stay at Parents&#8217; House</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 19:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229934</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_img.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_img.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The former FTX CEO can stay at his parents' home in California. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried is to be released on bail, as ruled by a New York federal judge on Wednesday.</p>
<p>The bail deal, as orchestrated by federal prosecutors and Bankman Fried’s defense attorneys, will see the former billionaire post a $250 million bond and be required to stay at his parents’ home in Palo Alto, California.</p>
<h2><strong>No Prison for SBF?</strong></h2>
<p>According to Assistant U.S. Attorney Nicolas Roos, Bankman-Fried was responsible for perpetrating a “fraud of epic proportions.” However, he chose to allow for bail given that Bankman-Fried opted to waive extradition.</p>
<p>The bail terms are strict. Besides his monetary penalty, Bankman-Fried will have to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/22/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-to-be-released-on-250-million-bail.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wear</a> an electronic monitoring bracelet, and be disallowed from leaving th Northern District of California. Judge Gabriel Gorenstein added that Bankman-Fried would require “strict” supervision during his stay.</p>
<p>He will also have to submit to mental health counseling. The ex-CEO has previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-sam-bankman-fried-planned-to-tell-congress-about-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">claimed</a> to be depressed and “sad” for an extended period of time and required medication to cope.</p>
<p>The $250 million payment, which prosecutors call the “largest ever pretrial bond, is a big step up from the $100,000 Bankman-Fried claimed he&#8217;d had left in his account in November. On the other hand, it pales in comparison to the $10 billion shortfall his company had on customer deposits last month, which ultimately drove it to bankruptcy.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried’s parents, both of whom are Stanford law professors, were present in the courtroom on Thursday. They will be required to post equity in their home for partial satisfaction of bail conditions.</p>
<p>Finally, the former FTX boss will be prevented from taking out any new lines of credit while he awaits trial.</p>
<h2><strong>FTX Executives Plead Guilty</strong></h2>
<p>On Thursday, FTX co-founder Gary Wang and Alameda Research former CEO Caroline Ellison pled guilty to various forms of fraud, including securities fraud and money laundering, as part of a multi-year scheme involving Sam Bankman-Fried. Reports suggest they each face 50 years and 110 years in prison, respectively.</p>
<p>Gary Wang reportedely engineered a backdoor into FTX’s accounting system that allowed FTX to siphon money off to Alameda. FTX’s bankruptcy lawyer, John Ray, later confirmed that Alemeda used FTX clients’ funds for margin trading, and lost tremendous money in the process.</p>
<p>The trading desk was also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alameda-secretly-exempted-from-ftxs-auto-liquidation-engine-court-filing/" data-wpel-link="internal">exempt</a> from FTX’s auto-liquidation engine – a trading advantage Bitcoin billionaire Michael Saylor <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-the-most-diabolical-thing-about-ftx-and-sbf-according-to-michael-saylor/" data-wpel-link="internal">referred to</a> as “god mode.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" rel="nofollow">Sam Bankman-Fried Released on a $250M Bail, Can Stay at Parents&#8217; House</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazilian President Signs Off on National Crypto Rules</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/brazilian-president-signs-off-on-national-crypto-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229927</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/brazil.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/brazil.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto firms have 180 days to adapt to the new regulations. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">President Jair Bolsonaro of Brazil has approved a bill of crypto industry regulations most recently passed by the nation’s Senate and Chamber of Deputies.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The bill, signed into law on Thursday, will take effect in 180 days, by which time crypto companies in the region must adapt to the new rules. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Having </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazils-parliament-passes-bill-for-greater-crypto-regulation-what-does-it-mean/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">passed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> through Parliament in late November, the bill would make it possible for crypto firms to register in the country and establish physical offices. These include firms that offer crypto financing services or those that allow for the conversion of crypto assets into national currencies. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">It also paves the way for a new federal agency that will regulate digital asset firms and establishes a “virtual service provider” license. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Under the law, digital assets deemed to be securities will be overseen by the Brazilian Securities and Exchange Commission, while others will be regulated by an entity yet to be established. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Similar laws are being fast-tracked and pushed in several jurisdictions after FTX’s implosion last month. Indonesia is </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indonesia-plans-to-tighten-crypto-regulation-following-ftxs-insolvency/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">grappling</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with a similar bill that would move regulation of the industry to the Financial Services Authority, and away from the Commodity Futures Trading Regulatory Agency.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Canada’s Securities Administrators established rules last week </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-securities-regulators-ban-crypto-margin-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">banning</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the provision of cryptocurrency margin trading to Canadian clients. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazilian-president-signs-off-on-national-crypto-rules/" rel="nofollow">Brazilian President Signs Off on National Crypto Rules</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guggenheim CIO Scott Minerd Dies Suddenly: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/guggenheim-cio-scott-minerd-dies-suddenly-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229920</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/ScottMinerd-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/ScottMinerd-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The investment officer and commentator experienced a heart attack during one of his regular workouts. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Scott Minerd – Chief Investment Officer of global investment firm Guggenheim Partners – passed away on the morning of December 22 due to a heart attack. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/guggenheim-partners-announces-the-untimely-and-unexpected-death-of-scott-minerd-301709159.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Guggenheim on Thursday, Minerd’s “untimely” and “unexpected” heart attack occurred during one of his regular workouts.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the statement, Minerd joined Guggenheim as a Managing Partner shortly after the company was formed. He was a frequent market commentator on both television and social media. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">“I have known Scott for over 30 years and we were partners much of that time,” said Mark Walter, CEO and a Founder of Guggenheim Partners, on Minerd&#8217;s passing. “Scott was a key innovator and thought leader who was instrumental in building Guggenheim Investments into the global business it is today. &#8221; </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“He will be greatly missed by all. My deepest condolences are with his husband, family and loved ones,&#8221; he continued. </span></p></blockquote>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Minerd also offered frequent commentary on the crypto markets. Last week, he </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-contagion-is-not-over-yet-guggenheims-scott-minerd-warns/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">predicted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the fallout from FTX’s collapse is not yet over and that there will be a “washout” similar to the internet bubble. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In July, Minerd called for Bitcoin to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/guggenheims-scott-minerd-predicts-that-btc-could-drop-to-15k/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">drop</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> as low as $15,000, which proved true in November. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/guggenheim-cio-scott-minerd-dies-suddenly-report/" rel="nofollow">Guggenheim CIO Scott Minerd Dies Suddenly: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Hard-Stuck Below $17K But Market Sentiment Healing (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-hard-stuck-below-17k-but-market-sentiment-healing-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229876</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is grappling with a crucial resistance level at roughly $17K, which also aligns with the 100-day moving average. A breakout from here will potentially initiate an uptrend in the short term. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart The price has been trapped inside a descending wedge pattern for several months and is consolidating [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is grappling with a crucial resistance level at roughly $17K, which also aligns with the 100-day moving average. A breakout from here will potentially initiate an uptrend in the short term.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The price has been trapped inside a descending wedge pattern for several months and is consolidating with significantly lower volatility. Meanwhile, the 100-day moving average has served as a powerful barrier at around $17K.</p>
<p>The current action demonstrates a concerning lack of activity in Bitcoin’s market, which can be explained by recent events, which resulted in a lack of demand.</p>
<p>Considering the current market sentiment, it appears that one of the more probable outlooks for Bitcoin is to continue consolidating between the two substantial levels of $15K and $19K until a breakout occurs.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229878" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229878" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229878 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large.jpeg" alt="btc_price_chart_221201" width="1280" height="791" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large.jpeg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large-300x185.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large-1024x633.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large-768x475.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-1D-Large-50x31.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229878" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>In the 4-hour timeframe, the price has finally dropped below the ascending flag pattern. As is evident in the chart, the 0.5 level of Fibonacci retracement has acted as a great resistance and pushed the price towards the $15K support.</p>
<p>BTC seems likely to retest the flag’s lower boundary and complete the pullback pattern before the next downward rally.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the RSI indicator is currently standing at almost 50, indicating equilibrium has currently been reached.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229879" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229879" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229879 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large.jpeg" alt="btc_price_chart_221202" width="1280" height="791" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large.jpeg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large-300x185.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large-1024x633.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large-768x475.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Btc-4H-Large-50x31.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229879" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>All on-chain valuation indicators conclude that Bitcoin is significantly undervalued. However, it is essential for whales to start accumulating again in order for the cryptocurrency to bottom out successfully.</p>
<p>Whales have continued to reduce spending, which is now at the lowest level since before Terra and Luna&#8217;s failure. The short-term local resistance for Bitcoin is the 1m-3m holder realized price, which is currently at $18.4k. In fact, this level has acted as a barrier during the market&#8217;s recent low-momentum rally.</p>
<p>Finally, based on the following graph, compared to the COVID and China-ban crashes, the funding rates metric seems to have rebounded much faster. It illustrates that the market sentiment is healing.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229880" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229880" style="width: 2514px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229880 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307.jpg" alt="btc_funding_rates_221201" width="2514" height="1583" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307.jpg 2514w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/IMG_0307-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2514px) 100vw, 2514px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229880" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-hard-stuck-below-17k-but-market-sentiment-healing-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Hard-Stuck Below $17K But Market Sentiment Healing (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Plunges 11% Weekly, is $0.30 The Next Target for the Bears? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-plunges-11-weekly-is-0-30-the-next-target-for-the-bears-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229883</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple has spent the week in a tight trading range, but there is no question that the bear market rages on. The price action seems relatively quiet following the large drop XRP experienced last week. Technical Analysis By Grizzly The Daily Chart On the daily chart, the price is close to the November low. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple has spent the week in a tight trading range, but there is no question that the bear market rages on. The price action seems relatively quiet following the large drop XRP experienced last week.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/GrizzlyBTClover" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Grizzly</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price is close to the November low. The range of $0.3 to $0.32 (in white) is currently regarded as the level of block orders, providing solid support.</p>
<p>The 50% and 61.8% Fib levels in the $0.42 to $0.45 resistance region, which were challenged in late November, are on the upswing once more.</p>
<p>Given that the overall structure is negative, the asset must climb over $0.45 to initiate a sustained rally. If it happens, the bearish momentum will weaken in the short term, and the cryptocurrency will be ready to test the long-term resistance at $0.55.</p>
<p>Alternatively, if the price slips below $0.3, it would become much more likely for the steep bear market to continue.</p>
<p><strong>Moving Averages:<br />
</strong>MA20: $0.37<br />
MA50: $0.39<br />
MA100: $0.42<br />
MA200: $0.38</p>
<figure id="attachment_229885" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229885" style="width: 2450px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229885 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min.png" alt="xrp_price_chart_221201" width="2450" height="1239" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min.png 2450w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min-300x152.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min-1024x518.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min-768x388.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min-1536x777.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min-2048x1036.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-22nd-Dec-min-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2450px) 100vw, 2450px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229885" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The XRP/BTC Chart</h3>
<p>Against Bitcoin, the pair is attempting to maintain its position above the ascending line of support (in green). It is now critical not to create a lower low as the price goes below 2200 SATs (in white).</p>
<p>If the pair closes below 1950 SATs (in yellow), the bullish trend will reverse. The horizontal support at 1800 SATs will likely be tested in this situation.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support Levels:</strong> 1950 SATS, 1800 SATs<br />
<strong>Key Resistance Levels:</strong> 2200 SATs, 2500 SATs</p>
<figure id="attachment_229884" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229884" style="width: 2450px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229884 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min.png" alt="xrp_price_chart_221202" width="2450" height="1235" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min.png 2450w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min-300x151.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min-1024x516.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min-768x387.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min-1536x774.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min-2048x1032.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPBTC-22nd-Dec-min-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2450px) 100vw, 2450px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229884" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-plunges-11-weekly-is-0-30-the-next-target-for-the-bears-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Plunges 11% Weekly, is $0.30 The Next Target for the Bears? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
