<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Here is Uniswap&#8217;s Biggest Competitor According to Messari</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-uniswaps-biggest-competitor-according-to-messari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 20:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232070</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The report also states that Uniswap is the "final DeFi Unicorn." ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hayden Adams, the Uniswap creator, was just a 23-year-old native of the suburbs of New York in 2017 when he was laid off from his role as an engineer at Siemens.</p>
<p>Adams began by writing an application from scratch, and his friend <a href="https://uniswap.org/blog/uniswap-history" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">built</a> a sleek new interface for Uniswap on top of what he describes as an &#8220;incredibly shitty&#8221; React codebase.</p>
<p>Fast forward five years, and Uniswap has still managed to retain its position as a DEX leader.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-232169" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover.jpg" alt="unicron_uniswap_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/unicron_uniswap_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Uniswap&#8217;s Continued Dominance</h2>
<p>According to Messari&#8217;s new <a href="https://messari.io/crypto-theses-for-2023/thanks?__s=4re00jujkosdjjimy8ri" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> titled &#8220;Crypto Thesis for 2023, Uniswap&#8217;s V3 iteration has proven to be a &#8220;true 10x improvement&#8221; in terms of the working capital the decentralized exchanges require to run &#8220;reliable and low-slippage&#8221; operations.</p>
<p>The existing automated market makers (AMMs) have failed to overcome several challenges. For instance, PankcakeSwap&#8217;s transaction settlement is deemed to be fairly centralized and relies on a close relationship with popular CEX &#8211; Binance. Additionally, Terra&#8217;s collapse hit Osmosis hard, while FTX&#8217;s self-immolation killed Serum.</p>
<p>With AMM DEXs busy confronting their own unique challenges, Messari&#8217;s report states that dethroning Uniswap with tokenomic tricks or marginal price improvements may not transpire anytime soon. Ryan Selkis, the founder of the market intelligence company, believes that Uniswap could be an &#8220;unassailable protocol&#8221; in the AMM<br />
category.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;You don’t compete on fees, you compete on value, and Uniswap has proven that Uniswap is Uniswap’s biggest competitor when it comes to creating incremental value for its users. The only question I have for 2023 is how the community will design and implement the protocol’s fee switch, in which UNI token holders will vote to (finally) direct a portion of protocol trading fees to the treasury.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2022, Uniswap <a href="https://uniswap.org/blog/bringing-web3-to-everyone" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">raised</a> $165 million in a Series B round at a $1.7 billion valuation. The DEX became a unicorn after garnering backing from Polychain Capital, including Andreessen Horowitz, Paradigm, SV Angel, and Variant Fund. The same year, its venture capital arm entered the NFT space and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-labs-taps-fiat-space-with-moonpay-partnership/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> a partnership with crypto payments processor MoonPay as it ramped up its game with new fiat integration.</p>
<h2>Largest Gas Guzzler</h2>
<p>Uniswap V3 went on to become the most popular Ethereum contract in 2022, ranking first with respect to total gas used throughout the year. <a href="https://twitter.com/haydenzadams/status/1607871712405733378?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Data</a> suggest that the newest iteration of the popular DEX used 2.8 million gas, which is over three times higher than the amount of gas consumed in V2 last year.</p>
<p>Its V2 iteration also witnessed 17% of its transactions reverted, the highest rate out of all of the top Ethereum contracts.</p>
<p>Overall, Uniswap recorded a whopping 15.5 million transactions as it exceeded OpeanSea&#8217;s Seaport NFT marketplace and the NFT giant OpenSea itself. Meanwhile, its V3 grabbed the top spot with over 1.5 million unique addresses, higher than any other Ethereum decentralized application.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-uniswaps-biggest-competitor-according-to-messari/" rel="nofollow">Here is Uniswap&#8217;s Biggest Competitor According to Messari</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Charles Hoskinson’s New Hospital Will Accept Cardano (ADA) for Payments</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/charles-hoskinsons-new-hospital-will-accept-cardano-ada-for-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232060</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/charles_hoskinson_cardano_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/charles_hoskinson_cardano_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hoskinson says customers can pay for medical services using ADA at his new hospital when it becomes fully operational next month. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson has announced the launch of his new hospital called &#8220;Hoskinson Health &amp; Wellness Clinic,&#8221; which will allow customers to pay for medical services using ADA, the native token of the Cardano ecosystem.</p>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1">Announcing</span> the development a few days ago, Hoskinson said the hospital would be open for business by February 2023. However, the Cardano founder did not reveal whether his new medical center will accept other major crypto assets such as bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH).</p>
<h2>Charles Hoskinson Launches New Hospital</h2>
<p class="p2">Hoskinson shared the update in response to one of his Twitter followers who asked if they could pay their bills at the newly-launched clinic using ADA. The Cardano founder <a href="https://twitter.com/IOHK_Charles/status/1611183700770959361" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">replied</a> with a &#8220;Yes.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Next Month, open for business <a href="https://t.co/yj2pHqLdpl" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/yj2pHqLdpl</a></p>
<p>— Charles Hoskinson (@IOHK_Charles) <a href="https://twitter.com/IOHK_Charles/status/1611182631210868736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="p2">According to the hospital&#8217;s website, Hoskinson Health &amp; Wellness Clinic is based in Wyoming, United States. The hospital offers its clients a wide range of medical services, including primary care, mental health care, women&#8217;s health, proactive health screenings, cancer screenings, diet/nutritional medicine, and cardiovascular care.</p>
<p class="p2">The medical facility also focuses on life extensions for aging patients, biological food supplements, diets, exercise, and medical treatment,</p>
<p class="p2">The clinic is partly open and will be fully operational next month. According to the company&#8217;s LinkedIn page, the hospital currently has around ten staff members and is looking to increase its headcount.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Driving ADA Adoption</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Hoskinson has continued to make moves recently to drive the adoption of the ADA token. In June, the blockchain developer <a href="https://twitter.com/IOHK_Charles/status/1586508990128984064" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> the launch of Nessie&#8217;s restaurant and a whiskey lounge in Wyoming, where ADA is accepted as a payment option.</p>
<p class="p2">However, the decision to make ADA a payment method was unsatisfactory for some customers. Some people suggested that Hoskinson could have opted for alternative payment options based on Cardano, such as DJED, Cardano&#8217;s first decentralized stablecoin.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/charles-hoskinsons-new-hospital-will-accept-cardano-ada-for-payments/" rel="nofollow">Charles Hoskinson’s New Hospital Will Accept Cardano (ADA) for Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Look at Emerging Crypto Trends in 2023: Nansen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/first-look-at-emerging-crypto-trends-in-2023-nansen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232091</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/trends_2023_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/trends_2023_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto analytics provider Nansen with a first look at some of the emerging trends in 2023. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Amid the bear market and the fall of FTX, the crypto industry is still struggling to get back on its feet as innovation and technological advancement continue.</p>
<p class="p2">However, the market has shown signs of improvement in the first week of 2023, with the Ethereum ecosystem leading the way. According to a report by blockchain data analytics firm Nansen, Ethereum liquid staking platforms have seen a significant increase in price in recent weeks.</p>
<h2 class="p3">Liquid Staking Protocols Spike as Staked ETH Hits ATH</h2>
<p class="p2">Per the report, this surge is largely due to the upcoming Shanghai upgrade on the Ethereum network scheduled to go live in March. The highly-anticipated upgrade will enable investors to withdraw their assets currently locked in various staking protocols while significantly reducing the risks involved in staking ETH.</p>
<p class="p2">Just as the Merge that happened last year built up bullish momentum in the weeks leading up to the event, the Shanghai upgrade is currently driving massive hype within the crypto market.</p>
<p class="p2">According to Nansen, the governance tokens of several liquid staking protocols have jumped over the past week as hype builds up.</p>
<p class="p2">Lido, the largest liquid staking derivatives platform, is seeing an influx of large sums, with its native token increasing by 65% in the last seven days. Last week, Lido briefly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-protocol-lido-reaches-5-9b-in-tvl-dethroning-makerdao/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">surpassed MakerDAO</span></a> to become the largest DeFi protocol in the market.</p>
<p class="p2">The official ETH2 staking contract is also recording impressive figures over the past few weeks, with a new all-time high of <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/staking/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">15.9 million ETH </span></a>currently being staked.</p>
<p class="p2">As anticipation for the Shanghai upgrade builds up, it will likely push the tokens of these liquid staking contracts to new highs, providing an opportunity for these platforms to grow.</p>
<h2 class="p3">Ethereum L2 Protocols Record Massive Growth</h2>
<p class="p2">The Nansen report further pointed out that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-layer-2-scaling-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum layer 2 solutions</a>, such as Arbitrum and Optimism, have been gaining traction over the last couple of months, with the number of transactions on these chains increasing significantly.</p>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-polygon-matic/" data-wpel-link="internal">Polygon</a> ecosystem is also not left out, with the number of daily transactions on the chain currently at approximately 3 million, which is 3x that of Ethereum. On the other hand, on-chain volume on the Ethereum network has slightly declined over the past few weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/first-look-at-emerging-crypto-trends-in-2023-nansen/" rel="nofollow">First Look at Emerging Crypto Trends in 2023: Nansen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Race for Bitcoin Is A Matter of National Security (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-race-for-bitcoin-is-a-matter-of-national-security-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 14:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232049</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_king_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_king_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The race for Bitcoin is a matter of national security. Here's why. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Financial markets for everything, including crypto, remain on pause as we mark off the first week of 2023. At this time of global economic uncertainty, people are holding their cash close. Here&#8217;s why it&#8217;ll be increasingly important for governments to hold their Bitcoin close.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-jumps-toward-17k-on-positive-us-job-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">barely budged</a> after the release of the latest jobs report. It moved less than a percent, holding above $16,900 as the job data <a href="https://www.kitco.com/news/2023-01-05/Bitcoin-holds-above-16-850-as-positive-economic-data-points-to-further-interest-rate-hikes.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">suggested more</a> rate hikes.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Poised To Become The World&#8217;s &#8220;Primary Monetary Good&#8221;</h2>
<p>Let&#8217;s set aside investors&#8217; woes over the crypto price winter for a moment and consider the reality of Bitcoin in 2023. People used to question whether the cryptocurrency was even here to stay. Now, successful investors and even banking giants have acknowledged its merits.</p>
<p>Fidelity Investments not only considers Bitcoin a more secure and resilient cryptocurrency than most of its peers, but its <a href="https://www.fool.com/investing/2023/01/06/why-this-financial-giant-thinks-bitcoin-is-unlike/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report states</a> the bank&#8217;s opinion that BTC has the characteristics and positioning to become the world&#8217;s &#8220;primary monetary good.&#8221;</p>
<p>Not only is Bitcoin here to stay, but it will underpin more global reserves as the decade goes on. That poses serious concerns and opportunities for U.S. national security and for that of all major world powers in the international hegemony.</p>
<h2>National Security Stake in Joining The Bitcoin Race</h2>
<p>We&#8217;re near an important inflection point in Bitcoin&#8217;s history. 14 years into the grand experiment, it is now understood by technical professionals and industry investors as a mature technology platform. It has proven its security and reliability, stacking a new block without interruption every ten minutes for 14 years now.</p>
<p>Markets are starting to reflect this new reality of Bitcoin&#8217;s stability and ascendency in world finance. The Bitcoin price is at historically low volatility. While traders who profit from roiling markets may not find it as interesting, institutions and governments are stepping up to bat next.</p>
<p>When regulations get clearer, the U.S. will have to rethink its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-rise-of-bitcoin-in-el-salvador-portends-a-new-us-foreign-policy-toolkit-op-ed/" data-wpel-link="internal">entire foreign policy toolkit</a>. Other sovereign nations are making haste to jump into the Bitcoin race. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-to-start-buying-1-bitcoin-per-day-says-bukele/" data-wpel-link="internal">El Salvador is most notable</a> among them, and others in Central America.</p>
<p>In <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Biden-Harris-Administrations-National-Security-Strategy-10.2022.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">its latest</a> National Security Strategy document (NSS), the Biden Administration says:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We will explore the merits and responsibly lead development of digital assets, including a digital dollar, with high standards and protections for stability, privacy, and security to benefit a strong and inclusive U.S. financial system and reinforce its global primacy.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>That will be important over the next decade. The dollar will never go away as a major world reserve. It is too stable, too conventional, and it&#8217;s backed by the United States. But many parts of the world actively pursue a de-dollarization policy unheard of in the last century.</p>
<p>The U.S. can only preserve its global dominance and relevance at 20th-century levels by joining the Bitcoin race for hash power and BTC.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-race-for-bitcoin-is-a-matter-of-national-security-opinion/" rel="nofollow">The Race for Bitcoin Is A Matter of National Security (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s How Crypto Is Already Addressing FDIC Fed Joint Statement on Risk Assets</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-crypto-is-already-addressing-fdic-fed-joint-statement-on-risk-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231694</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A closer look at how the cryptocurrency industry is already addressing a lot of the issues brought up by the Fed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Reserve and FDIC (Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation) released a joint statement on Tuesday, Jan 3. The paper describes the risks of holding digital assets. But here are some of the ways crypto is addressing those risks with network design and code.</p>
<p>The Fed and FDIC say that with crypto, there is a &#8220;risk of fraud and scams among crypto-asset sector participants.&#8221; But there are also several countermeasures and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-security-company-hexens-helps-bring-crypto-to-mass-adoption-through-security/" data-wpel-link="internal">security techniques</a> in crypto. Furthermore, cryptocurrency actually uses these to reduce the risk of fraud or scams.</p>
<p>No one is claiming that cryptocurrency is completely incorruptible. Neither is it said that crypto is immune to fraud, scams, or cyber-criminal exploits of the code. There&#8217;s no perfect software solution, just as there is no perfect business solution.</p>
<p>Everything in an economy is a tradeoff among comparative advantages. Moreover, those tradeoffs are part of a market game to produce the most and meet the most wants.</p>
<p>But cryptocurrency does offer some features and benefits that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/monero-executes-hard-fork-to-improve-security-and-privacy-features/" data-wpel-link="internal">gain more security</a>. That&#8217;s not just to hold your crypto but also against fraud or scams. These fraud and scam benefits, however, come as a trade-off. You get <em>less</em> control over your account <em>through</em> a centrally regulated, corporate customer help desk.</p>
<h2>&#8220;Risk of fraud and scams among crypto-asset sector participants&#8230;&#8221;</h2>
<p>DeFi protocols are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-labs-leads-funding-round-for-web3-security-startup/" data-wpel-link="internal">increasingly developing</a> countermeasures to fraud and scams. DeFi is short for &#8220;decentralized finance.&#8221; Developers for these platforms are constantly scripting up fraud and scam defenses for the blockchain.</p>
<p>For instance, zero-knowledge proof techniques are touted to be one of the great things to come up next as a <em>revolutionary </em>step forward. Crypto can pair ZK techniques with anti-money laundering (AML) and KYC (know your customer) enforcement. Therefore they can regulate exchange volume to authentic transactions. With ZK proofs, developers can implement this at scale. Furthermore, it can proactively contain solvency problems like what happened at FTX partly because of fake volume.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nber.org/system/files/working_papers/w30783/w30783.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">A study</a> by the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER) of statistical and behavioral patterns on crypto exchanges found that some 70% of unregulated exchange transactions are wash trading. So, as these upgrades continue to scale to the ecosystems, there will be less fraud and scams as a result of them.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-232153" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg" alt="crypto_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>&#8220;Legal uncertainties related to custody practices&#8230;&#8221;</h2>
<p>This is an understandable item on the FDIC and Federal Reserve&#8217;s list of cautions about cryptocurrency. After 2022, many crypto consumers would now say there was an unfair amount of ambiguity in terms of service and misleading marketing.</p>
<p>This was true for many companies that experienced insolvency in 2022 as the crypto price winter wore on. That includes crypto companies like Blockfi, Genesis, 3 Arrows Capital, FTX, and more.</p>
<p>At the same time, many cryptocurrencies already solved this problem before it became a real, full-blown crypto financial crisis in 2022. In fact, the premier cryptocurrency, Bitcoin (BTC), is predicated on the idea that it could not be more clear whose money is whose on its blockchain:</p>
<blockquote><p>Not your private keys, not your Bitcoin. Your private keys, your Bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>It&#8217;s ironic that cryptocurrency companies that had solvency crises made their fame off Bitcoin&#8217;s coattails. The reason Bitcoin was invented was so that you could be sure your deposits were still there and you could be sure they hadn&#8217;t been inflated away through unfair economics.</p>
<h2>&#8220;Inaccurate or misleading representations and disclosures&#8230;&#8221;</h2>
<p>Again, after the kind of insolvency plague we&#8217;ve seen in the crypto industry in 2022, with customers turning to places like FTX and Celsius and finding their crypto was gone, this is an understandable warning.</p>
<p>Many people giving their money to these crypto custodians offering yield did not understand they were making an unsecured loan. The fine print pages on websites for companies like Celsius explained they were lending these companies their money.</p>
<p>The customers thought these were deposits. They didn&#8217;t know they were becoming creditors and that if the loan wasn&#8217;t repaid, they would legally just have to take the loss. So that was obviously hugely unfair. It was definitely a deceptive tactic to increase their customer registrations.</p>
<p>However, the bad year for centralized finance spells an opportunity <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-nft-remains-resilient-despite-ftx-implosion-dappradar/" data-wpel-link="internal">for DeFi</a>. Smart contracts, dApps, and web3 platforms <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-security-and-auditing-firms-are-thriving-during-the-bear-market/" data-wpel-link="internal">are evolving to </a>counter fraud and scams. Users will reward solutions that are simple, fundamentally sound, and automated.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-crypto-is-already-addressing-fdic-fed-joint-statement-on-risk-assets/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s How Crypto Is Already Addressing FDIC Fed Joint Statement on Risk Assets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ApeCoin Charts Monthly High, Bitcoin Calm Below $17K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/apecoin-charts-monthly-high-bitcoin-calm-below-17k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 09:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232138</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_ApeCoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_ApeCoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lido DAO is also well in the green today once more, registering yet another local peak.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin continues to be unable to overcome $17,000, despite briefly jumping above that level yesterday.</p>
<p>The altcoins have also calmed following the notable gains charted at the start of the weekend. ApeCoin, though, has marked a near one-month high.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Stalls Below $17K</h2>
<p>2022 brought little joy for the bitcoin bulls and the end of the year was quite similar, with the asset falling to a multi-week low of under $16,500. After a few calm days around New Year&#8217;s Day, the cryptocurrency began to increase in value on Monday.</p>
<p>The next few days were similar, with BTC adding a few hundred dollars. This culminated in a price jump toward $17,000, but bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-unable-to-top-17k-yet-ethereum-classic-pumps-5-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">couldn&#8217;t challenge</a> that line until early Saturday morning.</p>
<p>This is when the asset was finally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-lido-dao-soars-to-2-month-high-btc-touched-17k/" data-wpel-link="internal">able to tap</a> that coveted level for the first time since December 20. However, the bears were quick to intercept the move and pushed BTC south almost immediately.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has remained inches away from $17,000 since then and has not made any big moves as the trading volumes have declined as with previous weekends.</p>
<p>Consequently, BTC&#8217;s market cap is just over $325 billion, while its dominance over the alts is at 39.6%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232139" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232139" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-232139" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-7-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232139" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>ApeCoin Marks Monthly High</h2>
<p>The best performer in the past week or so has been Lido DAO (LDO), as the popular DeFi project <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-protocol-lido-reaches-5-9b-in-tvl-dethroning-makerdao/" data-wpel-link="internal">began a battle</a> with MakerDAO for the TVL throne. While the latter has taken back its first position as of now, LDO has skyrocketed by double digits within a week. The past 24 hours brought another 6% increase, leading to another multi-month high at over $1.6.</p>
<p>ApeCoin and Solana are two other notable gainers on a daily scale. Both are up by between 3-4%. APE jumped to its highest price position since December 13, while SOL has neared $14 once again.</p>
<p>The larger-cap alts are significantly less volatile. Despite a minor daily retracement, Ethereum is still north of $1,250, and Binance Coin is above $260.</p>
<p>OKB has lost the most ground from the top 15 assets, following a 1.3% daily decline. Nevertheless, the crypto market cap is still close to $825 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232140" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232140" style="width: 1845px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-232140" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1845" height="738" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4.jpg 1845w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4-300x120.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4-1024x410.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4-768x307.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4-1536x614.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-4-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1845px) 100vw, 1845px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232140" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/apecoin-charts-monthly-high-bitcoin-calm-below-17k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">ApeCoin Charts Monthly High, Bitcoin Calm Below $17K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Scope of Crypto Winter: 70K BTC Millionaires Shook Out in 2022</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-scope-of-crypto-winter-70k-btc-millionaires-shook-out-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 08:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231512</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The number of addresses holding $1 million worth of BTC or more has taken a beating as the crypto winter rages on.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the turnover of the new year, Bitcoin price analyst predictions are out. Meanwhile, a survey of the damage from the protracted 2022 crypto winter shows 70K fewer BTC wallet addresses with $1 million USD worth of Bitcoin or more.</p>
<p>It has now been over a year since Bitcoin&#8217;s (BTC) last all-time price high of $68,789 on November 10, 2021. Since then, at today&#8217;s fair market price on crypto exchanges of around $16,900 for the coin, the Bitcoin price had declined 75% from the record high.</p>
<p>That was just 13 months ago, but the return on the investment depends entirely on the individual cost basis and whether it&#8217;s in a loss or a profit at BTC&#8217;s current prices. They have remained consistently below $20,000 now since September. Crypto prices across markets keep taking massive write-downs as more and more bad news about <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-customers-file-class-action-against-defunct-exchange-top-execs-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">CeFi insolvencies</a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-under-attack-1-5b-stolen-in-top-5-crypto-heists-of-2022-forbes/" data-wpel-link="internal">DeFi hacks</a> rolls out.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Predictions for 2023 Are Out</h2>
<p>With the price tumultuously tumbling all these twelve months past and since the Nov 2021 ATH, investors are looking for that relief rally. Before September, they were hoping that the powerful psychological key support at $20,000 would persist until another bull market.</p>
<p>Now they&#8217;re just holding out hope that they will be able to make it back to $20,000. Meanwhile, as regulatory consensus firms up, institutional investors with deep pockets in chase of high-performing ROI are poised to buoy BTC markets&#8217; fortunes.</p>
<p>One analyst estimate, that of Mark Mobius, who made his name trading at Franklin Templeton Investments, is that Bitcoin price will dive another 70% to $10,000. He bases his guess on rising interest rates and tightening central bank policy over the next year.</p>
<p>Still, other analysts have optimistically bullish projections. They <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/02/the-boldest-bitcoin-price-predictions-for-2023.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">range from</a> $50,000 by Q3 or Q4, according to Prof. Carol Alexander (Sussex University), to as high as $250,000 per BTC, according <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/four-great-and-one-terrible-bitcoin-price-predictions-for-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">to venture capitalist Tim Draper</a>.</p>
<p>Draper reasons that when women begin to adopt Bitcoin, that&#8217;s when the price will make this moonshot movement. He says he expects it by mid-2023:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;My assumption is that since women control 80% of retail spending, and only 1 in 7 bitcoin wallets are currently held by women that the dam is about to break.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In the meanwhile, the on-chain data reveal a drastically different Bitcoin ecosystem than the one flush with capital and volume during the bubble that ended in 2021.</p>
<h2>On Chain Data Gloomy for Investors</h2>
<p>It was a different picture in May 2021 when crypto summer was still raging. At that time, the total market capitalization of Bitcoin was $1 trillion.</p>
<p>Back then, on-chain data <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/top-100-richest-bitcoin-addresses.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that the number of Bitcoin addresses with $1,000,000 or more USD worth of Bitcoin held had crossed the 100,000 threshold.</p>
<p>That represented a 400% increase from the 25,000 level five months earlier.</p>
<p>Today it&#8217;s a different story. There are now 70,000 fewer Bitcoin addresses holding one million USD or more worth of the gold standard cryptocurrency over the last year. Whereas the blockchain started off 2022 with over 99,000 millionaire addresses, it enters Jan 2023 with some 24,391 millionaire wallet addresses.</p>
<p>That doesn&#8217;t necessarily mean there are that many fewer millionaires. It is possible that they have spread their holdings out over more addresses.</p>
<p>But overall, it&#8217;s attributable to the deep freeze on crypto prices. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-to-consolidate-or-retrace-even-further-in-2023-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">If they swing back</a> again, with renewed interest from retail and professional investors, especially at big institutional funds, those numbers will go right back up again.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-scope-of-crypto-winter-70k-btc-millionaires-shook-out-in-2022/" rel="nofollow">The Scope of Crypto Winter: 70K BTC Millionaires Shook Out in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US SEC Charges 8 People and Businesses Linked to a $45 Million Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-charges-8-people-and-businesses-linked-to-a-45-million-crypto-scam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 23:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231818</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/US_SEC4.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/US_SEC4.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC accused eight individuals and organizations of stealing $45 million from investors via their CoinDeal crypto project.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) charged Neil Chandran and seven other individuals and entities for orchestrating the fraudulent cryptocurrency investment scheme called CoinDeal. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The suspects allegedly defrauded investors with around $45 million over the years and used the money to buy real estate, cars, and a boat.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Halting the Crime</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Neil Chandran, Michael Glaspie, Garry Davidson, Linda Knott, Amy Mossel, AEO Publishing Inc, Banner Co-Op, Inc, and BannersGo, LLC of embezzling $45 million from consumers through their fraudulent entity CoinDeal. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The individuals promised to sell the blockchain-based project to a group of prominent buyers which would guarantee great returns for investors. They also deceived them about CoinDeal&#8217;s valuation and the companies involved in the potential acquisition deal.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The defendants ran their scheme between January 2019 and 2022. CoinDeal&#8217;s sale never happened, and investors did not receive any distributions for their involvement in the project. The SEC further maintained that Chandran, Glaspie, Davidson, Knott, and Mossel used the amassed $45 million to purchase cars, properties, and a boat. Daniel Gregus &#8211; Director of the SEC&#8217;s Chicago Regional Office &#8211; commented:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We allege the defendants falsely claimed access to valuable blockchain technology and that the imminent sale of the technology would generate investment returns of more than 500,000 times for investors.</span></p>
<p>As alleged in our complaint, in reality, this was all just an elaborate scheme where the defendants enriched themselves while defrauding tens of thousands of retail investors.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Department of Justice previously arrested Chandran for offenses related to wire fraud and engaging in illicit money transactions while being part of CoinDeal.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Commission seeks to impose penalties and permanent injunctions against all defendants. At the same time, it insists that Chandran should be a subject of a conduct-based injunction. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC&#8217;s Previous Hunt</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-sues-owner-of-alleged-ponzi-like-cryptocurrency-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> another investigation against two advisory companies and their owner &#8211; Gabriel Edelman &#8211; for running a Ponzi-like cryptocurrency scheme in September last year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organizations supposedly operated between February 2017 and May 2021, raising nearly $4.4 million from investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Edelman promised he would invest the capital in cryptocurrencies purchased at discounted rates. However, he funneled &#8220;only a small portion of investor funds in digital assets,&#8221; using the rest to buy personal items and send money to family members. The SEC explained in detail how Edelman&#8217;s Ponzi scheme worked:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;For example, one Investor initially invested $50,000. Edelman returned $75,000 within a few months, and the Investor subsequently invested an additional $600,000. Edelman then returned $720,000 a few months later. After that, the Investor invested $1,000,000–based on purported past performance and Edelman&#8217;s promise that the Investor would receive a 15% return. Thereafter, Edelman did not return any funds to that Investor.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-charges-8-people-and-businesses-linked-to-a-45-million-crypto-scam/" rel="nofollow">US SEC Charges 8 People and Businesses Linked to a $45 Million Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>$3.8B of Cumulative Volume Moved Overseas Since Indian Crypto Taxes Kicked In</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3-8b-of-cumulative-volume-moved-overseas-since-indian-crypto-taxes-kicked-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231600</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/india-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/india-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[India introduced two new taxes on crypto transactions - 30% capital gains tax and 1% transaction tax as TDS - effective April 1, 2022.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Indian crypto exchanges lost a significant portion of their trading volume after new taxes for the sector came into force, the losses, so far, were referred to in percentage terms, with most estimates quoting them to be above 90%, compared to the previous year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Now, a new study has quantified the value of cumulative trading that shifted from Indian to foreign crypto exchanges after the new taxes kicked in.</span></p>
<p><em>CryptoPotato</em> reported earlier that Indian traders are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/traders-flock-to-binance-as-new-taxes-send-indian-exchanges-out-of-business-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">flocking</a> to foreign exchanges after the tax and regulatory environment in the country has become &#8220;<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-has-no-big-plans-for-india-due-to-high-taxation-says-cz/" data-wpel-link="internal">unviable</a>.&#8221;</p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">$3.8 Billion Moved</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Esya Centre, an Indian think tank on technology policy matters, in a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.esyacentre.org/documents/2022/12/12/virtual-digital-asset-tax-architecture-in-india-a-critical-examination" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> published on January 3, said that Rs. 32,000 crores ($3.85 billion) of cumulative trade volume shifted from Indian crypto exchanges to foreign competitors between February and October 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report, titled &#8220;Virtual Digital Asset Tax Architecture in India: A Critical Examination,&#8221; examines how the new taxes for the domestic crypto market proposed in the Union budget 2022-23 on February 1 impacted the overall business in this sector.  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It said Rs. 25,300 crores ($3.05 billion) of cumulative trading moved out of Indian crypto exchanges in the six months to October 2022, that is, since the new taxes became effective on April 1. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Taking peer-to-peer trade into account, the total contribution of trade volume from India to foreign exchanges is to the tune of Rs. 80,000 crores ($9.67 billion), the Esya Centre report said.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;India’s tax treatment of VDAs is regressive in comparison to other countries with high VDA adoption rates, such as the USA, UK, South Africa, Vietnam, Philippines, and Brazil,&#8221; it claimed.  </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fall in Volume </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decline in trading volume came in a phased manner, the report said, with the initial onslaught claiming 15% of the trading volume coming in the first two months since the tax amendment made by Indian Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her budget speech on February 1, 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another 14% was lost in the three months since April 2022, when the 30% tax on crypto gains became effective. The steep taxation was implemented without the provision to set off losses against profits.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The third and final blow arrived when a 1% transaction tax came into force on July 1, 2022, which eroded up to 81% of the trading volume from the Indian exchanges, the report said.     </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Many Indian VDA users seem to be switching from domestic centralised VDA exchanges to foreign counterparts (an estimated 17 lakh users switched in the period analysed), a trend visible starting Feb 2022 (i.e. following from the Union Budget announcement),&#8221; the report claimed. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-8b-of-cumulative-volume-moved-overseas-since-indian-crypto-taxes-kicked-in/" rel="nofollow">$3.8B of Cumulative Volume Moved Overseas Since Indian Crypto Taxes Kicked In</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Despite SEC Battle, XRP Investment Products Saw Record Inflows in 2022: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/despite-sec-battle-xrp-investment-products-saw-record-inflows-in-2022-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231640</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple_XRP.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple_XRP.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the incessant tepid price action, market players choosing to invest are tactically adding to positions during price weakness.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 saw many crypto-assets lose value, prompting investors to pull their money from the market. During turbulent times, inflows plummeted massively.</p>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-112-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-e00679d7fea6" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by CoinShares, the digital asset inflow was recorded at $433 million, the lowest in four years. The last time figures were hovering near the current level was in 2018, when inflows stood at $233 million.</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin saw the third-worst year for inflows with $287 million after declining by well over 60% this year.</li>
<li>Multi-asset investment products recorded inflows of just $209 million.</li>
<li>The Merge was the biggest highlight in the Ethereum ecosystem. But investor concerns over a successful transition to proof of stake (PoS) translated into outflows of $402 million.</li>
<li>The figure was in a sharp reversal compared to the previous two years when Ethereum saw massive inflows of more than $1.8 billion and $920 million, respectively.</li>
<li>Other altcoins that bore the brunt of the tumultuous year were Binance Coin (BNB) with $24 million and Tron (TRX) with $3 million outflows.</li>
<li>On the other hand, Litecoin (LTC) and Polygon (MATIC) oriented products registered inflows of $2 million and $1 million, respectively.</li>
<li>While the washout of crypto exchange FTX severely affected the Solana network, it wrapped up the year on a positive note with $121 million.</li>
<li>XRP remained unfazed by the twists and turns of the battle between crypto firm Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In fact, XRP-related investment products clocked in $32 million in inflows, the second highest in the last five years.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, short-investment products came to the fore with inflows worth $108 million for the whole of 2022.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-sec-battle-xrp-investment-products-saw-record-inflows-in-2022-report/" rel="nofollow">Despite SEC Battle, XRP Investment Products Saw Record Inflows in 2022: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
