<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Sui Foundation Ends Partnership With MoveEX Following Contract Violation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sui-foundation-ends-partnership-with-moveex-following-contract-violation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262881</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Network.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Network.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The foundation asked MovEX to move the entire 2.5 million SUI to a qualified custodian who will release them according to the token emission schedule.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sui Foundation, the non-profit organization behind the Sui Network, has terminated its partnership with MovEX, a decentralized exchange (DEX) and liquidity management platform, following the violation of a lockup agreement.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://blog.sui.io/understanding-sui-token-supply/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> by the Sui Foundation, MovEX moved some Sui tokens (SUI) that were subject to a contractual lockup without informing or seeking consent from the organization, sparking accusations of misrepresented emissions from the crypto community.</p>
<h2>Sui Foundation Cuts Ties With MovEX</h2>
<p>MovEx was an early contributor to Sui during its mainnet <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-faced-massive-volatility-minutes-after-mainnet-launch/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> in May, serving as a core builder for the network’s DeepBook, a shared decentralized central limit order book created for the ecosystem.</p>
<p>At the time, 5.15% of the total SUI supply was in circulation, with the rest released on a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-sui-networks-tokens-will-be-unlocked/" data-wpel-link="internal">preset schedule</a> to early contributors to maintain network stability. The tokens were subject to a lockup period in line with the release schedule.</p>
<p>In June, however, the pseudonymous Twitter user DefiSquared <a href="https://twitter.com/DefiSquared/status/1673572324145078273?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">accused</a> Sui of intentionally misrepresenting token emissions and dumping rewards from locked, non-circulating staked SUI on crypto exchange Binance.</p>
<p>Through several investigations, the Sui Foundation discovered that MovEX executed the transactions that stirred the accusations. Out of the 2.5 million SUI received as payment for contributing to DeepBook, the decentralized exchange had initiated three transactions of 625,000 SUI to three different wallets, leaving the rest in the original wallet.</p>
<p>Sui Foundation has ended its relationship with MovEX as the DEX breached the contractual lockup and failed to seek consent before initiating those transactions. Earlier this month, the foundation asked MovEX to move the 2.5 million SUI to a qualified custodian who will release them according to the token emission schedule.</p>
<h2>MovEX Reponds</h2>
<p>In response to the announcement by Sui Foundation, MovEX took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/joinMovEX/status/1684496073967140864?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">explain</a> that it had only distributed the tokens to custodian and non-custodian wallets.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We would like to express our understanding regarding the conclusion of our partnership with Sui. We deeply value the journey filled with dedication, hard work, and honors, and we are truly appreciative of the support we received from the community,” MovEX said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Sui Foundation has assured the crypto community that “all other tokens subject to contractual lockups are held in qualified custodian accounts that have agreed to enforce the terms of such lockups.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-foundation-ends-partnership-with-moveex-following-contract-violation/" rel="nofollow">Sui Foundation Ends Partnership With MoveEX Following Contract Violation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Republicans Blast White House For Failure To Compromise On Stablecoin Bill</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/republicans-blast-white-house-for-failure-to-compromise-on-stablecoin-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263013</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Stablecoins_Regulations.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Stablecoins_Regulations.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[House Democrats accuse Republicans of being impatient with negotiations for payment stablecoins.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The House Financial Services Committee (HFSC) failed to reach an agreement for stablecoin legislation on Thursday due to a number of disagreements Democrats had with its existing text.</p>
<p>Committee Chair Patrick McHenry (R-NC) blamed the White House for holding up the bill, while Democrats alleged that Republicans were attempting to rush incomplete legislation.</p>
<h2>No Compromise For Stablecoin Bill</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.congress.gov/118/bills/hr4766/BILLS-118hr4766ih.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">bill</a>, titled the Clarity for Payment Stablecoins Act of 2023, would allow the Federal Reserve to write requirements for stablecoin issuers, but still preserve the authority of state-level payment stablecoin regulators while outlining other requirements.</p>
<p>After 15 months of negotiations, McHenry <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FGjvuDjXiq0&amp;ab_channel=U.S.HouseCommitteeonFinancialServices" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">claimed</a> the committee was “closer than we’d ever been” to a bipartisan deal aside from a few “small provisions.”</p>
<p>“It was the White House’s unwillingness to compromise that has once again brought negotiations to a halt,” he said. He did not specify which elements of the bill the Biden administration had objected to.</p>
<p>The agency’s ranking member, Maxine Waters (D-CA), blamed McHenry’s “impatience” for pushing forward a “deeply flawed” bill, which she said lacked support from both the Treasury Department and Federal Reserve. Previously, Federal Reserve chairman Jerome Powell has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-chairman-refers-to-stablecoins-as-a-form-of-money/" data-wpel-link="internal">emphasized</a> that the central bank ought to have a role within the industry as the ultimate source of credibility on money.</p>
<p>Waters claimed the bill would give states too much authority to expand the number of eligible reserve assets for backing stablecoins, creating risks for token holders. Furthermore, she said it would allow tech giants to issue their own stablecoins – a threat reminiscent of Facebook’s now-defunct stablecoin project, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/diems-downfall-from-an-ambitious-single-global-digital-currency-idea-to-a-painful-end/" data-wpel-link="internal">Diem</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We too would like a real bi-partisan bill,” said Waters in her opening statement on Thursday. “I don’t know what the rush is. Why the rush at this particular time?”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Success of FIN21</h2>
<p>Unlike the stablecoin bill, the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act proposed on Wednesday managed to secure bipartisan approval. All Republicans on the committee voted in its favor, alongside 6 Democrats.</p>
<p>The bill <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/congressional-stablecoin-bill-still-reeks-of-sam-bankman-fried-democrats-say/" data-wpel-link="internal">outlines</a> which market regulators should have authority over what cryptocurrencies, and clarifies that a crypto asset may be issued in a securities transaction without being a security itself.</p>
<p>Though crypto critics like Brad Sherman (D-CA) thought the bill was too friendly to the crypto industry, Congressman Ritchie Torres (D-NY) acknowledged that it was still leagues ahead of the regulations in place today.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This legislation is far from perfect, but it represents a good-faith attempt to create clarity where none exists,” said Torres. “I will not let perfect be the enemy of good.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/republicans-blast-white-house-for-failure-to-compromise-on-stablecoin-bill/" rel="nofollow">Republicans Blast White House For Failure To Compromise On Stablecoin Bill</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Presidential Candidate Robert Kennedy Purchased 14 BTC for his Children</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-purchased-14-btc-for-his-children/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 21:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262832</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert_Kennedy-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert_Kennedy-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kennedy purchased approximately $380,000 worth of BTC for his kids right after the Bitcoin Conference in Miami in May this year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy Jr. &#8211; nephew of former US President John F. Kennedy and one of the presidential candidates for the elections in 2024 &#8211; reiterated his support for bitcoin, saying he had bought two BTC for each of his seven kids. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading digital asset stands at the center of his political campaign, with Kennedy promising to exempt its conversion to the US dollar from capital gains taxes. He also vowed to back America&#8217;s national currency with &#8220;real finite assets,&#8221; such as gold, silver, platinum, and bitcoin.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Passing BTC for the Next Generation</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US presidential candidate from the Democratic party – Robert F. Kennedy (known for his controversial views on nuclear power, the COVID-19 vaccination program, and weapons) &#8211; has also captured the attention of Bitcoiners, presenting himself as a keen advocate.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent Twitter Spaces gathering hosted by Scott Melker (known as &#8220;The Wolf of All Streets&#8221;), he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/scottmelker/status/1684262327854432266?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">admitted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> purchasing two BTC for each of his seven children shortly after the Bitcoin Conference in Miami in May this year. The asset&#8217;s price was hovering around $27,000 at that time, meaning he must have spent around $380,000 to acquire the stash.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Right after that Bitcoin conference, I got a big check, and I said, okay, you know, I&#8217;m going to put my money where my mouth is, and so I bought two BTC for every one of my seven children,&#8221; Kennedy stated.<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_245914" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-245914" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-245914" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" alt="Robert F. Kennedy Jr" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-245914" class="wp-caption-text">Robert F. Kennedy Jr, Source: STAT News</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the 69-year-old explained he first heard of the primary cryptocurrency in 2009, he did not pay much attention to it back then. However, everything changed for Kennedy at the beginning of 2022 during the massive truckers&#8217; strike in Canada. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recall that protesters received significant crypto donations, whereas the local authorities ordered financial firms to cease facilitating any proceedings to addresses tied to them. This sparked huge controversy, with many highlighting BTC&#8217;s decentralized nature and opposing the government&#8217;s decision to adjust such transactions.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thanking all Bitcoiners</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, Kennedy appreciated the support he received from the Bitcoin community, saying he has a &#8220;spiritual bond&#8221; with them. He described those parts of the ecosystem as a &#8220;unique breed&#8221; that is not only interested in money but also in freedom:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Bitcoiners are a unique breed. Of all the financial people I&#8217;ve met in my life, people in finance are mainly interested in making a big pile for themselves, and whoever dies with the most money wins.</span></p>
<p>Bitcoiners are different breed, they like money, and they like profits, but mainly because it shows that you can make money by doing good, by winning freedom. They are ideologically based.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of CNN</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-kennedy-purchased-14-btc-for-his-children/" rel="nofollow">US Presidential Candidate Robert Kennedy Purchased 14 BTC for his Children</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Better Than Bitcoin? Jack Dorsey to Coinbase CEO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/whats-better-than-bitcoin-jack-dorsey-to-coinbase-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263003</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/jack_dorsey.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/jack_dorsey.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong wants to see crypto payments upgrade to the next level. Is Bitcoin's lightning network the answer?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey pressed Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong on Wednesday over his alleged refusal to acknowledge the power of Bitcoin’s lightning network – a layer-2 scaling solution designed to make BTC easier to spend.</p>
<p>His question sparked an online debate about the benefits and limitations of lightning in the payments realm, compared to other cryptocurrencies such as stablecoins.</p>
<h2>Why Not Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>In a tweet on Wednesday, Armstrong claimed that crypto’s next step was to make payments “instant and free globally,” through collective work on layer 2 solutions and user onboarding. He referenced a coffee shop that now accepted gas-free USDC payments using Coinbase Wallet, which integrated <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/say-gm-with-messaging-on-coinbase-wallet" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">messaging</a> this month.</p>
<p>The CEO acknowledged that crypto was still “stuck on layer 1,” prompting Dorsey to question him about Bitcoin’s premiere layer 2 network. “Why do you continue to ignore bitcoin and lightning?” he asked.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Why do you continue to ignore bitcoin and lightning?</p>
<p>what &quot;crypto&quot; is a better money transmission protocol and why?</p>
<p>&mdash; jack (@jack) <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1684298214198108160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Lightning makes BTC payments instant and virtually free by taking transaction settlement off the network’s main blockchain. The latter can get bloated and slow in times of peak demand, as seen when an explosion of Bitcoin-based memecoins in May sent transaction fees above $30 apiece.</p>
<p>The event caused withdrawal delays at <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-successfully-integrates-bitcoin-on-lightning-network-enabling-deposits-and-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance</a>, which has since decided to integrate Bitcoin’s lightning network as a solution for future base-layer fee spikes. However, despite common demand from Bitcoiners including MicroStrategy’s <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1684301676390367232" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Michael Saylor</a>, Coinbase is yet to do the same.</p>
<p>While Armstrong didn’t respond to Dorsey directly, Solana Labs co-founder Anatoly Yakovenko answered his question. “USDC on Solana is cheaper and faster than Bitcoin and lightning and it’s the currency that people want to use globally,” he said.</p>
<p>USDC is a stablecoin value-pegged to the U.S. dollar, allowing it to avoid the short-term volatility of other cryptos, and better serve as a medium of exchange. The world’s most popular stablecoins including USDT and USDC primarily circulate on networks like Ethereum and Solana, but not Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Dorsey has previously <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1535322732249993219" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">disregarded</a> both Ethereum and Solana for being centrally controlled and prone to corporate capture.</p>
<p>Spiral – a subsidiary of Dorsey’s payments company, Block – has created tools to help developers better integrate the lightning network into their apps. The company’s popular payment service, CashApp, has also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-network-transfers-are-now-fully-available-on-cashapp/" data-wpel-link="internal">integrated lightning</a>.</p>
<h2>Solutions for Bitcoin</h2>
<p>The adoption of Bitcoin’s lightning network continues to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-lightning-networks-public-capacity-surpasses-5000-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">grow</a> over time, as do the network’s capabilities. Last year, Bitcoin infrastructure company Galoy <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/galoy-launches-stablesats-bringing-us-dollar-balances-to-lightning-network/" data-wpel-link="internal">developed</a> “Stablesats” – a centralized solution for effectively transacting “dollars” over lightning using perpetual futures trades on the back end.</p>
<p>https://twitter.com/_pretyflaco/status/1684328205396717570</p>
<p>Another company, Stably, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stably-launches-bitcoins-first-brc-20-stablecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> Bitcoin’s first-ever base-layer stablecoin back in May, leveraging the newly popularized BRC-20 token standard. However, BRC-20’s creator has admitted that tokenization solutions for Bitcoin are best found with <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-aims-to-bitcoinize-the-dollar-with-taros-alpha-release/" data-wpel-link="internal">Taro</a> – a company allowing for alternative asset transfers over the lightning network.</p>
<p>The company behind Taro, Lightning Labs, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-unveils-toolkit-to-enable-ai-transact-in-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> a toolkit earlier this month allowing AI to interact with Bitcoin’s lightning network.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/whats-better-than-bitcoin-jack-dorsey-to-coinbase-ceo/" rel="nofollow">What&#8217;s Better Than Bitcoin? Jack Dorsey to Coinbase CEO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Contemporary Giant Yue Minjun Embarks on a Web3 Journey with First NFT Project Exclusively on LiveArt</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/contemporary-giant-yue-minjun-embarks-on-a-web3-journey-with-first-nft-project-exclusively-on-liveart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262994</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Yue_Minjun_Premint_14_1690471927NMbsdmfSQ3.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Yue_Minjun_Premint_14_1690471927NMbsdmfSQ3.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, USA, July 27th, 2023] LiveArt, the Web3 Platform for Art and Culture, announced a groundbreaking NFT collection, Kingdom of the Laughing Man, by Yue Minjun, one of the most important contemporary Chinese artists creating today. Yue Minjun, the contemporary art giant of the 21st century, enters the digital art space [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, USA, July 27th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://liveart.xyz/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">LiveArt</a>, the Web3 Platform for Art and Culture, announced a groundbreaking NFT collection, <strong>Kingdom of the Laughing Man,</strong> by Yue Minjun, one of the most important contemporary Chinese artists creating today.</p>
<p>Yue Minjun, the contemporary art giant of the 21st century, enters the digital art space with his inaugural Web3 project. The artist’s works fetch millions of dollars at auctions worldwide (USD 6.9 million sales record at Christie&#8217;s HK) and are in the permanent collections of the SFMoma, Denver Art Museum, The Culture Centre of Francois Mitterrand, Guangdong Museum of Art, Shenzhen Art Museum, and other leading art institutions. Collaborations with artists like KAWS and fashion brands like Comme De Garcons have cemented Yue Minjun&#8217;s signature style in global pop culture.</p>
<p><strong>Kingdom of the Laughing Man</strong> launches with <strong>Boundless</strong>, a generative collection of 1,200 unique NFT artworks echoing Yue Minjun’s iconic self-portraits. All Yue Minjun <strong>Boundless</strong> collection holders will have the opportunity to purchase unique physical prints signed by the artist based on the NFTs they own. Subsequent drops will feature 3D animated art and culminate with an immersive metaverse experience. The <a href="https://liveart.xyz/artist/yue-minjun/kingdom-of-the-laughing-man" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">collection</a> is offered exclusively on LiveArt.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I&#8217;ve explored numerous media with my art over the years. This new digital frontier excites me the most as I can bring my art to life in a way that I haven&#8217;t been able to with physical media. In Web3 I can create a new engaging experience and relationship with the next generations of art collectors shaping the art world of the future,&#8221; says Yue Minjun.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Yue Minjun exemplifies the caliber of artists who call LiveArt home in this new digital world. I think he is probably the most significant contemporary artist to commit fully to a Web3 journey today, and we are honored and excited for the historic opportunity we can offer our collectors,&#8221; says Boris Pevzner, CEO and Co-Founder of LiveArt.</p></blockquote>
<p>The first drop is set to launch on <strong>August 8, 2023, </strong>on LiveArt. It is expected to sell out during a &#8220;pre-sale&#8221; exclusive to collectors and LiveArt X Card holders, according to LiveArt insiders. To ensure a spot on the pre-sale list, click <a href="https://www.premint.xyz/yue-minjun/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">here</a>.</p>
<h2>About LiveArt</h2>
<p>Founded by Sotheby&#8217;s and Christie&#8217;s art market veterans and backed by Binance Labs and Animoca Brands, <a href="https://liveart.xyz/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">LiveArt</a> is the global Web3 platform for art and culture. LiveArt blends AI and blockchain with intimate art market knowledge to bring exclusive Web3 collecting experiences to a global audience. LiveArt&#8217;s $ART utility token powers the LiveArt Protocol that drives value for the LiveArt ecosystem through membership and loyalty programs for the communities of LiveArt and its partners.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/aveMl_NpRXuxbVf7cZjXKoQi5rwhAc3wLv4gWrQJiJ8dZokkro_16904724100k2sxObsoY.jpeg" /></p>
<p>Yue Minjun, photo by Michelle Yue</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/i3eWivitKtXn_T-UjvKWgEnzrMGSydFkwU2Kc3dtioXUgbhTD8_1690472410mMvSatc8nh.jpeg" /></p>
<p>Artwork from the <strong>Kingdom of the Laughing Man: Boundless</strong> (2023) collection by Yue Minjun, published by LiveArt.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/k5p4Fb2yrMRVFAkhO0WrvzF41nUWUflf8yV5LPOgw_a1qxYhpb_1690472410pcjvKCOKSb.jpeg" /></p>
<p>Artwork from the <strong>Kingdom of the Laughing Man: Boundless</strong> (2023) collection by Yue Minjun, published by LiveArt.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/zqzuhwjlXpWmjbUDsdUEt7zxourzeD_YQpoKumOynmEXvN0hHe_1690472410ZWJrSFVd0M.jpeg" /></p>
<p>Artwork from the <strong>Kingdom of the Laughing Man: Boundless</strong> (2023) collection by Yue Minjun, published by LiveArt.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/75KaIMhmOnAhqf_4dWVqG3mSIARX_koeMPFCOkSUtwpLrojhfg_1690472409mGZbcXpXz3.jpeg" /></p>
<p>Artwork from the <strong>Kingdom of the Laughing Man: Boundless</strong> (2023) collection by Yue Minjun, published by LiveArt.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/contemporary-giant-yue-minjun-embarks-on-a-web3-journey-with-first-nft-project-exclusively-on-liveart/" rel="nofollow">Contemporary Giant Yue Minjun Embarks on a Web3 Journey with First NFT Project Exclusively on LiveArt</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tim Draper Explains Why Bitcoin Will Rise Above Fiat</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tim-draper-explains-why-bitcoin-will-rise-above-fiat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 17:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262815</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is a "better, safer technology" than fiat, Draper argued.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American venture capital investor Tim Draper predicted that bitcoin&#8217;s price will surge in the future due to the cryptocurrency&#8217;s advantages over fiat currency.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The billionaire claimed in 2020 that the COVID-19 pandemic will have a disastrous consequence on the global economy, but it will be a flourishing factor for BTC. The primary digital asset climbed to an all-time high of almost $70,000 the following year, whereas a financial crisis and record inflation rates shuttered many regions across the globe.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Here&#8217;s Why BTC is Better</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the biggest proponents of bitcoin &#8211; Tim Draper &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/WatcherGuru/status/1684211035509518336" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">doubled down</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on his support for the asset in a recent interview for Fox Business.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He believes it will &#8220;rise above fiat&#8221; due to its advantages over the dollar and other currencies. One flaw that national currencies have is that they are controlled by a bank or a government, while BTC&#8217;s network is secured by &#8220;hundreds of thousands of nodes,&#8221; he added:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Having to have a bank and a government that decides on what currency is good is not as effective as having a bitcoin where you have a trusted third party which is hundreds of thousands of nodes out there checking to make sure that the transaction was done properly.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_262816" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-262816" style="width: 601px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-scaled.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-262816" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-scaled.jpeg" alt="Tim Draper" width="601" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-scaled.jpeg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-1024x682.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-768x511.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-1536x1022.jpeg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-2048x1363.jpeg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tim-Draper-50x33.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 601px) 100vw, 601px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-262816" class="wp-caption-text">Tim Draper, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that central banks can also affect the supply of fiat currency by printing colossal amounts.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Federal Reserve, for example, printed trillions of dollars in 2020 and 2021 to tackle the consequences of the coronavirus outbreak. While this move was somewhat helpful in the beginning, it later became one of the reasons for<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-inflation-clocks-in-at-9-1-for-june/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the record inflation rate</a> in the USA.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Meanwhile, bitcoin has a fixed maximum supply of 21 million coins ever to exist. Many supporters think this gives the asset an upper hand against inflation rates. In addition, its decentralized nature (the fact that no banking institution or a government can control it) could make it more attractive to people than fiat, whose supply is constantly adjusted by centralized authorities.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;So I think it&#8217;s just better, safer technology, and eventually, the rest of the world will come onboard,&#8221; Draper concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Failure With the Previous Forecast</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American billionaire has not always been spot on in his predictions regarding bitcoin&#8217;s future valuation. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/everybody-will-accept-bitcoin-and-its-price-will-reach-250k-in-2022-says-tim-draper/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">forecasted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in 2021 that BTC would climb to $250,000 by the end of last year, while in 2020, he suggested the asset would reach that milestone at the beginning of 2023. Despite the significant price increase in the past three years, bitcoin came nowhere near the $250K target.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Draper </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/TimDraper/status/1674859367311745024?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1674859367311745024%7Ctwgr%5Ea520d7ca968eb6ccc356b568dc82722577fb6716%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fthecryptobasic.com%2F2023%2F07%2F26%2Ftim-draper-this-decade-will-redefine-currency-and-commerce-thanks-to-bitcoin%2F" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in a recent tweet that &#8220;we have to wait a little longer (maybe 2 years)&#8221; before BTC skyrockets to that level. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tim-draper-explains-why-bitcoin-will-rise-above-fiat/" rel="nofollow">Tim Draper Explains Why Bitcoin Will Rise Above Fiat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Custodia Bank vs. Feds: Legal Brawl as Important as Ripple&#8217;s XRP Case: Lawyer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/custodia-bank-vs-feds-legal-brawl-as-important-as-ripples-xrp-case-lawyer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262917</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[XRP advocate John Deaton believes the court cases against the Fed are threatening to end the institution's "arbitrary and capricious conduct."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wyoming-based Custodia Bank&#8217;s application to become a member of the Federal Reserve System was rejected earlier this year by the Kansas City Fed. But the platform has no intention of backing down.</p>
<p>The legal dispute took a new turn after Custodia slapped three lawsuits against the regulator in three separate circuits. According to attorney John Deaton, Custodia&#8217;s fight against the Feds is &#8220;arguably just as important (if not more)&#8221; as the Ripple-XRP case.</p>
<h2>Custodia vs. Feds</h2>
<p>Custodia was founded by Morgan Stanley veteran Caitlin Long in 2020. The platform offers a bridge between digital assets and the US dollar system. In its lawsuit, Custodia accused the Federal Reserve of unlawfully delaying its application for a so-called master account, which happens to be an important component necessary to effectively participate in the US financial ecosystem.</p>
<p>After moving to court, Custodia notched a key win as Wyoming Federal Judge denied the Federal Reserve&#8217;s bid to dismiss its lawsuit against it. As for the Fed, its official reason for denial was concerns over Custodia&#8217;s short history and what the institution considers to be a problematic business model &#8211; that involves primarily fees, such as for storing crypto tokens, instead of investments, by lending out customer deposits.</p>
<p>The Fed even released an 86-page order explaining its decision in March. Its argument centers around Custodia Bank’s business model being &#8220;too risky,&#8221; indicating the platform lacks FDIC deposit insurance, which is used to make deposit holders whole in the event of a bank failure.</p>
<p>In short, the Fed disapproves of Custodia accepting crypto assets as deposits due to the &#8220;speculative and volatile nature of the crypto-asset ecosystem.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Case of Power Grab</h2>
<p>Custodia maintained that the dispute is a clear case of a power grab by the Fed and is looking forward to the court&#8217;s review.</p>
<p>In a new <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1684404657672667139" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweet</a>, Deaton also echoed a similar sentiment when he said that the Custodia vs. Fed case is as important as the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple vs. SEC battle</a>, in which the blockchain firm scored a partial victory. The attorney believes the Custodia lawsuit serves as a clear example that major regulators have been neglecting their statutory obligations.</p>
<p>Deaton further added that the court cases are threatening to end the Federal Reserve&#8217;s &#8220;arbitrary and capricious conduct.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/custodia-bank-vs-feds-legal-brawl-as-important-as-ripples-xrp-case-lawyer/" rel="nofollow">Custodia Bank vs. Feds: Legal Brawl as Important as Ripple&#8217;s XRP Case: Lawyer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Evil Pepe Coin Raises Over $1 Million With Just 6 Days of Presale Left</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/evil-pepe-coin-raises-over-1-million-with-just-6-days-of-presale-left/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262944</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/evilpepe_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/evilpepe_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Evil Pepe Coin is a hot new entrant in the meme coin space that has already raised over $1 million within ten days of its official launch. This surge in investor interest in Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE) is quite similar to the initial excitement of well-known meme coins like Pepe Coin, Dogecoin, and Shiba Inu. Especially [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Evil Pepe Coin is a hot new entrant in the meme coin space that has already raised over $1 million within ten days of its official launch.</p>
<p>This surge in investor interest in <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_evilpepe_35234?referrer=evil-pepe-coin-raises-over-1-million-with-just-6-days-of-presale-left" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE)</a> is quite similar to the initial excitement of well-known meme coins like Pepe Coin, Dogecoin, and Shiba Inu.</p>
<p>Especially with the current market conditions showing signs of recovery, many buyers are rushing to buy the $EVILPEPE coin in its ongoing presale phase.</p>
<p>While buyers can grab the token at only $0.000333, the buying pressure is mounting before the token presale ends in under six days.</p>
<h2><strong>Is $EVILPEPE The Next Pepe Coin?</strong></h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://evilpepecoin.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Evil Pepe Coin whitepaper</a>, $EVILPEPE isn’t just a token—it seeks to be a reform against the usual crypto norms.</p>
<p>Evil Pepe Coin captures the charm of trendy &#8216;shitcoins,&#8217; offering an exciting ride without worrying about high-risk moves.</p>
<p>$EVILPEPE differs from usual meme coins, blending meme culture&#8217;s chaotic vibe with speculative appeal. This coin taps into the Fear Of Missing Out (FOMO) sentiment, creating a bold &amp; unapologetic community.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-27.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-262947" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-27.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="690" height="266" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-27.jpg 690w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-27-300x116.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-27-50x19.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 690px) 100vw, 690px" /></a></p>
<p>The platform believes that every meme coin investor needs a bit of daring. Evil Pepe Coin allows you to unleash your inner ‘meme villain.’</p>
<p>Moreover, well-known analyst and YouTuber Jacob Bury has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=id_14XzIWTc" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">predicted Evil Pepe Coin to be the next Pepe Coin</a> and see big gains.</p>
<h2><strong>Community-Focused Tokenomics &amp; Presale</strong></h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_evilpepe_35234?referrer=evil-pepe-coin-raises-over-1-million-with-just-6-days-of-presale-left" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$EVILPEPE token</a> has a total supply of 6.66 billion. This platform intends to distribute 90% of these tokens via the presale.</p>
<p>This approach highlights their strategy to create a strong community &#8211; a pillar for the long-term success of any meme coin. The rest, 10% of tokens, will be reserved for a liquidity lock for one month.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-39.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-262946" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-39.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="705" height="326" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-39.jpg 705w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-39-300x139.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-39-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 705px) 100vw, 705px" /></a></p>
<p>At press time, buyers can get $EVILPEPE at a presale price of just $0.000333 USDT, payable via USDT, ETH, BNB, or credit card.</p>
<p>The token has already sparked significant interest, raising over $1 million within the first ten days of its launch.</p>
<p>$EVILPEPE can offer an upside opportunity, but it&#8217;s vital to gauge your risk tolerance levels and financial goals first. Remember, meme cryptos with solid community support usually have a bright future potential.</p>
<p>Stay tuned to <a href="https://twitter.com/evilpepe_token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Evil Pepe&#8217;s Twitter handle</a> for more presale updates.</p>
<h2><strong>Evil Pepe Coin Roadmap: Potential DEX Listing, Targeting a $100M Market Cap</strong></h2>
<p>Participating in the presale allows you to take advantage of the potential DEX listing in the coming quarters</p>
<p>As Evil Pepe Coin picks up pace and the DEX debut nears, the chance for substantial growth becomes quite tangible.</p>
<p>Evil Pepe is not only capitalizing on the current hype &#8211; it&#8217;s aiming for a bright future. Its strategic roadmap highlights its bold aspirations while accepting the uncertainty the future presents.</p>
<p>The first stage involves Evil Pepe creating excitement by communicating its mission on social media platforms.</p>
<p>This will help create FOMO among potential investors, evidenced by the $1 million raised within a few days of launch. The DEX listing will occur once this excitement peaks, ensuring smooth trading and liquidity.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-37.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-262945" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-37.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="686" height="302" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-37.jpg 686w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-37-300x132.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-37-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 686px) 100vw, 686px" /></a></p>
<p>In the second stage, Evil Pepe plans to broaden its impact. It will partner with significant meme market players creating strategic partnerships to push $EVILPEPE to new heights.</p>
<p>The final stage for the platform is about redefining the meme coin landscape. Aiming for a $100,000,000 market cap, Evil Pepe will aim to dominate, not just participate.</p>
<p>$EVILPEPE&#8217;s unique charm lies in its daring, unconventional attitude. This coin challenges the typical rules of the meme crypto space, bringing an element of thrill and unpredictability.</p>
<p>Potential buyers can enter the <a href="https://t.me/Evilpepetoken" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Evil Pepe Coin Telegram channel</a> to stay updated on the project&#8217;s progress.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_evilpepe_35234?referrer=evil-pepe-coin-raises-over-1-million-with-just-6-days-of-presale-left" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Evil Pepe Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/evil-pepe-coin-raises-over-1-million-with-just-6-days-of-presale-left/" rel="nofollow">Evil Pepe Coin Raises Over $1 Million With Just 6 Days of Presale Left</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Calls for Voting in Favor of FIT21</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-calls-for-voting-in-favor-of-fit21/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262876</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong is pushing American citizens to contact their representatives to vote in favor of FIT21.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rapidly changing digital asset landscape has resulted in a flexing of regulatory muscles between different watchdogs in defining terms and drawing lines of authority. This is especially true in the case of the United States where the SEC and CFTC are engaged in a turf war over regulatory oversight of the space. But this conflict could come to an end soon with the help of FIT21.</p>
<p>Weeks after the historic verdict on the Ripple vs. SEC case, the US is waiting for the approval of the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21 Century Act (FIT21), which is being touted as a crucial step in advancing toward the much-needed regulatory clarity.</p>
<h2>Coinbase CEO Pushes for FIT21</h2>
<p>Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1684417921244880896" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">explain</a> that the House Financial Services Committee and the House Agriculture Committee in the US House of Representatives are taking an important step toward providing clarity for crypto by voting on the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act.</p>
<p>He urged the American citizens to email their representative to vote &#8216;Yes&#8217; to it. The exec admitted that the legislation is only the first step in a bigger process but highlighted its importance in achieving the broader goal that the industry has been pinning for.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;FIT21 would create much-needed regulatory clarity in the United States for crypto and holds promising outcomes to protect consumers, promote job opportunities, and strengthen national security. However, we cannot achieve this alone – we need your support to ensure the legislative process continues to progress in Congress.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Bill</h2>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Introducing the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act. This bill establishes a regulatory framework for digital assets, protects consumers, fosters innovation, and positions America as a leader in finance and technology. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#crypto</a> <a href="https://t.co/0ihzY3MP0k" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/0ihzY3MP0k</a></p>
<p>— House Committee on Agriculture (@HouseAgGOP) <a href="https://twitter.com/HouseAgGOP/status/1682132996931960834?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>FIT21 essentially seeks to increase the Commodity Futures Trading Commission&#8217;s (CFTC) oversight over the crypto industry and clarify the jurisdiction of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The bill is now headed to the Senate for a vote, where it is expected to face considerable opposition from Democratic lawmakers.</p>
<p>Congresswoman Maxine Waters, the top Democrat on the House Financial Services Committee, <a href="https://democrats-financialservices.house.gov/news/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=410718" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">aired</a> her frustration and said she was &#8220;disappointed&#8221; that Republicans have made the unilateral decision to move forward with a massive market structure bill to rewrite the country&#8217;s investor protection laws. According to Waters, the bill exhibited a bias toward the interests of the crypto industry at the expense of regulators and consumers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-calls-for-voting-in-favor-of-fit21/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Calls for Voting in Favor of FIT21</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: Is a Crash to $27K Imminent for BTC? Key Factors to Watch in the Coming Days</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-is-a-crash-to-27k-imminent-for-btc-key-factors-to-watch-in-the-coming-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262904</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price is yet to recover above the $30K level after falling below a few days ago. However, the price is currently being supported at around $29,000. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, the price has been consolidating in a very tight range below the $30K level. The 50-day moving [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price is yet to recover above the $30K level after falling below a few days ago. However, the price is currently being supported at around $29,000.</p>
<h2><strong>Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price has been consolidating in a very tight range below the $30K level. The 50-day moving average is around the $29K mark at the moment. If it gets broken to the downside, the 200-day moving average located around the $27K level would be the next probable target in the short term.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if the market rebounds and breaks above the $30K zone, a rally toward $38K would be expected.</p>
<figure id="attachment_262905" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-262905" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-262905 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2707231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-27-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-262905" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>The 4-Hour Chart:</strong></h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour chart, the price has been painting lower highs and lows. The $30K level has turned into resistance, pushing it lower. In case Bitcoin fails to climb above $30K again, the $27,500 support level would likely get tested.</p>
<p>Moreover, the RSI indicator is also showing values around 50%, offering little insight into the potential direction for the short term. Therefore, the market is currently located in a key area, and the price action in the coming weeks relies on the reaction to this zone.</p>
<figure id="attachment_262906" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-262906" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-262906 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2707232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-27-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-262906" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>Bitcoin has experienced significant fluctuations in the past two years since it peaked at $69K and entered a bearish cycle. Various factors, such as the ongoing pandemic, inflation concerns, and the Russia-Ukraine war, have contributed to these unstable periods, resulting in an atmosphere of uncertainty and doubt prevailing in the financial markets.</p>
<p>The Realized Cap – UTXO Age Bands (%) metric can be employed to assess Bitcoin’s supply dynamics. This metric categorizes coins based on their lifetimes and the proportion of the total realized cap.</p>
<p>Despite the price plunging significantly below $20K in the recent bearish phase, the accumulation rate seems to have surpassed that of the 2018 bearish period. This observation suggests that many market participants still view Bitcoin as a valuable asset, reinforcing their confidence in its potential despite the challenges faced during this bearish cycle.</p>
<figure id="attachment_262907" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-262907" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-262907 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--scaled.jpg" alt="btc_realized_cap_chart_2707231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Realized-Cap-UTXO-Age-Bands--50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-262907" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-is-a-crash-to-27k-imminent-for-btc-key-factors-to-watch-in-the-coming-days/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price Analysis: Is a Crash to $27K Imminent for BTC? Key Factors to Watch in the Coming Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
