<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 07:50:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Prepares NFT Marketplace Support For Bitcoin Ordinals]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-prepares-nft-marketplace-support-for-bitcoin-ordinals</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-china-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-china-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-china-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-prepares-nft-marketplace-support-for-bitcoin-ordinals</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance has announced plans to support Bitcoin Ordinals inscriptions on its NFT marketplace later this month. This move marks Binance's entry into the rapidly growing Bitcoin-based parallel NFT market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The update to Binance's NFT marketplace will be rolled out in the coming weeks, allowing users to buy and trade Ordinals inscriptions using their Binance accounts. In March, the NFT marketplace expanded its range of supported networks by adding select NFT collections from Polygon to the platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's Head of Product, Mayur Kamat, sees the prepared listing to be a significant development. Kamat commented:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Bitcoin is the OG of crypto. We believe things are just getting started here and can't wait to see what the future holds in this space."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Several inscriptions marketplaces have emerged as a result of Ordinals' initial surge in popularity, including Ordswap, Ordinals Market, and Ordinals Wallet. Magic Eden, the largest Solana NFT marketplace, was the first among established platforms to enter the Ordinals market, launching an inscriptions marketplace in March.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's NFT marketplace announcement comes just days after the exchange temporarily paused Bitcoin withdrawals due to network congestion, while its competitors remained fully operational. The pause occurred when Bitcoin transaction fees were at a high, and the network's mempool&mdash;where transactions wait to be verified&mdash;was heavily backlogged.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Many in crypto Twitter (CT) believe that transactions related to BRC-20 tokens were contributing to the network congestion. BRC-20 tokens, which are built and traded using Ordinals, use text-based inscriptions instead of image-based ones, just like Bitcoin NFTs. Currently, Binance's Bitcoin NFT marketplace does not support BRC-20 tokens.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In recent weeks, image-based inscriptions have been eclipsed by Bitcoin-based tokens and text-based inscriptions. On Sunday, 99.7% of inscriptions made through Ordinals were text-based, according to a Dune dashboard. Simultaneously, 65% of all Bitcoin transactions were related to BRC-20 tokens, as reported by another Dune dashboard.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The excitement surrounding BRC-20 tokens intensified on Monday as Ordi, the first BRC-20 token launched as an experiment in March, was listed on cryptocurrency exchanges Crypto.com and Gate.io. Binance's support for Ordinals inscriptions signals its commitment to staying at the forefront of the ever-evolving cryptocurrency landscape.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The addition of Ordinals inscriptions to Binance's NFT marketplace represents a significant milestone in the expansion of digital assets on the Bitcoin blockchain. As we dive deeper into the world of Ordinals and the underlying technology, it's important to understand how this development will impact Binance users and the broader cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ordinals inscriptions on the Bitcoin blockchain are often referred to as "digital artifacts," and they represent a different approach to NFTs compared to the more familiar Ethereum-based NFTs. Ordinals are created by inscribing satoshis, the atomic units of a Bitcoin, with digital artifacts or machine-readable language. This process aligns with the immutable nature of the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Bitcoin Ordinals project, initiated by Casey Rodarmor, a former blockchain developer at Chaincode Labs for Bitcoin Core, offers a new perspective on the concept of NFTs. The project documentation states, "Digital artifacts are permissionless. An NFT which cannot be sold without paying a royalty is not permissionless, and thus not a digital artifact." This distinction highlights the unique characteristics of Ordinals as opposed to traditional NFTs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As Binance adds support for Ordinals inscriptions to its NFT marketplace, users will have access to a new type of digital asset that is more closely tied to the Bitcoin blockchain. Unlike Ethereum-based NFTs, which often rely on off-chain data from the Interplanetary File System (IPFS), Bitcoin Ordinals do not require off-chain connections. This development represents a significant technical advancement within the digital asset space, addressing a previously unresolved (or, to some extent, unrealized) challenge in the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The process of creating Ordinals inscriptions involves inscribing satoshis with arbitrary content, resulting in bitcoin-native digital artifacts without the need for a sidechain or separate token. These inscribed satoshis can be transferred using bitcoin transactions, sent to bitcoin addresses, and held in bitcoin UTXOs. The transactions, addresses, and UTXOs are treated as normal bitcoin entities, with the exception that transactions must control the order and value of inputs and outputs according to ordinal theory.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's decision to support Ordinals inscriptions on its NFT marketplace is a testament to the growing interest and excitement surrounding this new form of digital asset. As Yuga Labs, the creator of the popular Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection, said, "Stepping into the Ordinals Discord a month ago felt like getting a glimpse of the 2017-era Ethereum NFT ecosystem. It&rsquo;s the type of energy and excitement we love."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">With the addition of Ordinals inscriptions to Binance's NFT marketplace, users can expect a more diverse range of digital assets available for trading and collecting. The integration of this innovative Bitcoin-based technology also signals the exchange's commitment to staying at the forefront of the rapidly evolving digital asset landscape. The support for Bitcoin Ordinals could be a harbinger of even more groundbreaking developments in the space.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance has announced plans to support Bitcoin Ordinals inscriptions on its NFT marketplace later this month. This move marks Binance's entry into the rapidly growing Bitcoin-based parallel NFT market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The update to Binance's NFT marketplace will be rolled out in the coming weeks, allowing users to buy and trade Ordinals inscriptions using their Binance accounts. In March, the NFT marketplace expanded its range of supported networks by adding select NFT collections from Polygon to the platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's Head of Product, Mayur Kamat, sees the prepared listing to be a significant development. Kamat commented:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Bitcoin is the OG of crypto. We believe things are just getting started here and can't wait to see what the future holds in this space."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Several inscriptions marketplaces have emerged as a result of Ordinals' initial surge in popularity, including Ordswap, Ordinals Market, and Ordinals Wallet. Magic Eden, the largest Solana NFT marketplace, was the first among established platforms to enter the Ordinals market, launching an inscriptions marketplace in March.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's NFT marketplace announcement comes just days after the exchange temporarily paused Bitcoin withdrawals due to network congestion, while its competitors remained fully operational. The pause occurred when Bitcoin transaction fees were at a high, and the network's mempool&mdash;where transactions wait to be verified&mdash;was heavily backlogged.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Many in crypto Twitter (CT) believe that transactions related to BRC-20 tokens were contributing to the network congestion. BRC-20 tokens, which are built and traded using Ordinals, use text-based inscriptions instead of image-based ones, just like Bitcoin NFTs. Currently, Binance's Bitcoin NFT marketplace does not support BRC-20 tokens.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In recent weeks, image-based inscriptions have been eclipsed by Bitcoin-based tokens and text-based inscriptions. On Sunday, 99.7% of inscriptions made through Ordinals were text-based, according to a Dune dashboard. Simultaneously, 65% of all Bitcoin transactions were related to BRC-20 tokens, as reported by another Dune dashboard.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The excitement surrounding BRC-20 tokens intensified on Monday as Ordi, the first BRC-20 token launched as an experiment in March, was listed on cryptocurrency exchanges Crypto.com and Gate.io. Binance's support for Ordinals inscriptions signals its commitment to staying at the forefront of the ever-evolving cryptocurrency landscape.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The addition of Ordinals inscriptions to Binance's NFT marketplace represents a significant milestone in the expansion of digital assets on the Bitcoin blockchain. As we dive deeper into the world of Ordinals and the underlying technology, it's important to understand how this development will impact Binance users and the broader cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ordinals inscriptions on the Bitcoin blockchain are often referred to as "digital artifacts," and they represent a different approach to NFTs compared to the more familiar Ethereum-based NFTs. Ordinals are created by inscribing satoshis, the atomic units of a Bitcoin, with digital artifacts or machine-readable language. This process aligns with the immutable nature of the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Bitcoin Ordinals project, initiated by Casey Rodarmor, a former blockchain developer at Chaincode Labs for Bitcoin Core, offers a new perspective on the concept of NFTs. The project documentation states, "Digital artifacts are permissionless. An NFT which cannot be sold without paying a royalty is not permissionless, and thus not a digital artifact." This distinction highlights the unique characteristics of Ordinals as opposed to traditional NFTs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As Binance adds support for Ordinals inscriptions to its NFT marketplace, users will have access to a new type of digital asset that is more closely tied to the Bitcoin blockchain. Unlike Ethereum-based NFTs, which often rely on off-chain data from the Interplanetary File System (IPFS), Bitcoin Ordinals do not require off-chain connections. This development represents a significant technical advancement within the digital asset space, addressing a previously unresolved (or, to some extent, unrealized) challenge in the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The process of creating Ordinals inscriptions involves inscribing satoshis with arbitrary content, resulting in bitcoin-native digital artifacts without the need for a sidechain or separate token. These inscribed satoshis can be transferred using bitcoin transactions, sent to bitcoin addresses, and held in bitcoin UTXOs. The transactions, addresses, and UTXOs are treated as normal bitcoin entities, with the exception that transactions must control the order and value of inputs and outputs according to ordinal theory.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's decision to support Ordinals inscriptions on its NFT marketplace is a testament to the growing interest and excitement surrounding this new form of digital asset. As Yuga Labs, the creator of the popular Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection, said, "Stepping into the Ordinals Discord a month ago felt like getting a glimpse of the 2017-era Ethereum NFT ecosystem. It&rsquo;s the type of energy and excitement we love."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">With the addition of Ordinals inscriptions to Binance's NFT marketplace, users can expect a more diverse range of digital assets available for trading and collecting. The integration of this innovative Bitcoin-based technology also signals the exchange's commitment to staying at the forefront of the rapidly evolving digital asset landscape. The support for Bitcoin Ordinals could be a harbinger of even more groundbreaking developments in the space.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Yesports Announces 14-day Staking Extravaganza for Pepe Meme Token Holders]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/yesports-announces-14-day-staking-extravaganza-for-pepe-meme-token-holders</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-05-10_064629_16836940288SPUp2Ncxj.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-05-10_064629_16836940288SPUp2Ncxj.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-05-10_064629_16836940288SPUp2Ncxj.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 06:16:37 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/yesports-announces-14-day-staking-extravaganza-for-pepe-meme-token-holders</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>New York, United states, May 10th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Yesports, the leading esports to web3 gaming platform, is thrilled to announce a special staking event for holders of the Pepe meme token. This 14-day extravaganza offers Pepe token holders the chance to stake and earn YESP rewards.</p><p>Beginning 11th of May, Pepe holders can stake their tokens and receive a share of 3m YESP, which will be distributed over 14 days. As part of the special offer event, Pepe holders can also participate in Yesports&rsquo; popular NFT prize games which enable gamers and collectors to explore web3 games and provide engaging new ways to win exclusive NFTs.&nbsp;</p><p>Building strong communities is a central focus for businesses in both traditional gaming and web3. Given the speed at which blockchain technology advances and its ability to support the rapid growth of ardent communities, Yesports aims to expand its platform offerings further through this timely new event, activating utility for Pepe meme token holders.&nbsp;</p><p>Meme tokens serve to keep communities and audiences engaged through shared values, which are often represented by and translated through comical designs and themes. To date, the industry has seen very few meaningful examples of utility for meme tokens. The most notable can be backtracked to 2014 when Dogecoin holders sponsored NASCAR driver Josh Wise. For Yesports, this special event speaks to the sentiment of its web3 gaming community and its extended industry partners who share in the same vision and values.</p>"Offering this staking event for Pepe token holders is something we believe to not only be fun, but necessary, some might even say inevitable," says Sebastian Quinn, CEO of Yesports. "For a limited time, Pepe token holders can earn rewards while supporting the Yesports ecosystem, and Yesports can strengthen its community of avid gamers, esports organisations, fans and collectors."<p>To participate in the staking event, Pepe token holders can visit the Yesports website and follow the instructions provided at yesports.gg. For more information and FAQ about YESP, visit Yesports blog here and get details about NFT prize games here.</p><p>About Yesports</p><p>Yesports is disrupting the traditional gaming world and democratizing the industry in its mission to deliver complete, user-friendly experiences and bridge the gap between gaming, fans, and web3. Bringing entertainment and access closer to the user, Yesports is leading the way in creating a more inclusive gaming world leveraging new technology. Backed by leading VCs and built with world-leading technology, Yesports is focused on delivering the most valuable digital products for gamers everywhere.</p>ContactChief Operations OfficerMajella MensahYesportshello@yesports.gg]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York, United states, May 10th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Yesports, the leading esports to web3 gaming platform, is thrilled to announce a special staking event for holders of the Pepe meme token. This 14-day extravaganza offers Pepe token holders the chance to stake and earn YESP rewards.</p><p>Beginning 11th of May, Pepe holders can stake their tokens and receive a share of 3m YESP, which will be distributed over 14 days. As part of the special offer event, Pepe holders can also participate in Yesports&rsquo; popular NFT prize games which enable gamers and collectors to explore web3 games and provide engaging new ways to win exclusive NFTs.&nbsp;</p><p>Building strong communities is a central focus for businesses in both traditional gaming and web3. Given the speed at which blockchain technology advances and its ability to support the rapid growth of ardent communities, Yesports aims to expand its platform offerings further through this timely new event, activating utility for Pepe meme token holders.&nbsp;</p><p>Meme tokens serve to keep communities and audiences engaged through shared values, which are often represented by and translated through comical designs and themes. To date, the industry has seen very few meaningful examples of utility for meme tokens. The most notable can be backtracked to 2014 when Dogecoin holders sponsored NASCAR driver Josh Wise. For Yesports, this special event speaks to the sentiment of its web3 gaming community and its extended industry partners who share in the same vision and values.</p>"Offering this staking event for Pepe token holders is something we believe to not only be fun, but necessary, some might even say inevitable," says Sebastian Quinn, CEO of Yesports. "For a limited time, Pepe token holders can earn rewards while supporting the Yesports ecosystem, and Yesports can strengthen its community of avid gamers, esports organisations, fans and collectors."<p>To participate in the staking event, Pepe token holders can visit the Yesports website and follow the instructions provided at yesports.gg. For more information and FAQ about YESP, visit Yesports blog here and get details about NFT prize games here.</p><p>About Yesports</p><p>Yesports is disrupting the traditional gaming world and democratizing the industry in its mission to deliver complete, user-friendly experiences and bridge the gap between gaming, fans, and web3. Bringing entertainment and access closer to the user, Yesports is leading the way in creating a more inclusive gaming world leveraging new technology. Backed by leading VCs and built with world-leading technology, Yesports is focused on delivering the most valuable digital products for gamers everywhere.</p>ContactChief Operations OfficerMajella MensahYesportshello@yesports.gg]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bittrex Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/crypto-exchange-bittrex-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bittrex-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bittrex-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bittrex-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/crypto-exchange-bittrex-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bittrex Inc filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection on Monday. The filing comes after the exchange suspended its US operations. </p>
<p>Seattle-based cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex Inc filed for bankruptcy on May 8, just weeks after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) accused it of operating as an unregistered securities exchange, broker-deal, and clearinghouse.</p>
<p>According to Reuters, Bittrex Inc, which ceased its operations in the US on April 30 due to regulatory concerns, said its bankruptcy filing would not affect Bittrex Global, which serves customers outside the US.</p>
<p>The bankruptcy petition filed in a Delaware court indicates Bittrex&rsquo;s assets and liabilities were between $500 million and $1 billion, with over 100,000 creditors.</p>
<p>Reuters further reports that the exchange still holds assets of some of its US customers that did not withdraw funds before the April 30 deadline. Bittrex assured its customers that the funds were &ldquo;safe and secure.&rdquo;</p>
Bittrex&rsquo;s Woes
<p>Bittrex announced on March 31 that it would suspend its operations in the US, claiming that it was not &ldquo;economically viable&rdquo; to continue doing business there.</p>
<p>The exchange said its offshore operations, Bittrex Global, which serves traders in Europe, Canada, and South America, would remain unaffected.</p>
<p>Soon after the exchange announced its decision to leave the US, the SEC charged the firm for operating as an unregistered securities exchange, broker-dealer, and clearinghouse.</p>
<p>The agency also charged Bittrex&rsquo;s former CEO, William Shihara, for his involvement in the company&rsquo;s alleged violations.</p>
<p>The SEC further alleges that from 2017 to 2022, the exchange earned over $1.3 billion in revenue from transaction fees from investors while offering its services without the necessary registration from the agency.</p>
<p>Bittrex&rsquo;s counsel, David Maria, said the exchange attempted to comply with the agency&rsquo;s rules but could not do so unless it essentially ceased all its revenue-producing services in the US. It was, however, unable to do so over the agency&rsquo;s failure to provide clear guidelines for the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bittrex Inc filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection on Monday. The filing comes after the exchange suspended its US operations. </p>
<p>Seattle-based cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex Inc filed for bankruptcy on May 8, just weeks after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) accused it of operating as an unregistered securities exchange, broker-deal, and clearinghouse.</p>
<p>According to Reuters, Bittrex Inc, which ceased its operations in the US on April 30 due to regulatory concerns, said its bankruptcy filing would not affect Bittrex Global, which serves customers outside the US.</p>
<p>The bankruptcy petition filed in a Delaware court indicates Bittrex&rsquo;s assets and liabilities were between $500 million and $1 billion, with over 100,000 creditors.</p>
<p>Reuters further reports that the exchange still holds assets of some of its US customers that did not withdraw funds before the April 30 deadline. Bittrex assured its customers that the funds were &ldquo;safe and secure.&rdquo;</p>
Bittrex&rsquo;s Woes
<p>Bittrex announced on March 31 that it would suspend its operations in the US, claiming that it was not &ldquo;economically viable&rdquo; to continue doing business there.</p>
<p>The exchange said its offshore operations, Bittrex Global, which serves traders in Europe, Canada, and South America, would remain unaffected.</p>
<p>Soon after the exchange announced its decision to leave the US, the SEC charged the firm for operating as an unregistered securities exchange, broker-dealer, and clearinghouse.</p>
<p>The agency also charged Bittrex&rsquo;s former CEO, William Shihara, for his involvement in the company&rsquo;s alleged violations.</p>
<p>The SEC further alleges that from 2017 to 2022, the exchange earned over $1.3 billion in revenue from transaction fees from investors while offering its services without the necessary registration from the agency.</p>
<p>Bittrex&rsquo;s counsel, David Maria, said the exchange attempted to comply with the agency&rsquo;s rules but could not do so unless it essentially ceased all its revenue-producing services in the US. It was, however, unable to do so over the agency&rsquo;s failure to provide clear guidelines for the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wakweli Partners With Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG) ]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-blg</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-21.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-21.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-21.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/wakweli-partners-with-blockchain-lawyers-group-blg</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Image: Wakweli</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Web 3 certification platform Wakweli partners with Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG).&nbsp;</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">The partnership aims to boost legal expertise in the Web 3 industry.&nbsp;</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Wakweli also announced its new initiative to offer token grants to developers.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Wakweli, a decentralized NFT certification protocol, announced its partnership with the Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG) aiming to extend the solid legal expertise in the Web 3 ecosystem. In addition, the partnership will also see the BLG group conduct deeper protocol refinements for Wakweli&rsquo;s proof-of-democracy (PoD) consensus algorithm.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Wakweli is an NFT certification protocol that aims to improve trust in the decentralized ecosystem by issuing certificates of authenticity for NFTs and other tokenized assets to combat fraud in the growing web3 ecosystem. The Blockchain Lawyers Group consists of a global network of legal professionals and experts experienced in Web 3 and blockchain matters. The group of lawyers offers easy access to competent and qualified legal advice through an NFT membership model.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The partnership between Wakweli and BLG aims to foster stronger relationships and extend legal knowledge to Web 3 users. As part of the collaboration, BLG lawyers will take part in the validation of the very first certificates offered on Wakweli, helping boost trust in the whole decentralized certification process. Apart from upholding the market integrity of the NFTs and tokenized assets, the partnership also brings Wakweli to the Web 3 map, setting it as a benchmark of trust for the decentralized ecosystem.</p>

<p>"We are excited to partner with such an innovative company as Wakweli, which is trying to solve a preeminent issue in the NFT space,&rdquo; said Blockchain Lawyers Group Founder and Member Miguel Dinis Lucas. &ldquo;We are confident that our collaboration will bring new levels of innovation and user-friendliness to the market."</p>

<p>The statement from the Wakweli team labels the latest partnership &ldquo;significant&rdquo; as the platform pushes for more competent and qualified legal advice in the blockchain and crypto ecosystem. Additionally, it bonds well with its certification protocol and ensures Wakweli users get easy access to legal advice for businesses, digital assets, and protocols they have in the Web 3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the $1.1 million Wakweli seed funding round in 2022, the company has taken massive strides in pushing for more development in the decentralized industry. The protocol launched its website, whitepaper, roadmap and Alpha release in the course of the past year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the statement released today, Wakweli announced a new funding initiative that calls on Web 3 developers to apply for token grants from its on-chain treasury. It plans to launch a special foundation later this year to manage the initiative.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Image: Wakweli</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Web 3 certification platform Wakweli partners with Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG).&nbsp;</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">The partnership aims to boost legal expertise in the Web 3 industry.&nbsp;</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Wakweli also announced its new initiative to offer token grants to developers.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Wakweli, a decentralized NFT certification protocol, announced its partnership with the Blockchain Lawyers Group (BLG) aiming to extend the solid legal expertise in the Web 3 ecosystem. In addition, the partnership will also see the BLG group conduct deeper protocol refinements for Wakweli&rsquo;s proof-of-democracy (PoD) consensus algorithm.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Wakweli is an NFT certification protocol that aims to improve trust in the decentralized ecosystem by issuing certificates of authenticity for NFTs and other tokenized assets to combat fraud in the growing web3 ecosystem. The Blockchain Lawyers Group consists of a global network of legal professionals and experts experienced in Web 3 and blockchain matters. The group of lawyers offers easy access to competent and qualified legal advice through an NFT membership model.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The partnership between Wakweli and BLG aims to foster stronger relationships and extend legal knowledge to Web 3 users. As part of the collaboration, BLG lawyers will take part in the validation of the very first certificates offered on Wakweli, helping boost trust in the whole decentralized certification process. Apart from upholding the market integrity of the NFTs and tokenized assets, the partnership also brings Wakweli to the Web 3 map, setting it as a benchmark of trust for the decentralized ecosystem.</p>

<p>"We are excited to partner with such an innovative company as Wakweli, which is trying to solve a preeminent issue in the NFT space,&rdquo; said Blockchain Lawyers Group Founder and Member Miguel Dinis Lucas. &ldquo;We are confident that our collaboration will bring new levels of innovation and user-friendliness to the market."</p>

<p>The statement from the Wakweli team labels the latest partnership &ldquo;significant&rdquo; as the platform pushes for more competent and qualified legal advice in the blockchain and crypto ecosystem. Additionally, it bonds well with its certification protocol and ensures Wakweli users get easy access to legal advice for businesses, digital assets, and protocols they have in the Web 3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the $1.1 million Wakweli seed funding round in 2022, the company has taken massive strides in pushing for more development in the decentralized industry. The protocol launched its website, whitepaper, roadmap and Alpha release in the course of the past year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the statement released today, Wakweli announced a new funding initiative that calls on Web 3 developers to apply for token grants from its on-chain treasury. It plans to launch a special foundation later this year to manage the initiative.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the Premier Crypto Events in Asia for 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/unveiling-the-premier-crypto-events-in-asia-for-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-47.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-47.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-47.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/unveiling-the-premier-crypto-events-in-asia-for-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The world has witnessed remarkable growth in cryptocurrency adoption, with Asia emerging as a dominant force in the digital asset landscape. Leading countries such as China, South Korea, and Japan have significantly contributed to this growth. As more Asian nations embrace blockchain technology and digital currencies, the region has experienced a surge in crypto events and conferences.</p>
<p>These events have played a crucial role in fostering collaboration, innovation, and knowledge exchange among industry insiders, investors, and enthusiasts. As 2023 unfolds, Asia remains a hub for groundbreaking discussions on the future of blockchain, Web3, and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>1. IVS Crypto 2023 KYOTO: A Premier Event for Web3 Innovators (Kyoto, Japan, June 28-30, 2023)</p>
<p>IVS Crypto 2023 KYOTO, scheduled for June 28-30 in Kyoto, Japan, is a premier event with many sub-events to look forward to. Notable highlights include HONEYCON (an NFT theme park) and a strong list of speakers representing Digital Garage, Circle, Bank of Japan, Quantstamp, etc. All of these companies will help attendees further understand the growing importance of Web3 technology.</p>
<p>Another exciting sub-event is "SHAKE! KYOTO," a Web3 game-specific contest. Finalists will be selected from submitted Web3 game projects and compete for awards. All outstanding entries will gain the attention of publishers, licensors, and venture capitalists, further propelling their projects into the spotlight.</p>
<p>2. WebX: Introducing Decentralized Technologies to Society (Tokyo, Japan, July 25-26, 2023)</p>
<p>WebX, Asia's largest web3 conference, comes to you from the Tokyo International Forum. The two-day global event emphasizes the impact of decentralized technologies on society. While it maintains a Japan-first focus, these implications traverse country borders and will eventually make their way throughout Asia.</p>
<p>WebX features various side events, offering something for every type of attendee. Furthermore, the crowd has a vast buffet of industry speakers to listen to. Representatives of Salesforce, Ripple, Chiliz, Nansen, and other crypto firms will share their insights and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p>3. Korea Blockchain Week: Redefining the Future of Finance (Seoul, South Korea, September 4-9, 2023)</p>
<p>Korea Blockchain Week, founded by FACTBLOCK and co-hosted by Hashed, returns for its sixth year in Seoul. This annual event gathers the brightest minds in the industry to discuss, redefine, and celebrate the future of finance. There is a sturdy lineup of industry speakers to pay attention to, including Nick Szabo, Adam Back, Vitalik Buterin, and Changpeng Zhao, among many others.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Like the other Asian events, KBW has several side activities for visitors to explore. The official and affiliated side events all provide a different flair to attendees, with many networking opportunities to explore. It is always worthwhile connecting with like-minded people.&nbsp;</p>
4. TOKEN2049: Asia's Premier Crypto Gathering (Singapore, September 13-14, 2023)
<p>TOKEN2049, held annually in Singapore, is Asia's premier crypto event. As the flagship event of Asia Crypto Week, it brings together founders and executives of leading Web3 companies and projects. The event is known for its massive networking opportunities, enabling attendees to forge new connections and explore potential opportunities. Plus, it has a top-tier list of speakers willing to guide attendees on their journey into crypto, Web3, NFTs, etc.</p>
<p>From September 13-14, 2023, TOKEN2049 transforms Singapore into a vibrant crypto hub. The event provides everything one needs, including numerous side events, drinks, and parties. Moreover, TOKEN2049 will coincide with the Formula 1 Grand Prix of Singapore in 2023. There is nothing like an F1 race to get the blood pumping!A Year of Unprecedented Crypto Events in Asia</p>
<p>As the cryptocurrency landscape evolves, Asia's role as a pivotal player in the global digital asset market becomes increasingly evident. As a result, the region's premier crypto events in 2023, such as TOKEN2049, Korea Blockchain Week, WebX, and IVS Crypto 2023 KYOTO, will serve as crucial platforms for industry leaders, investors, developers, and enthusiasts to collaborate, innovate, and exchange knowledge.</p>
<p>These conferences facilitate discussions on the future of blockchain, Web3, and cryptocurrencies and provide unparalleled networking and learning opportunities for those involved in this rapidly advancing sector.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The world has witnessed remarkable growth in cryptocurrency adoption, with Asia emerging as a dominant force in the digital asset landscape. Leading countries such as China, South Korea, and Japan have significantly contributed to this growth. As more Asian nations embrace blockchain technology and digital currencies, the region has experienced a surge in crypto events and conferences.</p>
<p>These events have played a crucial role in fostering collaboration, innovation, and knowledge exchange among industry insiders, investors, and enthusiasts. As 2023 unfolds, Asia remains a hub for groundbreaking discussions on the future of blockchain, Web3, and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>1. IVS Crypto 2023 KYOTO: A Premier Event for Web3 Innovators (Kyoto, Japan, June 28-30, 2023)</p>
<p>IVS Crypto 2023 KYOTO, scheduled for June 28-30 in Kyoto, Japan, is a premier event with many sub-events to look forward to. Notable highlights include HONEYCON (an NFT theme park) and a strong list of speakers representing Digital Garage, Circle, Bank of Japan, Quantstamp, etc. All of these companies will help attendees further understand the growing importance of Web3 technology.</p>
<p>Another exciting sub-event is "SHAKE! KYOTO," a Web3 game-specific contest. Finalists will be selected from submitted Web3 game projects and compete for awards. All outstanding entries will gain the attention of publishers, licensors, and venture capitalists, further propelling their projects into the spotlight.</p>
<p>2. WebX: Introducing Decentralized Technologies to Society (Tokyo, Japan, July 25-26, 2023)</p>
<p>WebX, Asia's largest web3 conference, comes to you from the Tokyo International Forum. The two-day global event emphasizes the impact of decentralized technologies on society. While it maintains a Japan-first focus, these implications traverse country borders and will eventually make their way throughout Asia.</p>
<p>WebX features various side events, offering something for every type of attendee. Furthermore, the crowd has a vast buffet of industry speakers to listen to. Representatives of Salesforce, Ripple, Chiliz, Nansen, and other crypto firms will share their insights and expertise.&nbsp;</p>
<p>3. Korea Blockchain Week: Redefining the Future of Finance (Seoul, South Korea, September 4-9, 2023)</p>
<p>Korea Blockchain Week, founded by FACTBLOCK and co-hosted by Hashed, returns for its sixth year in Seoul. This annual event gathers the brightest minds in the industry to discuss, redefine, and celebrate the future of finance. There is a sturdy lineup of industry speakers to pay attention to, including Nick Szabo, Adam Back, Vitalik Buterin, and Changpeng Zhao, among many others.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Like the other Asian events, KBW has several side activities for visitors to explore. The official and affiliated side events all provide a different flair to attendees, with many networking opportunities to explore. It is always worthwhile connecting with like-minded people.&nbsp;</p>
4. TOKEN2049: Asia's Premier Crypto Gathering (Singapore, September 13-14, 2023)
<p>TOKEN2049, held annually in Singapore, is Asia's premier crypto event. As the flagship event of Asia Crypto Week, it brings together founders and executives of leading Web3 companies and projects. The event is known for its massive networking opportunities, enabling attendees to forge new connections and explore potential opportunities. Plus, it has a top-tier list of speakers willing to guide attendees on their journey into crypto, Web3, NFTs, etc.</p>
<p>From September 13-14, 2023, TOKEN2049 transforms Singapore into a vibrant crypto hub. The event provides everything one needs, including numerous side events, drinks, and parties. Moreover, TOKEN2049 will coincide with the Formula 1 Grand Prix of Singapore in 2023. There is nothing like an F1 race to get the blood pumping!A Year of Unprecedented Crypto Events in Asia</p>
<p>As the cryptocurrency landscape evolves, Asia's role as a pivotal player in the global digital asset market becomes increasingly evident. As a result, the region's premier crypto events in 2023, such as TOKEN2049, Korea Blockchain Week, WebX, and IVS Crypto 2023 KYOTO, will serve as crucial platforms for industry leaders, investors, developers, and enthusiasts to collaborate, innovate, and exchange knowledge.</p>
<p>These conferences facilitate discussions on the future of blockchain, Web3, and cryptocurrencies and provide unparalleled networking and learning opportunities for those involved in this rapidly advancing sector.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Lifted from 27279 - 10 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-lifted-from-27279-10-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-may-2023-240-1920-1080-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-may-2023-240-1920-1080-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-may-2023-240-1920-1080-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-lifted-from-27279-10-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Lifted to 27768:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) sought additional upside momentum early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 27768.37 area after buying pressure emerged around the 27279.66 area, its weakest print since late April.&nbsp; &nbsp;Demand emerged around the 27455.01 area during the climb, representing a test of the 61.8% retracement of the short-term appreciating range from 27279.66 to 27768.37.&nbsp;&nbsp; The move higher to the 27686.67 area represented a test of the 23.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 29139.22 to 27279.66.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 27930, 27990, 28117, 28209, 28261, 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas.&nbsp; Significant buying and selling activity recently took place around the 29298.31 area during the depreciation, an upside price objective linked to buying pressure that increased around the 28122 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives relate to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28476.09 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28121.71.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;26533.04/ 25604.51/ 25094.62 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Lifted to 27768:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) sought additional upside momentum early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 27768.37 area after buying pressure emerged around the 27279.66 area, its weakest print since late April.&nbsp; &nbsp;Demand emerged around the 27455.01 area during the climb, representing a test of the 61.8% retracement of the short-term appreciating range from 27279.66 to 27768.37.&nbsp;&nbsp; The move higher to the 27686.67 area represented a test of the 23.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 29139.22 to 27279.66.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 27930, 27990, 28117, 28209, 28261, 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas.&nbsp; Significant buying and selling activity recently took place around the 29298.31 area during the depreciation, an upside price objective linked to buying pressure that increased around the 28122 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives relate to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28476.09 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28121.71.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;26533.04/ 25604.51/ 25094.62 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Set Sail for Wealth with Yachtify (YCHT): Outperforming Uniswap (UNI) and Arbitrum (ARB)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/set-sail-for-wealth-with-yachtify-ycht-outperforming-uniswap-uni-and-arbitrum-arb</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-155535.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-155535.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-155535.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/set-sail-for-wealth-with-yachtify-ycht-outperforming-uniswap-uni-and-arbitrum-arb</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">Yachtify (YCHT) emerges as an innovative investment platform that holds the potential to outshine established cryptocurrencies like Uniswap (UNI) and Arbitrum (ARB). By granting investors access to the exclusive yacht market through fractional ownership, Yachtify (YCHT) paves the way for a unique and lucrative investment opportunity, allowing participants to diversify their portfolios and embark on a voyage toward wealth accumulation.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY YACHTIFY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">Set Sail for Wealth with Yachtify (YCHT)</p>
<p class="s7">Embark on a journey towards financial prosperity with Yachtify (YCHT), a groundbreaking platform that offers investors access to the exclusive yacht market through fractional ownership. As the Yachtify (YCHT) presale approaches, investors are presented with an unparalleled opportunity to secure their position in this thriving market at an attractive entry point of just $0.10 per token.</p>
<p class="s7">The Yachtify (YCHT) presale not only provides a competitive pricing structure but also offers enticing bonuses, making it an even more appealing investment for those seeking long-term growth and portfolio diversification. This innovative platform combines the luxury of yacht ownership with the accessibility and flexibility of fractional ownership, allowing investors to participate in the lucrative yacht market without the financial burden of full ownership.</p>
<p class="s7">By capitalizing on the Yachtify (YCHT) presale, investors can confidently set sail toward financial success, harnessing the potential of this unique investment opportunity. With its competitive pricing, attractive bonuses, and the promise of tapping into an exclusive market, Yachtify (YCHT) is poised to become a sought-after asset among savvy investors looking for an innovative way to propel their portfolio to new heights. Don't miss the chance to embark on this exciting voyage and secure your Yachtify (YCHT) tokens during the presale event.</p>
<p class="s10">Unraveling the Factors Behind Uniswap (UNI) Market Volatility: A Closer Look at the Challenges and Competition</p>
<p class="s7">Uniswap (UNI) has recently experienced significant fluctuations in its value, prompting investors to explore alternative investment options. Since its inception, Uniswap (UNI) has gained prominence for enabling the trading of Ethereum-based tokens. However, the price of Uniswap(UNI) has plummeted from a notable $44 to a humble $6.32, in spite of a recent 11% increase. </p>
<p class="s7">This drop in Uniswap (UNI) value has raised concerns among investors regarding its prospects for long-term returns and its ability to recover its previous standing in the market. Additionally, Uniswap faces increasing competition from emerging decentralized exchange platforms and the ever-evolving crypto landscape. </p>
<p class="s7">Consequently, many investors are turning to alternative investments that display more appealing growth prospects. While optimism for Uniswap (UNI) remains, its ability to attract investor interest and compete with other emerging contenders in the constantly changing crypto landscape is uncertain.</p>
<p class="s10">Arbitrum (ARB): Promising Potential but Disappointing Delivery - The Quest for More Innovative Alternatives</p>
<p class="s7">Arbitrum (ARB) has garnered significant attention within the decentralized finance ecosystem for its potential to enhance the scalability and efficiency of Ethereum-based decentralized applications. However, despite its high potential, Arbitrum (ARB) has struggled to deliver on its promises, leaving investors searching for better alternatives such as Yachtify (YCHT).</p>
<p class="s7">Concerns over the centralization of Arbitrum (ARB) validators have emerged among investors and users, leading to questions about its security and decentralization. Moreover, Arbitrum(ARB) faces tough competition from other layer 2 scaling solutions and faster layer 1 platforms that offer better scalability and efficiency.</p>
<p class="s7">As the search for more innovative and reliable alternatives continues, platforms like Yachtify(YCHT) have risen to prominence. Yachtify offers a unique investment opportunity by granting investors access to the exclusive yacht market through fractional ownership, paving the way for lucrative investments and portfolio diversification. By prioritizing technological advancements, a secure foundation, and dynamic growth potential, Yachtify (YCHT) offers a refreshing outlook on the decentralized finance market, making it a smarter investment option for those seeking long-term returns.</p>
<p class="s7">While Arbitrum (ARB) has high potential, its disappointing delivery and concerns over centralization have left investors searching for better alternatives. Yachtify (YCHT) represents an innovative and reliable alternative that prioritizes technological advancements and dynamic growth potential, making it a smarter investment choice in today's decentralized finance ecosystem.</p>
<p class="s13">Join Presale: https://buy.yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s13">Telegram: https://t.me/yachtify</p>
<p class="s13">Twitter: https://twitter.com/yachtify_market</p>
<p class="s13">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s13">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">Yachtify (YCHT) emerges as an innovative investment platform that holds the potential to outshine established cryptocurrencies like Uniswap (UNI) and Arbitrum (ARB). By granting investors access to the exclusive yacht market through fractional ownership, Yachtify (YCHT) paves the way for a unique and lucrative investment opportunity, allowing participants to diversify their portfolios and embark on a voyage toward wealth accumulation.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY YACHTIFY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">Set Sail for Wealth with Yachtify (YCHT)</p>
<p class="s7">Embark on a journey towards financial prosperity with Yachtify (YCHT), a groundbreaking platform that offers investors access to the exclusive yacht market through fractional ownership. As the Yachtify (YCHT) presale approaches, investors are presented with an unparalleled opportunity to secure their position in this thriving market at an attractive entry point of just $0.10 per token.</p>
<p class="s7">The Yachtify (YCHT) presale not only provides a competitive pricing structure but also offers enticing bonuses, making it an even more appealing investment for those seeking long-term growth and portfolio diversification. This innovative platform combines the luxury of yacht ownership with the accessibility and flexibility of fractional ownership, allowing investors to participate in the lucrative yacht market without the financial burden of full ownership.</p>
<p class="s7">By capitalizing on the Yachtify (YCHT) presale, investors can confidently set sail toward financial success, harnessing the potential of this unique investment opportunity. With its competitive pricing, attractive bonuses, and the promise of tapping into an exclusive market, Yachtify (YCHT) is poised to become a sought-after asset among savvy investors looking for an innovative way to propel their portfolio to new heights. Don't miss the chance to embark on this exciting voyage and secure your Yachtify (YCHT) tokens during the presale event.</p>
<p class="s10">Unraveling the Factors Behind Uniswap (UNI) Market Volatility: A Closer Look at the Challenges and Competition</p>
<p class="s7">Uniswap (UNI) has recently experienced significant fluctuations in its value, prompting investors to explore alternative investment options. Since its inception, Uniswap (UNI) has gained prominence for enabling the trading of Ethereum-based tokens. However, the price of Uniswap(UNI) has plummeted from a notable $44 to a humble $6.32, in spite of a recent 11% increase. </p>
<p class="s7">This drop in Uniswap (UNI) value has raised concerns among investors regarding its prospects for long-term returns and its ability to recover its previous standing in the market. Additionally, Uniswap faces increasing competition from emerging decentralized exchange platforms and the ever-evolving crypto landscape. </p>
<p class="s7">Consequently, many investors are turning to alternative investments that display more appealing growth prospects. While optimism for Uniswap (UNI) remains, its ability to attract investor interest and compete with other emerging contenders in the constantly changing crypto landscape is uncertain.</p>
<p class="s10">Arbitrum (ARB): Promising Potential but Disappointing Delivery - The Quest for More Innovative Alternatives</p>
<p class="s7">Arbitrum (ARB) has garnered significant attention within the decentralized finance ecosystem for its potential to enhance the scalability and efficiency of Ethereum-based decentralized applications. However, despite its high potential, Arbitrum (ARB) has struggled to deliver on its promises, leaving investors searching for better alternatives such as Yachtify (YCHT).</p>
<p class="s7">Concerns over the centralization of Arbitrum (ARB) validators have emerged among investors and users, leading to questions about its security and decentralization. Moreover, Arbitrum(ARB) faces tough competition from other layer 2 scaling solutions and faster layer 1 platforms that offer better scalability and efficiency.</p>
<p class="s7">As the search for more innovative and reliable alternatives continues, platforms like Yachtify(YCHT) have risen to prominence. Yachtify offers a unique investment opportunity by granting investors access to the exclusive yacht market through fractional ownership, paving the way for lucrative investments and portfolio diversification. By prioritizing technological advancements, a secure foundation, and dynamic growth potential, Yachtify (YCHT) offers a refreshing outlook on the decentralized finance market, making it a smarter investment option for those seeking long-term returns.</p>
<p class="s7">While Arbitrum (ARB) has high potential, its disappointing delivery and concerns over centralization have left investors searching for better alternatives. Yachtify (YCHT) represents an innovative and reliable alternative that prioritizes technological advancements and dynamic growth potential, making it a smarter investment choice in today's decentralized finance ecosystem.</p>
<p class="s13">Join Presale: https://buy.yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s13">Telegram: https://t.me/yachtify</p>
<p class="s13">Twitter: https://twitter.com/yachtify_market</p>
<p class="s13">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s13">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[3 Cryptos Under $1 Set For Gains in 2023: The Sandbox (SAND), Chiliz (CHZ), Collateral Network (COLT)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/3-cryptos-under-1-set-for-gains-in-2023-the-sandbox-sand-chiliz-chz-collateral-network-colt</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-154244.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-154244.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-154244.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/3-cryptos-under-1-set-for-gains-in-2023-the-sandbox-sand-chiliz-chz-collateral-network-colt</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With growing inflationary fears and worries about the fundamental health of the banking sector, digital assets have never been more appealing. On-chain data shows hundreds of thousands of fresh wallets being created by new users, and analysts believe that The Sandbox (SAND), Chiliz(CHZ), and Collateral Network (COLT) will be the biggest gainers in 2023. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY COLT TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Collateral Network (COLT) and easy pick with first mover advantageAnalysts stated that Collateral Network (COLT) was an easy pick given its first mover advantage in real-world asset narrative. The protocol leads a new standard in the DeFi lending space, being the first to integrate real-world assets. Asset owners can leverage institutional-level liquidity on Collateral Network (COLT) and unlock capital from their assets. Collateral Network (COLT) uses 100% asset-backed NFTs to achieve this and powers new liquidity options for owners worldwide. Collateral Network (COLT) delivers much-needed updates to the asset-backed lending industry famously held back by bureaucracy and allows permissionless access to its services. Functioning as a multi-sided platform, borrowers unlock liquidity, lenders earn passive income on stable assets, and it opens the path for millions, perhaps billions of dollars, to be onboarded into DeFi. Analysts have forecast a 3,500% surge in the coming weeks. With plans to launch on various major centralized exchanges featured in the protocol&rsquo;s roadmap, several analysts further predicted 100X for early presale participants. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY COLT TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Is The Sandbox (SAND) a good investment?The Sandbox (SAND) is a metaverse open economy allowing users to interact digitally and own their gaming experience through holding NFTs. The Sandbox (SAND) is one of the big three metaverse land brokers, and all land purchases require The Sandbox (SAND) native token, giving it a great source of buy pressure. Analysts expect The Sandbox (SAND) to trade between $1.07 and $1.27 in 2023, citing increased curiosity in the metaverse. The Sandbox (SAND) underwent a brutal period in 2022 as metaverse funding dried up, but with bolstered market sentiment, funding slowly returns to The Sandbox (SAND) and other metaverse projects. The Sandbox (SAND) has also recently worked on integrating new NFT projects into its metaverse, such as CyberKongz. The ability to use an NFT as an avatar naturally gives more people a reason to visit The Sandbox (SAND) and could drive significant growth in 2023. </p>
<p>How much could Chiliz (CHZ) be worth?Chiliz (CHZ) blends blockchain and sports. It gives fans a more direct role in club governance and allows sports teams to monetize their supporter base more effectively. Fans purchase Chiliz(CHZ) tokens and exchange them for club-specific tokens on the Socios platform. Chiliz (CHZ) remains the most significant sports and entertainment crypto project and recently launched its own layer one blockchain. Analysts expect Chiliz (CHZ) could trade between $0.22 and $0.28 by the end of the year, listing the massive partnerships Chiliz (CHZ) has secured to validate their bullish predictions. The most recent partnership Chiliz (CHZ) engaged in was with Sony Pictures for the launch of Spider-Man, and with this caliber of partnership, Chiliz (CHZ) could take off in 2023.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Collateral Network presale here:</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://www.collateralnetwork.io/</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: https://app.collateralnetwork.io/register</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/collateralnwk</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Collateralnwk</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With growing inflationary fears and worries about the fundamental health of the banking sector, digital assets have never been more appealing. On-chain data shows hundreds of thousands of fresh wallets being created by new users, and analysts believe that The Sandbox (SAND), Chiliz(CHZ), and Collateral Network (COLT) will be the biggest gainers in 2023. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY COLT TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Collateral Network (COLT) and easy pick with first mover advantageAnalysts stated that Collateral Network (COLT) was an easy pick given its first mover advantage in real-world asset narrative. The protocol leads a new standard in the DeFi lending space, being the first to integrate real-world assets. Asset owners can leverage institutional-level liquidity on Collateral Network (COLT) and unlock capital from their assets. Collateral Network (COLT) uses 100% asset-backed NFTs to achieve this and powers new liquidity options for owners worldwide. Collateral Network (COLT) delivers much-needed updates to the asset-backed lending industry famously held back by bureaucracy and allows permissionless access to its services. Functioning as a multi-sided platform, borrowers unlock liquidity, lenders earn passive income on stable assets, and it opens the path for millions, perhaps billions of dollars, to be onboarded into DeFi. Analysts have forecast a 3,500% surge in the coming weeks. With plans to launch on various major centralized exchanges featured in the protocol&rsquo;s roadmap, several analysts further predicted 100X for early presale participants. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY COLT TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Is The Sandbox (SAND) a good investment?The Sandbox (SAND) is a metaverse open economy allowing users to interact digitally and own their gaming experience through holding NFTs. The Sandbox (SAND) is one of the big three metaverse land brokers, and all land purchases require The Sandbox (SAND) native token, giving it a great source of buy pressure. Analysts expect The Sandbox (SAND) to trade between $1.07 and $1.27 in 2023, citing increased curiosity in the metaverse. The Sandbox (SAND) underwent a brutal period in 2022 as metaverse funding dried up, but with bolstered market sentiment, funding slowly returns to The Sandbox (SAND) and other metaverse projects. The Sandbox (SAND) has also recently worked on integrating new NFT projects into its metaverse, such as CyberKongz. The ability to use an NFT as an avatar naturally gives more people a reason to visit The Sandbox (SAND) and could drive significant growth in 2023. </p>
<p>How much could Chiliz (CHZ) be worth?Chiliz (CHZ) blends blockchain and sports. It gives fans a more direct role in club governance and allows sports teams to monetize their supporter base more effectively. Fans purchase Chiliz(CHZ) tokens and exchange them for club-specific tokens on the Socios platform. Chiliz (CHZ) remains the most significant sports and entertainment crypto project and recently launched its own layer one blockchain. Analysts expect Chiliz (CHZ) could trade between $0.22 and $0.28 by the end of the year, listing the massive partnerships Chiliz (CHZ) has secured to validate their bullish predictions. The most recent partnership Chiliz (CHZ) engaged in was with Sony Pictures for the launch of Spider-Man, and with this caliber of partnership, Chiliz (CHZ) could take off in 2023.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Collateral Network presale here:</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://www.collateralnetwork.io/</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: https://app.collateralnetwork.io/register</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/collateralnwk</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Collateralnwk</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC Faces Major Congestion Issues, Crypto Daily TV 9/5/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-faces-major-congestion-issues-crypto-daily-tv-9-5-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-issues-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-issues-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-issues-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-faces-major-congestion-issues-crypto-daily-tv-9-5-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Peer-to-peer Bitcoin exchange Paxful back online</p>
<p>Peer-to-peer bitcoin exchange Paxful has resumed operations after being shut down for over a month. Paxful shut down in April after CEO Ray Youssef expressed concerns about the safety of customer funds as a result of a lawsuit by co-founder Artur Schaback, who sued Youssef and the company for wrongful termination.</p>
<p>Pepecoin drops nearly 45%</p>
<p>Pepecoin holders may be taking profits on their positions following one of the most spectacular rises in the history of altcoins with an almost 5,000,000% rise in the past few weeks. The tokens are down nearly 45% after setting a peak last week</p>
<p>Meme-coin mania, Binance congestion issues</p>
<p>The largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization was recently trading at around $27,350, as investors continued to mull over a surge in interest in the PEPE meme coin and Binance congestion issues that forced the exchange giant to temporarily suspend bitcoin withdrawals over the weekend.</p>
BTC/USD plummeted 3.3% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 3.3% in the last session. The CCI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 279901 and Resistance is at 294121.</p>
<p>The CCI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD dove 1.6% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 1.6% in the last session. According to the Williams indicator, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 1830.6433 and Resistance is at 1951.5433.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD plummeted 6.1% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair plummeted 6.1% in the last session. The ROC's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 0.4377 and Resistance is at 0.4658.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD plummeted 7.7% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dropped 7.7% in the last session after rising as much as 2.3% during the session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 82.0133 and Resistance is at 85.3733.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP JP Foreign Reserves</p>
<p>The Foreign Reserves are the total of a country's gold holdings and convertible foreign currencies held by its central bank. Japan's JP Foreign Reserves will be released at 23:50 GMT, the French Exports at 06:45 GMT, and Japan's 10-y Bond Auction at 03:35 GMT.</p>
<p>FR Exports</p>
<p>The Exports measure the total exports of goods and services by the local economy. Steady demand for exports helps to support growth in the trade surplus.</p>
<p>JP 10-y Bond Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bonds auctioned off. Yields are set by bond market investors, and therefore they can be used to estimate investors' outlook on future interest rates.</p>
<p>US NFIB Business Optimism Index</p>
<p>The NFIB Business Optimism Index is the result of Small Business Economic Trends data collected from quarterly surveys since 1974 and monthly surveys since 1986. The US NFIB Business Optimism Index will be released at 10:00 GMT, the French Imports at 06:45 GMT, and the US Redbook Index at 12:55 GMT.</p>
<p>FR Imports</p>
<p>Imports of goods and services consist of transactions in goods and services (purchases, barter, gifts, or grants) from non-residents to residents. </p>
<p>US Redbook Index</p>
<p>The Johnson Redbook Index measures the year-over-year same-store sales growth from a sample of large general merchandise retailers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Peer-to-peer Bitcoin exchange Paxful back online</p>
<p>Peer-to-peer bitcoin exchange Paxful has resumed operations after being shut down for over a month. Paxful shut down in April after CEO Ray Youssef expressed concerns about the safety of customer funds as a result of a lawsuit by co-founder Artur Schaback, who sued Youssef and the company for wrongful termination.</p>
<p>Pepecoin drops nearly 45%</p>
<p>Pepecoin holders may be taking profits on their positions following one of the most spectacular rises in the history of altcoins with an almost 5,000,000% rise in the past few weeks. The tokens are down nearly 45% after setting a peak last week</p>
<p>Meme-coin mania, Binance congestion issues</p>
<p>The largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization was recently trading at around $27,350, as investors continued to mull over a surge in interest in the PEPE meme coin and Binance congestion issues that forced the exchange giant to temporarily suspend bitcoin withdrawals over the weekend.</p>
BTC/USD plummeted 3.3% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 3.3% in the last session. The CCI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 279901 and Resistance is at 294121.</p>
<p>The CCI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD dove 1.6% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 1.6% in the last session. According to the Williams indicator, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 1830.6433 and Resistance is at 1951.5433.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD plummeted 6.1% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair plummeted 6.1% in the last session. The ROC's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 0.4377 and Resistance is at 0.4658.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD plummeted 7.7% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dropped 7.7% in the last session after rising as much as 2.3% during the session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 82.0133 and Resistance is at 85.3733.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP JP Foreign Reserves</p>
<p>The Foreign Reserves are the total of a country's gold holdings and convertible foreign currencies held by its central bank. Japan's JP Foreign Reserves will be released at 23:50 GMT, the French Exports at 06:45 GMT, and Japan's 10-y Bond Auction at 03:35 GMT.</p>
<p>FR Exports</p>
<p>The Exports measure the total exports of goods and services by the local economy. Steady demand for exports helps to support growth in the trade surplus.</p>
<p>JP 10-y Bond Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bonds auctioned off. Yields are set by bond market investors, and therefore they can be used to estimate investors' outlook on future interest rates.</p>
<p>US NFIB Business Optimism Index</p>
<p>The NFIB Business Optimism Index is the result of Small Business Economic Trends data collected from quarterly surveys since 1974 and monthly surveys since 1986. The US NFIB Business Optimism Index will be released at 10:00 GMT, the French Imports at 06:45 GMT, and the US Redbook Index at 12:55 GMT.</p>
<p>FR Imports</p>
<p>Imports of goods and services consist of transactions in goods and services (purchases, barter, gifts, or grants) from non-residents to residents. </p>
<p>US Redbook Index</p>
<p>The Johnson Redbook Index measures the year-over-year same-store sales growth from a sample of large general merchandise retailers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tradecurve (TCRV) Set For 100x Growth Can Uniswap (UNI) And Decentraland (MANA) Challenge?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tradecurve-tcrv-set-for-100x-growth-can-uniswap-uni-and-decentraland-mana-challenge</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-152921.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-152921.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-152921.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tradecurve-tcrv-set-for-100x-growth-can-uniswap-uni-and-decentraland-mana-challenge</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Investing early in a growth-bound project is considered the most profitable investment strategy. Market bulls usually follow this strategy, and have done it again with Tradecurve. Soon after the presale of Tradecurve was launched, investors started to accumulate a large number of TCRV tokens. It is projected to rise 50x during the presale phase, and 100x upon launch. On the contrary, Decentraland (MANA) and Uniswap (UNI) have lost their growth momentum.</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s9">Uniswap (UNI) Crosses $1.5 Trillion In Trading Volume</p>
<p class="s6">The decentralized crypto exchange, Uniswap (UNI), has crossed a major milestone by trading volume. According to the latest data, Uniswap (UNI) has officially passed $1.5 trillion in trading volume. The Uniswap (UNI) exchange has witnessed a cumulative trading volume increase of $500 billion since April 2022. According to experts, Uniswap&rsquo;s (UNI) developmental measures taken in the past few months have been the primary reason behind the increased trading volume of the exchange. Recently, Uniswap (UNI) successfully secured approval from Apple&rsquo;s App Store for its iOS mobile app, which can increase its trade volume further. Meanwhile, the price of Uniswap (UNI) has increased by 3% in the past week. Currently, Uniswap (UNI) is changing hands at $5.61.</p>
<p class="s9">Decentraland (MANA) Falls Vertically</p>
<p class="s6">Amid the fizzling hype around the metaverse-based cryptocurrencies, Decentraland (MANA) has been pushing forward with new initiatives to increase its market presence. However, the price movement of Decentraland (MANA) has not followed the projects&rsquo; development. The market value of Decentraland (MANA) has plunged by 7% in the past month. Consequently, Decentraland (MANA) is currently trading at $0.56. The much-anticipated 2023 Metaverse Fashion Week of Decentraland (MANA) failed to attract users, due to the declining popularity of the project. Now, in the latest event, Decentraland (MANA) has partnered with Fidelity International to build an education-based metaverse. However, investors are worried whether Decentraland (MANA) will ever be able to regain its market, as the user count on the platform is continuously declining.</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s9">Tradecurve (TCRV) Shows The Best Growth Potential</p>
<p class="s6">There are many exchanges that allow the trade of cryptocurrencies, while others facilitate the trading of traditional instruments like equities, bonds, ETFs, Options, commodities, and more. However, there was an absence of a platform that enabled trading of all asset classes under a single hood, until the launch of Tradecurve.io </p>
<p class="s6">It is a Web3 trading exchange that allows the trading of a wide range of assets, without FIAT payments. Notably, the cryptocurrency market size was expected to showcase a CAGR of 12.8% from 2021 to 2030. Besides, a survey has indicated that 71% of top global investors expect the trading of equities to grow in 2023. Hence, Tradecurve has massive growth potential, and bulls are buoyed by this. &nbsp; </p>
<p class="s6">On this platform, traders can open an account using an email ID, and begin trading without any KYC process. Moreover, its users hold their keys, and control their assets. The platform also protects users&rsquo; privacy through DeFi capabilities, unlike platforms like Binance, which has mandated the completion of KYC before trading. &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Tradecurve's presale phase is live, and currently in its first stage. TCRV tokens are currently available at $0.01, and only 40% of the total 1.8 billion tokens will be supplied during the presale phase.</p>
<p class="s6">Register for the presale by following the links below</p>
<p class="s6">Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s6">Website: https://tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s6">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Investing early in a growth-bound project is considered the most profitable investment strategy. Market bulls usually follow this strategy, and have done it again with Tradecurve. Soon after the presale of Tradecurve was launched, investors started to accumulate a large number of TCRV tokens. It is projected to rise 50x during the presale phase, and 100x upon launch. On the contrary, Decentraland (MANA) and Uniswap (UNI) have lost their growth momentum.</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s9">Uniswap (UNI) Crosses $1.5 Trillion In Trading Volume</p>
<p class="s6">The decentralized crypto exchange, Uniswap (UNI), has crossed a major milestone by trading volume. According to the latest data, Uniswap (UNI) has officially passed $1.5 trillion in trading volume. The Uniswap (UNI) exchange has witnessed a cumulative trading volume increase of $500 billion since April 2022. According to experts, Uniswap&rsquo;s (UNI) developmental measures taken in the past few months have been the primary reason behind the increased trading volume of the exchange. Recently, Uniswap (UNI) successfully secured approval from Apple&rsquo;s App Store for its iOS mobile app, which can increase its trade volume further. Meanwhile, the price of Uniswap (UNI) has increased by 3% in the past week. Currently, Uniswap (UNI) is changing hands at $5.61.</p>
<p class="s9">Decentraland (MANA) Falls Vertically</p>
<p class="s6">Amid the fizzling hype around the metaverse-based cryptocurrencies, Decentraland (MANA) has been pushing forward with new initiatives to increase its market presence. However, the price movement of Decentraland (MANA) has not followed the projects&rsquo; development. The market value of Decentraland (MANA) has plunged by 7% in the past month. Consequently, Decentraland (MANA) is currently trading at $0.56. The much-anticipated 2023 Metaverse Fashion Week of Decentraland (MANA) failed to attract users, due to the declining popularity of the project. Now, in the latest event, Decentraland (MANA) has partnered with Fidelity International to build an education-based metaverse. However, investors are worried whether Decentraland (MANA) will ever be able to regain its market, as the user count on the platform is continuously declining.</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s9">Tradecurve (TCRV) Shows The Best Growth Potential</p>
<p class="s6">There are many exchanges that allow the trade of cryptocurrencies, while others facilitate the trading of traditional instruments like equities, bonds, ETFs, Options, commodities, and more. However, there was an absence of a platform that enabled trading of all asset classes under a single hood, until the launch of Tradecurve.io </p>
<p class="s6">It is a Web3 trading exchange that allows the trading of a wide range of assets, without FIAT payments. Notably, the cryptocurrency market size was expected to showcase a CAGR of 12.8% from 2021 to 2030. Besides, a survey has indicated that 71% of top global investors expect the trading of equities to grow in 2023. Hence, Tradecurve has massive growth potential, and bulls are buoyed by this. &nbsp; </p>
<p class="s6">On this platform, traders can open an account using an email ID, and begin trading without any KYC process. Moreover, its users hold their keys, and control their assets. The platform also protects users&rsquo; privacy through DeFi capabilities, unlike platforms like Binance, which has mandated the completion of KYC before trading. &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Tradecurve's presale phase is live, and currently in its first stage. TCRV tokens are currently available at $0.01, and only 40% of the total 1.8 billion tokens will be supplied during the presale phase.</p>
<p class="s6">Register for the presale by following the links below</p>
<p class="s6">Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s6">Website: https://tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s6">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Monero (XRM) and Stellar (XMR) Slow Down While Sparklo (SPRK) Leaps Ahead]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/monero-xrm-and-stellar-xmr-slow-down-while-sparklo-sprk-leaps-ahead</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-153335.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-153335.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-09-at-153335.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/monero-xrm-and-stellar-xmr-slow-down-while-sparklo-sprk-leaps-ahead</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Across the traditional financial space, many centralized banks have begun to collapse and to get close. The distrust in centralized, traditional industries, as a result, has been lowering on an annual basis.</p>
<p class="s5">Many investors and traders are turning towards cryptocurrencies as alternatives.</p>
<p class="s5">Today, we will be going over the performance of Monero (XRM) and Stellar (XMR) and see why they have stagnated in value while presale-stage projects such as Sparklo have managed to get ahead with their momentum.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Sparklo (SPRK) To Make Precious Metals Easily Accessible</p>
<p class="s5">Sparklo is being developed as an alternative investment platform that will enable anyone the opportunity to make investments in and begin trading precious metals.</p>
<p class="s5">On top of the platform, every time an investor aim to make an investment in the asset class, a non-fungible token (NFT) gets minted. Then, this NFT is fractionalized. Investors have the opportunity to either buy a fraction of it or buy the entire NFT. If an investor buys an entire NFT that represents a gold bar, for example, they can get the real-world asset delivered to them at any location.</p>
<p class="s5">The platform has already been audited by InterFi Network, and the liquidity will also be locked for 100 years. At the level one presale stage, the SPRK token trades at a value of just $0.017. Analysts have predicted that its value can increase by 4,000% throughout the span of the upcoming few months, and savvy investors know that the most significant gains can be made by getting into it early.</p>
<p class="s9">Monero (XRM) Sees a Decrease of 3.2%</p>
<p class="s5">Monero (XRM) made an announcement where they celebrated their ninth birthday. This makes Monero (XRM) one of the oldest blockchain-based projects out there that is relevant to this day. Additionally, we saw the MoneroKon 2023 preliminary schedule go live.</p>
<p class="s5">As for the value of the Monero (XRM) cryptocurrency, on May 2, 2023, it traded at $154.51. In the last 30 days, Monero (XRM) saw a drop of just 1.5%, and in the last 14 days, this decrease has been at 3.2%. As such, it is clear why some investors might be interested in diversifying away from Monero (XRM).</p>
<p class="s9">Stellar (XMR) Enters Red Zone With A Drop of 14.7%</p>
<p class="s5">The team behind Stellar (XMR) took to Twitter to announce that the Stellar Community Fund is in Round 15 and is accepting submissions up until May 14. Moreover, the team also noted that Stellar (XMR) Questers, a new quest, went live, which teaches community members the power of "Muxed Account IDs."</p>
<p class="s5">As for the value of the Stellar (XMR) cryptocurrency, on May 2, 2023, it traded at $0.092464.</p>
<p class="s5">In the last 30 days, Stellar (XMR) saw a decrease in its value by 14.7%, and in the last 14 days, its overall decrease was at 11.2%. It is clear why Stellar (XMR) wants to diversify.</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p class="s12">Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Across the traditional financial space, many centralized banks have begun to collapse and to get close. The distrust in centralized, traditional industries, as a result, has been lowering on an annual basis.</p>
<p class="s5">Many investors and traders are turning towards cryptocurrencies as alternatives.</p>
<p class="s5">Today, we will be going over the performance of Monero (XRM) and Stellar (XMR) and see why they have stagnated in value while presale-stage projects such as Sparklo have managed to get ahead with their momentum.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Sparklo (SPRK) To Make Precious Metals Easily Accessible</p>
<p class="s5">Sparklo is being developed as an alternative investment platform that will enable anyone the opportunity to make investments in and begin trading precious metals.</p>
<p class="s5">On top of the platform, every time an investor aim to make an investment in the asset class, a non-fungible token (NFT) gets minted. Then, this NFT is fractionalized. Investors have the opportunity to either buy a fraction of it or buy the entire NFT. If an investor buys an entire NFT that represents a gold bar, for example, they can get the real-world asset delivered to them at any location.</p>
<p class="s5">The platform has already been audited by InterFi Network, and the liquidity will also be locked for 100 years. At the level one presale stage, the SPRK token trades at a value of just $0.017. Analysts have predicted that its value can increase by 4,000% throughout the span of the upcoming few months, and savvy investors know that the most significant gains can be made by getting into it early.</p>
<p class="s9">Monero (XRM) Sees a Decrease of 3.2%</p>
<p class="s5">Monero (XRM) made an announcement where they celebrated their ninth birthday. This makes Monero (XRM) one of the oldest blockchain-based projects out there that is relevant to this day. Additionally, we saw the MoneroKon 2023 preliminary schedule go live.</p>
<p class="s5">As for the value of the Monero (XRM) cryptocurrency, on May 2, 2023, it traded at $154.51. In the last 30 days, Monero (XRM) saw a drop of just 1.5%, and in the last 14 days, this decrease has been at 3.2%. As such, it is clear why some investors might be interested in diversifying away from Monero (XRM).</p>
<p class="s9">Stellar (XMR) Enters Red Zone With A Drop of 14.7%</p>
<p class="s5">The team behind Stellar (XMR) took to Twitter to announce that the Stellar Community Fund is in Round 15 and is accepting submissions up until May 14. Moreover, the team also noted that Stellar (XMR) Questers, a new quest, went live, which teaches community members the power of "Muxed Account IDs."</p>
<p class="s5">As for the value of the Stellar (XMR) cryptocurrency, on May 2, 2023, it traded at $0.092464.</p>
<p class="s5">In the last 30 days, Stellar (XMR) saw a decrease in its value by 14.7%, and in the last 14 days, its overall decrease was at 11.2%. It is clear why Stellar (XMR) wants to diversify.</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p class="s12">Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[4 Predictions for The Future of Crypto in 2023: NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP), StableXSwap (STAX) and Uwerx (WERX) Can Reach 10x In Value]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/4-predictions-for-the-future-of-crypto-in-2023-near-protocol-near-optimism-op-stablexswap-stax-and-uwerx-werx-can-reach-10x-in-value</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5217.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5217.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5217.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/4-predictions-for-the-future-of-crypto-in-2023-near-protocol-near-optimism-op-stablexswap-stax-and-uwerx-werx-can-reach-10x-in-value</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s4">With over 22,900 coin and token options for investors and traders to pick from, it can be difficult to distinguish blockchain-based projects that are primed for success from others that might fail.</p>
<p class="s4">Based on analytical data, price predictions, and the overall performance of the market, NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP), StableXSwap (STAX), and Uwerx might just be the best four cryptocurrencies to consider in 2023. Uwerx has stood out due to the success of its presale, and today, we will go over why this has been the case.</p>
<p class="s8">The Value Behind NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP) and StableXSwap (STAX)</p>
<p class="s4">Based on the price prediction made for the NEAR Protocol (NEAR) coin, its value can climb to a maximum of $2.93 by Q4, 2023.</p>
<p class="s4">As for its value in Q3 of 2025, NEAR Protocol (NEAR) coin can climb to $6.34. This price prediction indicates a bullish outlook for the NEAR Protocol (NEAR) coin.</p>
<p class="s4">Then there is the Optimism (OP) token, trading at $2.56 as of March 15, 2023. Price predictions were also made for the future of the Optimism (OP) token, where they showcase that by the end of Q4 2023, its maximum value will equal $3.68. As for Its performance by the end of 2025, the Optimism (OP) token can climb to $7.43.</p>
<p class="s4">The StableXSwap (STAX) token also has growth potential, trading at $0.243181 as of March 15, 2023. Analysts familiar with the StableXSwap (STAX) token have predicted that by the end of Q4 2023, it can climb to $0.43.</p>
<p class="s4">As for its future in 2025, by the end of the year, the StableXSwap (STAX) token can reach a value of $0.88.</p>
<p class="s4">It is clear that NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP), and StableXSwap (STAX) are all solid options for traders and investors, but there is an altcoin that can climb in value much further based on the success of its current presale, and that token is WERX.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): A Stands Out Freelance Platform</p>
<p class="s4">Remote work models are increasing in popularity and appeal, and the freelancer space has grown exponentially over the past few years.</p>
<p class="s4">&ldquo;Freelancers now represent 46.5% of the global workforce&rdquo;, reported Freelance Informer.</p>
<p class="s4">Companies have also begun to realize the advantages, and some of the biggest names on a global scale are beginning to adopt the freelance model.</p>
<p class="s4">Centralized freelancer platforms, however, have issued, such as delays in payments, lack of transparency, and high fees at an average of 20%.</p>
<p class="s4">Based on the Polygon Network, Uwerx is a platform that aims to make it quicker and cheaper for freelancers and companies to connect and work together toward realizing specific projects and tasks. </p>
<p class="s4">Uwerx is being developed as a decentralized platform that establishes a trustless alternative that only charges a 1% fee and provides far more value and features than any centralized platform.</p>
<p class="s4">Being built on top of a blockchain, it enables immutable records, smart contract support, and access to a distributed ledger that records everything transparently.</p>
<p class="s4">With built-in collaboration tools, personalized matching. With a built-in system for resolving disputes and transparent pricing, Uwerx can become a major player in the freelancer and Web3 space.</p>
<p class="s8">The True Value Of The Uwerx (WERX) Presale and its Future</p>
<p class="s4">At the start of the Presale, the WERX token, the native cryptocurrency behind the Uwerx project, is offered at a value of $0.012. The liquidity will be locked for 25 years once the presale ends. As for the platform's security, Uwerx was audited by InterFi Network and SolidProof ahead of the presale.</p>
<p class="s4">Investors and traders who want to take up the opportunity and get engaged in the early stages of a project that we believe will become a dominant force in the Web3 space can do so by visiting the links below. </p>
<p class="s4">Another price increase is due soon, and so is the Alpha version of the platform - we think now is the best time to invest, follow the links below to find out more!</p>
<p class="s4">Find Out More Here: </p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s4">With over 22,900 coin and token options for investors and traders to pick from, it can be difficult to distinguish blockchain-based projects that are primed for success from others that might fail.</p>
<p class="s4">Based on analytical data, price predictions, and the overall performance of the market, NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP), StableXSwap (STAX), and Uwerx might just be the best four cryptocurrencies to consider in 2023. Uwerx has stood out due to the success of its presale, and today, we will go over why this has been the case.</p>
<p class="s8">The Value Behind NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP) and StableXSwap (STAX)</p>
<p class="s4">Based on the price prediction made for the NEAR Protocol (NEAR) coin, its value can climb to a maximum of $2.93 by Q4, 2023.</p>
<p class="s4">As for its value in Q3 of 2025, NEAR Protocol (NEAR) coin can climb to $6.34. This price prediction indicates a bullish outlook for the NEAR Protocol (NEAR) coin.</p>
<p class="s4">Then there is the Optimism (OP) token, trading at $2.56 as of March 15, 2023. Price predictions were also made for the future of the Optimism (OP) token, where they showcase that by the end of Q4 2023, its maximum value will equal $3.68. As for Its performance by the end of 2025, the Optimism (OP) token can climb to $7.43.</p>
<p class="s4">The StableXSwap (STAX) token also has growth potential, trading at $0.243181 as of March 15, 2023. Analysts familiar with the StableXSwap (STAX) token have predicted that by the end of Q4 2023, it can climb to $0.43.</p>
<p class="s4">As for its future in 2025, by the end of the year, the StableXSwap (STAX) token can reach a value of $0.88.</p>
<p class="s4">It is clear that NEAR Protocol (NEAR), Optimism (OP), and StableXSwap (STAX) are all solid options for traders and investors, but there is an altcoin that can climb in value much further based on the success of its current presale, and that token is WERX.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): A Stands Out Freelance Platform</p>
<p class="s4">Remote work models are increasing in popularity and appeal, and the freelancer space has grown exponentially over the past few years.</p>
<p class="s4">&ldquo;Freelancers now represent 46.5% of the global workforce&rdquo;, reported Freelance Informer.</p>
<p class="s4">Companies have also begun to realize the advantages, and some of the biggest names on a global scale are beginning to adopt the freelance model.</p>
<p class="s4">Centralized freelancer platforms, however, have issued, such as delays in payments, lack of transparency, and high fees at an average of 20%.</p>
<p class="s4">Based on the Polygon Network, Uwerx is a platform that aims to make it quicker and cheaper for freelancers and companies to connect and work together toward realizing specific projects and tasks. </p>
<p class="s4">Uwerx is being developed as a decentralized platform that establishes a trustless alternative that only charges a 1% fee and provides far more value and features than any centralized platform.</p>
<p class="s4">Being built on top of a blockchain, it enables immutable records, smart contract support, and access to a distributed ledger that records everything transparently.</p>
<p class="s4">With built-in collaboration tools, personalized matching. With a built-in system for resolving disputes and transparent pricing, Uwerx can become a major player in the freelancer and Web3 space.</p>
<p class="s8">The True Value Of The Uwerx (WERX) Presale and its Future</p>
<p class="s4">At the start of the Presale, the WERX token, the native cryptocurrency behind the Uwerx project, is offered at a value of $0.012. The liquidity will be locked for 25 years once the presale ends. As for the platform's security, Uwerx was audited by InterFi Network and SolidProof ahead of the presale.</p>
<p class="s4">Investors and traders who want to take up the opportunity and get engaged in the early stages of a project that we believe will become a dominant force in the Web3 space can do so by visiting the links below. </p>
<p class="s4">Another price increase is due soon, and so is the Alpha version of the platform - we think now is the best time to invest, follow the links below to find out more!</p>
<p class="s4">Find Out More Here: </p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[DSCVR Passes 200k User Milestone]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/dscvr-passes-200k-user-milestone</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Untitled_design_6_1683633854AMJJEb8jS0.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Untitled_design_6_1683633854AMJJEb8jS0.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Untitled_design_6_1683633854AMJJEb8jS0.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:05:40 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/dscvr-passes-200k-user-milestone</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Los Angeles, California, May 9th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Retains Crown as Web3&rsquo;s Biggest Social Network and SocialFi Platform</p><p>DSCVR, the largest and most popular Web3 social network and social finance (SocialFi) platform, has surpassed the 200,000 user mark &ndash; a key milestone on its journey towards making crypto functionality easily accessible to anyone who knows how to use social media.</p><p>DSCVR&rsquo;s focus on coupling familiar social media experiences with the most diverse set of crypto features available in Web3 has made it an appealing choice for content creators, crypto projects, and community builders alike.&nbsp;</p><p>DSCVR is not just a social media platform, it is also an easy-to-navigate SocialFi economy. In the two years since its launch, a total of 6.7 million tokens have been transacted on the platform: a real demonstration of its users&rsquo; growing economic power.&nbsp;</p><p>A wide range of easy-to-use tools allow DSCVR&rsquo;s loyal and expanding user base to create, collaborate on, share, and monetize content, to interact with the creators they admire, and to interact with &ndash; and even build &ndash; user-governed communities tailored to their interests.&nbsp;</p><p>Communities and individual creators can earn digital assets through tips, airdrops, or NFT sales. Users can then choose how to deploy these profits &ndash; by putting them back into the community, for instance, or perhaps directing them toward a cause favored by members.&nbsp;</p><p>Users, meanwhile, can show their appreciation of content they admire through tips. Users can also send and receive airdrops and transfer tokens throughout the platform &ndash; all without ever having to set up a wallet.&nbsp;</p><p>DSCVR offers all the features users find most convenient about Web2 social platforms while making Web3 functionality more accessible than ever. Value flows seamlessly through the platform in the form of tokens, which can be easily shared or transacted. Users are building tokenized communities called portals around fungible tokens, NFTs, and Web3 games. Portals give ownership to communities by granting roles and permissions based on token holding.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>Further, DSCVR stays true to its Web3 ethos by emphasizing user ownership. With DSCVR, individuals can decide how to monetize their content, and what shows up in their feeds, and can even have a voice in the direction of the platform itself. The network also offers users a degree of financial power unheard of in Web2.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;Users, creators, and communities are increasingly frustrated by mainstream social media platforms with their limitations, unexpected rule changes, and opaque power structures,&rdquo; said DSCVR CEO Rick Porter.Rick added: "The future of social media lies in giving power back to users. They should be able to make their own decisions about how to structure their communities, how and with whom they connect, and whether and how to monetize their content. By giving users sway over their creations and their communities, DSCVR is leading the way in this movement.&rdquo;&nbsp;<p>With more than 200k users, 20M posts, comments and upvotes and more than 6.7 million tokens transacted, the network's continued growth is a testament to its potential to shape the future of social media.&nbsp;</p><p>Join the revolution with DSCVR and be part of the future of online communities.</p><p>About DSCVR</p><p>DSCVR (pronounced &ldquo;Discover&rdquo;) is a boundary-breaking Web3 social network that combines a familiar social media context with underlying crypto and fintech functionality. The most rapidly adopted Web3 social media network, DSCVR is also the largest.&nbsp;</p><p>By coupling the accessibility of Web2 platforms with the most diverse set of crypto features available in decentralized social media, DSCVR has become the social media and SocialFi network of choice for content creators and community builders. The platform has become a launchpad for tokenized communities where users can gate based on token ownership, configure governance, airdrop token rewards, and earn digital assets.&nbsp;</p>ContactMary Victoria MorenoAngle42maryvictoria@angle42.co]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Los Angeles, California, May 9th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Retains Crown as Web3&rsquo;s Biggest Social Network and SocialFi Platform</p><p>DSCVR, the largest and most popular Web3 social network and social finance (SocialFi) platform, has surpassed the 200,000 user mark &ndash; a key milestone on its journey towards making crypto functionality easily accessible to anyone who knows how to use social media.</p><p>DSCVR&rsquo;s focus on coupling familiar social media experiences with the most diverse set of crypto features available in Web3 has made it an appealing choice for content creators, crypto projects, and community builders alike.&nbsp;</p><p>DSCVR is not just a social media platform, it is also an easy-to-navigate SocialFi economy. In the two years since its launch, a total of 6.7 million tokens have been transacted on the platform: a real demonstration of its users&rsquo; growing economic power.&nbsp;</p><p>A wide range of easy-to-use tools allow DSCVR&rsquo;s loyal and expanding user base to create, collaborate on, share, and monetize content, to interact with the creators they admire, and to interact with &ndash; and even build &ndash; user-governed communities tailored to their interests.&nbsp;</p><p>Communities and individual creators can earn digital assets through tips, airdrops, or NFT sales. Users can then choose how to deploy these profits &ndash; by putting them back into the community, for instance, or perhaps directing them toward a cause favored by members.&nbsp;</p><p>Users, meanwhile, can show their appreciation of content they admire through tips. Users can also send and receive airdrops and transfer tokens throughout the platform &ndash; all without ever having to set up a wallet.&nbsp;</p><p>DSCVR offers all the features users find most convenient about Web2 social platforms while making Web3 functionality more accessible than ever. Value flows seamlessly through the platform in the form of tokens, which can be easily shared or transacted. Users are building tokenized communities called portals around fungible tokens, NFTs, and Web3 games. Portals give ownership to communities by granting roles and permissions based on token holding.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>Further, DSCVR stays true to its Web3 ethos by emphasizing user ownership. With DSCVR, individuals can decide how to monetize their content, and what shows up in their feeds, and can even have a voice in the direction of the platform itself. The network also offers users a degree of financial power unheard of in Web2.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;Users, creators, and communities are increasingly frustrated by mainstream social media platforms with their limitations, unexpected rule changes, and opaque power structures,&rdquo; said DSCVR CEO Rick Porter.Rick added: "The future of social media lies in giving power back to users. They should be able to make their own decisions about how to structure their communities, how and with whom they connect, and whether and how to monetize their content. By giving users sway over their creations and their communities, DSCVR is leading the way in this movement.&rdquo;&nbsp;<p>With more than 200k users, 20M posts, comments and upvotes and more than 6.7 million tokens transacted, the network's continued growth is a testament to its potential to shape the future of social media.&nbsp;</p><p>Join the revolution with DSCVR and be part of the future of online communities.</p><p>About DSCVR</p><p>DSCVR (pronounced &ldquo;Discover&rdquo;) is a boundary-breaking Web3 social network that combines a familiar social media context with underlying crypto and fintech functionality. The most rapidly adopted Web3 social media network, DSCVR is also the largest.&nbsp;</p><p>By coupling the accessibility of Web2 platforms with the most diverse set of crypto features available in decentralized social media, DSCVR has become the social media and SocialFi network of choice for content creators and community builders. The platform has become a launchpad for tokenized communities where users can gate based on token ownership, configure governance, airdrop token rewards, and earn digital assets.&nbsp;</p>ContactMary Victoria MorenoAngle42maryvictoria@angle42.co]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US crypto companies obliged to relocate overseas]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/us-crypto-companies-obliged-to-relocate-overseas</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec1-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec1-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec1-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:56:55 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/us-crypto-companies-obliged-to-relocate-overseas</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The United States' cryptocurrency companies are resorting more and more to the tactic of transporting their operations overseas, seeking out places with a friendlier regulatory stance towards cryptocurrency companies in general.</p>
SEC forces crypto companies' hand
<p>This phenomenon has been on the rise due to increasing pressure and criticism from sources such as the SEC, whose chairman Gary Gensler appears to have made it his mission to eradicate crypto from US shores.</p>
<p>In light of this, many crypto companies have begun scrutinising nations that have easier regulations when it comes to crypto trading, leading to a surge in relocation campaigns over recent years.</p>
Exchanges gone or leaving
<p>Major exchanges such as Binance, Kraken and Bitfinex have already shifted their locations over to countries with more lenient regulatory policies. Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, has offices and staff located in many countries, probably in order to be able to survive full-on government attacks.</p>
<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s regulatory and legal duel with the SEC are well documented. CEO Brian Armstrong has recently had talks in the UK over a possible move, and UAE is also being considered as a strategic hub.&nbsp;</p>
Ripple expands in MENA
<p>Another crypto company currently fighting a highly public battle with the SEC is Ripple. The company has 20% of its customers based in the MENA region, and according to CEO Brad Garlinghouse, Dubai is emerging as a key financial hub.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Ripple is expanding in Dubai. With 20 percent of our customers based in MENA and clear regulatory regimes being developed, it&rsquo;s no surprise that Dubai is emerging as a key global financial hub,&rdquo;</p>
Which nations will ultimately host crypto?
<p>The trend of US crypto companies relocating overseas continues even though some say that it raises possible concerns about potential risks for traders and investors alike.</p>
<p>Regardless, US-based crypto firms continue their search for friendlier jurisdictions beyond America's shores - which could result in more competition among selected nations eager to host new digital technology companies with their attendant benefits.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States' cryptocurrency companies are resorting more and more to the tactic of transporting their operations overseas, seeking out places with a friendlier regulatory stance towards cryptocurrency companies in general.</p>
SEC forces crypto companies' hand
<p>This phenomenon has been on the rise due to increasing pressure and criticism from sources such as the SEC, whose chairman Gary Gensler appears to have made it his mission to eradicate crypto from US shores.</p>
<p>In light of this, many crypto companies have begun scrutinising nations that have easier regulations when it comes to crypto trading, leading to a surge in relocation campaigns over recent years.</p>
Exchanges gone or leaving
<p>Major exchanges such as Binance, Kraken and Bitfinex have already shifted their locations over to countries with more lenient regulatory policies. Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, has offices and staff located in many countries, probably in order to be able to survive full-on government attacks.</p>
<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s regulatory and legal duel with the SEC are well documented. CEO Brian Armstrong has recently had talks in the UK over a possible move, and UAE is also being considered as a strategic hub.&nbsp;</p>
Ripple expands in MENA
<p>Another crypto company currently fighting a highly public battle with the SEC is Ripple. The company has 20% of its customers based in the MENA region, and according to CEO Brad Garlinghouse, Dubai is emerging as a key financial hub.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Ripple is expanding in Dubai. With 20 percent of our customers based in MENA and clear regulatory regimes being developed, it&rsquo;s no surprise that Dubai is emerging as a key global financial hub,&rdquo;</p>
Which nations will ultimately host crypto?
<p>The trend of US crypto companies relocating overseas continues even though some say that it raises possible concerns about potential risks for traders and investors alike.</p>
<p>Regardless, US-based crypto firms continue their search for friendlier jurisdictions beyond America's shores - which could result in more competition among selected nations eager to host new digital technology companies with their attendant benefits.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Launches Metaverse Show to Find The Next Big Web3 Entrepreneur]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-launches-metaverse-show-to-find-the-next-big-web3-entrepreneur</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Binance_BTB_KA_Horizontal_Static_PostPro_1683634518iOOQi47M2p.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Binance_BTB_KA_Horizontal_Static_PostPro_1683634518iOOQi47M2p.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Binance_BTB_KA_Horizontal_Static_PostPro_1683634518iOOQi47M2p.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:31:57 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-launches-metaverse-show-to-find-the-next-big-web3-entrepreneur</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, May 9th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Binance, the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider, is debuting &ldquo;Build The Block,&rdquo; a new global digital series where Web3 startups will compete for investment from Binance Labs. Build The Block is the first show format of its kind and Binance&rsquo;s first foray into the metaverse.&nbsp;</p><p>12 projects will compete for the top honor, each battling to impress a live audience and a panel of judges including Yi He, co-founder and CMO of Binance and head of Binance Labs; Yibo Ling, chief business officer of Binance; Guy Turner, co-founder of Coin Bureau; Azeem Khan, a member of the World Economic Forum&rsquo;s Crypto Sustainability Coalition and fundraising and partnership lead at Gitcoin; and Robby Yung, CEO of Animoca Brands and partner at Animoca Capital. The show will be hosted by Justin Bratton, host of Asia&rsquo;s Got Talent.&nbsp;</p><p>The contestants were handpicked from over 900 applications, and will compete live in front of a virtual studio audience and panel of judges. The show will air in seven episodes on Binance&rsquo;s YouTube channel and Binance Live, starting with the first episode on May 12 at 2 p.m. GMT. Episodes will air every Tuesday and Friday, with the finale airing Friday, June 2.</p>"Build The Block is Binance's latest innovative experiment -- creating the industry's first metaverse investment competition. This program has attracted many entrepreneurs and builders alike to showcase their Web3 projects and we hope a platform like this encourages others to innovate even further," said Yi He, co-founder of Binance and head of Binance Labs, "We believe in the potential of the metaverse and blockchain technology, and will continue to empower creators to build the future of internet together."&nbsp;<p></p><p>Build the Block contestants:&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Mind Network: a full encryption network built on a patented Adaptive Fully Homomorphic Encryption (FHE) framework to secure all user data, smart contracts and AI on Web3. It is firstly applied as a decentralized privacy-preserving datalake that offers encrypted high-performance &ldquo;Pay as You Go&rdquo; data storage and computation.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Kryptoskatt: Kryptoskatt simplifies Web3 finance for clients globally with a comprehensive suite of solutions that include accounting, portfolio management, and tax reporting. Supporting over 2000+ DeFi protocols, 100+ exchanges and wallets, and 50+ blockchains, Kryptoskatt is the one-stop-shop for all Web3 finance needs.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Sandbags Protocol: a platform that offers efficient and reliable security protection to help businesses protect their clients' assets from loss. It provides businesses with a way to secure on-chain assets with proactive protection mechanisms without affecting regular business operations.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Wallet Guard: a web3 security extension designed to block wallet drainers &amp; phishing attempts while also providing confidence on all your transactions. Open-source, installs within seconds and starts working immediately.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Ontropy: a blockchain platform that utilizes heavy cryptography and Zero-Knowledge (ZK) protocols to eliminate the need for oracles and bridges. It uses Proof of Result, a mechanism for off-chain consensus and immutability. With this system, users can validate their own data, guaranteeing security and reducing transaction costs by up to 80% at 3x the speed.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Hana: a Layer 0 for privacy, bringing security and confidentiality to all blockchains. It provides trustless interoperability, consisting of a multi-asset zk-UTXO (Zero-Knowledge Unspent Transaction Output), allowing for private payments in apps and enterprises.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; PIP: a Web3 payment company that aims to accelerate the future of global micropayments. They specialize in creating innovative payment products for individual users, and their services include Social Payments, Web 3 Identity (link-in-bio), Payment Button, and Payment Link. PIP's mission is to make it easy for individuals to make and receive payments in the Web3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; The Harvest: a third-person Hero Shooter game that is focused on team-play, mobility, and abilities. Made by gaming industry veterans and using elements of MOBAs and shooters in a battle between 4 teams of 3 players each, the game is designed to allow players to play in their own way and create unique strategies for success by combining different web2 and web3 items.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Notebook Labs: a platform that uses Zero-Knowledge proofs to embed fully compliant Know-Your-Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) infrastructure into DeFi protocols at the smart contract level. By doing so, institutions and retail investors can access decentralized markets, trade Real-World Assets (RWA), and provide liquidity in a compliant and privacy-preserving way.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; zkPass: a composable, privacy-preserving identity protocol based on Multi-party Computation (MPC) and Zero-knowledge Proof(ZKP). It empowers users to selectively prove their verifiable data in Web2 and Web3, including legal identities, financial, healthcare, social, experience, education, skills to 3rd parties without disclosing any personal privacy details.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Bracket Labs: builds leveraged structured products on-chain with simple interfaces and innovative, adaptive pricing to vastly improve usability. Bracket Labs has launched BracketX.fi, a platform that helps traders quickly take advantage of volatility in both sideways and trending market conditions.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; DappOS: a company that is focused on building an operating protocol to lower the barriers to entry for Web3 applications. dappOS is focused on creating solutions that improve the usability and accessibility of Web3 applications, with a particular focus on lowering the barriers to entry for users.&nbsp;</p><p>Build The Block was created by Binance Studio, Binance's in-house Web3 global creative studio, and set entirely in the metaverse using virtual cameras and custom avatars. The series was produced in partnership with Lifeform, the leading technology solution provider for Web3 virtual human avatars.&nbsp;</p><p>Follow along on Twitter at @BinanceLabs and #BuildtheBlock to find out more about the contestants, and see behind-the-scenes footage.&nbsp;</p><p>About Binance&nbsp;</p><p>Binance is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain ecosystem and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider with a financial product suite that includes the largest digital asset exchange by volume. Trusted by millions worldwide, the Binance platform is dedicated to increasing the freedom of money for users, and features an unmatched portfolio of crypto products and offerings, including: trading and finance, education, data and research, social good, investment and incubation, decentralization and infrastructure solutions, and more. For more information, visit: https://www.binance.com&nbsp;</p>ContactKirby Nadopr@binance.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, May 9th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Binance, the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider, is debuting &ldquo;Build The Block,&rdquo; a new global digital series where Web3 startups will compete for investment from Binance Labs. Build The Block is the first show format of its kind and Binance&rsquo;s first foray into the metaverse.&nbsp;</p><p>12 projects will compete for the top honor, each battling to impress a live audience and a panel of judges including Yi He, co-founder and CMO of Binance and head of Binance Labs; Yibo Ling, chief business officer of Binance; Guy Turner, co-founder of Coin Bureau; Azeem Khan, a member of the World Economic Forum&rsquo;s Crypto Sustainability Coalition and fundraising and partnership lead at Gitcoin; and Robby Yung, CEO of Animoca Brands and partner at Animoca Capital. The show will be hosted by Justin Bratton, host of Asia&rsquo;s Got Talent.&nbsp;</p><p>The contestants were handpicked from over 900 applications, and will compete live in front of a virtual studio audience and panel of judges. The show will air in seven episodes on Binance&rsquo;s YouTube channel and Binance Live, starting with the first episode on May 12 at 2 p.m. GMT. Episodes will air every Tuesday and Friday, with the finale airing Friday, June 2.</p>"Build The Block is Binance's latest innovative experiment -- creating the industry's first metaverse investment competition. This program has attracted many entrepreneurs and builders alike to showcase their Web3 projects and we hope a platform like this encourages others to innovate even further," said Yi He, co-founder of Binance and head of Binance Labs, "We believe in the potential of the metaverse and blockchain technology, and will continue to empower creators to build the future of internet together."&nbsp;<p></p><p>Build the Block contestants:&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Mind Network: a full encryption network built on a patented Adaptive Fully Homomorphic Encryption (FHE) framework to secure all user data, smart contracts and AI on Web3. It is firstly applied as a decentralized privacy-preserving datalake that offers encrypted high-performance &ldquo;Pay as You Go&rdquo; data storage and computation.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Kryptoskatt: Kryptoskatt simplifies Web3 finance for clients globally with a comprehensive suite of solutions that include accounting, portfolio management, and tax reporting. Supporting over 2000+ DeFi protocols, 100+ exchanges and wallets, and 50+ blockchains, Kryptoskatt is the one-stop-shop for all Web3 finance needs.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Sandbags Protocol: a platform that offers efficient and reliable security protection to help businesses protect their clients' assets from loss. It provides businesses with a way to secure on-chain assets with proactive protection mechanisms without affecting regular business operations.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Wallet Guard: a web3 security extension designed to block wallet drainers &amp; phishing attempts while also providing confidence on all your transactions. Open-source, installs within seconds and starts working immediately.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Ontropy: a blockchain platform that utilizes heavy cryptography and Zero-Knowledge (ZK) protocols to eliminate the need for oracles and bridges. It uses Proof of Result, a mechanism for off-chain consensus and immutability. With this system, users can validate their own data, guaranteeing security and reducing transaction costs by up to 80% at 3x the speed.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Hana: a Layer 0 for privacy, bringing security and confidentiality to all blockchains. It provides trustless interoperability, consisting of a multi-asset zk-UTXO (Zero-Knowledge Unspent Transaction Output), allowing for private payments in apps and enterprises.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; PIP: a Web3 payment company that aims to accelerate the future of global micropayments. They specialize in creating innovative payment products for individual users, and their services include Social Payments, Web 3 Identity (link-in-bio), Payment Button, and Payment Link. PIP's mission is to make it easy for individuals to make and receive payments in the Web3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; The Harvest: a third-person Hero Shooter game that is focused on team-play, mobility, and abilities. Made by gaming industry veterans and using elements of MOBAs and shooters in a battle between 4 teams of 3 players each, the game is designed to allow players to play in their own way and create unique strategies for success by combining different web2 and web3 items.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Notebook Labs: a platform that uses Zero-Knowledge proofs to embed fully compliant Know-Your-Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) infrastructure into DeFi protocols at the smart contract level. By doing so, institutions and retail investors can access decentralized markets, trade Real-World Assets (RWA), and provide liquidity in a compliant and privacy-preserving way.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; zkPass: a composable, privacy-preserving identity protocol based on Multi-party Computation (MPC) and Zero-knowledge Proof(ZKP). It empowers users to selectively prove their verifiable data in Web2 and Web3, including legal identities, financial, healthcare, social, experience, education, skills to 3rd parties without disclosing any personal privacy details.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; Bracket Labs: builds leveraged structured products on-chain with simple interfaces and innovative, adaptive pricing to vastly improve usability. Bracket Labs has launched BracketX.fi, a platform that helps traders quickly take advantage of volatility in both sideways and trending market conditions.&nbsp;</p><p>&#9679; DappOS: a company that is focused on building an operating protocol to lower the barriers to entry for Web3 applications. dappOS is focused on creating solutions that improve the usability and accessibility of Web3 applications, with a particular focus on lowering the barriers to entry for users.&nbsp;</p><p>Build The Block was created by Binance Studio, Binance's in-house Web3 global creative studio, and set entirely in the metaverse using virtual cameras and custom avatars. The series was produced in partnership with Lifeform, the leading technology solution provider for Web3 virtual human avatars.&nbsp;</p><p>Follow along on Twitter at @BinanceLabs and #BuildtheBlock to find out more about the contestants, and see behind-the-scenes footage.&nbsp;</p><p>About Binance&nbsp;</p><p>Binance is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain ecosystem and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider with a financial product suite that includes the largest digital asset exchange by volume. Trusted by millions worldwide, the Binance platform is dedicated to increasing the freedom of money for users, and features an unmatched portfolio of crypto products and offerings, including: trading and finance, education, data and research, social good, investment and incubation, decentralization and infrastructure solutions, and more. For more information, visit: https://www.binance.com&nbsp;</p>ContactKirby Nadopr@binance.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Navigating the Crypto Industry: Companies to Learn From]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/navigating-the-crypto-industry-companies-to-learn-from</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-14.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-14.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-14.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/navigating-the-crypto-industry-companies-to-learn-from</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>There are always fresh problems and possibilities in the crypto market for investors and developers. Many businesses are learning to swim in this increasingly murky industry as they strive to meet the needs of an ever-expanding customer base.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interestingly, some of these companies have seen widespread adoption and success in the crypto market by facilitating trading, staking, and lending, among other activities. These platforms have succeeded, whereas others have failed by catering to their users' needs with an intuitive interface, lightning-fast transaction processing, and friendly support staff. Notably, successful crypto marketing has been one of the main factors for a project's success, especially when working in sync with the product team.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the United States, high-income earners are disproportionately represented among crypto investors. Those making $100,000 annually comprise 25 percent of crypto owners but only 15 percent of the general public. This shows how proper crypto investment can skyrocket an investor.</p>
<p>In this piece, we'll look at some of the leading crypto firms that have managed to thrive despite their many challenges. These companies are at the top of their game because they've developed groundbreaking products and services.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Top Companies Uncovered By Our Compass</p>
<p>CoinPayments holds a prominent position as the leading and foremost cryptocurrency payment processor worldwide. With a user base exceeding one million and over 120,000 registered merchants hailing from more than 190 countries, CoinPayments stands out as one of the most widely-used multi-crypto payment platforms accessible on the internet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since its inception in 2013, CoinPayments has established a comprehensive crypto payment gateway solution that empowers merchants to accept more than 100 cryptocurrencies and hold over 2,000+ altcoins on a single platform.</p>
<p>Secondly, Contractus is a blockchain-based service that facilitates secure and encrypted one-click processing of contract signatures, cutting costs and accelerating the process. It operates on the highly scalable and rapidly expanding Solana blockchain, making it reliable and efficient. Contractus ensures instant execution of contracts, with no third-party intermediaries involved, and guarantees term fulfillment for all parties at a low fee of just 0.5% per transaction. It encrypts all client contract details and sensitive data, supports payment in various cryptocurrencies, and operates through an easy-to-use mobile application.</p>
<p>With integrated Shamir's Secret Sharing scheme and multi-signature approach, Contractus offers a secure and automated system for contract signing. It also provides third-party validation of contract results, ensuring work payment only after validation. These features make Contractus an efficient, cost-effective, and reliable platform for contract signing and execution, especially for transactions involving considerable sums. Principally, the company has a free-of-charge rate called Holder mode - when a client holds a 10.000 CTUS token and more or pays in Contractus tokens.</p>
<p>Also, at the forefront of Metaverse innovation, ALTAVA Group offers a one-of-a-kind platform that allows leading brands to connect their offline and online experiences via blockchain technology. ALTAVA's NFT prowess is on full display with its BAGC Collection, a golf-themed offshoot of the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), licensed from Elite Apes, The Sandbox, and Animoca Brands. The platform also operates the Second Skin NFT Collection, which is expertly integrated with WOY, the company's proprietary Metaverse, available on both the App Store and Play Store.&nbsp;</p>
<p>ALTAVA's got some big names backing it, like Hyundai, LG, Spartan, and Animoca Brands. Notably, the platform has seen over 300% year-over-year revenue growth. Despite that, TAVA's token price is way too low compared to its accomplishments. This year's expected to bridge all gaps for TAVA and ALTAVA as more people catch on to what this project is all about.</p>
<p>In addition to the list, Lossless is at the forefront of providing Web3 security solutions to high-level projects. The team of cybersecurity experts, blockchain engineers, finance professionals, and white-hat hackers invest heavily in research and development to develop innovative and novel security measures. With its groundbreaking solutions, Lossless mitigates any financial losses caused by exploitation or malicious cyber activity. Currently, the team is launching another exceptional solution to a broader audience.</p>
<p>Would you like to say hello to Aegis from Lossless? The All-Seeing Eye? It is a go-to tool for vigilantly monitoring contracts and wallets. Its mission is simple but incredibly effective: to help detect suspicious activity and alert on any unexpected changes in TVL, malicious smart contracts deployed, flash loans, and many other potentially harmful events as soon as possible. Whether a user is a retail user or a web3 company, Aegis provides an excellent way to track and monitor malicious action patterns and gives the necessary time and opportunity to take action if an attack occurs.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s worth mentioning that OneLedger is a blockchain platform that gives organizations a more straightforward approach to embracing blockchain technology. The company overcomes the scalability, security, and high transaction price challenges. Its interoperability function supports Ethereum, Bitcoin, BSC, Polkadot, and Matic. OneLedger's scalability feature allows 4,000 transactions per second compared to Ethereum's 4 transactions per second, making it ideal for high-volume transactions. Additionally, OneLedger offers low transaction fees, making it affordable for businesses to implement blockchain solutions.</p>
<p>The platform's developer-friendly tools make it simple for developers to create blockchain apps fast and effectively. Its SDK and OLVM let developers design blockchain apps. OneLedger's testnet, Frankenstein, and mainnet, Kratos, are also available via Google Cloud Marketplace and Opensea, which makes it simpler for developers to test and deploy their apps. With OneLedger, companies can profit from the promise of blockchain technology without worrying about scalability, security, and expensive transaction costs.</p>
<p>Wrapping up, Eldora is the premier financial center in the metaverse, revolutionizing the growth of business alliances and investment groups. Their goal is to give users more agency by giving them early access to curated financial information about cryptocurrencies, DeFi, trading, and related industries. Eldora is a game-changer for corporations and the ultra-wealthy alike; it's more than simply a decentralized package of services. With the platform, users can access various blockchain-based, decentralized services that protect privacy and make financial dealings completely transparent. The Eldora NFT grants membership into their gated community and use of its features.</p>
<p>Furthermore, users may launch their own company, solicit funding from friends and family, and publicize lucrative prospects for investment simply by connecting their property to Defi Services and the financial system. Eldora equips one with everything you need to navigate the dynamic financial markets of the metaverse. Join Eldora now before you lose out on this game-changing chance!</p>
<p>Thriving in the Cryptocurrency Market: Strategies for Success</p>
<p>Many companies have succeeded in the crypto challenging environment and established themselves as market leaders. These companies have achieved great success by focusing on what their clients want and working hard to meet those needs in novel ways.</p>
<p>Their dedication to improving the customer's overall experience is a driving force in their success. The complex nature of the crypto sector may put off new users. Still, businesses that have created user-friendly interfaces and provide excellent assistance have seen increased client acquisition.</p>
<p>The potential to create game-changing goods and services is another differentiating characteristic for thriving crypto businesses. This calls for in-depth familiarity with the industry and user requirements. Businesses that can anticipate the emergence of new trends and quickly respond with appropriate responses will be able to maintain a competitive edge.</p>
<p>Notably, the disproportionate number of high-income earners among investors is an intriguing trend in the cryptocurrency business. This indicates that there is an excellent chance for firms to capitalize on this market by catering to its specific requirements.</p>
<p>There is a lot of potential for experimentation and development in the cryptocurrency market since the sector as a whole is still in its infancy. Successful companies of the future will be those who master this challenging environment and provide novel answers to its many challenges.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are always fresh problems and possibilities in the crypto market for investors and developers. Many businesses are learning to swim in this increasingly murky industry as they strive to meet the needs of an ever-expanding customer base.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interestingly, some of these companies have seen widespread adoption and success in the crypto market by facilitating trading, staking, and lending, among other activities. These platforms have succeeded, whereas others have failed by catering to their users' needs with an intuitive interface, lightning-fast transaction processing, and friendly support staff. Notably, successful crypto marketing has been one of the main factors for a project's success, especially when working in sync with the product team.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the United States, high-income earners are disproportionately represented among crypto investors. Those making $100,000 annually comprise 25 percent of crypto owners but only 15 percent of the general public. This shows how proper crypto investment can skyrocket an investor.</p>
<p>In this piece, we'll look at some of the leading crypto firms that have managed to thrive despite their many challenges. These companies are at the top of their game because they've developed groundbreaking products and services.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Top Companies Uncovered By Our Compass</p>
<p>CoinPayments holds a prominent position as the leading and foremost cryptocurrency payment processor worldwide. With a user base exceeding one million and over 120,000 registered merchants hailing from more than 190 countries, CoinPayments stands out as one of the most widely-used multi-crypto payment platforms accessible on the internet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since its inception in 2013, CoinPayments has established a comprehensive crypto payment gateway solution that empowers merchants to accept more than 100 cryptocurrencies and hold over 2,000+ altcoins on a single platform.</p>
<p>Secondly, Contractus is a blockchain-based service that facilitates secure and encrypted one-click processing of contract signatures, cutting costs and accelerating the process. It operates on the highly scalable and rapidly expanding Solana blockchain, making it reliable and efficient. Contractus ensures instant execution of contracts, with no third-party intermediaries involved, and guarantees term fulfillment for all parties at a low fee of just 0.5% per transaction. It encrypts all client contract details and sensitive data, supports payment in various cryptocurrencies, and operates through an easy-to-use mobile application.</p>
<p>With integrated Shamir's Secret Sharing scheme and multi-signature approach, Contractus offers a secure and automated system for contract signing. It also provides third-party validation of contract results, ensuring work payment only after validation. These features make Contractus an efficient, cost-effective, and reliable platform for contract signing and execution, especially for transactions involving considerable sums. Principally, the company has a free-of-charge rate called Holder mode - when a client holds a 10.000 CTUS token and more or pays in Contractus tokens.</p>
<p>Also, at the forefront of Metaverse innovation, ALTAVA Group offers a one-of-a-kind platform that allows leading brands to connect their offline and online experiences via blockchain technology. ALTAVA's NFT prowess is on full display with its BAGC Collection, a golf-themed offshoot of the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), licensed from Elite Apes, The Sandbox, and Animoca Brands. The platform also operates the Second Skin NFT Collection, which is expertly integrated with WOY, the company's proprietary Metaverse, available on both the App Store and Play Store.&nbsp;</p>
<p>ALTAVA's got some big names backing it, like Hyundai, LG, Spartan, and Animoca Brands. Notably, the platform has seen over 300% year-over-year revenue growth. Despite that, TAVA's token price is way too low compared to its accomplishments. This year's expected to bridge all gaps for TAVA and ALTAVA as more people catch on to what this project is all about.</p>
<p>In addition to the list, Lossless is at the forefront of providing Web3 security solutions to high-level projects. The team of cybersecurity experts, blockchain engineers, finance professionals, and white-hat hackers invest heavily in research and development to develop innovative and novel security measures. With its groundbreaking solutions, Lossless mitigates any financial losses caused by exploitation or malicious cyber activity. Currently, the team is launching another exceptional solution to a broader audience.</p>
<p>Would you like to say hello to Aegis from Lossless? The All-Seeing Eye? It is a go-to tool for vigilantly monitoring contracts and wallets. Its mission is simple but incredibly effective: to help detect suspicious activity and alert on any unexpected changes in TVL, malicious smart contracts deployed, flash loans, and many other potentially harmful events as soon as possible. Whether a user is a retail user or a web3 company, Aegis provides an excellent way to track and monitor malicious action patterns and gives the necessary time and opportunity to take action if an attack occurs.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s worth mentioning that OneLedger is a blockchain platform that gives organizations a more straightforward approach to embracing blockchain technology. The company overcomes the scalability, security, and high transaction price challenges. Its interoperability function supports Ethereum, Bitcoin, BSC, Polkadot, and Matic. OneLedger's scalability feature allows 4,000 transactions per second compared to Ethereum's 4 transactions per second, making it ideal for high-volume transactions. Additionally, OneLedger offers low transaction fees, making it affordable for businesses to implement blockchain solutions.</p>
<p>The platform's developer-friendly tools make it simple for developers to create blockchain apps fast and effectively. Its SDK and OLVM let developers design blockchain apps. OneLedger's testnet, Frankenstein, and mainnet, Kratos, are also available via Google Cloud Marketplace and Opensea, which makes it simpler for developers to test and deploy their apps. With OneLedger, companies can profit from the promise of blockchain technology without worrying about scalability, security, and expensive transaction costs.</p>
<p>Wrapping up, Eldora is the premier financial center in the metaverse, revolutionizing the growth of business alliances and investment groups. Their goal is to give users more agency by giving them early access to curated financial information about cryptocurrencies, DeFi, trading, and related industries. Eldora is a game-changer for corporations and the ultra-wealthy alike; it's more than simply a decentralized package of services. With the platform, users can access various blockchain-based, decentralized services that protect privacy and make financial dealings completely transparent. The Eldora NFT grants membership into their gated community and use of its features.</p>
<p>Furthermore, users may launch their own company, solicit funding from friends and family, and publicize lucrative prospects for investment simply by connecting their property to Defi Services and the financial system. Eldora equips one with everything you need to navigate the dynamic financial markets of the metaverse. Join Eldora now before you lose out on this game-changing chance!</p>
<p>Thriving in the Cryptocurrency Market: Strategies for Success</p>
<p>Many companies have succeeded in the crypto challenging environment and established themselves as market leaders. These companies have achieved great success by focusing on what their clients want and working hard to meet those needs in novel ways.</p>
<p>Their dedication to improving the customer's overall experience is a driving force in their success. The complex nature of the crypto sector may put off new users. Still, businesses that have created user-friendly interfaces and provide excellent assistance have seen increased client acquisition.</p>
<p>The potential to create game-changing goods and services is another differentiating characteristic for thriving crypto businesses. This calls for in-depth familiarity with the industry and user requirements. Businesses that can anticipate the emergence of new trends and quickly respond with appropriate responses will be able to maintain a competitive edge.</p>
<p>Notably, the disproportionate number of high-income earners among investors is an intriguing trend in the cryptocurrency business. This indicates that there is an excellent chance for firms to capitalize on this market by catering to its specific requirements.</p>
<p>There is a lot of potential for experimentation and development in the cryptocurrency market since the sector as a whole is still in its infancy. Successful companies of the future will be those who master this challenging environment and provide novel answers to its many challenges.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ETH Staking Deposits Report Sharp Increase, Outpace Withdrawals]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/eth-staking-deposits-report-sharp-increase-outpace-withdrawals</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ethereum-shanghai-delayed-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ethereum-shanghai-delayed-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ethereum-shanghai-delayed-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/eth-staking-deposits-report-sharp-increase-outpace-withdrawals</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the Shanghai upgrade in the rearview mirror,&nbsp; Ethereum staking numbers have reported a sharp increase, outpacing ETH withdrawals by $189 Million.</p>
<p>The numbers show that since the completion of the upgrade allowing stakers to withdraw their ETH, most users are eager to begin ETH staking.</p>
ETH Staking Sees Considerable Growth
<p>Ethereum completed the Shapella upgrade on the 12th of April. Following the completion of the upgrade, Ethereum has seen 2.32 million ETH deposited, while 2.28 million ETH has been withdrawn. This means there is a positive net flow of around 32,000 ETH. In just the past 24 hours, investors have deposited 192,000 ETH while withdrawing only 29,000 ETH. This also marks the first time since Shapella that the cumulative amount of staked ETH has exceeded the total ETH withdrawn.</p>
<p>Additionally, there is also a significant uptick in the ETH burning rate. Over the past seven days, the network has seen 61,000 ETH burnt. This high burn rate can be primarily attributed to Uniswap, contributing to almost half of the ETH being burnt. ETH is the largest decentralized exchange by trading volume currently in operation. All of the data suggests that users are extremely bullish when it comes to staking with Ethereum. Analysts believe this is a good development for ETH. ETH being locked up for staking means there would be less ETH in the open market.</p>
Centralized Exchanges Drive Staking Withdrawals
<p>Looking at the breakdown of withdrawals, it is abundantly clear that centralized exchanges such as Binance, Conbase, and Kraken and driving them. According to data from Nansen, these exchanges are responsible for over 50% of withdrawals, totaling around 1.2 million ETH. In fact, Kraken alone has withdrawn about 609,410 ETH, while Binance and Coinbase have collectively withdrawn 624,650 ETH.</p>
<p>Other centralized exchanges that have made sizable ETH withdrawals include Gate.io, Huobi, and Gemini. Gate.io has withdrawn 36,560 ETH, while Huobi has removed 53,040 ETH. Meanwhile, Gemini has withdrawn 24,200 ETH. Even bankrupt crypto lender Celcius has withdrawn 6000 ETH. The data has also shown that Kraken staking customers in the United States have been almost completely removed from the staking system. This is because of regulatory action against Kraken by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Kraken eventually settled with the SEC after paying a $30 million fine and shuttering its staking operations in the United States in February.</p>
<p>Several entities are still waiting to withdraw their staked funds. Out of these, Coinbase is the largest, with around 55,000 ETH waiting to be withdrawn.</p>
Liquid Staking Protocols Make Significant Gains
<p>On the other hand, liquid staking protocols have made significant gains, with their total value locked (TVL) rising to over $16 billion. According to Nansen data, liquid staking protocols are responsible for most of the staked ETH. This category is dominated by Lido Finance, with its TVL rising by over 10% in the past month and going above the $12 billion mark. However, Lido&rsquo;s growth rate is relatively tame compared to the growth of other protocols, such as Rocketpool and Frax Ether. Rocketpool has reported a growth of nearly 28%, while Frax Ether has reported an increase of almost 44%. This sees their TVL rise to $1.55 billion and $345 million, respectively.</p>
<p>Liquid staling refers to users depositing their ETH into a protocol which then stakes it on the users&rsquo; behalf. In return, the user receives a token representing their staked positions. In the case of Lido, the token is stETH. According to Nansen, Lido&rsquo;s staked ETH takes up 79% of the total market. Next in line is Coinbase, with 15%.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the Shanghai upgrade in the rearview mirror,&nbsp; Ethereum staking numbers have reported a sharp increase, outpacing ETH withdrawals by $189 Million.</p>
<p>The numbers show that since the completion of the upgrade allowing stakers to withdraw their ETH, most users are eager to begin ETH staking.</p>
ETH Staking Sees Considerable Growth
<p>Ethereum completed the Shapella upgrade on the 12th of April. Following the completion of the upgrade, Ethereum has seen 2.32 million ETH deposited, while 2.28 million ETH has been withdrawn. This means there is a positive net flow of around 32,000 ETH. In just the past 24 hours, investors have deposited 192,000 ETH while withdrawing only 29,000 ETH. This also marks the first time since Shapella that the cumulative amount of staked ETH has exceeded the total ETH withdrawn.</p>
<p>Additionally, there is also a significant uptick in the ETH burning rate. Over the past seven days, the network has seen 61,000 ETH burnt. This high burn rate can be primarily attributed to Uniswap, contributing to almost half of the ETH being burnt. ETH is the largest decentralized exchange by trading volume currently in operation. All of the data suggests that users are extremely bullish when it comes to staking with Ethereum. Analysts believe this is a good development for ETH. ETH being locked up for staking means there would be less ETH in the open market.</p>
Centralized Exchanges Drive Staking Withdrawals
<p>Looking at the breakdown of withdrawals, it is abundantly clear that centralized exchanges such as Binance, Conbase, and Kraken and driving them. According to data from Nansen, these exchanges are responsible for over 50% of withdrawals, totaling around 1.2 million ETH. In fact, Kraken alone has withdrawn about 609,410 ETH, while Binance and Coinbase have collectively withdrawn 624,650 ETH.</p>
<p>Other centralized exchanges that have made sizable ETH withdrawals include Gate.io, Huobi, and Gemini. Gate.io has withdrawn 36,560 ETH, while Huobi has removed 53,040 ETH. Meanwhile, Gemini has withdrawn 24,200 ETH. Even bankrupt crypto lender Celcius has withdrawn 6000 ETH. The data has also shown that Kraken staking customers in the United States have been almost completely removed from the staking system. This is because of regulatory action against Kraken by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Kraken eventually settled with the SEC after paying a $30 million fine and shuttering its staking operations in the United States in February.</p>
<p>Several entities are still waiting to withdraw their staked funds. Out of these, Coinbase is the largest, with around 55,000 ETH waiting to be withdrawn.</p>
Liquid Staking Protocols Make Significant Gains
<p>On the other hand, liquid staking protocols have made significant gains, with their total value locked (TVL) rising to over $16 billion. According to Nansen data, liquid staking protocols are responsible for most of the staked ETH. This category is dominated by Lido Finance, with its TVL rising by over 10% in the past month and going above the $12 billion mark. However, Lido&rsquo;s growth rate is relatively tame compared to the growth of other protocols, such as Rocketpool and Frax Ether. Rocketpool has reported a growth of nearly 28%, while Frax Ether has reported an increase of almost 44%. This sees their TVL rise to $1.55 billion and $345 million, respectively.</p>
<p>Liquid staling refers to users depositing their ETH into a protocol which then stakes it on the users&rsquo; behalf. In return, the user receives a token representing their staked positions. In the case of Lido, the token is stETH. According to Nansen, Lido&rsquo;s staked ETH takes up 79% of the total market. Next in line is Coinbase, with 15%.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[MakerDAO Launches Spark, A New Lending And Borrowing Protocol]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/makerdao-launches-spark-a-brand-new-lending-and-borrowing-protocol</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/makerdao-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/makerdao-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/makerdao-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/makerdao-launches-spark-a-brand-new-lending-and-borrowing-protocol</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Finance (DeFi) pioneer MakerDAO has announced the launch of its lending and borrowing protocol, Spark.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The new protocol&rsquo;s initial iteration will function as a lending platform and allow users to lend and borrow ETH, DAI, stETH, and sDAI.&nbsp;</p>
Spark Protocol Launched&nbsp;
<p>MakerDAO announced the launch of the Spark Protocol on its official Twitter handle. The new protocol is specifically designed for the DAI stablecoin and gives users and holders access to competitive interest rates.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Announcing the Spark Protocol launch Starting May 9, 2023, Spark Protocol will be available to all DeFi users. An end-user, DAI-centered DeFi product deployed on Ethereum with supply and borrow features for ETH, stETH, DAI, and sDAI.&rdquo;</p>

<p>MakerDAO has also announced the Spark Protocol&rsquo;s first product, Spark Lend. The new protocol is also linked to Maker&rsquo;s D3M (Direct Deposit DAI Module). The Direct Deposit DAI Module is a system that enables secure interaction between the Maker ecosystem and third-party lending pools. As a result of the link between Spark Protocol and the Direct Deposit DAI Module, users can borrow the DAI stablecoin at competitive rates at an initial annual rate of 1.11%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In its announcement regarding the launch of the Spark Protocol, Maker briefly touched upon the connection between the protocol and the Direct Deposit DAI Module, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This direct wholesale credit line in DAI injects and automatically balances fresh DAI liquidity into Spark Lend and enables its users to access the best rates in the market.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Spark Protocol promises to significantly improve MakerDAO&rsquo;s DAI lending capability, increase overall liquidity, provide more liquidity options, and allow users to access improved rates and a yield-bearing version of DAI.&nbsp;</p>
MakerDAO&rsquo;s Focus On Stability&nbsp;
<p>Spark Protocol&rsquo;s Spark Lend product also introduces a tokenized version of the DAI stablecoin, which is deposited in the DAI Savings Rate (DSR). The tokenized version is called sDAI. However, the yields are quite low at the moment, with DAI deposits getting only 1.1%. It also utilizes a Peg Stability Module that helps to connect the liquidity infrastructure and offers instant swapping of DAI and sDAI for USDC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While current yields may be low, decentralized finance users have become wary of protocols offering risky, high, and often unsustainable yields. As a result, Maker has focused on providing stability, liquidity, and significantly lower risk.&nbsp;</p>
The Endgame Plan&nbsp;
<p>Spark Protocol has been launched as part of MakerDAO&rsquo;s Endgame plan. Under this plan, Maker has proposed making the DAI stablecoin a free-floating asset collateralized by real-world assets (RWA). Under the new plan, DAI will continue to remain pegged to the dollar for three years. Simultaneously, Maker also plans to accumulate as much Ethereum (ETH) as possible in an effort to increase the ratio of decentralized collateral backing the DAI.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DAI is the fourth-largest stablecoin in the crypto space and has a circulating supply of $4.7 billion. It has a market share of around 3.6%, making it the industry&rsquo;s largest decentralized stablecoin. Meanwhile, MakerDAO&rsquo;s native MKR token is trading at around $670, a drop of just over 1%.&nbsp;</p>
MakerDAO&rsquo;s New Constitution&nbsp;
<p>MakerDAO also recently proposed a new constitution to formalize governance processes and safeguard against any potential threat from malicious entities that could attempt to take over the protocol. In an effort to ensure the security of the Maker Protocol and safeguard user funds from potential threats and failures thanks to human or institutional decisions, the new constitution uses &ldquo;alignment engineering&rdquo; to solidify the core commitments of the community. The new document creates several categories of participants. Each category of participants has different powers and responsibilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Finance (DeFi) pioneer MakerDAO has announced the launch of its lending and borrowing protocol, Spark.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The new protocol&rsquo;s initial iteration will function as a lending platform and allow users to lend and borrow ETH, DAI, stETH, and sDAI.&nbsp;</p>
Spark Protocol Launched&nbsp;
<p>MakerDAO announced the launch of the Spark Protocol on its official Twitter handle. The new protocol is specifically designed for the DAI stablecoin and gives users and holders access to competitive interest rates.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Announcing the Spark Protocol launch Starting May 9, 2023, Spark Protocol will be available to all DeFi users. An end-user, DAI-centered DeFi product deployed on Ethereum with supply and borrow features for ETH, stETH, DAI, and sDAI.&rdquo;</p>

<p>MakerDAO has also announced the Spark Protocol&rsquo;s first product, Spark Lend. The new protocol is also linked to Maker&rsquo;s D3M (Direct Deposit DAI Module). The Direct Deposit DAI Module is a system that enables secure interaction between the Maker ecosystem and third-party lending pools. As a result of the link between Spark Protocol and the Direct Deposit DAI Module, users can borrow the DAI stablecoin at competitive rates at an initial annual rate of 1.11%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In its announcement regarding the launch of the Spark Protocol, Maker briefly touched upon the connection between the protocol and the Direct Deposit DAI Module, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This direct wholesale credit line in DAI injects and automatically balances fresh DAI liquidity into Spark Lend and enables its users to access the best rates in the market.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Spark Protocol promises to significantly improve MakerDAO&rsquo;s DAI lending capability, increase overall liquidity, provide more liquidity options, and allow users to access improved rates and a yield-bearing version of DAI.&nbsp;</p>
MakerDAO&rsquo;s Focus On Stability&nbsp;
<p>Spark Protocol&rsquo;s Spark Lend product also introduces a tokenized version of the DAI stablecoin, which is deposited in the DAI Savings Rate (DSR). The tokenized version is called sDAI. However, the yields are quite low at the moment, with DAI deposits getting only 1.1%. It also utilizes a Peg Stability Module that helps to connect the liquidity infrastructure and offers instant swapping of DAI and sDAI for USDC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While current yields may be low, decentralized finance users have become wary of protocols offering risky, high, and often unsustainable yields. As a result, Maker has focused on providing stability, liquidity, and significantly lower risk.&nbsp;</p>
The Endgame Plan&nbsp;
<p>Spark Protocol has been launched as part of MakerDAO&rsquo;s Endgame plan. Under this plan, Maker has proposed making the DAI stablecoin a free-floating asset collateralized by real-world assets (RWA). Under the new plan, DAI will continue to remain pegged to the dollar for three years. Simultaneously, Maker also plans to accumulate as much Ethereum (ETH) as possible in an effort to increase the ratio of decentralized collateral backing the DAI.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DAI is the fourth-largest stablecoin in the crypto space and has a circulating supply of $4.7 billion. It has a market share of around 3.6%, making it the industry&rsquo;s largest decentralized stablecoin. Meanwhile, MakerDAO&rsquo;s native MKR token is trading at around $670, a drop of just over 1%.&nbsp;</p>
MakerDAO&rsquo;s New Constitution&nbsp;
<p>MakerDAO also recently proposed a new constitution to formalize governance processes and safeguard against any potential threat from malicious entities that could attempt to take over the protocol. In an effort to ensure the security of the Maker Protocol and safeguard user funds from potential threats and failures thanks to human or institutional decisions, the new constitution uses &ldquo;alignment engineering&rdquo; to solidify the core commitments of the community. The new document creates several categories of participants. Each category of participants has different powers and responsibilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sports Illustrated Debuts Polygon NFT Ticket Platform]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sports-illustrated-debuts-polygon-nft-ticket-platform</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sports-illustrated-debuts-polygon-nft-ticket-platform</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Sports Illustrated&rsquo;s ticketing affiliate, SI Tickets, launched its new &ldquo;Box Office&rdquo; platform, a self-service ticketing service based on the Polygon blockchain. </p>
<p>Sports Illustrated Tickets (SI Tickets) announced the launch of Box Office, a new non-fungible token (NFT) ticketing platform built on the Polygon blockchain, an Ethereum scaling solution. Sports Illustrated&rsquo;s marketplace developed Box Office in partnership with Ethereum software firm ConsenSys. SI Tickets is a division of the Sports Illustrated magazine and media brand.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Introducing Box Office, the all-new event management platform from Sports Illustrated Tickets 🎟️ Create and sell tickets for your own free or paid event on our site. Partner with us for an easy event set-up and lower fees than our competitors. #sitickets #sportsillustrated pic.twitter.com/84ASQkZUYg</p>
&mdash; SI Tickets (@si_tickets_) May 2, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>According to the announcement:</p>

<p>Box Office is the first global platform to combine a complete NFT ticket solution for events of any size with visibility and adjacency to traditional, non-NFT tickets alongside the biggest in sports, concert and theatre on the SI Tickets marketplace.</p>

<p>Box Office delivers a seamless &ldquo;experience giving owners, organisers and host the ability to create, manage and promote a fully scalable, paid, or free ticketed live sporting event, performance or function fuelled by the Sports Illustrated Tickets platform.&rdquo;</p>
<p>SI Tickets CEO, David Lane, said this new marketplace aims to &ldquo;disrupt the primary ticket market.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Lane added:</p>

<p>Blockchain is the future of ticketing, and now owners, promoters, hosts and attendees have access to an advanced ticketing experience that transforms the antiquated barcode into engaging and collectable content.</p>

<p>Box Office caters to the biggest events in sports and music but welcomes ticket listings from smaller ticket issuers that typically appear on ticketing sites like Eventbrite or DICE. Lane commented on this, saying:</p>

<p>We&rsquo;re not here to compete against Ticketmaster, SeatGeek, or AXS. We&rsquo;re going after the self-service event market. We&rsquo;re trying to create the first mass-market adoption of NFT ticketing so that everyone from a 15-year-old to a 90-year-old can buy their first NFT ticket without having to go through a crypto tutorial on blockchain, or have to get a wallet and understand any aspects of it.</p>

<p>Box Office NFT tickets will confer a host of benefits to its holder. In addition to granting entry, event organisers can equip tickets with photo and video content, collectables, personalised messages, promotional offers and loyalty rewards. Tickets can be found inside the SI Tickets app.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sports Illustrated&rsquo;s ticketing affiliate, SI Tickets, launched its new &ldquo;Box Office&rdquo; platform, a self-service ticketing service based on the Polygon blockchain. </p>
<p>Sports Illustrated Tickets (SI Tickets) announced the launch of Box Office, a new non-fungible token (NFT) ticketing platform built on the Polygon blockchain, an Ethereum scaling solution. Sports Illustrated&rsquo;s marketplace developed Box Office in partnership with Ethereum software firm ConsenSys. SI Tickets is a division of the Sports Illustrated magazine and media brand.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Introducing Box Office, the all-new event management platform from Sports Illustrated Tickets 🎟️ Create and sell tickets for your own free or paid event on our site. Partner with us for an easy event set-up and lower fees than our competitors. #sitickets #sportsillustrated pic.twitter.com/84ASQkZUYg</p>
&mdash; SI Tickets (@si_tickets_) May 2, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>According to the announcement:</p>

<p>Box Office is the first global platform to combine a complete NFT ticket solution for events of any size with visibility and adjacency to traditional, non-NFT tickets alongside the biggest in sports, concert and theatre on the SI Tickets marketplace.</p>

<p>Box Office delivers a seamless &ldquo;experience giving owners, organisers and host the ability to create, manage and promote a fully scalable, paid, or free ticketed live sporting event, performance or function fuelled by the Sports Illustrated Tickets platform.&rdquo;</p>
<p>SI Tickets CEO, David Lane, said this new marketplace aims to &ldquo;disrupt the primary ticket market.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Lane added:</p>

<p>Blockchain is the future of ticketing, and now owners, promoters, hosts and attendees have access to an advanced ticketing experience that transforms the antiquated barcode into engaging and collectable content.</p>

<p>Box Office caters to the biggest events in sports and music but welcomes ticket listings from smaller ticket issuers that typically appear on ticketing sites like Eventbrite or DICE. Lane commented on this, saying:</p>

<p>We&rsquo;re not here to compete against Ticketmaster, SeatGeek, or AXS. We&rsquo;re going after the self-service event market. We&rsquo;re trying to create the first mass-market adoption of NFT ticketing so that everyone from a 15-year-old to a 90-year-old can buy their first NFT ticket without having to go through a crypto tutorial on blockchain, or have to get a wallet and understand any aspects of it.</p>

<p>Box Office NFT tickets will confer a host of benefits to its holder. In addition to granting entry, event organisers can equip tickets with photo and video content, collectables, personalised messages, promotional offers and loyalty rewards. Tickets can be found inside the SI Tickets app.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Worldcoin Launches Gas-free, Human-only Crypto Wallet]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/worldcoin-launches-gas-free-human-only-crypto-wallet</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/worldcoin-launches-gas-free-human-only-crypto-wallet</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Worldcoin, an innovative project designed to identify humans and distinguish them from artificial intelligence, has announced the launch of a unique gas-free cryptocurrency wallet exclusively for verified humans.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The World App, created by Tools For Humanity, incorporates the project's "World ID" system to differentiate between humans and bots. To access the gas-free transfers, users need to first register for a World ID by providing a phone number or submitting an iris scan. Interestingly, the project doesn't store users' personal data. Instead, it generates a zero-knowledge proof to verify that the user is human without revealing the data used to generate the proof. Such a system ensures a high level of security and privacy for users. Users who don't have a World ID yet, may still use the app but won't be able to take advantage of the feeless transactions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">One of the primary objectives of the World App is to simplify the process for inexperienced crypto users. Worldcoin core team member Tiago Sada explained that they initially tested regular wallets, but they proved to be overwhelming for ordinary users due to their complexity. With the World App, the focus is on simplicity and ease of use. Durikng its testing phase, the app has already managed to attract 1.5 million users and processes around 60,000 transactions on a typical day.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;When we first started, we actually just went out with normal wallets, the wallets a power user like me would use day-to-day, and it turns out those were too overwhelming for normal people. There were too many options, too many things to do, [which were] not super clear. [...] We&rsquo;re launching [this wallet] as a product so that there is this alternative wallet that is focused just on simplicity," Sada shares.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Available for download in over 80 countries, the World App aims to maximize inclusivity by offering support for phones that are over ten years old. This makes it more accessible for people in developing countries and those who may not have the latest smartphones. The app is also available in multiple languages, catering to a diverse user base.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The World App has partnered with regulated cryptocurrency exchanges like Moonpay and Ramp to facilitate seamless onboarding and offboarding directly from within the wallet. Users can easily deposit and withdraw funds using their bank accounts or local payment tools. Once the coins are held in the wallet, they can be swapped through the built-in Uniswap integration. Additionally, users can connect their phone numbers to the app to send and receive cryptocurrency through phone contacts, making the process even more convenient.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Worldcoin, co-founded by Sam Altman, who also co-founded ChatGPT developer OpenAI, plans to launch its token later this year. Users in eligible countries will be able to claim the token on a weekly or monthly basis. However, users in the U.S. are not meant to hold the asset. The World App's final version will run on Ethereum rollups and will focus on artificial intelligence (AI) and ID technology. The Worldcoin project claims that it seeks to provide AI-funded Universal Basic Income (UBI), empowering individuals in the Age of AI.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite its groundbreaking technology, Worldcoin has faced controversy since 2021 due to its reliance on retina-scanning ID technology, which many have labeled "dystopian." However, the project has attempted to address these concerns by integrating its World ID product into the World App on an optional basis. The app doesn't require any personal information from users, and they can delete their data instantly if they choose. World ID keys are self-custodied, although users have the option to back up their keys on cloud services.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Worldcoin is not directly related to OpenAI beyond Sam Altman's involvement in both firms. Altman has held various positions in the tech industry, including roles at the startup accelerator YCombinator between 2011 and 2019.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The wallet is compatible with both Android and iOS operating systems and runs on the Polygon (MATIC) network. Currently, the wallet supports Circle's USD stablecoin (USDC), Dai (DAI), Ether (ETH), Worldcoin (WLD), and Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Worldcoin, an innovative project designed to identify humans and distinguish them from artificial intelligence, has announced the launch of a unique gas-free cryptocurrency wallet exclusively for verified humans.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The World App, created by Tools For Humanity, incorporates the project's "World ID" system to differentiate between humans and bots. To access the gas-free transfers, users need to first register for a World ID by providing a phone number or submitting an iris scan. Interestingly, the project doesn't store users' personal data. Instead, it generates a zero-knowledge proof to verify that the user is human without revealing the data used to generate the proof. Such a system ensures a high level of security and privacy for users. Users who don't have a World ID yet, may still use the app but won't be able to take advantage of the feeless transactions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">One of the primary objectives of the World App is to simplify the process for inexperienced crypto users. Worldcoin core team member Tiago Sada explained that they initially tested regular wallets, but they proved to be overwhelming for ordinary users due to their complexity. With the World App, the focus is on simplicity and ease of use. Durikng its testing phase, the app has already managed to attract 1.5 million users and processes around 60,000 transactions on a typical day.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;When we first started, we actually just went out with normal wallets, the wallets a power user like me would use day-to-day, and it turns out those were too overwhelming for normal people. There were too many options, too many things to do, [which were] not super clear. [...] We&rsquo;re launching [this wallet] as a product so that there is this alternative wallet that is focused just on simplicity," Sada shares.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Available for download in over 80 countries, the World App aims to maximize inclusivity by offering support for phones that are over ten years old. This makes it more accessible for people in developing countries and those who may not have the latest smartphones. The app is also available in multiple languages, catering to a diverse user base.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The World App has partnered with regulated cryptocurrency exchanges like Moonpay and Ramp to facilitate seamless onboarding and offboarding directly from within the wallet. Users can easily deposit and withdraw funds using their bank accounts or local payment tools. Once the coins are held in the wallet, they can be swapped through the built-in Uniswap integration. Additionally, users can connect their phone numbers to the app to send and receive cryptocurrency through phone contacts, making the process even more convenient.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Worldcoin, co-founded by Sam Altman, who also co-founded ChatGPT developer OpenAI, plans to launch its token later this year. Users in eligible countries will be able to claim the token on a weekly or monthly basis. However, users in the U.S. are not meant to hold the asset. The World App's final version will run on Ethereum rollups and will focus on artificial intelligence (AI) and ID technology. The Worldcoin project claims that it seeks to provide AI-funded Universal Basic Income (UBI), empowering individuals in the Age of AI.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite its groundbreaking technology, Worldcoin has faced controversy since 2021 due to its reliance on retina-scanning ID technology, which many have labeled "dystopian." However, the project has attempted to address these concerns by integrating its World ID product into the World App on an optional basis. The app doesn't require any personal information from users, and they can delete their data instantly if they choose. World ID keys are self-custodied, although users have the option to back up their keys on cloud services.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Worldcoin is not directly related to OpenAI beyond Sam Altman's involvement in both firms. Altman has held various positions in the tech industry, including roles at the startup accelerator YCombinator between 2011 and 2019.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The wallet is compatible with both Android and iOS operating systems and runs on the Polygon (MATIC) network. Currently, the wallet supports Circle's USD stablecoin (USDC), Dai (DAI), Ether (ETH), Worldcoin (WLD), and Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
