<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Brazil: Suspected Braiscompany Crypto Fraudsters Detained in Argentina</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazil-suspected-braiscompany-crypto-fraudsters-detained-argentina.htm</link><description>Three suspected Brazilian crypto fraudsters have been detained while trying to flee to Argentina – as police continue to probe the troubled Braiscompany. &lt;br /&gt;
In March, a number of suspected employees were filmed apparently emptying the firm’s São Paulo premises under cover of night. &lt;br /&gt;
In May, police officers issued arrest warrants for a number of Braiscompany employees....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazil-suspected-braiscompany-crypto-fraudsters-detained-argentina.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazil: Suspected Braiscompany Crypto Fraudsters Detained in Argentina&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Police</category><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazil-suspected-braiscompany-crypto-fraudsters-detained-argentina.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117992/314773/policia-federal-faz-busca.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="157235"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Faces Double Top Resistance at $31,000, Will Bearish Correction Follow?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-faces-double-top-resistance-at-31000-will-bearish-correction-follow.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin garners global attention, investors and traders closely monitor its price movements.  &lt;br /&gt;
Currently, Bitcoin (BTC) encounters a significant obstacle in the form of double top resistance at the $31,000 level.  &lt;br /&gt;
This resistance has previously acted as a strong barrier, raising concerns about the potential for a bearish correction in the near future. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-faces-double-top-resistance-at-31000-will-bearish-correction-follow.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Faces Double Top Resistance at $31,000, Will Bearish Correction Follow?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-faces-double-top-resistance-at-31000-will-bearish-correction-follow.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117999/314780/26-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="484859"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Holds $0.00009 Level – When is the Next Leg Up?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-holds-000009-level-when-next-leg-up.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) has attracted attention in the crypto market as it rebounds after a period of inactivity, with over a 2% increase indicating a bullish trend.  &lt;br /&gt;
Investors are considering if it's a good time to buy before a potential breakout. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite the recent market crash and regulatory concerns, Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) has shown resilience. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-holds-000009-level-when-next-leg-up.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Holds $0.00009 Level – When is the Next Leg Up?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-holds-000009-level-when-next-leg-up.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117956/314777/terra.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="306261"/></item><item><title>FTX Investment Was Correct Decision, Claims Sequoia Partner Alfred Lin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-investment-was-correct-decision-claims-sequoia-partner-alfred-lin.htm</link><description>Following the sudden crash of FTX exchange, many firms tied to the platform also suffered, and many more who had invested in the platform concluded that their investments were the wrong move.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, American venture capitalist, Alfred Lin, who is also a partner at Sequoia Capital, has stood by the decision. &lt;br /&gt;
Sequoia invested $213.5 million into the now-bankrupt exchange, but Lin said in a recent talk that the investment was the right move at the time. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-investment-was-correct-decision-claims-sequoia-partner-alfred-lin.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Investment Was Correct Decision, Claims Sequoia Partner Alfred Lin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-investment-was-correct-decision-claims-sequoia-partner-alfred-lin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117924/314675/ftx-investment-was-correc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="364896"/></item><item><title>AI and Cryptocurrency Integration is Inevitable, say Experts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-cryptocurrency-integration-inevitable-say-experts.htm</link><description>The recent Coinbase State of Crypto Summit that took place last Thursday led participants into some interesting debates.  &lt;br /&gt;
One of the biggest and potentially most controversial ones was the future of crypto/blockchain technologies and AI. &lt;br /&gt;
Specifically, venture capitalists and AI experts shared their thoughts on the matter, with some believing that the two will soon become inseparable....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-cryptocurrency-integration-inevitable-say-experts.htm"&gt;Read More: AI and Cryptocurrency Integration is Inevitable, say Experts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-cryptocurrency-integration-inevitable-say-experts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117932/314691/ai-and-cryptocurrency-int.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="119774"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 26, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-june-26-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Pink BNB (PNB) &lt;br /&gt;
BinanceAdded Trading Pairs:BTC/ARSOP/TRYPAXG/TRY...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-june-26-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 26, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-june-26-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117953/314719/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried Shot Crypto MasterClass Prior to FTX Collapse</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-shot-crypto-masterclass-prior-to-ftx-collapse.htm</link><description>Disgraced crypto boss Sam Bankman-Fried had shot a tutorial video on cryptocurrency for MasterClass, a platform that offers courses taught by celebrity experts.  &lt;br /&gt;
The video, made last summer, was not included with other lessons presented by crypto and blockchain experts that MasterClass announced in December last year following FTX's collapse in November. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-shot-crypto-masterclass-prior-to-ftx-collapse.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried Shot Crypto MasterClass Prior to FTX Collapse&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>MasterClass</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-shot-crypto-masterclass-prior-to-ftx-collapse.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117978/314758/screenshot-2022-12-16-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="30103"/></item><item><title>Volatility Shares Trust Seeks SEC Approval for Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/volatility-shares-trust-seeks-sec-approval-for-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-1.htm</link><description>A new exchange-traded fund (ETF) backed by Bitcoin (BTC) futures and with 2x leverage is set to go live on Tuesday after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) appears to have given the greenlight. &lt;br /&gt;
The ETF, sponsored by Volatility Shares Trust, will be listed on the CBOE BZX Exchange under the ticker BITX, according to an SEC filing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/volatility-shares-trust-seeks-sec-approval-for-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Volatility Shares Trust Seeks SEC Approval for Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>ETF</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/volatility-shares-trust-seeks-sec-approval-for-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117979/314759/etf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="64317"/></item><item><title>2020 Twitter Hack Mastermind Gets Five-Year Sentence for Crypto Theft</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/2020-twitter-hack-mastermind-gets-five-year-sentence-for-crypto-theft.htm</link><description>A culprit in the infamous 2020 Twitter hack who phished thousands of dollars in Bitcoin from Twitter users has been sentenced to five years in prison for his crime, as well as for a separate SIM swapping scheme. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/2020-twitter-hack-mastermind-gets-five-year-sentence-for-crypto-theft.htm"&gt;Read More: 2020 Twitter Hack Mastermind Gets Five-Year Sentence for Crypto Theft&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/2020-twitter-hack-mastermind-gets-five-year-sentence-for-crypto-theft.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117976/314755/adobestock-479240343.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="78411"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Prosecutors Impose Travel Ban on Haru Execs, US Retailers Hit with Bomb Threats &amp; Bitcoin Demands, Gemini Allows Withdrawals for Voyager Users</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-prosecutors-impose-travel-ban-on-haru-execs-us-retailers-hit-with-bomb-threats-bitcoin-demands-gemini-allows-withdrawals-for-voyager-users.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-prosecutors-impose-travel-ban-on-haru-execs-us-retailers-hit-with-bomb-threats-bitcoin-demands-gemini-allows-withdrawals-for-voyager-users.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Prosecutors Impose Travel Ban on Haru Execs, US Retailers Hit with Bomb Threats &amp; Bitcoin Demands, Gemini Allows Withdrawals for Voyager Users&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Legal</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Binance</category><category>Austria</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Voyager Digital</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Turkey</category><category>ByBit</category><category>Cyprus</category><category>Europe</category><category>EU</category><category>Security</category><category>USA</category><category>Japan</category><category>Tax</category><category>UK</category><category>FCA</category><category>Career</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-prosecutors-impose-travel-ban-on-haru-execs-us-retailers-hit-with-bomb-threats-bitcoin-demands-gemini-allows-withdrawals-for-voyager-users.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117918/314685/adobestock-africa-studio-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="395508"/></item><item><title>ECB Executive Fabio Panetta: Cryptocurrencies Hold No Societal Benefits, Likens to Gambling</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ecb-executive-fabio-panetta-cryptocurrencies-hold-no-societal-benefits-likens-gambling.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrencies hold “no societal benefits,” and should instead be seen as a form of gambling, according to European Central Bank (ECB) board member Fabio Panetta. &lt;br /&gt;
In a speech held at the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) last week, Panetta argued that cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), fail to serve any meaningful purpose in society....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ecb-executive-fabio-panetta-cryptocurrencies-hold-no-societal-benefits-likens-gambling.htm"&gt;Read More: ECB Executive Fabio Panetta: Cryptocurrencies Hold No Societal Benefits, Likens to Gambling&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>ECB</category><category>Gambling</category><category>Regulation</category><category>EU</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ecb-executive-fabio-panetta-cryptocurrencies-hold-no-societal-benefits-likens-gambling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117949/314718/gambling.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="260620"/></item><item><title>Token Issuers in Japan to Be Exempt from 30% Crypto Tax on Unrealized Gains</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/token-issuers-japan-exempt-from-30-crypto-tax-unrealized-gains.htm</link><description>Japanese token issuers have been exempted from corporate taxes on unrealized cryptocurrency gains. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent announcement, the country's National Tax Agency revealed that it has revised its law to exempt crypto token issuers from 30% corporate taxes on unrealized gains, effective from June 20. &lt;br /&gt;
The move comes as Japan seeks to boost its blockchain and crypto sectors amid a push for "new capitalism", according to Prime Minister Fumio Kishida. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/token-issuers-japan-exempt-from-30-crypto-tax-unrealized-gains.htm"&gt;Read More: Token Issuers in Japan to Be Exempt from 30% Crypto Tax on Unrealized Gains&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Japan</category><category>Tax</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/token-issuers-japan-exempt-from-30-crypto-tax-unrealized-gains.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117929/314684/jezael-melgoza-nosmx8kgoo.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="904742"/></item><item><title>FC Barcelona Partners with World of Women for NFT Collection</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fc-barcelona-partners-with-world-of-women-for-nft-collection.htm</link><description>European football giant FC Barcelona has partnered with the non-fungible token (NFT) project World of Women to release the second artwork in its 'Masterpiece' collection. &lt;br /&gt;
Titled 'Empowerment', the NFT artwork is inspired by Alexia Putellas, a renowned Spanish football player. Alexia, who captains Barcelona and represents the national team of Spain, serves as the inspiration for this unique piece....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fc-barcelona-partners-with-world-of-women-for-nft-collection.htm"&gt;Read More: FC Barcelona Partners with World of Women for NFT Collection&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><category>Sport</category><category>Opensea</category><category>Art</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fc-barcelona-partners-with-world-of-women-for-nft-collection.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117898/314654/screenshot-2023-06-26-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="423436"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Blasts Up 15% – Is a New Bull Market Starting</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-blasts-up-15-new-bull-market-starting.htm</link><description>The price of Bitcoin has experienced a remarkable surge, skyrocketing by 15% in recent days.  &lt;br /&gt;
This significant uptick in value has sparked speculation and excitement among cryptocurrency enthusiasts and investors alike.  &lt;br /&gt;
Many are now wondering if this surge indicates the start of a new bull market for Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, it is worth noting that Bitcoin faces a major challenge in breaking above the $31,000 double-top pattern. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-blasts-up-15-new-bull-market-starting.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Blasts Up 15% – Is a New Bull Market Starting&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-blasts-up-15-new-bull-market-starting.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117902/314627/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1676690"/></item><item><title>NEAR Foundation and Alibaba Cloud Join Forces to Boost Web3 Development in Asia</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/near-foundation-alibaba-cloud-join-forces-boost-web3-development-asia.htm</link><description>NEAR Foundation, a non-profit organization responsible for developing the NEAR protocol, has partnered with Alibaba Cloud to facilitate the growth of Web3 in Asia and the Middle East.  &lt;br /&gt;
As part of the partnership, NEAR Foundation will gain access to Alibaba Cloud's developer ecosystem across the aforementioned regions, enabling more developers to create projects on the NEAR protocol....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/near-foundation-alibaba-cloud-join-forces-boost-web3-development-asia.htm"&gt;Read More: NEAR Foundation and Alibaba Cloud Join Forces to Boost Web3 Development in Asia&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>NEAR Protocol</category><category>NEAR</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Alibaba</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/near-foundation-alibaba-cloud-join-forces-boost-web3-development-asia.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117905/314635/adobestock-472835112-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="56082"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Hospital Will Accept Crypto Pay in National First</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-hospital-will-accept-crypto-pay-national-first.htm</link><description>A hospital in the Brazilian state of Rio Grande do Sul has become the first in the nation to accept crypto pay. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Brazilian media outlet Livecoins, the hospital in question is the Rolante Hospital Foundation (FHR), a large general hospital in the municipality of Rolante. &lt;br /&gt;
FHR is the oldest hospital in the municipality. &lt;br /&gt;
FHR patients will now be able to use crypto to settle their medical bills, pay for outpatient treatment, and buy medicine....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-hospital-will-accept-crypto-pay-national-first.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Hospital Will Accept Crypto Pay in National First&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Crypto Pay</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-hospital-will-accept-crypto-pay-national-first.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117885/314590/adobestock-542179982.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="421520"/></item><item><title>South Korean Court Rules That Bitcoin ‘Is Not Money’ – And Crypto’s Not Subject to Interest Rate Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-court-rules-that-bitcoin-is-not-money-cryptos-not-subject-interest-rate-rules.htm</link><description>A South Korean court has ruled that “Bitcoin (BTC) is not money,” and that “interest rate rules don’t apply” to business deals involving cryptoassets. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Hanguk Kyungjae, the ruling was made by the Seoul High Court’s Civil Division in a case involving two firms, both of which were unnamed for legal reasons....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-court-rules-that-bitcoin-is-not-money-cryptos-not-subject-interest-rate-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Court Rules That Bitcoin ‘Is Not Money’ – And Crypto’s Not Subject to Interest Rate Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-court-rules-that-bitcoin-is-not-money-cryptos-not-subject-interest-rate-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117881/314584/adobestock-182913144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="359234"/></item><item><title>Crypto Trading Crucial to Virtual Asset Ecosystem, Says Hong Kong SFC Chief</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-trading-crucial-virtual-asset-ecosystem-says-hong-kong-sfc-chief.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency trading is an important part of the virtual asset ecosystem, according to Julia Leung Fung-yee, CEO of the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) of Hong Kong. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent speech, Leung said the city-state recognizes the importance of crypto trading, adding that it welcomes the application of related technologies to financial services, including bond tokenization and investment funds. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-trading-crucial-virtual-asset-ecosystem-says-hong-kong-sfc-chief.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Trading Crucial to Virtual Asset Ecosystem, Says Hong Kong SFC Chief&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Crypto Trading</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-trading-crucial-virtual-asset-ecosystem-says-hong-kong-sfc-chief.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117882/314588/florian-wehde-8bjnp3yhntg.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="877350"/></item><item><title>Crypto Firm Wintermute Entangled in Lawsuit Against Celsius Network</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-firm-wintermute-entangled-lawsuit-against-celsius-network.htm</link><description>Creditors of the bankrupt landing firm Celsius have amended their lawsuit to include Wintermute.  &lt;br /&gt;
Plaintiffs in the class-action lawsuit against Celsius Network have now alleged that Wintermute helped the crypto lending firm in wash trading. &lt;br /&gt;
The new court filing shows Wintermute Trading Ltd as a new defendant in the ongoing class-action lawsuit, Bloomberg reported. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-firm-wintermute-entangled-lawsuit-against-celsius-network.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Firm Wintermute Entangled in Lawsuit Against Celsius Network&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Celsius</category><category>Wintermute</category><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-firm-wintermute-entangled-lawsuit-against-celsius-network.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117868/314583/celsius-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99557"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as $10 Billion Trading Volume Floods In On the Weekend – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-10-billion-trading-volume-floods-weekend-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has experienced a significant surge, reaching the $31,250 level and marking a nearly 15% increase in its value.  &lt;br /&gt;
This dramatic uptrend has caught the attention of investors and analysts alike, leading to speculation about continuing this bullish trend. &lt;br /&gt;
With a massive influx of trading volume, reaching $10 billion over the weekend, the question arises: Are whales buying into Bitcoin and fueling its upward momentum? ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-10-billion-trading-volume-floods-weekend-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as $10 Billion Trading Volume Floods In On the Weekend – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-10-billion-trading-volume-floods-weekend-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/117863/314559/25-4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="528337"/></item></channel></rss>
