<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:21:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Voyager Approved to Start Repaying Frozen Customers’ Accounts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-approved-to-start-repaying-frozen-customers-accounts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251121</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Voyager.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Voyager.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Voyager can only muster enough funds to pay back 36% of customer claims. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bankrupt crypto lending platform Voyager Digital won court approval on Wednesday to begin repaying its customers’ long-trapped money.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">So far, customers are only guaranteed to receive 36% of what they’re owed. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The approval to commence liquidation procedures comes over 10 months after Voyageur </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-files-for-bankruptcy-as-voyager-digital-suspends-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">froze</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> customer withdrawals in July 2022, shortly after defunct hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) filed for bankruptcy. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/failed-crypto-broker-voyager-digital-cleared-to-start-repaying-customers-frozen-funds-1.1921589" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Bloomberg, Judge Michael Wiles said that “nobody is happy with the liquidation,” referring to customers dissatisfied with the bankruptcy process and result. Common criticisms included the cost of the bankruptcy, the amount being paid to lawyers, the oversight of the case, and the fractional returns that creditors would receive. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, Wiles noted that this was their only option since Voyager simply lacks the funds to repay customers in full. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">“Hindsight’s 20/20 – ’m sure everybody wishes that something better had happened,” said Wiles. “We are where we are, we’re trying to do the best with where we are.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Voyager’s misfortunes continued long after </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-suspending-withdrawals-voyager-digital-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for bankruptcy in July. Its initial plan to strike a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-us-wins-bid-to-acquire-bankrupt-lender-voyagers-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">buyout deal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with FTX fell through when the crypto exchange imploded in November.  Voyager creditors later subpoenaed FTX’s executives for information about its plan to buyout the company, investigating whether it was a reasonable offer or just a publicity stunt. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Voyager’s $1 billion buyout deal with Binance US also fell through last month, with the former pulling out citing a “hostile and uncertain regulatory climate in the United States.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The lender currently has just $630 million to repay $1.8 billion in customer claims, according to a court filing on May 5. Its holdings may increase if a pending dispute with FTX proves fruitful.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-approved-to-start-repaying-frozen-customers-accounts/" rel="nofollow">Voyager Approved to Start Repaying Frozen Customers’ Accounts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Crypto Hub Ambitions on Rocks as Treasury Wants to Treat it as Gambling</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uk-crypto-hub-ambitions-on-rocks-as-treasury-wants-to-treat-it-as-gambling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250951</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/UKUnitedKingdom.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/UKUnitedKingdom.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Britain’s plans to become a crypto hub are on the rocks as lawmakers have other ideas about how digital assets should be regulated.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United Kingdom has grand aspirations of becoming a digital assets hub, just as London already is for traditional finance.</p>
<p>However, those plans are being thwarted by watchdogs and policymakers who want to take a heavy-handed approach to regulation.</p>
<p>On May 17, it was reported that a panel of UK lawmakers said crypto assets should be regulated as gambling “given they are potentially used by fraudsters and pose significant risks to consumers.”</p>
<p>The report from Parliament&#8217;s Treasury Committee added that cryptocurrencies are not backed by any currency or asset. This leads to “volatility in prices and the potential for all money invested in them to be wiped out,” <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-should-be-regulated-gambling-uk-lawmakers-say-2023-05-16/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to Reuters.</p>
<h2>Crypto is Gambling, Not Finance</h2>
<p>It is a similar stance to that taken in the United States, where a number of policymakers have labeled digital assets as everything from ‘shadow banking’ to ‘casino chips.’</p>
<p>The UK Treasury Committee said regulating retail trading and investment in unbacked cryptocurrencies could create a &#8216;halo&#8217; effect. This could lead to consumers thinking the activity is safer than it is or that they’re protected when they’re not.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We therefore strongly recommend that the Government regulates retail trading and investment activity in unbacked cryptoassets as gambling rather than as a financial service, consistent with its stated principle of ‘same risk, same regulatory outcome’.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Harriett Baldwin, chair of the Treasury Committee, labeled the industry a “wild west.” She said the events of 2022 highlighted the risks posed to consumers.</p>
<p>In April, economic secretary to the UK Treasury, Andrew Griffith, said that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-regulations-coming-within-a-year-in-the-uk-andrew-griffith-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto regulations</a> will be rolled out within the next 12 months.</p>
<h2>The Views of Sunak and Bailey</h2>
<p>Prime Minister Rishi Sunak is keen to promote the country as a crypto hub but is facing a lot of resistance from the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-treasury-will-consult-on-defi-taxation-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Treasury</a> and Central Bank.</p>
<p>Bank of England Governor, Andrew Bailey, has repeatedly argued that Bitcoin and its brethren have “no intrinsic value.” UK banks are also increasingly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-banks-refuse-to-work-with-crypto-companies-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">refusing to work</a> with crypto companies and putting up barriers for their customers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-crypto-hub-ambitions-on-rocks-as-treasury-wants-to-treat-it-as-gambling/" rel="nofollow">UK Crypto Hub Ambitions on Rocks as Treasury Wants to Treat it as Gambling</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jordan Peterson: Bitcoin is the Only Alternative to a CBDC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jordan-peterson-bitcoin-is-the-only-alternative-to-a-cbdc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251110</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Jordan_Peterson.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Jordan_Peterson.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The famous psychologist still believes in Bitcoin, and has an idea about how to leverage its permanent ledger for measuring IQ.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Famous Canadian psychologist and political commentator Jordan Peterson believes Bitcoin is the only “viable” monetary alternative in a future world dominated by central bank digital currency (CBDC).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The intellectual recently spoke with tech expert and entrepreneur Brian Roemmele about artificial intelligence and other emerging technologies, highlighting how Bitcoin can serve to shield the world from its tyrannical excesses. </span></p>
<h2>Using Bitcoin for Communication</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S_E4t7tWHUY&amp;ab_channel=JordanBPeterson" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> published on Monday, Roemmele said that he sees blockchain – specifically Bitcoin – being wrapped up into a popular payment system, due to the “way it was made.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Peterson followed up by saying that Bitcoin is the “only alternative I can see to a centralized bank digital currency,” which he predicted will be “foisted upon us at any point.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Bitcoin actually is decentralized,” said Peterson. “It isn’t amenable to control by a bureaucracy.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As the psychologist noted how Bitcoin could, in principle, be used for “wealth storage” and as a “currency,” Roemmele added that it could also be used for “communication.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Encrypted within a blockchain is almost an unlimited amount of data,” he said. “You can actually memorialize information that you want decentralized and never to go away.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Unlike traditional bank transfers, Bitcoin transactions that have been registered on the public blockchain for more than one hour are virtually irreversible and logged across tens of thousands of Bitcoin nodes across the world. This feature of Bitcoin has recently become popular for memorializing NFTs through the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-inscription-exceeds-5m-after-doubling-in-a-week-data/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ordinals protocol</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, which bakes image data directly into the public blockchain. </span></p>
<h2>Peterson’s Blockchain Idea</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Peterson noted that he’d be interested in using Bitcoin as a form of “permanent, incorruptible information storage” to develop a “blockchain corpus of general knowledge questions” for running IQ tests, and prevent people from “gerrymandering the measurement of general cognitive ability.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“You could derive random samples of general ability tests that would be 100% robust reliable and valid, and nobody could gerrymander them,” he said. “Just the way Bitcoins stops fiat currency producers from inflating the currency.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Peterson has previously </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jordan-peterson-bought-more-bitcoin-as-a-hedge-against-inflation/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">praised</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Bitcoin as a way of combatting tyrannical control imposed by CBDCs in the past. He’s also </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jordan-peterson-bought-more-bitcoin-as-a-hedge-against-inflation/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">regarded</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> it as an inflation hedge, and bought some as an inflation shield in November 2021 – though the asset hasn’t performed well since that time. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jordan-peterson-bitcoin-is-the-only-alternative-to-a-cbdc/" rel="nofollow">Jordan Peterson: Bitcoin is the Only Alternative to a CBDC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FDIC Chair Blames Crypto Exposure for Signature Bank&#8217;s Demise</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fdic-chair-blames-crypto-exposure-for-signature-banks-demise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250906</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Signature_Bank.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Signature_Bank.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Signature’s collapse was the third-largest commercial bank failure in the history of the United States.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Signature Bank&#8217;s involvement in the digital asset industry was the reason that ultimately caused its demise, according to FDIC&#8217;s Martin Gruenberg.</p>
<p>The chair also acknowledged FDIC&#8217;s shortcomings in not acting sooner to prevent the crisis from spreading throughout Signature&#8217;s operations. Gruenberg further added that the agency&#8217;s supervision could have been stronger.</p>
<h2>Crypto Culpable in Signature&#8217;s Collapse: FDIC Chair</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.fdic.gov/news/speeches/2023/spmay1523.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">speech</a> before the House Committee on Financial Services, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) chairman explicitly blamed Signature&#8217;s reliance on crypto industry deposits or its vulnerability to contagion from digital asset industry turmoil in late 2022 and into 2023.</p>
<p>He said that Signature Bank’s poor governance and inadequate risk management practices dragged the institution into a position where it could not effectively manage its liquidity in a time of stress, thereby making it unable to meet very large withdrawal requests.</p>
<p>Signature Bank was not exclusively a crypto bank, but its efforts toward the industry became more pronounced during the pandemic-era bull run. During this time, the New York-based bank became one of the major legacy institutions to embrace crypto.</p>
<p>However, the fall of FTX was a major turning point. In a bid to reduce its exposure to the industry in a turbulent time, Signature Bank distance itself. The claim was backed by the chairman and co-founder of the now-defunct bank, Scott Shay, during a prepared <a href="https://twitter.com/TheTranscript_/status/1658348508984795136" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">testimony</a> on Monday.</p>
<p>The former exec revealed that the bank made significant reductions in digital asset deposits as a result of heightened market volatility as well as regulatory apprehensions towards the end of the previous year.</p>
<h2>Blame Game</h2>
<p>Over the past several weeks, reports exploring the collapse of Signature Bank in March included exposure to the crypto industry alongside potential reasons. The premise that the bank’s ties to crypto-related businesses were behind its closure was also speculated by many.</p>
<p>But the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) Superintendent dismissed the assumption in an <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-had-no-relation-to-signature-banks-closure-new-york-finance-regulator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">interview</a> and assured that the bank was facing severe operational difficulties leading up to its shutdown.</p>
<p>The crypto industry reacted strongly to Signature&#8217;s seizure deeming the move as unnecessary, and blamed the regulators for specifically targeting them. Industry trade group the Blockchain Association submitted Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests to the FDIC and other agencies and pointed that the government actions might have &#8220;improperly contributed&#8221; to the failures.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fdic-chair-blames-crypto-exposure-for-signature-banks-demise/" rel="nofollow">FDIC Chair Blames Crypto Exposure for Signature Bank&#8217;s Demise</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DRC-20 Hype Fest Triggers Huge Spike in Dogecoin (DOGE) Transaction Volume</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/drc-20-hype-fest-triggers-huge-spike-in-dogecoin-doge-transaction-volume/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 20:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250877</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Dogecoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Dogecoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dogecoin's development of its very own DRC-20 has skyrocketed participation on the network]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the frenzy of BRC-20 tokens in the Bitcoin network, their DRC-20 counterparties have triggered a massive spike in Dogecoin&#8217;s transaction volume.</p>
<p>The OG memecoin experienced a significant surge in daily transactions and even surpassed that of Bitcoin and Litecoin briefly for the first time ever.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to data <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/transactions-btc-ltc-doge-dogecoin.html#1y" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">compiled</a> by BitInfoCharts, the daily Dogecoin skyrocketed on May 13th and peaked above 628,000. Transactions for Bitcoin and Litecoin, on the other hand, stood at 575,490 and 341,082, respectively.</li>
<li>An update <a href="https://twitter.com/mishaboar/status/1657923671371948034" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">shared</a> by DOGE community member Mishaboar pointed out the advent of DRC-20 &#8211; inspired by Bitcoin&#8217;s BRC-20 standard &#8211;  as a major catalyst prompting the memecoin&#8217;s transactions to go parabolic.</li>
<li>Lately, several Dogecoin <a href="https://twitter.com/wacy_time1/status/1657681995080798209" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">advocates</a> on Twitter have been pushing the narrative that DRC-20 is the new BRC-20 with &#8220;100x potential.&#8221;</li>
<li>This new token standard was released last week and enables users to inscribe digital artifacts on each of the smallest indivisible units of DOGE, which is known as &#8220;elons.&#8221; As such, one DOGE is equivalent to 100,000,000 elons.</li>
<li>Similar to BRC-20, inscriptions inscribe &#8220;elons&#8221; with arbitrary content, creating dogecoin-native digital artifacts, or NFTs. Inscriptions do not require a sidechain or separate token.</li>
<li>The transaction spike had a minor effect on the active address count of Dogecoin, which surged to above 67,000. The figures <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-doge-active-address-spike-above-100k-for-the-first-time-in-9-months/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">climbed</a> to levels not seen since August 2022, going above 100k in April amid the memecoin resurgence driven by PEPE.</li>
<li>Besides, Litecoin was caught in a wave of surging active addresses thanks to the introduction of LTC:20, the crypto-asset&#8217;s experimental standard for NFTs.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/drc-20-hype-fest-triggers-huge-spike-in-dogecoin-doge-transaction-volume/" rel="nofollow">DRC-20 Hype Fest Triggers Huge Spike in Dogecoin (DOGE) Transaction Volume</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Moved Nearly $900M of ETH Within a Week: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-moved-nearly-900m-of-eth-within-a-week-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251036</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Celsius_Tokens.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Celsius_Tokens.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In March, the company transferred to convert Wrapped Bitcoin (wBTC) tokens into Bitcoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celsius&#8217; wallets have been quite active amid its ongoing bankruptcy and restructuring process. The beleaguered crypto lender &#8211; which remains one of the biggest firms with a staked ETH portfolio &#8211; has transferred almost $900 million worth of the crypto asset over the past week.</p>
<h2>Celsius&#8217; Ether Movement</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1658771312834142208" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> shared by the blockchain intelligence firm Arkham, Celsius has moved around $20 million of ETH to Wintermute OTC and Custody Withdrawals. Subsequently, the bankrupt crypto lending firm also transferred 30,800 ETH, worth around $57 million at press time price, to a smart contract called &#8220;Figment ETH2 Beacon Depositor 1.&#8221;</p>
<p>The transaction to Figment, which is a non-custodial service, represented one of the largest movements of funds for the crypto lender since it filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in July.</p>
<p>Besides, Arkham also observed that Celsius unstaked the $779 million of ETH it had with the liquid staking derivatives protocol, Lido, which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-launches-v2-and-releases-staked-ethereum-for-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal">enabled</a> withdrawals on May 15 with a protocol upgrade to v2. The fund movement by Celsius is not surprising given that numerous entities that withdrew their staked ETH have already started <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thats-a-first-after-shanghai-ether-staked-volume-exceeds-withdrawals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">re-staking</a> them since mid-April.</p>
<p>Commenting on the move, Bitcoin pioneer and Celsius creditor Simon Dixon <a href="https://twitter.com/SimonDixonTwitt/status/1658142907012980738" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">speculated</a> that the firm could be &#8220;lining up for staking directly without Lido in the middle.&#8221; The withdrawn ether may also be used as part of the platforms&#8217; restructuring and creditor repayment plans.</p>
<h2>Celsius Story So Far</h2>
<p>Earlier this month, Celsius enabled eligible users to withdraw the remaining 6% of distributable custody assets from the platform following court approval. The same users &#8211;  mostly those who only ever held funds in custody accounts &#8211; were limited to withdrawing up to 94% of their funds until January this year.</p>
<p>The reimbursement move was viewed as a sign of progress for the now-defunct crypto lender, which froze user withdrawals last June as a result of tremendous pressure after the sudden implosion of blockchain project Terra and the subsequent meltdown of the crypto market.</p>
<p>Celsius <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-calls-for-consolidating-us-and-uk-entities-amidst-poor-record-keeping-allegations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for consolidating US and UK entities amidst poor record-keeping allegations and glaring deficiencies in its internal systems.</p>
<p>Its founder Alex Mashinsky was accused of defrauding investors out of billions of dollars in crypto by hiding the &#8220;failing health&#8221; of the lending platform. The exec &#8211; who stepped down from his CEO role in September &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-files-defense-motion-in-response-to-nyags-complaint/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> a response seeking to dismiss the New York State complaint against him.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-moved-nearly-900m-of-eth-within-a-week-data/" rel="nofollow">Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Moved Nearly $900M of ETH Within a Week: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diversification Doesn&#8217;t Work? NFT Influencers That Made or Lost Money With Memecoins</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/diversification-doesnt-work-nft-influencers-that-made-or-lost-money-with-memecoins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250880</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crypto_Funding.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crypto_Funding.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Recent data revealed that investing in only one memecoin has a higher chance to turn profitable than diversifying with many assets. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Savvy investors and NFT influencers have used the recent hype around memecoins as an opportunity to make solid profits. However, the majority of those who made money on such investments have only dealt with Pepe Coin (PEPE), while those diversifying with more than one have not been that successful.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite its recent price fluctuations, the now-trending memecoin is still intriguing for crypto whales and NFT traders. Certain users have sold digital art part of the Bored Ape Yacht Collection (BAYC) below the floor price to purchase PEPE.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Betting on Memecoins Could be Tricky</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lookonchain recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1658089349651763200" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> how four out of eight NFT influencers did when investing in popular memecoins such as PEPE, GENSLR, KEK, and TURBO. Two of them, going by the names &#8220;Vince_Van_Dough&#8221; and &#8220;ohhshiny,&#8221; made money after dealing only with the frog-inspired digital asset. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The former spent $167,000 worth of ETH to buy 96B PEPE and later sold the stash for $174K. &#8220;ohhshiny&#8221; was even more fortunate, purchasing 700B PEPE for 326 ETH ($610K). They then parted with 479B PEPE for nearly $1 million and kept the remaining amount. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For his part, &#8220;Zeneca&#8221; made $14K after investing in TURBO &#8211; an AI-related memecoin whose price and market capitalization peaked at the beginning of the month. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, the NFT influencers &#8220;ColeThereum,&#8221; &#8220;dingalingts,&#8221; and &#8220;boredGenius&#8221; recorded some losses after diversifying with numerous assets. &#8220;ColeThereum&#8221; invested in more than a dozen memecoins and lost a total of $3,365. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;dingalingts&#8221; parted with approximately $16,000 after trading FOUR, THEND, TURBO, and COPE, whereas &#8220;boredGenius&#8221; lost over $7,000.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">PEPE is Still a Trend</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The memecoin, launched in mid-April, quickly gained steam and emerged as one of crypto&#8217;s best performers in the last few weeks. The craze around it was so high that its market cap surpassed $1.6 billion at the beginning of May (CoinMarketCap data), while some investors </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-someone-turned-27-into-1-million-in-days-with-pepe-but-theres-a-catch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">made</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> spectacular profits from its almost daily ATHs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, the token&#8217;s price tumbled in the past seven days, hinting that the hype is over. Certain crypto whales did not support that thesis and kept accumulating.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One user who previously made $2.2 million on the memecoin </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1657339024812699648" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">spent</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $2.1 million to repurchase PEPE. Another </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1657990290509283329" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">exchanged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> nearly 400,000 APE for almost 750M PEPE.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-dominates-doge-and-shib-in-daily-trading-volume-despite-25-weekly-decline/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this week, the asset&#8217;s daily trading volume remained unbeaten in the memecoin field for over a week. Yesterday&#8217;s figures showed that PEPE&#8217;s 24h volume surpassed $350 million, while DOGE was second with $214 million. Today&#8217;s numbers are also in favor of the frog-themed coin, although with a decreased lead. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/diversification-doesnt-work-nft-influencers-that-made-or-lost-money-with-memecoins/" rel="nofollow">Diversification Doesn&#8217;t Work? NFT Influencers That Made or Lost Money With Memecoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Symbiosis Brings SIS Token to zkSync</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/symbiosis-brings-sis-token-to-zksync/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251067</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/downloadeee_1684312106UTVYX0Tv0K.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/downloadeee_1684312106UTVYX0Tv0K.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, May 17th, 2023] Symbiosis is a cross-chain DEX that aggregates liquidity from different blockchains, making it effortless for users to trade any token and transfer their assets across chains. The Symbiosis team is thrilled to announce the deployment of $SIS, the governance token of the Symbiosis ecosystem, on zkSync, a [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, May 17th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Symbiosis is a cross-chain DEX that aggregates liquidity from different blockchains, making it effortless for users to trade any token and transfer their assets across chains.</p>
<p>The Symbiosis team is thrilled to announce the deployment of $SIS, the governance token of the Symbiosis ecosystem, on zkSync, a layer-two scaling solution that enhances privacy and throughput for Ethereum and other blockchains.</p>
<p>$SIS serves as a means of staking for running a node in the network of relayers and is rewarded to users as an incentive. Until now, $SIS was deployed only on Ethereum, BNB Chain, and Arbitrum, supporting the veSIS mechanism, token rewards for stable farms, LP farms on DEX, and DAO voting.</p>
<p>Now, Symbiosis is expanding its multi-chain environment by introducing $SIS on zkSync, which marks a significant step forward. The project believes that zero-knowledge proofs are necessary for the blockchain&#8217;s privacy and scalability. By having $SIS on zkSync, Symbiosis aims to attract a broader community to its native token.</p>
<p>Symbiosis continues to innovate in the cross-chain space, and zkSync integration is just the beginning. The project is committed to offering exciting updates and expanding its features to create a more seamless and decentralized swapping experience.</p>
<p><strong>Contract address: </strong>0xdd9f72afED3631a6C85b5369D84875e6c42f1827</p>
<p>Symbiosis is the perfect solution for DeFi enthusiasts who want to swap any token with ease and transfer their assets across different blockchains. With just one click, any-to-any cross-chain operations are executed, providing competitive exchange rates and minimal transaction costs.</p>
<p><strong>Join Symbiosis on social media to stay updated on the latest developments:</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-center"><a href="https://twitter.com/symbiosis_fi" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/symbiosis_finance" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://discord.gg/DckkhfWN" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a> |</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/symbiosis-brings-sis-token-to-zksync/" rel="nofollow">Symbiosis Brings SIS Token to zkSync</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pantos Releases Multichain Token Creator, Enabling Users to Deploy Tokens on Multiple Blockchains</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pantos-releases-multichain-token-creator-enabling-users-to-deploy-tokens-on-multiple-blockchains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251060</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pantos_Token_Creator_1684328856TLUjmUqlTd.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pantos_Token_Creator_1684328856TLUjmUqlTd.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Vienna, Austria, May 17th, 2023] Pantos, a Multichain Token System conceived by the team behind Bitpanda, today announced the public release of the Multichain Token Creator. It is an easy-to-use web app that allows users to configure and deploy their own multichain tokens built on top of the Pantos Digital Asset Standard [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Vienna, Austria, May 17th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Pantos, a Multichain Token System conceived by the team behind Bitpanda, today announced the public release of the Multichain Token Creator. It is an easy-to-use web app that allows users to configure and deploy their own multichain tokens built on top of the Pantos Digital Asset Standard (PANDAS). Moreover, developers can configure their base token and download the contract code to extend it with their custom functionality.</p>
<p>The Multichain Token Creator makes it easy for projects to launch on multiple blockchain networks, increasing their reach without much effort and creating more opportunities for the community and the projects themselves. Developers, users, and their assets no longer have to be locked to a single chain.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our Multichain Token Creator is a defining innovation in the blockchain space, offering developers and projects an effortless way to adopt a revolutionary multichain token standard that drives unparalleled cross-chain collaboration and opens up endless possibilities for the future of decentralized technology,” said Marius Ciortan, the Director of Product Engineering at Pantos.</p></blockquote>
<p>For developers, the Token Creator dramatically reduces the time and complexity of developing multichain assets, enabling them to launch their tokens within minutes. Users, on the other hand, will have a smoother multichain experience thanks to the increased availability of native multichain assets through the easy token creation process.</p>
<p>Pantos will showcase the Token Creator to the public for the first time during Super Demo at the upcoming EDCON conference, to be held between May 19-23 in Montenegro. It will also introduce the Pantos Digital Asset Standard (PANDAS) at the event. The EDCON Super Demo provides a platform for the startups or projects promoting the development of Ethereum technology and its ecosystem. The Super Demo starts on the first day of the conference, May 19th, and concludes on May 22nd.</p>
<p>Pantos began in 2018 as an in-house research project by Bitpanda in collaboration with TU Wien (Austria) and later also TU Hamburg (Germany) to establish an open standard for truly decentralized multichain token transfers and blockchain interoperability. It allows developers and users to send tokens, wrap native coins of supported chains, and create and deploy native multichain tokens easily with a few clicks.</p>
<p>Pantos currently supports seven chains on testnet: Ethereum, Polygon, Avalanche, BNB, Cronos, Celo and Fantom; and plans to integrate more EVM and non-EVM chains continuously. Earlier this month, Pantos won the &#8216;Best Business Model&#8217; award at the Austrian Blockchain Award Gala.</p>
<h2>About Pantos</h2>
<p>Started as a research project by the team behind Bitpanda in 2018, Pantos is an open-source protocol on a mission to make Web3 truly interoperable. It aims to become an enabler for sophisticated Web3 applications. Pantos’ cutting-edge technology allows existing and upcoming tokens to be deployed on multiple blockchain networks, giving users the freedom to choose the most suitable network for their digital assets. It secured $12.1 million in funding through an Initial Coin Offering (ICO) on Bitpanda in 2018.</p>
<p><strong>For more information, visit</strong>: <a href="https://pantos.io/en" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a>  |  <a href="https://twitter.com/PantosIO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pantos-releases-multichain-token-creator-enabling-users-to-deploy-tokens-on-multiple-blockchains/" rel="nofollow">Pantos Releases Multichain Token Creator, Enabling Users to Deploy Tokens on Multiple Blockchains</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>IOVLabs Introduces a $2.5M Program to Boost the Development of Bitcoin&#8217;s Sidechain Rootstock</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/iovlabs-introduces-a-2-5m-program-to-boost-the-development-of-bitcoins-sidechain-rootstock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 13:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251008</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Bitcoin_Dark.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Bitcoin_Dark.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[IOVLabs launche a $2.5 million program and a Hackaton to support the advancement of Rootstock. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">IOVLabs &#8211; a company that develops decentralized blockchain technologies &#8211; launched a $2.5 million &#8220;strategic grants program&#8221; to accelerate the adoption of Rootstock.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latter is a sidechain tied with Bitcoin and designated to enable smart contracts for the ecosystem.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Strong Commitment&#8217; to Advance BTC</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a document seen by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the Argentina-based blockchain entity will use the financing to enhance the development of Bitcoin&#8217;s sidechain &#8211; Rootstock. IOVLabs алсо announced the launch of a Hackaton in a mutual effort with HackerEarth.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ежент will run from May to July and will pass through three phases: an ideation stage, a development period, and a final pitch to a panel of judges from the Bitcoin and Rootstock ecosystems. The program is available for blockchain developers from each part of the globe. Hackaton participants could win more than $25,000 in awards.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pei Chen &#8211; IOVLabs VP of Growth &#8211; said the $2.5 million program demonstrates the entity&#8217;s &#8220;strong commitment&#8221; to &#8220;build a truly decentralized financial system on Bitcoin.&#8221; She thinks developers could harness the Rootstock sidechain and &#8220;help create a freer and fairer financial system for all.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Chen praised the sidechain for becoming &#8220;the home of DeFi on Bitcoin,&#8221; which is why it should be available to everyone regardless of their technical ability.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This is how the first billion users will be onboarded to Web3, and together, we can make it happen,&#8221; she concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">President Daniel Fogg said he is &#8220;excited&#8221; to see how developers use Bitcoin&#8217;s potential to solve daily issues for people around the world. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Every network has its sweet spot, and for Rootstock, it&#8217;s all about using Bitcoin to create a more accessible and fairer financial system for all. By bringing together EVM compatibility with the unmatched security of Bitcoin, Rootstock offers developers a network that can be trusted to support the financial futures of people worldwide, no matter their economic status,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Previous Effort</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CryptoPotato</span></em><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/iov-labs-launches-rif-flyover-to-ease-transfers-between-bitcoin-and-rootstock/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this year, IOVLabs launched its Rootstock Infrastructure Framework (RIF) Flyover to allow smooth and quicker transfers between Bitcoin and the Rootstock sidechain. The initiative requires the services of third-party liquidity providers. Sergio Demian &#8211; Chief Scientist at IOVLabs &#8211; commented:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are excited to release the RIF Flyover protocol to the Rootstock community. The protocol significantly reduces the amount of time required to transfer bitcoins between the Bitcoin and the Rootstock chain without compromising security. This is achieved by ensuring that the funds are never in custody of a third party during the transfer.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/iovlabs-introduces-a-2-5m-program-to-boost-the-development-of-bitcoins-sidechain-rootstock/" rel="nofollow">IOVLabs Introduces a $2.5M Program to Boost the Development of Bitcoin&#8217;s Sidechain Rootstock</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
