<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 04:37:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Left Behind After Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Surges 655% in Presale]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/cardano-ada-left-behind-after-orbeon-protocol-orbn-surges-655-in-presale</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-14-at-215728.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-14-at-215728.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-14-at-215728.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/cardano-ada-left-behind-after-orbeon-protocol-orbn-surges-655-in-presale</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has set new highs leaving behind Cardano (ADA) which has been dropping lately. </p>
<p>With stage 3 of the presale already underway, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) price has risen by over 655% in just a few weeks, while Cardano (ADA) continues to underperform. </p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s look at a few reasons for the fast growth of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) while Cardano (ADA) stagnates. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Surges by 655% in Presale</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol facilitates secure and transparent interactions between investors and emerging companies. Orbeon Protocol offers a number of safety measures, such as a "Fill or Kill," mechanism that make investing simple and risk-free. If a project doesn't raise enough money within the required amount of time, investors' money is returned.</p>
<p>The pre-sale for Orbeon Protocol has been quite successful. It is in phase 1 of its presale, and the price of ORBN tokens has increased by 655%. The growing popularity of the Orbeon Protocol can largely be attributed to its utility or use cases. </p>
<p>Thanks to Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), virtually anybody can now make seed investments in new businesses of their choice. </p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol facilitates this through the use of its NFT-as-a-Service (NFTaaS). The service creates equity-based fractionalized NFTs for companies that investors can buy at a low price. These NFTs are accessible to anybody and everyone who holds ORBN tokens for as little as $1.</p>
<p>This type of NFT-based investment paves the way for new entrants to enter the speculative venture capital industry without restrictions. It is making funding via non-traditional channels, such as venture capital (VC) and crowdsourcing, less cumbersome for the average investor. The new approach is also helping startups better engage with their communities in a Web3 environment. </p>
<p>In the presale phase, investors can purchase ORBN tokens at a discount and make profits later on. Market analysts predict a price increase of 6000%. Orbeon Protocol is definitely worth looking into as we head to 2023. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) </p>
<p>Charles Hoskinson, a controversial figure and co-creator of Ethereum, launched Cardano in 2015. </p>
<p>Cardano is a cryptocurrency that runs on the Cardano blockchain and enables its users to create tokens, develop and deploy dApps, and execute smart contracts. Cardano is well-prepared for operation, and its creators are dedicated to making it even better. </p>
<p>Cardano (ADA), the utility token for the platform, is a well-known crypto asset with a huge market capitalization. However, since the crypto winter hit, Cardano (ADA) has not been able to repeat its stellar performance of 2020. </p>
<p>This month alone has seen a huge decline in Cardano's value, and the cryptocurrency is now trading at a price that is 90% under its all-time peak of $3.09.</p>
<p>Cardano's ambitious goal of fostering a more autonomous and decentralized society has attracted a sizable online following. However, its performance lately has been anything but promising. </p>
<p>For Cardano investors, getting into the innovative technology that the Orbeon Protocol is introducing to the crowdfunding and VC industries is a double win. Orbeon, like Cardano, seeks to bring about change for those who have been excluded from the global financial system.</p>
<p class="s9">Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s12">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has set new highs leaving behind Cardano (ADA) which has been dropping lately. </p>
<p>With stage 3 of the presale already underway, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) price has risen by over 655% in just a few weeks, while Cardano (ADA) continues to underperform. </p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s look at a few reasons for the fast growth of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) while Cardano (ADA) stagnates. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Surges by 655% in Presale</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol facilitates secure and transparent interactions between investors and emerging companies. Orbeon Protocol offers a number of safety measures, such as a "Fill or Kill," mechanism that make investing simple and risk-free. If a project doesn't raise enough money within the required amount of time, investors' money is returned.</p>
<p>The pre-sale for Orbeon Protocol has been quite successful. It is in phase 1 of its presale, and the price of ORBN tokens has increased by 655%. The growing popularity of the Orbeon Protocol can largely be attributed to its utility or use cases. </p>
<p>Thanks to Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), virtually anybody can now make seed investments in new businesses of their choice. </p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol facilitates this through the use of its NFT-as-a-Service (NFTaaS). The service creates equity-based fractionalized NFTs for companies that investors can buy at a low price. These NFTs are accessible to anybody and everyone who holds ORBN tokens for as little as $1.</p>
<p>This type of NFT-based investment paves the way for new entrants to enter the speculative venture capital industry without restrictions. It is making funding via non-traditional channels, such as venture capital (VC) and crowdsourcing, less cumbersome for the average investor. The new approach is also helping startups better engage with their communities in a Web3 environment. </p>
<p>In the presale phase, investors can purchase ORBN tokens at a discount and make profits later on. Market analysts predict a price increase of 6000%. Orbeon Protocol is definitely worth looking into as we head to 2023. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) </p>
<p>Charles Hoskinson, a controversial figure and co-creator of Ethereum, launched Cardano in 2015. </p>
<p>Cardano is a cryptocurrency that runs on the Cardano blockchain and enables its users to create tokens, develop and deploy dApps, and execute smart contracts. Cardano is well-prepared for operation, and its creators are dedicated to making it even better. </p>
<p>Cardano (ADA), the utility token for the platform, is a well-known crypto asset with a huge market capitalization. However, since the crypto winter hit, Cardano (ADA) has not been able to repeat its stellar performance of 2020. </p>
<p>This month alone has seen a huge decline in Cardano's value, and the cryptocurrency is now trading at a price that is 90% under its all-time peak of $3.09.</p>
<p>Cardano's ambitious goal of fostering a more autonomous and decentralized society has attracted a sizable online following. However, its performance lately has been anything but promising. </p>
<p>For Cardano investors, getting into the innovative technology that the Orbeon Protocol is introducing to the crowdfunding and VC industries is a double win. Orbeon, like Cardano, seeks to bring about change for those who have been excluded from the global financial system.</p>
<p class="s9">Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s12">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Gaming survey finds that gamers are keen to earn crypto rewards]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/gaming-survey-finds-that-gamers-are-keen-to-earn-crypto-rewards</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gam-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gam-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gam-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 18:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/gaming-survey-finds-that-gamers-are-keen-to-earn-crypto-rewards</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the ongoing crypto winter, a new survey reveals that the integration of blockchain and gaming is far from dead. According to the survey, gamers are generally positive about the benefits of playing and earning with blockchain-based games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The survey, undertaken by gaming industry payment processor ZEBEDEE, asked 903 gamers in North America, Europe, China and Southeast Asia about their opinions on blockchain-based gaming. Results indicated that 68% of respondents were open to integrating crypto assets into game play while 76% said they were interested in earning rewards in exchange for playing games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ben Cousens, Chief Strategy Officer for ZEBEDEE, said of his company&rsquo;s survey findings:</p>

<p>&ldquo;the majority of gamers have not yet encountered Play-and-Earn gaming with real financial rewards. The findings suggest that gamers are overall more open to seeing these technologies integrated into games, which presents an opportunity for the industry to educate, engage and attract new gamers to the Play-and-Earn ecosystem."</p>

<p>Gamers also expressed an interest in using cryptocurrencies to acquire virtual items such as characters or weapons within games (70%), as well as exchanging these items for real money (66%). Furthermore, 74% said they would like to be able to securely store their digital assets within a wallet connected to a game platform or server cluster.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This research shows us that despite some scepticism surrounding blockchain gaming technology, there is still potential for growth amongst avid players. The results suggest that gamers are ready for increased innovation when it comes to incorporating different elements from the crypto world into their gameplay experience - helping both developers and players alike discover new ways of enjoying digital entertainment safely and rewardingly.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the ongoing crypto winter, a new survey reveals that the integration of blockchain and gaming is far from dead. According to the survey, gamers are generally positive about the benefits of playing and earning with blockchain-based games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The survey, undertaken by gaming industry payment processor ZEBEDEE, asked 903 gamers in North America, Europe, China and Southeast Asia about their opinions on blockchain-based gaming. Results indicated that 68% of respondents were open to integrating crypto assets into game play while 76% said they were interested in earning rewards in exchange for playing games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ben Cousens, Chief Strategy Officer for ZEBEDEE, said of his company&rsquo;s survey findings:</p>

<p>&ldquo;the majority of gamers have not yet encountered Play-and-Earn gaming with real financial rewards. The findings suggest that gamers are overall more open to seeing these technologies integrated into games, which presents an opportunity for the industry to educate, engage and attract new gamers to the Play-and-Earn ecosystem."</p>

<p>Gamers also expressed an interest in using cryptocurrencies to acquire virtual items such as characters or weapons within games (70%), as well as exchanging these items for real money (66%). Furthermore, 74% said they would like to be able to securely store their digital assets within a wallet connected to a game platform or server cluster.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This research shows us that despite some scepticism surrounding blockchain gaming technology, there is still potential for growth amongst avid players. The results suggest that gamers are ready for increased innovation when it comes to incorporating different elements from the crypto world into their gameplay experience - helping both developers and players alike discover new ways of enjoying digital entertainment safely and rewardingly.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Nexera ID To Revolutionize Web3 Privacy With  On-Chain Identities]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/nexera-id-to-revolutionize-web3-privacy-with-on-chain-identities</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-224.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-224.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-224.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/nexera-id-to-revolutionize-web3-privacy-with-on-chain-identities</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency and DeFi users now have a better way to protect their identities and ensure they won&rsquo;t lose access to their crypto assets, and it&rsquo;s all thanks to a new, self-sovereign identity solution called Nexera ID.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Announced today by the DeFi ecosystem provider AllianceBlock, Nexera ID is a non-custodial solution that enables users to create a &ldquo;programmable smart wallet&rdquo; that relies on multi-factor authentication, as opposed to private keys. With it, users can store verifiable identity credentials on the blockchain that can be used to access any kind of Web3 service. The solution works by using a technique known as &ldquo;zero-knowledge proofs&rdquo;, which allows users to prove that they are who they say they are, without giving up any personal information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For those scratching their heads wondering how this is possible, it&rsquo;s actually fairly simple. With Nexera ID, individuals can undergo a KYC check just one, or businesses can verify themselves via KYB with a single provider. After doing this, the user creates a verifiable credential that safeguards their identity while simultaneously satisfying the verification requirements of any Web3 service. It basically provides a way for crypto users to say, yes I have been verified, by someone else, and here is the proof. For Web3 businesses, it promises to be an ideal tool for onboarding thousands of privacy-minded users.</p>
<p>What&rsquo;s really good about Nexera ID is its flexibility, being able to integrate with any wallet, be it custodial or non-custodial. It means users can sign up to almost any service with their preferred wallet, while retaining control of their private data.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nexera ID is based on open-source trustless identity verification (TIDV) technology that provides a number of other key benefits that are likely going to become essential if the world of decentralized finance is ever to take off. One of the reasons why DeFi remains a niche industry is that self-custody of digital assets remains a major headache. In 2021, more than $14 billion worth of cryptocurrency was stolen through hacks, and millions of dollars more have been lost as a result of mismanagement of users&rsquo; funds. The most recent example of the latter was the collapse of the FTX cryptocurrency exchange, which suddenly declared bankruptcy, leaving thousands of users unable to withdraw their funds from the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The FTX disaster once again shined the spotlight on the dangers of so-called &ldquo;custodial wallets&rdquo;, where users don&rsquo;t manage the private keys to access them. Not your keys, not your funds, or so the mantra goes. The only way users can ensure they&rsquo;ll always be able to access their funds is with the use of a non-custodial wallet, but doing this means the onus is on the users to safely store their private keys. Doing so is a big responsibility, however, and there have been numerous instances that have hit the headlines, where people have lost access to millions of dollar&rsquo;s worth of funds after misplacing their private key.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nexera ID offers an interesting solution to this conundrum, with a slick and easy-to-use interface that enables users to set up access to their wallet using more familiar login credentials such as email, facial recognition and social logins. Using multi-factor authentication, users can also set up their own recovery mechanisms to regain access to their wallet, in the event they misplace their private key.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The capabilities of Nexera ID therefore solve a number of key problems that AllianceBlock says are holding back user adoption in crypto and the wider Web3 space. It provides a simple solution to login to a range of Web3 dApps using familiar credentials, a way for users to protect their identity, and most importantly a simple method for recovering crypto assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AllianceBlock CEO Rachid Ajaja said Nexera ID&rsquo;s technology will prove to be &ldquo;revolutionary&rdquo; for the crypto industry. &ldquo;With Nexera ID, we are ushering in the next era of self-sovereignty, self-custody, security of digital assets and protecting users&rsquo; privacy,&rdquo; he said.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nexera ID is just the first of a number of promised solutions built by Nexera and AllianceBlock, with others targeting areas such as blockchain gaming and automated trading strategies for DeFi users set to arrive in the near future.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency and DeFi users now have a better way to protect their identities and ensure they won&rsquo;t lose access to their crypto assets, and it&rsquo;s all thanks to a new, self-sovereign identity solution called Nexera ID.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Announced today by the DeFi ecosystem provider AllianceBlock, Nexera ID is a non-custodial solution that enables users to create a &ldquo;programmable smart wallet&rdquo; that relies on multi-factor authentication, as opposed to private keys. With it, users can store verifiable identity credentials on the blockchain that can be used to access any kind of Web3 service. The solution works by using a technique known as &ldquo;zero-knowledge proofs&rdquo;, which allows users to prove that they are who they say they are, without giving up any personal information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For those scratching their heads wondering how this is possible, it&rsquo;s actually fairly simple. With Nexera ID, individuals can undergo a KYC check just one, or businesses can verify themselves via KYB with a single provider. After doing this, the user creates a verifiable credential that safeguards their identity while simultaneously satisfying the verification requirements of any Web3 service. It basically provides a way for crypto users to say, yes I have been verified, by someone else, and here is the proof. For Web3 businesses, it promises to be an ideal tool for onboarding thousands of privacy-minded users.</p>
<p>What&rsquo;s really good about Nexera ID is its flexibility, being able to integrate with any wallet, be it custodial or non-custodial. It means users can sign up to almost any service with their preferred wallet, while retaining control of their private data.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nexera ID is based on open-source trustless identity verification (TIDV) technology that provides a number of other key benefits that are likely going to become essential if the world of decentralized finance is ever to take off. One of the reasons why DeFi remains a niche industry is that self-custody of digital assets remains a major headache. In 2021, more than $14 billion worth of cryptocurrency was stolen through hacks, and millions of dollars more have been lost as a result of mismanagement of users&rsquo; funds. The most recent example of the latter was the collapse of the FTX cryptocurrency exchange, which suddenly declared bankruptcy, leaving thousands of users unable to withdraw their funds from the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The FTX disaster once again shined the spotlight on the dangers of so-called &ldquo;custodial wallets&rdquo;, where users don&rsquo;t manage the private keys to access them. Not your keys, not your funds, or so the mantra goes. The only way users can ensure they&rsquo;ll always be able to access their funds is with the use of a non-custodial wallet, but doing this means the onus is on the users to safely store their private keys. Doing so is a big responsibility, however, and there have been numerous instances that have hit the headlines, where people have lost access to millions of dollar&rsquo;s worth of funds after misplacing their private key.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nexera ID offers an interesting solution to this conundrum, with a slick and easy-to-use interface that enables users to set up access to their wallet using more familiar login credentials such as email, facial recognition and social logins. Using multi-factor authentication, users can also set up their own recovery mechanisms to regain access to their wallet, in the event they misplace their private key.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The capabilities of Nexera ID therefore solve a number of key problems that AllianceBlock says are holding back user adoption in crypto and the wider Web3 space. It provides a simple solution to login to a range of Web3 dApps using familiar credentials, a way for users to protect their identity, and most importantly a simple method for recovering crypto assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AllianceBlock CEO Rachid Ajaja said Nexera ID&rsquo;s technology will prove to be &ldquo;revolutionary&rdquo; for the crypto industry. &ldquo;With Nexera ID, we are ushering in the next era of self-sovereignty, self-custody, security of digital assets and protecting users&rsquo; privacy,&rdquo; he said.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nexera ID is just the first of a number of promised solutions built by Nexera and AllianceBlock, with others targeting areas such as blockchain gaming and automated trading strategies for DeFi users set to arrive in the near future.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  17999 Paid - 15 December 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-price-analysis-17999-paid-15-december-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-14-december-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-14-december-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-14-december-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-price-analysis-17999-paid-15-december-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Upside Momentum Rallies:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 15 December 2022</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) worked to sustain recent upside gains early in the Asian session as the pair retained its bullish short-term outlook after trading as high as the 17999.99 area before coming off.&nbsp; Bids emerged around the 17611.25 area when BTC/USD pulled back, above the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 17089.17 to 17999.99.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected above the 17221.04, 17302.51, and 17434.51 levels during the ascent, upside price objectives related to buying pressure that emerged around the 16875.83 and 17089.17 areas. &nbsp;Price activity accelerated above additional Stops that were triggered above the 17779.81 and 17872.75 levels.&nbsp; Additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp; Following recent gains from two-year lows around the 15460 area, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 17400.55, 17029.71, 16730, 16430.28, 16059.44, and 16003.56 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 1200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 17111.21 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 17281.67.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Upside Momentum Rallies:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 15 December 2022</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) worked to sustain recent upside gains early in the Asian session as the pair retained its bullish short-term outlook after trading as high as the 17999.99 area before coming off.&nbsp; Bids emerged around the 17611.25 area when BTC/USD pulled back, above the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 17089.17 to 17999.99.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected above the 17221.04, 17302.51, and 17434.51 levels during the ascent, upside price objectives related to buying pressure that emerged around the 16875.83 and 17089.17 areas. &nbsp;Price activity accelerated above additional Stops that were triggered above the 17779.81 and 17872.75 levels.&nbsp; Additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp; Following recent gains from two-year lows around the 15460 area, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 17400.55, 17029.71, 16730, 16430.28, 16059.44, and 16003.56 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 1200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 17111.21 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 17281.67.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Planet Mojo’s First Charity Tournament A Smashing Success]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/planet-mojos-first-charity-tournament-a-smashing-success</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Tournament-Thanks-1_16710236057uWk5BT8U2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Tournament-Thanks-1_16710236057uWk5BT8U2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Tournament-Thanks-1_16710236057uWk5BT8U2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 14:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/planet-mojos-first-charity-tournament-a-smashing-success</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Boston, United States, 14th December, 2022, Chainwire</p>Mojo Melee Charity Smackdown Tournament Brought Together The Biggest Names In Web3 Gaming For A Good Cause
<p>Planet Mojo, the hotly anticipated Web3 gaming metaverse developed by Mystic Moose, hosted the 2022 Mojo Melee Charity Smackdown Tournament on Friday, December 9th. Eight leading voices within the Web3 gaming industry competed to earn $2,500 for a charity of their choice. Following a heated final showdown between the final two remaining competitors, influencer Brycent won the honor for Black Girls Code, a nonprofit providing technology education for African American youth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Participants included BoredElonMusk, Brycent, The Crypto Herd, CryptoStache, JonahBlake, Mostafa of Polkastarter Gaming, ReadyPlayer Rich of ReadyPlayer DAO, and ProfessorLP of Merit Circle. Each selected a charity they&rsquo;re passionate about before the tournament, and the group battled it out in Mojo Melee, Planet Mojo&rsquo;s upcoming first title where magical creatures and a range of Champions with diverse abilities go head-to-head in a strategy game.</p>
<p>Thousands of Web3 aficionados, Planet Mojo followers, and fans of the influencers tuned in to watch the live stream. The tournament came down to a final close match between Brycent and ProfessorLP of Merit Circle. Brycent spent weeks grinding hard at the game in preparation for the tournament, and his practice paid off with a thrilling win.&nbsp;</p>
<p>"I care deeply about Black Girls Code and I'm thrilled I could bring home the W for them!&rdquo; said Brycent. "$2500 is a meaningful amount of money, and I can't thank Planet Mojo enough for putting on such a great tournament."</p>
<p>As Planet Mojo prepares for Mojo Melee&rsquo;s release, the team has been looking for ways to give back to the gaming community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;One of the most rewarding aspects of working in our industry is the close-knit, one-of-a-kind communities that gaming creates between people all over the world,&rdquo; said Mike Levine, founder of Planet Mojo. &ldquo;As we establish ourselves in the future of Web3 gaming, we want to continue to hold these relationships close and celebrate what we can achieve when we put our heads together to support important causes.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Set in a mysterious alien world with rich storytelling and eccentric details, the Planet Mojo metaverse is quickly attracting creative gamers. With over 80k followers on Twitter and 65k Discord members, Planet Mojo is expected to become one of Web3&rsquo;s most popular communities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Private playtests of Mojo Melee have been underway since August 2022 to gather user feedback and refine the playing experience ahead of the game&rsquo;s release. More playtests are happening every weekend for the rest of the year, heading towards an open beta period in early 2023. Interested players are encouraged to head to the Planet Mojo Discord and try the game.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Learn more about Planet Mojo and playtest Mojo Melee on PlanetMojo.io. Follow Planet Mojo on Twitter and Discord to keep up with announcements, release dates, and more.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About Planet Mojo</p>
<p>Planet Mojo is an ecosystem of interconnected games built by Mystic Moose and set inside a mysterious alien planet with an evolving narrative. Their soon-to-be-released Auto Chess Battler, MojoMelee has been recently nominated for Best Esports Game in the new Gam3r Awards from Polkastarter Gaming.</p>
<p>Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | Medium&nbsp;</p>
<p>Media Kit: Images &amp; Branding</p>ContactDirector of MarketingTed NewellMystic Mooseted.newell@planetmojo.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Boston, United States, 14th December, 2022, Chainwire</p>Mojo Melee Charity Smackdown Tournament Brought Together The Biggest Names In Web3 Gaming For A Good Cause
<p>Planet Mojo, the hotly anticipated Web3 gaming metaverse developed by Mystic Moose, hosted the 2022 Mojo Melee Charity Smackdown Tournament on Friday, December 9th. Eight leading voices within the Web3 gaming industry competed to earn $2,500 for a charity of their choice. Following a heated final showdown between the final two remaining competitors, influencer Brycent won the honor for Black Girls Code, a nonprofit providing technology education for African American youth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Participants included BoredElonMusk, Brycent, The Crypto Herd, CryptoStache, JonahBlake, Mostafa of Polkastarter Gaming, ReadyPlayer Rich of ReadyPlayer DAO, and ProfessorLP of Merit Circle. Each selected a charity they&rsquo;re passionate about before the tournament, and the group battled it out in Mojo Melee, Planet Mojo&rsquo;s upcoming first title where magical creatures and a range of Champions with diverse abilities go head-to-head in a strategy game.</p>
<p>Thousands of Web3 aficionados, Planet Mojo followers, and fans of the influencers tuned in to watch the live stream. The tournament came down to a final close match between Brycent and ProfessorLP of Merit Circle. Brycent spent weeks grinding hard at the game in preparation for the tournament, and his practice paid off with a thrilling win.&nbsp;</p>
<p>"I care deeply about Black Girls Code and I'm thrilled I could bring home the W for them!&rdquo; said Brycent. "$2500 is a meaningful amount of money, and I can't thank Planet Mojo enough for putting on such a great tournament."</p>
<p>As Planet Mojo prepares for Mojo Melee&rsquo;s release, the team has been looking for ways to give back to the gaming community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;One of the most rewarding aspects of working in our industry is the close-knit, one-of-a-kind communities that gaming creates between people all over the world,&rdquo; said Mike Levine, founder of Planet Mojo. &ldquo;As we establish ourselves in the future of Web3 gaming, we want to continue to hold these relationships close and celebrate what we can achieve when we put our heads together to support important causes.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Set in a mysterious alien world with rich storytelling and eccentric details, the Planet Mojo metaverse is quickly attracting creative gamers. With over 80k followers on Twitter and 65k Discord members, Planet Mojo is expected to become one of Web3&rsquo;s most popular communities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Private playtests of Mojo Melee have been underway since August 2022 to gather user feedback and refine the playing experience ahead of the game&rsquo;s release. More playtests are happening every weekend for the rest of the year, heading towards an open beta period in early 2023. Interested players are encouraged to head to the Planet Mojo Discord and try the game.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Learn more about Planet Mojo and playtest Mojo Melee on PlanetMojo.io. Follow Planet Mojo on Twitter and Discord to keep up with announcements, release dates, and more.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About Planet Mojo</p>
<p>Planet Mojo is an ecosystem of interconnected games built by Mystic Moose and set inside a mysterious alien planet with an evolving narrative. Their soon-to-be-released Auto Chess Battler, MojoMelee has been recently nominated for Best Esports Game in the new Gam3r Awards from Polkastarter Gaming.</p>
<p>Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | Medium&nbsp;</p>
<p>Media Kit: Images &amp; Branding</p>ContactDirector of MarketingTed NewellMystic Mooseted.newell@planetmojo.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bumpy road ahead for Binance and for crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bumpy-road-ahead-for-binance-and-for-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 13:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bumpy-road-ahead-for-binance-and-for-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao warns that the next few months will be a bumpy road for crypto.</p>
Confidence undermined
<p>As well as suffering a year-long bear market in which several platforms have collapsed, crypto has come under the most brutal hammer as regards impending regulation and FUD is washing back and forth through the sector, undermining confidence as it does so.</p>
<p>This must be manna from heaven for governments and banks as they seek to take crypto out of the hands of retail investors and build a regulatory wall that keeps them out and ensures that the sector is squashed flat until they can roll out their central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).</p>
FUD continues
<p>Currently, Binance is bearing the brunt of all the FUD that has been propagated. Over recent days a total of more than $3 billion has been drawn off of the exchange. Binance appears to be solvent but who knows what could happen if the FUD were to continue?</p>
<p>It should be hoped that most retail investors would be aware by now that the best way to protect themselves is to take their digital assets off of centralised exchanges and store them in wallets held in their own custody.</p>
Binance services maintained
<p>Changpeng Zhao (CZ) noted that if governments could become more accommodating towards digital currencies, this would address some of the issues experienced by exchanges like Binance in recent weeks. Additionally, he implored people not to jump into cryptocurrencies without being aware of the risks associated with them.</p>
<p>Going forward, CZ said Binance would be focused on providing customers with reliable services and ensuring their security is always maintained at a high level. He also mentioned that they had set up various teams to monitor suspicious activity and combat fraud within their system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Overall, it looks like deposits are back on track for Binance users; however, it's important for all crypto holders to remain mindful of potential bumps along the way as well as the risks involved with the markets, traditional as well as crypto.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao warns that the next few months will be a bumpy road for crypto.</p>
Confidence undermined
<p>As well as suffering a year-long bear market in which several platforms have collapsed, crypto has come under the most brutal hammer as regards impending regulation and FUD is washing back and forth through the sector, undermining confidence as it does so.</p>
<p>This must be manna from heaven for governments and banks as they seek to take crypto out of the hands of retail investors and build a regulatory wall that keeps them out and ensures that the sector is squashed flat until they can roll out their central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).</p>
FUD continues
<p>Currently, Binance is bearing the brunt of all the FUD that has been propagated. Over recent days a total of more than $3 billion has been drawn off of the exchange. Binance appears to be solvent but who knows what could happen if the FUD were to continue?</p>
<p>It should be hoped that most retail investors would be aware by now that the best way to protect themselves is to take their digital assets off of centralised exchanges and store them in wallets held in their own custody.</p>
Binance services maintained
<p>Changpeng Zhao (CZ) noted that if governments could become more accommodating towards digital currencies, this would address some of the issues experienced by exchanges like Binance in recent weeks. Additionally, he implored people not to jump into cryptocurrencies without being aware of the risks associated with them.</p>
<p>Going forward, CZ said Binance would be focused on providing customers with reliable services and ensuring their security is always maintained at a high level. He also mentioned that they had set up various teams to monitor suspicious activity and combat fraud within their system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Overall, it looks like deposits are back on track for Binance users; however, it's important for all crypto holders to remain mindful of potential bumps along the way as well as the risks involved with the markets, traditional as well as crypto.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[YES WORLD launches Crypto Utility, Now use YES WORLD Token in 80 Countries]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/yes-world-launches-crypto-utility-now-use-yes-world-token-in-80-countries</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-14-at-145012.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-14-at-145012.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-14-at-145012.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/yes-world-launches-crypto-utility-now-use-yes-world-token-in-80-countries</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Singapore, -&nbsp;Leading blockchain based climate tech startup, operated by YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd based out of Singapore, launches Utility services portal that supports thousands of merchants in over 80 countries worldwide. YES WORLD announced today to the global community members that YES WORLD Token is getting adoption worldwide and thousands of new holders of YES WORLD Token are seen every single day.</p>
<p class="s7">YES World&rsquo;s Utility portal is a platform where users will be able to utilize YES WORLD Token and will be able to leverage YES cryptocurrency for their regular purchases for products and services at merchant locations. &nbsp;YES WORLD Token holders now have an option to not just hold to token for price appreciation, but also to use it for various usability and utility services available in their countries. </p>
<p class="s7">The consumers of YES WORLD utility services can redeem the coupons on all sort of platforms - online as well as offline. There are several merchants that are accepting YES WORLD Token directly over POS Terminal installed at the physical stores. Users will have to scan the bar-code presented at the checkout on the POS Terminal to make the payment using the token. As per the information, the integration work is underway to onboard leading e-commerce players where the users will soon be able to make purchases online using YES World Token as payment mode. </p>
<p class="s7">A recent study conducted over 22 countries indicated that 56% of consumers globally are more likely to transact with merchants accepting crypto, While the other research done with 202 merchant with an online annual turnover of over $250 million, indicates that 46% of merchants are currently accepting cryptocurrency as a for of payment. With such great deal of interest from both consumers and merchants, YES WORLD is bringing in the missing piece to facilitate payment acceptance with cryptocurrency. </p>
<p class="s7">Just last week, YES WORLD informed that it plans to hire 600 people worldwide for merchant on-boarding, technological upgrades, support functions, as well as newer innovations. &nbsp;It plans to onboard 10 million merchant establishment worldwide before the global launch on April 24, 2024 where the native token will be accepted for payments.</p>
<p class="s7">Launched in the spring of 2022, YES WORLD Token is getting good traction in crypto utility space and &nbsp;is already trading on several leading centralized exchanges including XT.com and Coinsbit.io, as well as on decentralized exchange - PancakeSwap.</p>
<p class="s7">YES WORLD Token is operated by YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd, based out of Singapore. It is a climate tech blockchain-based startup working on green technology to reduce carbon footprint. &nbsp;YES is the native token for YES WORLD's Save Earth mission. It is conceptualized to generating awareness around the global warming challenges to bring to critical mass to join the mission and take steps in the direction of reducing carbon footprint from the atmosphere.</p>
<p class="s7">YES WORLD is inceptualized and promoted by Save Earth activist Dr Sandeep Choudhary, who has constantly been working to generate awareness of global warming and climate change impacts. Under Dr. Choudhary's vision and leadership, YES WORLD has championed a noble cause of reducing carbon footprint and bringing forth the issue of global warming and climate change.</p>
<p class="s7">YES WORLD is currently in soft launch and planning one of the biggest airdrop campaigns starting on 23/3/2023, followed by a major global launch on April 24, 2024, more than 50 leading crypto exchanges will be enrolled before the global launch. </p>
<p class="s6">Important links :</p>
<p class="s6">Twitter -&nbsp;https://twitter.com/yesworld24</p>
<p class="s6">CMC -&nbsp;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yes-world-token/</p>
<p class="s6">Website - www.yesworld.io</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Singapore, -&nbsp;Leading blockchain based climate tech startup, operated by YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd based out of Singapore, launches Utility services portal that supports thousands of merchants in over 80 countries worldwide. YES WORLD announced today to the global community members that YES WORLD Token is getting adoption worldwide and thousands of new holders of YES WORLD Token are seen every single day.</p>
<p class="s7">YES World&rsquo;s Utility portal is a platform where users will be able to utilize YES WORLD Token and will be able to leverage YES cryptocurrency for their regular purchases for products and services at merchant locations. &nbsp;YES WORLD Token holders now have an option to not just hold to token for price appreciation, but also to use it for various usability and utility services available in their countries. </p>
<p class="s7">The consumers of YES WORLD utility services can redeem the coupons on all sort of platforms - online as well as offline. There are several merchants that are accepting YES WORLD Token directly over POS Terminal installed at the physical stores. Users will have to scan the bar-code presented at the checkout on the POS Terminal to make the payment using the token. As per the information, the integration work is underway to onboard leading e-commerce players where the users will soon be able to make purchases online using YES World Token as payment mode. </p>
<p class="s7">A recent study conducted over 22 countries indicated that 56% of consumers globally are more likely to transact with merchants accepting crypto, While the other research done with 202 merchant with an online annual turnover of over $250 million, indicates that 46% of merchants are currently accepting cryptocurrency as a for of payment. With such great deal of interest from both consumers and merchants, YES WORLD is bringing in the missing piece to facilitate payment acceptance with cryptocurrency. </p>
<p class="s7">Just last week, YES WORLD informed that it plans to hire 600 people worldwide for merchant on-boarding, technological upgrades, support functions, as well as newer innovations. &nbsp;It plans to onboard 10 million merchant establishment worldwide before the global launch on April 24, 2024 where the native token will be accepted for payments.</p>
<p class="s7">Launched in the spring of 2022, YES WORLD Token is getting good traction in crypto utility space and &nbsp;is already trading on several leading centralized exchanges including XT.com and Coinsbit.io, as well as on decentralized exchange - PancakeSwap.</p>
<p class="s7">YES WORLD Token is operated by YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd, based out of Singapore. It is a climate tech blockchain-based startup working on green technology to reduce carbon footprint. &nbsp;YES is the native token for YES WORLD's Save Earth mission. It is conceptualized to generating awareness around the global warming challenges to bring to critical mass to join the mission and take steps in the direction of reducing carbon footprint from the atmosphere.</p>
<p class="s7">YES WORLD is inceptualized and promoted by Save Earth activist Dr Sandeep Choudhary, who has constantly been working to generate awareness of global warming and climate change impacts. Under Dr. Choudhary's vision and leadership, YES WORLD has championed a noble cause of reducing carbon footprint and bringing forth the issue of global warming and climate change.</p>
<p class="s7">YES WORLD is currently in soft launch and planning one of the biggest airdrop campaigns starting on 23/3/2023, followed by a major global launch on April 24, 2024, more than 50 leading crypto exchanges will be enrolled before the global launch. </p>
<p class="s6">Important links :</p>
<p class="s6">Twitter -&nbsp;https://twitter.com/yesworld24</p>
<p class="s6">CMC -&nbsp;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yes-world-token/</p>
<p class="s6">Website - www.yesworld.io</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Stock Takes A Dive, Crypto Daily TV 14/12/2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/coinbase-stock-takes-a-dive-crypto-daily-tv-14-12-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-coinbase4.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-coinbase4.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-coinbase4.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/coinbase-stock-takes-a-dive-crypto-daily-tv-14-12-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>US prosecutors look to charge Binance and executives.</p>
<p>US prosecutors are considering criminal charges against crypto exchange Binance and individual executives, including founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao, Reuters reported, citing two people.</p>
<p>Coinbase Global stock is a falling meat cleaver</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency platform and exchange Coinbase Global stock have fallen alongside the crypto market and the price of bitcoin. However, things worsened after the FTX disaster as it hit new all-time lows of $40.15 last week. The year-end tax loss selling is underway as investors reconsider the merits of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Bitcoin group agrees to buy German bank.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Group (ADE), a holding company focusing on the blockchain and cryptocurrency industries, said it agreed to buy all of Germany&rsquo;s Bankhaus von der Heydt for US$15 million in cash and 150,000 shares.</p>
BTC/USD exploded 3.2% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained 3.2% in the last session after rising as much as 4.3% during the session. The Williams indicator indicates an overbought market. Support is at 16769.3333 and resistance at 17487.3333.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD exploded 3.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 3.4% in the last session. According to the Williams indicator, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 1227.961 and resistance at 1301.861.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 1.8% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 1.8% in the last session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.3638 and resistance at 0.4014.</p>
<p>The CCI is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded 1.8% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.8% in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator gives a positive signal. Support is at 72.4067 and resistance at 78.5867.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>EMU Industrial Production</p>
<p>Industry is a basic category of business activity. Changes in the volume of the physical output of the nation's factories, mines, and utilities are measured by the index of industrial production. The Eurozone's Industrial Production will be released at 10:00 GMT, the US Fed's Monetary Policy Statement at 19:00 GMT, and the US Fed Interest Rate Decision at 19:00 GMT.</p>
<p>US Fed's Monetary Policy Statement</p>
<p>Following the Fed's rate decision, the FOMC released a statement regarding its monetary policy.</p>
<p>US Fed Interest Rate Decision</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve announced the Fed Interest Rate Decision. The interest rates are a key mechanism through which the central bank influences inflation.</p>
<p>FI Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services. Finland's Consumer Price Index will be released at 06:00 GMT, the UK's Consumer Price Index at 07:00 GMT, and the UK's Core Consumer Price Index at 07:00 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>UK Core Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) measures the changes in the prices of goods and services, excluding food and energy.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>US prosecutors look to charge Binance and executives.</p>
<p>US prosecutors are considering criminal charges against crypto exchange Binance and individual executives, including founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao, Reuters reported, citing two people.</p>
<p>Coinbase Global stock is a falling meat cleaver</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency platform and exchange Coinbase Global stock have fallen alongside the crypto market and the price of bitcoin. However, things worsened after the FTX disaster as it hit new all-time lows of $40.15 last week. The year-end tax loss selling is underway as investors reconsider the merits of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Bitcoin group agrees to buy German bank.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Group (ADE), a holding company focusing on the blockchain and cryptocurrency industries, said it agreed to buy all of Germany&rsquo;s Bankhaus von der Heydt for US$15 million in cash and 150,000 shares.</p>
BTC/USD exploded 3.2% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained 3.2% in the last session after rising as much as 4.3% during the session. The Williams indicator indicates an overbought market. Support is at 16769.3333 and resistance at 17487.3333.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD exploded 3.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 3.4% in the last session. According to the Williams indicator, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 1227.961 and resistance at 1301.861.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 1.8% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 1.8% in the last session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.3638 and resistance at 0.4014.</p>
<p>The CCI is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded 1.8% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.8% in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator gives a positive signal. Support is at 72.4067 and resistance at 78.5867.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>EMU Industrial Production</p>
<p>Industry is a basic category of business activity. Changes in the volume of the physical output of the nation's factories, mines, and utilities are measured by the index of industrial production. The Eurozone's Industrial Production will be released at 10:00 GMT, the US Fed's Monetary Policy Statement at 19:00 GMT, and the US Fed Interest Rate Decision at 19:00 GMT.</p>
<p>US Fed's Monetary Policy Statement</p>
<p>Following the Fed's rate decision, the FOMC released a statement regarding its monetary policy.</p>
<p>US Fed Interest Rate Decision</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve announced the Fed Interest Rate Decision. The interest rates are a key mechanism through which the central bank influences inflation.</p>
<p>FI Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services. Finland's Consumer Price Index will be released at 06:00 GMT, the UK's Consumer Price Index at 07:00 GMT, and the UK's Core Consumer Price Index at 07:00 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>UK Core Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) measures the changes in the prices of goods and services, excluding food and energy.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Adds 19 Million Verified Users Despite Market Downturn]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/coinbase-adds-19-million-verified-users-despite-market-downturn</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 12:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/coinbase-adds-19-million-verified-users-despite-market-downturn</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The unprecedented market turndown has certainly claimed many victims in 2022, with companies and crypto exchanges crashing left, right and center. Despite these harsh conditions, Coinbase has managed to onboard 19 million verified users to its platform this year. </p>
<p>Although the market has treated many harshly, more and more individuals have begun to embrace cryptocurrencies including Bitcoin, and therefore trading platforms such as Coinbase have recorded increased user growth in recent times and appear to be rather unaffected by the prolonged bear market. Reports by Finbold suggest that Coinbase has added 19 million verified users globally between December 31, 2021, and September 30, 2022 &ndash; a growth percentage of 21.35%. According to this data, the platform has added at least two million users per month in 2022.</p>
<p>The data presented by Finbold indicates that Coinbase had 98 million users &ndash; an addition of nine million users from the 2021 Q4 figure of 89 million. In Q2, the total number of verified users was 103 million, and in Q3 Coinbase registered its highest number of verified users at 108 million. As of December 6, 2022, Coinbase held a global market share of 3% among crypto platforms while this number only stood at 2.6% in November. In July, Coinbase&rsquo;s market share was a mere 1.6%, but this number has been steadily increasing this year after the firm recorded its highest market share in November 2021 at 4.2% during the crypto bull run.</p>
<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s increased user growth underscores the platform&rsquo;s popularity in the United States as it promoted a secure platform with a commitment to adhering to cryptocurrency compliance laws which naturally boosted trust among crypto investors. Part of Coinbase&rsquo;s success can also be attributed to the fact that it appeals to both beginners and advanced cryptocurrency investors by exposing them to a wide range of digital assets and educational resources thereby enabling users to learn about the crypto sector while providing them with incentives. Further, Coinbase has partnered with many leading global brands including Google in an effort to drive Web 3.0 innovation while enabling the use of its platform to accept cryptocurrency payments for cloud storage services.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The unprecedented market turndown has certainly claimed many victims in 2022, with companies and crypto exchanges crashing left, right and center. Despite these harsh conditions, Coinbase has managed to onboard 19 million verified users to its platform this year. </p>
<p>Although the market has treated many harshly, more and more individuals have begun to embrace cryptocurrencies including Bitcoin, and therefore trading platforms such as Coinbase have recorded increased user growth in recent times and appear to be rather unaffected by the prolonged bear market. Reports by Finbold suggest that Coinbase has added 19 million verified users globally between December 31, 2021, and September 30, 2022 &ndash; a growth percentage of 21.35%. According to this data, the platform has added at least two million users per month in 2022.</p>
<p>The data presented by Finbold indicates that Coinbase had 98 million users &ndash; an addition of nine million users from the 2021 Q4 figure of 89 million. In Q2, the total number of verified users was 103 million, and in Q3 Coinbase registered its highest number of verified users at 108 million. As of December 6, 2022, Coinbase held a global market share of 3% among crypto platforms while this number only stood at 2.6% in November. In July, Coinbase&rsquo;s market share was a mere 1.6%, but this number has been steadily increasing this year after the firm recorded its highest market share in November 2021 at 4.2% during the crypto bull run.</p>
<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s increased user growth underscores the platform&rsquo;s popularity in the United States as it promoted a secure platform with a commitment to adhering to cryptocurrency compliance laws which naturally boosted trust among crypto investors. Part of Coinbase&rsquo;s success can also be attributed to the fact that it appeals to both beginners and advanced cryptocurrency investors by exposing them to a wide range of digital assets and educational resources thereby enabling users to learn about the crypto sector while providing them with incentives. Further, Coinbase has partnered with many leading global brands including Google in an effort to drive Web 3.0 innovation while enabling the use of its platform to accept cryptocurrency payments for cloud storage services.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Australia to regulate crypto service providers by early 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/australia-to-regulate-crypto-service-providers-by-early-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aus.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aus.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aus.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/australia-to-regulate-crypto-service-providers-by-early-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Australia will put a comprehensive framework together in early 2023 in which rules will be established for regulating crypto service providers.</p>
<p>The Australian government is expected to regulate crypto service providers, in an effort to provide stronger protection for digital currency users. This regulation will encompass a range of activities, from the registration and licensing of crypto service providers to the implementation of anti-money laundering and counter-terrorism financing measures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to MP Stephen Jones, Minister for Financial Services, in a joint media release, the preparation for regulation will be along the following lines:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The next steps in the Government&rsquo;s ongoing &lsquo;token mapping&rsquo; work will include the release of a consultation paper in early 2023 to inform what digital assets should be regulated by financial services laws, and the development of appropriate custody and licensing settings to safeguard consumers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The new regulations should ensure that customers are properly protected when using cryptocurrency services within Australia. The regulations are intended to promote customer safety by requiring crypto service providers, such as exchanges and wallets, to obtain licences in order to operate in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move reflects a growing trend among governments worldwide of placing greater oversight on the cryptocurrency industry. It also gives greater legitimacy and trustworthiness for Australian businesses dealing with digital currencies by making them subject to transparent regulatory oversight.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposed regulatory changes will not be imposed straight away, and a consultation will go out in early 2023 in order to take the views of all stakeholders first.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Australia will put a comprehensive framework together in early 2023 in which rules will be established for regulating crypto service providers.</p>
<p>The Australian government is expected to regulate crypto service providers, in an effort to provide stronger protection for digital currency users. This regulation will encompass a range of activities, from the registration and licensing of crypto service providers to the implementation of anti-money laundering and counter-terrorism financing measures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to MP Stephen Jones, Minister for Financial Services, in a joint media release, the preparation for regulation will be along the following lines:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The next steps in the Government&rsquo;s ongoing &lsquo;token mapping&rsquo; work will include the release of a consultation paper in early 2023 to inform what digital assets should be regulated by financial services laws, and the development of appropriate custody and licensing settings to safeguard consumers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The new regulations should ensure that customers are properly protected when using cryptocurrency services within Australia. The regulations are intended to promote customer safety by requiring crypto service providers, such as exchanges and wallets, to obtain licences in order to operate in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move reflects a growing trend among governments worldwide of placing greater oversight on the cryptocurrency industry. It also gives greater legitimacy and trustworthiness for Australian businesses dealing with digital currencies by making them subject to transparent regulatory oversight.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposed regulatory changes will not be imposed straight away, and a consultation will go out in early 2023 in order to take the views of all stakeholders first.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Algorand To Support Digital Guarantees Platform In Italy]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/algorand-to-support-digital-guarantees-platform-in-italy</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/algorand-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/algorand-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/algorand-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/algorand-to-support-digital-guarantees-platform-in-italy</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Layer-1 blockchain technology protocol Algorand has been chosen as the public blockchain to support bank and guarantees insurance in Italy.&nbsp;</p>
First Blockchain As Digital Guarantee In EU
<p>The Algorand-supported digital guarantees platform will be used in Italy&rsquo;s banking and insurance markets and will be launched in early 2023. The company announced the news on December 13 at a three-day forum hosted by the Research Center for Technologies, Innovations and Finance of the Catholic University of Milan (CETIF).&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per the announcement, this is the first time an EU country will use blockchain technology for bank and insurance guarantees. The center has been focusing on developing a blockchain-based ecosystem for a &ldquo;Digital Sureties&rdquo; platform for the country&rsquo;s banking and insurance markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Under the bank guarantee, a lending institution would cover the loss if a borrower defaults on a loan instead of having to provide a deposit or a deposit bond to a supplier or vendor. Similarly, for an insurance guarantee, the insurance provider would cover the loss instead of the bank in case of a default.&nbsp;</p>
More On The Digital Sureties Platform
<p>This new Digital Sureties platform is being developed by the CETIF board and has been endorsed by the Bank of Italy and the Italian insurance authority IVASS.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A professor at CETIF, Federico Rajola, spoke about the decision to choose Algorand as the blockchain for the project.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"We selected Algorand because of its unparalleled level of innovation and security among permissionless DLTs, as well as because of its leadership in sustainability. Our goal is to help Italy not only recover from the economic impact of Covid-19, but also excel through innovation and leadership. Our ecosystemic projects are meant to help generate strategic platforms, such as the Digital Sureties platform supported by Algorand. We believe these platforms can and will dramatically contribute to the country's competitive sustainability for the benefit of all."</p>

Other Projects On Algorand
<p>Algorand has been scaling up for a while now. In September, the protocol underwent a major upgrade that boosted its transaction speed, processing capacity, and cross-chain functionality. Several institutions have chosen to launch their projects on the Algorand blockchain in the past. A year ago, Miami launched air quality monitoring sensors to transcribe aggregated sensor data to the Algorand Blockchain. A few months later, in May 2022, Algorand became the official blockchain partner of FIFA. The music streaming platform Napster also launched its token on the Algorand blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Layer-1 blockchain technology protocol Algorand has been chosen as the public blockchain to support bank and guarantees insurance in Italy.&nbsp;</p>
First Blockchain As Digital Guarantee In EU
<p>The Algorand-supported digital guarantees platform will be used in Italy&rsquo;s banking and insurance markets and will be launched in early 2023. The company announced the news on December 13 at a three-day forum hosted by the Research Center for Technologies, Innovations and Finance of the Catholic University of Milan (CETIF).&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per the announcement, this is the first time an EU country will use blockchain technology for bank and insurance guarantees. The center has been focusing on developing a blockchain-based ecosystem for a &ldquo;Digital Sureties&rdquo; platform for the country&rsquo;s banking and insurance markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Under the bank guarantee, a lending institution would cover the loss if a borrower defaults on a loan instead of having to provide a deposit or a deposit bond to a supplier or vendor. Similarly, for an insurance guarantee, the insurance provider would cover the loss instead of the bank in case of a default.&nbsp;</p>
More On The Digital Sureties Platform
<p>This new Digital Sureties platform is being developed by the CETIF board and has been endorsed by the Bank of Italy and the Italian insurance authority IVASS.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A professor at CETIF, Federico Rajola, spoke about the decision to choose Algorand as the blockchain for the project.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"We selected Algorand because of its unparalleled level of innovation and security among permissionless DLTs, as well as because of its leadership in sustainability. Our goal is to help Italy not only recover from the economic impact of Covid-19, but also excel through innovation and leadership. Our ecosystemic projects are meant to help generate strategic platforms, such as the Digital Sureties platform supported by Algorand. We believe these platforms can and will dramatically contribute to the country's competitive sustainability for the benefit of all."</p>

Other Projects On Algorand
<p>Algorand has been scaling up for a while now. In September, the protocol underwent a major upgrade that boosted its transaction speed, processing capacity, and cross-chain functionality. Several institutions have chosen to launch their projects on the Algorand blockchain in the past. A year ago, Miami launched air quality monitoring sensors to transcribe aggregated sensor data to the Algorand Blockchain. A few months later, in May 2022, Algorand became the official blockchain partner of FIFA. The music streaming platform Napster also launched its token on the Algorand blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[FTX Stored Private Keys Without Encryption; Left Funds Vulnerable]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/ftx-stored-private-keys-without-encryption-left-funds-vulnerable</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1450-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1450-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1450-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/ftx-stored-private-keys-without-encryption-left-funds-vulnerable</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Pandora&rsquo;s Box that is the FTX debacle continues to churn out one astonishing revelation after another about the leadup to the exchange&rsquo;s dramatic collapse, as it emerged that the exchange stored private keys without encryption.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The revelation was made as part of the prepared testimony by FTX&rsquo;s new Chief Executive, John Ray III.&nbsp;</p>
Private Keys Stored Without Encryption&nbsp;
<p>FTX&rsquo;s new Chief Executive, John Ray III, has made some damning revelations during his testimony to the US House Financials Committee, which is conducting a hearing into the exchange&rsquo;s unprecedented collapse. One of the most concerning statements made by Ray during the testimony was that FTX stored private keys to crypto wallets without encryption, leaving customer funds worth millions vulnerable to theft and other malicious activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The revelations were part of a prepared testimony to the House Financial Committee. However, he added that the new management had taken concrete steps to secure over $1 billion worth of digital assets since taking over. Private keys allow users to access their funds held in crypto wallets and must be stored securely on systems that leverage encryption. According to security analysts, storing these keys in an unencrypted mechanism leaves them vulnerable to hackers or unauthorized transfers. CEO of non-custodial wallet provider Casa, Nick Neuman, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;FTX storing private keys unencrypted would allow any employee with internal systems access, or any external actor who is able to obtain systems access, to move, and/or steal, customer funds relatively trivially.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>These unsecured funds could have been stolen in a number of ways, where hackers could obtain the private keys through phishing or simply hacking the system.&nbsp;</p>
FTX&rsquo;s November Hack&nbsp;
<p>FTX exchange wallets had, in November, faced a significant hack, with estimates by security firms Peckshield and Halborn stating that the exchange was compromised, losing an estimated $400 million. While the hacker&rsquo;s identity is still unknown, Bankman-Fried spoke of &ldquo;disgruntled employees and other bad actors&rdquo; who may have stolen the private keys.&nbsp;</p>
A Damning Congressional Testimony&nbsp;
<p>Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s successor, in his testimony, peeled away FTX&rsquo;s and Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s carefully constructed image of sophistication. The testimony began with the unsealing of an eight-count indictment against SBF, for which the embattled ex-FTX CEO faces up to 115 years in prison. US Attorney for the Southern District of New York, Damian Williams, called the FTX debacle one of the biggest financial frauds in American history.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried is accused of using customer funds to cover losses incurred by sister concern Alameda Research; the independent crypto hedge fund also helmed by SBF. Additionally, prosecutors also accused him of violating campaign finance laws by using customer funds to make millions worth of illegal political donations. Ray called these revelations &ldquo;old-fashioned embezzlement,&rdquo; stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This is really just old-fashioned embezzlement. This is just taking money from customers and using it for your own purpose. Not sophisticated at all.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Ray also stated that the exchange did not have a complete inventory of their crypto wallets nor any record of their location. He further added that the company was using QuickBooks for accounting.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;They used QuickBooks. Nothing against QuickBooks - very nice tool, just not for a multi-billion dollar company.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Ray also told the committee that they were actively tracking the $477 million worth of crypto stolen from FTX on the 12th of November.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re relying on forensic and cybersecurity experts who are tracking the crypto. You can ultimately find where the crypto ends up. We&rsquo;ve got law enforcement involved. So we&rsquo;re tracking it. I think we got all the help we need on that front.&rdquo;</p>

Bankman-Fried Sent To Custody&nbsp;
<p>Meanwhile, a court in the Bahamas directed authorities to take Bankman-Fried into custody, with the ex-CEO likely to be extradited to the United States of America next year. The judge chose to ignore requests that SBF remain free on bail so that he can stick to his vegan diet and also have access to his allergy medicines and prescription Adderall.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Pandora&rsquo;s Box that is the FTX debacle continues to churn out one astonishing revelation after another about the leadup to the exchange&rsquo;s dramatic collapse, as it emerged that the exchange stored private keys without encryption.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The revelation was made as part of the prepared testimony by FTX&rsquo;s new Chief Executive, John Ray III.&nbsp;</p>
Private Keys Stored Without Encryption&nbsp;
<p>FTX&rsquo;s new Chief Executive, John Ray III, has made some damning revelations during his testimony to the US House Financials Committee, which is conducting a hearing into the exchange&rsquo;s unprecedented collapse. One of the most concerning statements made by Ray during the testimony was that FTX stored private keys to crypto wallets without encryption, leaving customer funds worth millions vulnerable to theft and other malicious activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The revelations were part of a prepared testimony to the House Financial Committee. However, he added that the new management had taken concrete steps to secure over $1 billion worth of digital assets since taking over. Private keys allow users to access their funds held in crypto wallets and must be stored securely on systems that leverage encryption. According to security analysts, storing these keys in an unencrypted mechanism leaves them vulnerable to hackers or unauthorized transfers. CEO of non-custodial wallet provider Casa, Nick Neuman, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;FTX storing private keys unencrypted would allow any employee with internal systems access, or any external actor who is able to obtain systems access, to move, and/or steal, customer funds relatively trivially.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>These unsecured funds could have been stolen in a number of ways, where hackers could obtain the private keys through phishing or simply hacking the system.&nbsp;</p>
FTX&rsquo;s November Hack&nbsp;
<p>FTX exchange wallets had, in November, faced a significant hack, with estimates by security firms Peckshield and Halborn stating that the exchange was compromised, losing an estimated $400 million. While the hacker&rsquo;s identity is still unknown, Bankman-Fried spoke of &ldquo;disgruntled employees and other bad actors&rdquo; who may have stolen the private keys.&nbsp;</p>
A Damning Congressional Testimony&nbsp;
<p>Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s successor, in his testimony, peeled away FTX&rsquo;s and Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s carefully constructed image of sophistication. The testimony began with the unsealing of an eight-count indictment against SBF, for which the embattled ex-FTX CEO faces up to 115 years in prison. US Attorney for the Southern District of New York, Damian Williams, called the FTX debacle one of the biggest financial frauds in American history.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried is accused of using customer funds to cover losses incurred by sister concern Alameda Research; the independent crypto hedge fund also helmed by SBF. Additionally, prosecutors also accused him of violating campaign finance laws by using customer funds to make millions worth of illegal political donations. Ray called these revelations &ldquo;old-fashioned embezzlement,&rdquo; stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This is really just old-fashioned embezzlement. This is just taking money from customers and using it for your own purpose. Not sophisticated at all.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Ray also stated that the exchange did not have a complete inventory of their crypto wallets nor any record of their location. He further added that the company was using QuickBooks for accounting.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;They used QuickBooks. Nothing against QuickBooks - very nice tool, just not for a multi-billion dollar company.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Ray also told the committee that they were actively tracking the $477 million worth of crypto stolen from FTX on the 12th of November.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re relying on forensic and cybersecurity experts who are tracking the crypto. You can ultimately find where the crypto ends up. We&rsquo;ve got law enforcement involved. So we&rsquo;re tracking it. I think we got all the help we need on that front.&rdquo;</p>

Bankman-Fried Sent To Custody&nbsp;
<p>Meanwhile, a court in the Bahamas directed authorities to take Bankman-Fried into custody, with the ex-CEO likely to be extradited to the United States of America next year. The judge chose to ignore requests that SBF remain free on bail so that he can stick to his vegan diet and also have access to his allergy medicines and prescription Adderall.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Announces Resumption Of USDC Stablecoin Withdrawals]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/binance-announces-resumption-of-usdc-stablecoin-withdrawals</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/usdc-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/usdc-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/usdc-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/binance-announces-resumption-of-usdc-stablecoin-withdrawals</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has announced that it is resuming USDC stablecoins after temporarily pausing requests for several hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The halt in withdrawals was announced as the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange faces record stablecoin outflows.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals
<p>Binance&rsquo;s decision to temporarily halt withdrawals did give some market watchers the jitters. However, after several hours, the exchange announced the resumption of USDC stablecoin withdrawals. The decision to halt withdrawals was taken as the exchange faced a record level of outflows, with Binance reporting at least $5.2 billion worth of stablecoin outflows on Tuesday alone. This was the exchange&rsquo;s highest-ever outflows recorded, according to on-chain data analytics firm CryptoQuant.&nbsp;</p>
Reason For The Pause&nbsp;
<p>According to Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, the exchange had to temporarily pause processing USDC withdrawals because of inadequate USDC reserves on the platform. The pause was necessitated because it needed to complete a token swap. Binance holds a significant chunk of its stablecoin holdings, over $11.5 billion, in the Paxos-issued BUSD, a fiat-backed stablecoin founded by Binance and Paxos, according to Nansen data.</p>
<p>The pause was initiated so that the exchange could swap its BUSD holdings with the USDC stablecoin. However, the swaps could be completed only after banks in New York opened for business since the token swaps needed to be routed through a New York bank, hindering Binance&rsquo;s ability to process USDC withdrawal requests, albeit only temporarily.&nbsp;</p>
Changpeng Zhao Expects Normalcy&nbsp;
<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao took to Twitter to assure users that the pause was only a temporary measure. The CEO tweeted that the situation would normalize as soon as banks opened.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;On USDC, we have seen an increase in withdrawals. However, the channel to swap from PAX/BUSD to USDC requires going through a bank in NY in USD. The banks are not open for another few hours. We expect the situation will be restored when the banks open. These are 1:1 conversions with no margin or leverage involved. We will also try to establish more fluid swap channels in the future. In the meantime, feel free to withdraw any other stablecoin, BUSD, USDT, etc.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Binance has seen the market cap of its BUSD stablecoin drop from $21.4 billion to $20.2 billion, according to data sourced from Etherscan. The current market cap is down to $18.8 billion.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
A Temporary Pause&nbsp;
<p>Binance&rsquo;s decision to pause USDC withdrawals was seen as an unexpected move in almost all quarters of the crypto ecosystem, and while markets may have become a little anxious over the move, Binance insisted all was normal. At the time, Binance had stated that the withdrawals were halted due to &ldquo;technical difficulties.&rdquo; However, it later emerged that Binance needed to complete token swaps from BUSD to USDC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CEO ZHAO tweeted that he believes Binance is receiving quite a bit of FUD, expressing his annoyance. However, he stated that despite all the negativity, Binance continues to grow as an exchange.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;FUD helps us grow, even though they are thoroughly annoying. You can FUD about someone without explicitly mentioning their name, which spreads awareness. It also helps unite their supporters because it forms a common defense alliance. We thank you for all your support over the years. And let&rsquo;s continue to build together.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has announced that it is resuming USDC stablecoins after temporarily pausing requests for several hours.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The halt in withdrawals was announced as the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange faces record stablecoin outflows.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Resumes USDC Withdrawals
<p>Binance&rsquo;s decision to temporarily halt withdrawals did give some market watchers the jitters. However, after several hours, the exchange announced the resumption of USDC stablecoin withdrawals. The decision to halt withdrawals was taken as the exchange faced a record level of outflows, with Binance reporting at least $5.2 billion worth of stablecoin outflows on Tuesday alone. This was the exchange&rsquo;s highest-ever outflows recorded, according to on-chain data analytics firm CryptoQuant.&nbsp;</p>
Reason For The Pause&nbsp;
<p>According to Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, the exchange had to temporarily pause processing USDC withdrawals because of inadequate USDC reserves on the platform. The pause was necessitated because it needed to complete a token swap. Binance holds a significant chunk of its stablecoin holdings, over $11.5 billion, in the Paxos-issued BUSD, a fiat-backed stablecoin founded by Binance and Paxos, according to Nansen data.</p>
<p>The pause was initiated so that the exchange could swap its BUSD holdings with the USDC stablecoin. However, the swaps could be completed only after banks in New York opened for business since the token swaps needed to be routed through a New York bank, hindering Binance&rsquo;s ability to process USDC withdrawal requests, albeit only temporarily.&nbsp;</p>
Changpeng Zhao Expects Normalcy&nbsp;
<p>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao took to Twitter to assure users that the pause was only a temporary measure. The CEO tweeted that the situation would normalize as soon as banks opened.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;On USDC, we have seen an increase in withdrawals. However, the channel to swap from PAX/BUSD to USDC requires going through a bank in NY in USD. The banks are not open for another few hours. We expect the situation will be restored when the banks open. These are 1:1 conversions with no margin or leverage involved. We will also try to establish more fluid swap channels in the future. In the meantime, feel free to withdraw any other stablecoin, BUSD, USDT, etc.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Binance has seen the market cap of its BUSD stablecoin drop from $21.4 billion to $20.2 billion, according to data sourced from Etherscan. The current market cap is down to $18.8 billion.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
A Temporary Pause&nbsp;
<p>Binance&rsquo;s decision to pause USDC withdrawals was seen as an unexpected move in almost all quarters of the crypto ecosystem, and while markets may have become a little anxious over the move, Binance insisted all was normal. At the time, Binance had stated that the withdrawals were halted due to &ldquo;technical difficulties.&rdquo; However, it later emerged that Binance needed to complete token swaps from BUSD to USDC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CEO ZHAO tweeted that he believes Binance is receiving quite a bit of FUD, expressing his annoyance. However, he stated that despite all the negativity, Binance continues to grow as an exchange.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;FUD helps us grow, even though they are thoroughly annoying. You can FUD about someone without explicitly mentioning their name, which spreads awareness. It also helps unite their supporters because it forms a common defense alliance. We thank you for all your support over the years. And let&rsquo;s continue to build together.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Reuters: Justice Department Looks to Charge Binance, Executives]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/reuters-justice-department-looks-to-charge-binance-executives</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-bnb-chain-exploit-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-bnb-chain-exploit-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-bnb-chain-exploit-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/reuters-justice-department-looks-to-charge-binance-executives</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to reports by the news agency Reuters, United States prosecutors are considering filing criminal charges against cryptocurrency exchange Binance and executives of the company, including founder and CEO Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao. Reuters cites four persons familiar with the matter. </p>
<p>Prosecutors in the United States Attorney&rsquo;s Office in Seattle launched an investigation into Binance in 2018 after instances were recorded that saw criminals use Binance to transfer illicit funds. According to Reuters, Binance has been under investigation for possible money laundering and criminal sanctions violations. Splits between prosecutors from the Department of Justice have however been delaying the conclusion of this long-running investigation into the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange. Some of the half dozen federal prosecutors involved in the case believe that the evidence gathers thus far justifies moving forward and bringing action against Binance and some of its executives. Others in the department however are arguing to take more time to sufficiently review the evidence.</p>
<p>The Justice Department&rsquo;s investigation involves three offices: the Money Laundering and Asset Recovery Section (MLARS), the U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office for the Western District of Washington in Seattle, and finally the National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team. According to the sources, Justice Department regulations stipulate that money laundering charges against a financial institution must be approved by the MLARS chief. Further, leaders from the two other offices, as well as higher-level DOJ officials, would also have to sign off on any action leveled against Binance.</p>
Prosecution Would Be Problematic for Crypto Industry
<p>The crypto industry finds itself in a very precarious position now. The sector has been plagued by negative news ever since the collapse of Binance&rsquo;s rival exchange FTX in November. Should the investigation into Binance and Zhao continue and eventually lead to formal charges, it could loosen Binance&rsquo;s grip on the industry which has strengthened tremendously since the demise of FTX. Defense attorneys for Binance at U.S. law firm Gibson Dunn have attended several meetings with Justice Department officials over the past couple of months according to people familiar with the matter. Binance has posited a couple of arguments which include the facts that a criminal prosecution would have a disastrous effect on the market which already finds itself in a prolonged downturn. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The investigation has focused on unlicensed money transmission, money laundering conspiracy, and criminal sanctions violations. Although no final charging decisions have been made, prosecutors view Zhao and several executives to be the subject of these investigations. Should the investigation prove to be fruitful for the DOJ, the department may bring indictments against Binance and its executives, negotiate a settlement, or may close the case without taking any action against them at all. &nbsp;</p>
Binance Denies Claims Made by DOJ
<p>Binance issued a statement in which it refuted the claims made in the Reuters article. Binance&rsquo;s global head of intelligence and investigations, Tigran Gambaryan, said that the exchange has &ldquo;responded to over 47,000 law enforcement requests&rdquo; since November 2021.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Binance said:</p>

<p>As has been reported widely, regulators are doing a sweeping review of every crypto company against many of the same issues. This nascent industry has grown quickly and Binance has shown its commitment to security and compliance through large investments in our team as well as the tools and technology we use to detect and deter illicit activity.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to reports by the news agency Reuters, United States prosecutors are considering filing criminal charges against cryptocurrency exchange Binance and executives of the company, including founder and CEO Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao. Reuters cites four persons familiar with the matter. </p>
<p>Prosecutors in the United States Attorney&rsquo;s Office in Seattle launched an investigation into Binance in 2018 after instances were recorded that saw criminals use Binance to transfer illicit funds. According to Reuters, Binance has been under investigation for possible money laundering and criminal sanctions violations. Splits between prosecutors from the Department of Justice have however been delaying the conclusion of this long-running investigation into the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange. Some of the half dozen federal prosecutors involved in the case believe that the evidence gathers thus far justifies moving forward and bringing action against Binance and some of its executives. Others in the department however are arguing to take more time to sufficiently review the evidence.</p>
<p>The Justice Department&rsquo;s investigation involves three offices: the Money Laundering and Asset Recovery Section (MLARS), the U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office for the Western District of Washington in Seattle, and finally the National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team. According to the sources, Justice Department regulations stipulate that money laundering charges against a financial institution must be approved by the MLARS chief. Further, leaders from the two other offices, as well as higher-level DOJ officials, would also have to sign off on any action leveled against Binance.</p>
Prosecution Would Be Problematic for Crypto Industry
<p>The crypto industry finds itself in a very precarious position now. The sector has been plagued by negative news ever since the collapse of Binance&rsquo;s rival exchange FTX in November. Should the investigation into Binance and Zhao continue and eventually lead to formal charges, it could loosen Binance&rsquo;s grip on the industry which has strengthened tremendously since the demise of FTX. Defense attorneys for Binance at U.S. law firm Gibson Dunn have attended several meetings with Justice Department officials over the past couple of months according to people familiar with the matter. Binance has posited a couple of arguments which include the facts that a criminal prosecution would have a disastrous effect on the market which already finds itself in a prolonged downturn. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The investigation has focused on unlicensed money transmission, money laundering conspiracy, and criminal sanctions violations. Although no final charging decisions have been made, prosecutors view Zhao and several executives to be the subject of these investigations. Should the investigation prove to be fruitful for the DOJ, the department may bring indictments against Binance and its executives, negotiate a settlement, or may close the case without taking any action against them at all. &nbsp;</p>
Binance Denies Claims Made by DOJ
<p>Binance issued a statement in which it refuted the claims made in the Reuters article. Binance&rsquo;s global head of intelligence and investigations, Tigran Gambaryan, said that the exchange has &ldquo;responded to over 47,000 law enforcement requests&rdquo; since November 2021.</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Binance said:</p>

<p>As has been reported widely, regulators are doing a sweeping review of every crypto company against many of the same issues. This nascent industry has grown quickly and Binance has shown its commitment to security and compliance through large investments in our team as well as the tools and technology we use to detect and deter illicit activity.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Whale Initiates Massive $12,000,000 Polygon (MATIC) Transaction, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Price Increases Again]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/whale-initiates-massive-12000000-polygon-matic-transaction-orbeon-protocol-orbn-price-increases-again</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-13-at-195440.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-13-at-195440.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2022-12-13-at-195440.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/whale-initiates-massive-12000000-polygon-matic-transaction-orbeon-protocol-orbn-price-increases-again</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon is showing bullish signals after crypto whale moved $12 million.</p>
<p>Last week, crypto tracking platform Whale Alert reported a massive $12 million Polygon (MATIC) transaction. The whale moved the funds from cold storage to a wallet managed by Coinbase.</p>
<p>This is likely in preparation for some larger transactions. The news comes after Polygon rose 10% the week prior. Polygon has been showing bullish signs recently, and could surge in the following weeks.</p>
<p>At the same time, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has seen its price increase again. ORBN is up 655% since its presale, and is projected to rise even more in the following weeks.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">What is Polygon (MATIC)</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) started out as a way to enable faster, cheaper, and more decentralized transactions for Ethereum.</p>
<p>The Layer 2 scaling solution allows large-scale DApps to be more efficient and affordable. It uses a highly optimized form of proof of stake consensus mechanism.</p>
<p>By focusing on scalability, Polygon enables developers to build high-throughput applications. These include DeFi, NFTs, non-fungible tokens and games.</p>
<p>As an upgrade to Ethereum's ecosystem, Polygon is taking some load away from the largest DeFi network. It also benefits from Ethereum's huge development infrastructure and vibrant community.</p>
<p>This helps boost MATIC, Polygon's native currency. MATIC has the function of validating transactions and settling fees on the network.</p>
<p>As Ethereum's ecosystem grows, Polygon is set to benefit. This is especially true since some of Ethereum's smaller competitors were hit by the recent FTX crash.</p>
<p>Ethereum's surge will benefit not just Polygon, but also other projects in its ecosystem. One of these projects is Orbeon Protocol.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">What is Orbeon Protocol (ORBN)</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol is a decentralized investment platform that challenges the traditional venture capital model. It's a crowdfunding platform that aims to build an inclusive economy through blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Startups can use Orbeon Protocol&rsquo;s NFTs as a service (NFTsaaS) to mint equity-backed, fractionalized NFTs to issue during funding rounds, allowing them much quicker and easier access to capital. In turn, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) allows investors to support these funding rounds from as low as $1.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol offers a secure way to access investments in innovative projects. It provides investors with liquidity options and allows them to monitor their investments through the blockchain.</p>
<p>At the same time, Orbeon Protocol allows startup founders to raise funds more easily, efficiently, and cost-effectively. It also allows founders to connect more easily to their backers.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol has plans to become a multichain, metaverse-enabled platform. Right now, it is built on the Ethereum network, with plans to expand to Polygon next. That's why it could benefit from the growing interest in Polygon.</p>
<p>The Orbeon ecosystem is powered by the project&rsquo;s native ORBN token, a utility coin that provides holders with various benefits ranging from governance rights, staking bonuses and transaction fee discounts. </p>
<p>The project is making waves in the DeFi space as ORBN&rsquo;s price has been steadily increasing over the past months. Investors are optimistic, as the token has increased 655% since the presale. Experts predict ORBN will surge as high as 6000% before the presale ends.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon is showing bullish signals after crypto whale moved $12 million.</p>
<p>Last week, crypto tracking platform Whale Alert reported a massive $12 million Polygon (MATIC) transaction. The whale moved the funds from cold storage to a wallet managed by Coinbase.</p>
<p>This is likely in preparation for some larger transactions. The news comes after Polygon rose 10% the week prior. Polygon has been showing bullish signs recently, and could surge in the following weeks.</p>
<p>At the same time, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has seen its price increase again. ORBN is up 655% since its presale, and is projected to rise even more in the following weeks.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">What is Polygon (MATIC)</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) started out as a way to enable faster, cheaper, and more decentralized transactions for Ethereum.</p>
<p>The Layer 2 scaling solution allows large-scale DApps to be more efficient and affordable. It uses a highly optimized form of proof of stake consensus mechanism.</p>
<p>By focusing on scalability, Polygon enables developers to build high-throughput applications. These include DeFi, NFTs, non-fungible tokens and games.</p>
<p>As an upgrade to Ethereum's ecosystem, Polygon is taking some load away from the largest DeFi network. It also benefits from Ethereum's huge development infrastructure and vibrant community.</p>
<p>This helps boost MATIC, Polygon's native currency. MATIC has the function of validating transactions and settling fees on the network.</p>
<p>As Ethereum's ecosystem grows, Polygon is set to benefit. This is especially true since some of Ethereum's smaller competitors were hit by the recent FTX crash.</p>
<p>Ethereum's surge will benefit not just Polygon, but also other projects in its ecosystem. One of these projects is Orbeon Protocol.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">What is Orbeon Protocol (ORBN)</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol is a decentralized investment platform that challenges the traditional venture capital model. It's a crowdfunding platform that aims to build an inclusive economy through blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Startups can use Orbeon Protocol&rsquo;s NFTs as a service (NFTsaaS) to mint equity-backed, fractionalized NFTs to issue during funding rounds, allowing them much quicker and easier access to capital. In turn, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) allows investors to support these funding rounds from as low as $1.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol offers a secure way to access investments in innovative projects. It provides investors with liquidity options and allows them to monitor their investments through the blockchain.</p>
<p>At the same time, Orbeon Protocol allows startup founders to raise funds more easily, efficiently, and cost-effectively. It also allows founders to connect more easily to their backers.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol has plans to become a multichain, metaverse-enabled platform. Right now, it is built on the Ethereum network, with plans to expand to Polygon next. That's why it could benefit from the growing interest in Polygon.</p>
<p>The Orbeon ecosystem is powered by the project&rsquo;s native ORBN token, a utility coin that provides holders with various benefits ranging from governance rights, staking bonuses and transaction fee discounts. </p>
<p>The project is making waves in the DeFi space as ORBN&rsquo;s price has been steadily increasing over the past months. Investors are optimistic, as the token has increased 655% since the presale. Experts predict ORBN will surge as high as 6000% before the presale ends.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Canada bans leveraged crypto trading]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/canada-bans-leveraged-crypto-trading</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/can-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/can-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/can-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/canada-bans-leveraged-crypto-trading</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Canada is set to prohibit crypto firms from offering leveraged trading to its citizens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The decision was explained on the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) website, where it was stated that these activities should not be allowed as they are considered &ldquo;high-risk, speculative investments.&rdquo; This means that firms will no longer be able to offer leveraged trading of cryptocurrencies to Canadians.</p>
<p>The announcement by the CSA is the latest in a string of measures taken to protect investors from the perceived volatile nature of cryptocurrencies. In the past, the agency has cracked down on crypto firms offering services such as margin trading, which allow customers to borrow money to speculate on the price of digital coins.</p>
<p>The new rule is intended to prevent customers from taking on more risk than they can handle. It also serves to protect against possible issues, which can occur when customers are not aware of the potential losses they may incur when investing in leveraged trading.</p>
<p>Overall, this move could be seen to have a positive effect on crypto retail traders in Canada. By limiting the risk involved with leveraged trading, the CSA could be seen to be helping to protect these investors from potential losses, but on the other hand, some might see this as a Big Brother type move.</p>
Stablecoins ban?
<p>The CSA also gave the view that stablecoins &ldquo;may constitute securities, and/or derivatives&rdquo;. Therefore registered or pre-registration undertaking (PRU) trading platforms are reminded that they are prohibited from allowing Canadian citizens to trade or have any exposure to such an asset.</p>
Opinion
<p>It would certainly be the case that many retail investors have taken some heavy losses due to leverage trading. Such a strategy is assuredly best undertaken by those traders who are experienced in this area.</p>
<p>However, the sheer level of regulation that is in place, or that is coming into effect in many countries in the near future, might be considered huge overreach, and a step too far.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Already in the traditional financial sector the average retail investor is completely barred from trading in instruments that are considered to be only for those with &ldquo;accredited investor status&rdquo;.</p>
<p>That stablecoins also might be prohibited to retail traders could be the last nail in the coffin of retail investor participation in much of crypto. Stablecoins are a tool for trading in and out of cryptocurrencies and are useful for holding value in downturns.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Canada is set to prohibit crypto firms from offering leveraged trading to its citizens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The decision was explained on the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) website, where it was stated that these activities should not be allowed as they are considered &ldquo;high-risk, speculative investments.&rdquo; This means that firms will no longer be able to offer leveraged trading of cryptocurrencies to Canadians.</p>
<p>The announcement by the CSA is the latest in a string of measures taken to protect investors from the perceived volatile nature of cryptocurrencies. In the past, the agency has cracked down on crypto firms offering services such as margin trading, which allow customers to borrow money to speculate on the price of digital coins.</p>
<p>The new rule is intended to prevent customers from taking on more risk than they can handle. It also serves to protect against possible issues, which can occur when customers are not aware of the potential losses they may incur when investing in leveraged trading.</p>
<p>Overall, this move could be seen to have a positive effect on crypto retail traders in Canada. By limiting the risk involved with leveraged trading, the CSA could be seen to be helping to protect these investors from potential losses, but on the other hand, some might see this as a Big Brother type move.</p>
Stablecoins ban?
<p>The CSA also gave the view that stablecoins &ldquo;may constitute securities, and/or derivatives&rdquo;. Therefore registered or pre-registration undertaking (PRU) trading platforms are reminded that they are prohibited from allowing Canadian citizens to trade or have any exposure to such an asset.</p>
Opinion
<p>It would certainly be the case that many retail investors have taken some heavy losses due to leverage trading. Such a strategy is assuredly best undertaken by those traders who are experienced in this area.</p>
<p>However, the sheer level of regulation that is in place, or that is coming into effect in many countries in the near future, might be considered huge overreach, and a step too far.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Already in the traditional financial sector the average retail investor is completely barred from trading in instruments that are considered to be only for those with &ldquo;accredited investor status&rdquo;.</p>
<p>That stablecoins also might be prohibited to retail traders could be the last nail in the coffin of retail investor participation in much of crypto. Stablecoins are a tool for trading in and out of cryptocurrencies and are useful for holding value in downturns.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Introducing Our New Weekly Video Feature]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/introducing-our-new-weekly-video-feature</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-roundup-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-roundup-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-roundup-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/introducing-our-new-weekly-video-feature</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptodaily has been at the forefront of delivering insightful news and updates from the crypto ecosystem. Today, we introduce a new weekly video feature, allowing our audience to catch up with the hottest news from the crypto sector in a new format.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>This week, we will cover Orthogonal Trading&rsquo;s loan default, Ren Protocol&rsquo;s warning to users, Nomad&rsquo;s bridge relaunch, Binance&rsquo;s Proof of Reserves, and the FTX hearings.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
Orthogonal Trading Defaults On Loans
<p>The week saw Orthogonal Trading default on eight loans worth $36 million. The loans were taken on DeFi lending platform Maple Finance. The default occurred because Orthogonal&rsquo;s funds were tied up with the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX and impacted 30% of all active loans on the protocol. As a result of the default, Maple Finance severed all ties with Orthogonal Trading.</p>
Ren Protocol Warns Users Of Potential Loss Of Funds
<p>Alameda Research-backed Ren Protocol has warned its users that they risk losing their funds as it prepares to shutter its current Ren Version 1.0. According to the Ren team, once the current version is retired, users will not be able to recover their funds. The team encouraged users to redeem their tokens before the current version shuts down and their assets lose their value.</p>
Nomad To Relaunch Bridge
<p>Cross-chain bridge Nomad has announced that it will be relaunching its bridge after suffering a crippling hack in August. The Nomad team also stated that it would be offering impacted users partial refunds. Nomad suffered a serious exploit in August when malicious actors discovered a loophole in Nomad&rsquo;s smart contracts, resulting in the protocol losing $190 million.</p>
Binance Reveals Proof of Reserves
<p>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, announced that it completed an independent audit of its reserves. The audit confirmed that the exchange&rsquo;s Bitcoin reserves are overcollateralized. The audit was carried out by the global audit and advisory company Mazars. The audit set several minds at ease, as it revealed that customer assets are safe and sound.</p>
FTX Hearings To Take Place This Week
<p>The Financial Services Committee and the Senate Banking Committee have confirmed that they will be holding hearings this week to look into the astonishing collapse of the FTX exchange and its sister concern, Alameda Research. The Committees also asked FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried to appear before them and stated that subpoenas could be an option if Bankman-Fried refused to appear before the committees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptodaily has been at the forefront of delivering insightful news and updates from the crypto ecosystem. Today, we introduce a new weekly video feature, allowing our audience to catch up with the hottest news from the crypto sector in a new format.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>This week, we will cover Orthogonal Trading&rsquo;s loan default, Ren Protocol&rsquo;s warning to users, Nomad&rsquo;s bridge relaunch, Binance&rsquo;s Proof of Reserves, and the FTX hearings.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
Orthogonal Trading Defaults On Loans
<p>The week saw Orthogonal Trading default on eight loans worth $36 million. The loans were taken on DeFi lending platform Maple Finance. The default occurred because Orthogonal&rsquo;s funds were tied up with the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX and impacted 30% of all active loans on the protocol. As a result of the default, Maple Finance severed all ties with Orthogonal Trading.</p>
Ren Protocol Warns Users Of Potential Loss Of Funds
<p>Alameda Research-backed Ren Protocol has warned its users that they risk losing their funds as it prepares to shutter its current Ren Version 1.0. According to the Ren team, once the current version is retired, users will not be able to recover their funds. The team encouraged users to redeem their tokens before the current version shuts down and their assets lose their value.</p>
Nomad To Relaunch Bridge
<p>Cross-chain bridge Nomad has announced that it will be relaunching its bridge after suffering a crippling hack in August. The Nomad team also stated that it would be offering impacted users partial refunds. Nomad suffered a serious exploit in August when malicious actors discovered a loophole in Nomad&rsquo;s smart contracts, resulting in the protocol losing $190 million.</p>
Binance Reveals Proof of Reserves
<p>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, announced that it completed an independent audit of its reserves. The audit confirmed that the exchange&rsquo;s Bitcoin reserves are overcollateralized. The audit was carried out by the global audit and advisory company Mazars. The audit set several minds at ease, as it revealed that customer assets are safe and sound.</p>
FTX Hearings To Take Place This Week
<p>The Financial Services Committee and the Senate Banking Committee have confirmed that they will be holding hearings this week to look into the astonishing collapse of the FTX exchange and its sister concern, Alameda Research. The Committees also asked FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried to appear before them and stated that subpoenas could be an option if Bankman-Fried refused to appear before the committees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lightning Network To Enable EU-Africa Fiat Payments]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-lightning-network-to-enable-eu-africa-fiat-payments</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-lighitning-network-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-lighitning-network-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-lighitning-network-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-lightning-network-to-enable-eu-africa-fiat-payments</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin Lightning Network will be facilitating cross-border fiat payments between the EU (UK and Europe) and Africa.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto trading companies CoinCorner and Bitnob have teamed up to introduce cross-border payment between the European and African continents through the Bitcoin Lightning Network. As a result, users will now be able to send funds from the UK and Europe to select African countries. The application, Send Globally, will use the Bitcoin Lightning Network to send funds in fiat currencies. Under the application, users can send funds in British Pounds (GBP) or Euros (EUR) to the countries of Nigeria, Kenya, and Ghana, where they will be converted into the local currencies of Nigerian Naira (NGN), Kenyan Shilling (KES), and Ghanaian Cedi (GHS). The Lightning Network will automatically convert the funds from GBP or EUR to BTC. They are then converted to the local currency of the African country and directly deposited into the recipient's bank account or online wallet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This development bodes well for the crypto industry, struggling in 2022, with crypto prices taking a plunge amidst several firms going bankrupt. Before this initiative, users wishing to send funds across continents only had the option of a third-party, centralized facilitator like Western Union. The issues associated with centralized money exchanges include longer transaction times and higher transaction fees. Considering that the high remittances sent from European countries to sub-Saharan Africa are $40 billion, the transaction fees alone would amount to millions of dollars.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CoinCorner CEO Danny Scott acknowledged the scope of the remittance market and the role BTC can play in it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He pointed out,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The remittance market is a huge opportunity for Bitcoin. By partnering with Bitnob to provide a seamless cross-border experience using Bitcoin and the Lightning Network, we hope to remove some of the friction and cost that customers experience when using traditional FX and money remittance companies.&rdquo;</p>

Sub-Saharan Remittance Corridor
<p>There has been a spur of crypto adoption in the MENA (Middle East and Africa) region, despite the efforts of the IMF to discourage the industry. With the introduction of the Lightning Network, Africans working in the UK and Europe can send funds home without worrying about extended processing times or high percentage cuts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitnob CEO Bernad Parah believes the initiative will significantly reduce the costs of sending funds to the sub-Saharan region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;For us at Bitnob, this is another leap forward in economic empowerment for Africans. Sub-Saharan Africa remains the most expensive region to send money to, where sending $200 costs an average of 8.2 percent in the fourth quarter of 2020 according to the World Bank. Bitcoin is powering the future of money and this partnership highlights a strong use case of what the future will look like.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin Lightning Network will be facilitating cross-border fiat payments between the EU (UK and Europe) and Africa.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto trading companies CoinCorner and Bitnob have teamed up to introduce cross-border payment between the European and African continents through the Bitcoin Lightning Network. As a result, users will now be able to send funds from the UK and Europe to select African countries. The application, Send Globally, will use the Bitcoin Lightning Network to send funds in fiat currencies. Under the application, users can send funds in British Pounds (GBP) or Euros (EUR) to the countries of Nigeria, Kenya, and Ghana, where they will be converted into the local currencies of Nigerian Naira (NGN), Kenyan Shilling (KES), and Ghanaian Cedi (GHS). The Lightning Network will automatically convert the funds from GBP or EUR to BTC. They are then converted to the local currency of the African country and directly deposited into the recipient's bank account or online wallet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This development bodes well for the crypto industry, struggling in 2022, with crypto prices taking a plunge amidst several firms going bankrupt. Before this initiative, users wishing to send funds across continents only had the option of a third-party, centralized facilitator like Western Union. The issues associated with centralized money exchanges include longer transaction times and higher transaction fees. Considering that the high remittances sent from European countries to sub-Saharan Africa are $40 billion, the transaction fees alone would amount to millions of dollars.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CoinCorner CEO Danny Scott acknowledged the scope of the remittance market and the role BTC can play in it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He pointed out,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The remittance market is a huge opportunity for Bitcoin. By partnering with Bitnob to provide a seamless cross-border experience using Bitcoin and the Lightning Network, we hope to remove some of the friction and cost that customers experience when using traditional FX and money remittance companies.&rdquo;</p>

Sub-Saharan Remittance Corridor
<p>There has been a spur of crypto adoption in the MENA (Middle East and Africa) region, despite the efforts of the IMF to discourage the industry. With the introduction of the Lightning Network, Africans working in the UK and Europe can send funds home without worrying about extended processing times or high percentage cuts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitnob CEO Bernad Parah believes the initiative will significantly reduce the costs of sending funds to the sub-Saharan region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;For us at Bitnob, this is another leap forward in economic empowerment for Africans. Sub-Saharan Africa remains the most expensive region to send money to, where sending $200 costs an average of 8.2 percent in the fourth quarter of 2020 according to the World Bank. Bitcoin is powering the future of money and this partnership highlights a strong use case of what the future will look like.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Gaming Platform Azarus to list on Uniswap - onramps multi-million streaming audience to blockchain]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/gaming-platform-azarus-to-list-on-uniswap-onramps-multi-million-streaming-audience-to-blockchain</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/twitch_announcement_1670884043f6phcNOdNV.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/twitch_announcement_1670884043f6phcNOdNV.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/twitch_announcement_1670884043f6phcNOdNV.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/gaming-platform-azarus-to-list-on-uniswap-onramps-multi-million-streaming-audience-to-blockchain</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco, USA, 13th December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>Azarus will be hosting a keynote stream in partnership with Animoca Brands at 7am UTC on Wednesday, December 14th (11pm PST on Tuesday, December 13th) to reveal the imminent listing on Uniswap of the AzaCoin, an ERC-20 Token on Ethereum Mainnet, which will list on Uniswap on January 11, 2023. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Founded in 2018, Azarus has been demonstrating that &ldquo;streams are not TV&rdquo; through its highly engaging Overlay Games. With Azarus, streamers run interactive games over their streams to play along in real-time with their entire audience, sponsored by brands. Overlay Games have generated over 4 million watch hours, distributing $2 million in prizes in the form of loyalty points redeemable in the Azarus Store.</p>
<p>Azarus is moving into a crypto-native rewards program, which will expose millions of loyal players to the benefits of true digital ownership. Azarus is upgrading its AZA points into a crypto-native token, the AzaCoin, giving Azarus holders ownership of the value of their attention and engagement. The AzaCoin will serve as a utility and governance token with the following benefits to the ecosystem:</p>
<ul>
  <li>For Streamers: Get immediate access to your earnings with AzaCoins. Host game sessions using your channel&rsquo;s community wallet. Engage your community through voting.</li>
  <li>For Streaming Communities: Gain full ownership of your rewards as AzaCoin is distributed directly to a winner&rsquo;s crypto wallet offering full control to redeem prizes, bid and buy instantly on streams or to purchase digital assets on the Azarus Marketplace</li>
  <li>For Brands: Run and sponsor games for streamers using Azarus as part of their programming</li>
</ul>
<p>This shared desire to participate in the Azarus ecosystem creates a mutually beneficial opportunity as stakeholder incentives align, amplifying the value of the token. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
&ldquo;Azarus has been built on blockchain since the early days, with the vision to materialize the true nature of streams as a distributed digital stadium,&rdquo; said founder Alex Cassassovici. &ldquo;Listing the AzaCoin today brings us one step closer to this vision, aligning incentives of all stakeholders and giving the fans true ownership of the rewards they collect playing on stream.&rdquo;
&ldquo;It&rsquo;s our belief that Azarus will bring web3 to millions of new users,&rdquo; wrote Animoca Brands founder Yat Siu. &ldquo;Since our initial investment, we have been continually impressed at Alex's leadership in transforming the medium of streaming into web3 that has already rewarded millions of players with millions of dollars. We're beyond excited for the future of Azarus and are proud investors and partners.&rdquo;&nbsp;
<p>Holders of AzaCoin will have the option to stake their token for 3 months upon earning them in return for receiving a percentage yield back. As a governance token, AzaCoin allows viewers to vote on the usage of AzaCoins in the community wallet to impact the life cycle of Azarus Games on their preferred stream. To learn more about the token, head to azarus.io/azacoin.</p>
<p>Viewers can head over to any Azarus-enabled streams to start playing Azarus Games alongside their favorite creators and other audience members. When they answer trivia questions correctly they will earn AzaCoins. Viewers can join the keynote stream at 7am UTC on Wednesday Dec. 14th for an opportunity to win AzaCoins and learn about the token release roadmap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About Azarus
Azarus is the pioneer of Overlay Games, a new form of casual games that layer over streams. Overlay Games are massively multiplayer, simple, fun, and rewarding. Azarus offers the first platform that provides an environment to build, distribute and monetize Overlay Games on any stream. Overlay Games bring together massive live audiences, revealing the true nature of streams as an interactive medium, supporting the company&rsquo;s vision that &ldquo;Streams are not TV.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>ContactChristina DavenportAzaruschristina@azarus.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco, USA, 13th December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>Azarus will be hosting a keynote stream in partnership with Animoca Brands at 7am UTC on Wednesday, December 14th (11pm PST on Tuesday, December 13th) to reveal the imminent listing on Uniswap of the AzaCoin, an ERC-20 Token on Ethereum Mainnet, which will list on Uniswap on January 11, 2023. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Founded in 2018, Azarus has been demonstrating that &ldquo;streams are not TV&rdquo; through its highly engaging Overlay Games. With Azarus, streamers run interactive games over their streams to play along in real-time with their entire audience, sponsored by brands. Overlay Games have generated over 4 million watch hours, distributing $2 million in prizes in the form of loyalty points redeemable in the Azarus Store.</p>
<p>Azarus is moving into a crypto-native rewards program, which will expose millions of loyal players to the benefits of true digital ownership. Azarus is upgrading its AZA points into a crypto-native token, the AzaCoin, giving Azarus holders ownership of the value of their attention and engagement. The AzaCoin will serve as a utility and governance token with the following benefits to the ecosystem:</p>
<ul>
  <li>For Streamers: Get immediate access to your earnings with AzaCoins. Host game sessions using your channel&rsquo;s community wallet. Engage your community through voting.</li>
  <li>For Streaming Communities: Gain full ownership of your rewards as AzaCoin is distributed directly to a winner&rsquo;s crypto wallet offering full control to redeem prizes, bid and buy instantly on streams or to purchase digital assets on the Azarus Marketplace</li>
  <li>For Brands: Run and sponsor games for streamers using Azarus as part of their programming</li>
</ul>
<p>This shared desire to participate in the Azarus ecosystem creates a mutually beneficial opportunity as stakeholder incentives align, amplifying the value of the token. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
&ldquo;Azarus has been built on blockchain since the early days, with the vision to materialize the true nature of streams as a distributed digital stadium,&rdquo; said founder Alex Cassassovici. &ldquo;Listing the AzaCoin today brings us one step closer to this vision, aligning incentives of all stakeholders and giving the fans true ownership of the rewards they collect playing on stream.&rdquo;
&ldquo;It&rsquo;s our belief that Azarus will bring web3 to millions of new users,&rdquo; wrote Animoca Brands founder Yat Siu. &ldquo;Since our initial investment, we have been continually impressed at Alex's leadership in transforming the medium of streaming into web3 that has already rewarded millions of players with millions of dollars. We're beyond excited for the future of Azarus and are proud investors and partners.&rdquo;&nbsp;
<p>Holders of AzaCoin will have the option to stake their token for 3 months upon earning them in return for receiving a percentage yield back. As a governance token, AzaCoin allows viewers to vote on the usage of AzaCoins in the community wallet to impact the life cycle of Azarus Games on their preferred stream. To learn more about the token, head to azarus.io/azacoin.</p>
<p>Viewers can head over to any Azarus-enabled streams to start playing Azarus Games alongside their favorite creators and other audience members. When they answer trivia questions correctly they will earn AzaCoins. Viewers can join the keynote stream at 7am UTC on Wednesday Dec. 14th for an opportunity to win AzaCoins and learn about the token release roadmap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About Azarus
Azarus is the pioneer of Overlay Games, a new form of casual games that layer over streams. Overlay Games are massively multiplayer, simple, fun, and rewarding. Azarus offers the first platform that provides an environment to build, distribute and monetize Overlay Games on any stream. Overlay Games bring together massive live audiences, revealing the true nature of streams as an interactive medium, supporting the company&rsquo;s vision that &ldquo;Streams are not TV.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>ContactChristina DavenportAzaruschristina@azarus.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  17434 Target Tested - 14 December 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-price-analysis-17434-target-tested-14-december-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-13-december-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-13-december-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-13-december-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-price-analysis-17434-target-tested-14-december-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Looks to Sustain Multi-Week Highs:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 14 December 2022</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered strong upward momentum early in the Asian session as the pair escalated higher to the 17500 level after finding technical support around the 17089.17 level, representing a test of the 50-hour simple moving average.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 17221.04, 17302.51, and 17434.51 levels during the ascent, upside price objectives related to buying pressure that emerged around the 16875.83 and 17089.17 areas.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives related to this appreciating range include the 17779.81 and 17872.75 levels.&nbsp; Additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 17791, 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Associated downside price objectives below current price activity include the 13369, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Technicians continue to eye the 14500.15 and 10432.73 areas as major downside targets, and additional downside price objectives include the 14613, 10727, and 9682 levels, areas that are related to selling pressure that intensified around the 20894.96 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 1200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 17069.47 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 17137.61.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Looks to Sustain Multi-Week Highs:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 14 December 2022</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered strong upward momentum early in the Asian session as the pair escalated higher to the 17500 level after finding technical support around the 17089.17 level, representing a test of the 50-hour simple moving average.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 17221.04, 17302.51, and 17434.51 levels during the ascent, upside price objectives related to buying pressure that emerged around the 16875.83 and 17089.17 areas.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives related to this appreciating range include the 17779.81 and 17872.75 levels.&nbsp; Additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 17791, 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Associated downside price objectives below current price activity include the 13369, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Technicians continue to eye the 14500.15 and 10432.73 areas as major downside targets, and additional downside price objectives include the 14613, 10727, and 9682 levels, areas that are related to selling pressure that intensified around the 20894.96 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 1200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 17069.47 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 17137.61.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
