<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Logan Paul Drops Threat of Lawsuit Against Coffeezilla But Will Alleged Victims Get Money Back?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/logan-paul-drops-threat-of-lawsuit-against-coffeezilla-but-will-alleged-victims-get-money-back.htm</link><description>Popular influencer and professional wrestler Logan Paul has dropped his threat of a lawsuit of YouTube journalist Coffeezilla after being accused of running a crypto investment scam. &lt;br /&gt;
“Hey all, just wanted to update you. I deleted my initial response to Coffee's series. It was rash and misaligned with the trust issue at hand, so I called him today and apologized,” Paul wrote in a message posted on a Discord server he operates, according to a screenshot shared online by Coffeezilla....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/logan-paul-drops-threat-of-lawsuit-against-coffeezilla-but-will-alleged-victims-get-money-back.htm"&gt;Read More: Logan Paul Drops Threat of Lawsuit Against Coffeezilla But Will Alleged Victims Get Money Back?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Logan Paul</category><category>Scam</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/logan-paul-drops-threat-of-lawsuit-against-coffeezilla-but-will-alleged-victims-get-money-back.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100750/248991/lawsuit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="128901"/></item><item><title>Gala Price Keeps Pumping Higher After Wahlberg and the Rock Deal - Can it Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-price-keeps-pumping-higher-after-wahlberg-and-the-rock-deal-can-it-reach-1.htm</link><description>Gala Games (GALA) recently made headlines as GALA's price surged by almost 60% in one day after an announcement that they'll be partnering with actors Dwayne ‘The Rock' Johnson and Mark Wahlberg in producing films for their ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-price-keeps-pumping-higher-after-wahlberg-and-the-rock-deal-can-it-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Gala Price Keeps Pumping Higher After Wahlberg and the Rock Deal - Can it Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>GALA price</category><category>GALA</category><category>FGHT</category><category>D2T</category><category>CCHG</category><category>RIA</category><category>Taro</category><category>Fight Out</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>C+Charge</category><category>RobotEra</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-price-keeps-pumping-higher-after-wahlberg-and-the-rock-deal-can-it-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100782/249041/gala.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="277521"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Expelled Chinese Communist Party Official Shamed on TV for Supporting Crypto Mining, Nigeria Considering a Regulatory Framework for Stablecoin Implementation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-expelled-chinese-communist-party-official-shamed-on-tv-for-supporting-crypto-mining-nigeria-considering-a-regulatory-framework-for-stablecoin-implementation.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-expelled-chinese-communist-party-official-shamed-on-tv-for-supporting-crypto-mining-nigeria-considering-a-regulatory-framework-for-stablecoin-implementation.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Expelled Chinese Communist Party Official Shamed on TV for Supporting Crypto Mining, Nigeria Considering a Regulatory Framework for Stablecoin Implementation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Politics</category><category>Mining</category><category>Legal</category><category>FTX</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Hack</category><category>Grayscale Investments</category><category>Nigeria</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Wyre</category><category>Investment</category><category>Turkey</category><category>Europe</category><category>EU</category><category>Hedera</category><category>India</category><category>Payments</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-expelled-chinese-communist-party-official-shamed-on-tv-for-supporting-crypto-mining-nigeria-considering-a-regulatory-framework-for-stablecoin-implementation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100731/248963/adobestock-k-tsygankova-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="77054"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Shows it is back From the Dead - Can the Resurrection Push Coin 2x to $30?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-shows-it-is-back-from-the-dead-can-the-resurrection-push-coin-2x-to-30.htm</link><description>Recent developments on the Solana blockchain network have led to increased activity among developers, which is being seen as a positive sign for the cryptocurrency--leading Solana's price to skyrocket in recent days. According to data from crypto aggregator Lunar Crush, social mentions of the dubbed "Ethereum Killer" altcoin spiked in January 2023, indicating growing popularity in the crypto community....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-shows-it-is-back-from-the-dead-can-the-resurrection-push-coin-2x-to-30.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Shows it is back From the Dead - Can the Resurrection Push Coin 2x to $30?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Bonk</category><category>Solana Price</category><category>Solana Price Prediction</category><category>SOL price</category><category>SOL price prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-shows-it-is-back-from-the-dead-can-the-resurrection-push-coin-2x-to-30.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100771/249019/sol.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="250761"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Announces Third Round of Layoffs, Reduces Headcount by 950 Employees</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-announces-third-round-of-layoffs-reduces-headcount-by-950-employees.htm</link><description>Major cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has announced its third round of layoffs amid the ongoing bear market, reducing its headcount by a total of 950 employees, or 20% of its workforce. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-announces-third-round-of-layoffs-reduces-headcount-by-950-employees.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Announces Third Round of Layoffs, Reduces Headcount by 950 Employees&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Crypto Winter</category><category>Brian Armstrong</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-announces-third-round-of-layoffs-reduces-headcount-by-950-employees.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100753/248993/adobestock-gguy-1-media-library-original-1350-901.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="188179"/></item><item><title>Nick Saponaro, CEO of Divi Project &amp; Wallet, on 2023 Predictions, Bitcoin, Altcoins, and DIVI | Ep. 194</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/nick-saponaro-ceo-of-divi-project-wallet-2023-predictions-bitcoin-altcoins-divi-ep-194.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Nick Saponaro, CEO of Divi Project &amp; Wallet, talks about what happened in 2022, areas of opportunity in 2023, CBDCs, Bitcoin, and altcoins.  &lt;br /&gt;
Nick Saponaro is the CEO of Divi Project and its Fintech Innovation Centre, Divi Labs. Nick is also an entrepreneur, crypto enthusiast, investor and keynote speaker who is regularly featured in the media talking about crypto related issues. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/nick-saponaro-ceo-of-divi-project-wallet-2023-predictions-bitcoin-altcoins-divi-ep-194.htm"&gt;Read More: Nick Saponaro, CEO of Divi Project &amp; Wallet, on 2023 Predictions, Bitcoin, Altcoins, and DIVI | Ep. 194&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/nick-saponaro-ceo-of-divi-project-wallet-2023-predictions-bitcoin-altcoins-divi-ep-194.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100687/248894/nick-saponaro-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="65747"/></item><item><title>These Businesses Will be The Survivors of the Crypto Winter, Says a Top Financial Services Lawyer</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/these-businesses-will-survivors-of-crypto-winter-says-top-financial-services-lawyer.htm</link><description>Crypto companies that keep their faith in the sector, and that are able to harness the value of traditional risk management and compliance, will survive the crypto winter, one leading financial services lawyer has argued....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/these-businesses-will-survivors-of-crypto-winter-says-top-financial-services-lawyer.htm"&gt;Read More: These Businesses Will be The Survivors of the Crypto Winter, Says a Top Financial Services Lawyer&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/these-businesses-will-survivors-of-crypto-winter-says-top-financial-services-lawyer.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100727/248952/crypto-winter.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1310515"/></item><item><title>Argentina Wants Citizens to Declare Their Crypto Holdings</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-wants-citizens-declare-their-crypto-holdings.htm</link><description>Argentina’s finance ministry is set to launch a draft bill that would essentially force citizens to declare their crypto holdings – or risk paying hefty tax penalties. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Errepar, the bill has been spearheaded by Sergio Massa, the Minister for the Economy. The draft law aims to tighten the country’s money laundering rules. It will be tabled in the upcoming parliamentary session, where the ruling Frente de Todos coalition has a slender majority....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-wants-citizens-declare-their-crypto-holdings.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina Wants Citizens to Declare Their Crypto Holdings&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-wants-citizens-declare-their-crypto-holdings.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100738/248965/1280px-palacio-de-hacienda-ministerio-de-economia.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="249274"/></item><item><title>Financial Bubbles Expert: Crypto a Bubble Like No Other or a Ponzi Scheme. Is He Right?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/financial-bubbles-expert-crypto-bubble-like-no-other-or-ponzi-scheme-he-right.htm</link><description>Some financial experts with a specialty in bubbles believe crypto is either one of the biggest bubbles in history or a smart Ponzi scheme not seen before.  &lt;br /&gt;
2022 can be considered one of the worst years for the crypto ecosystem as a number of high-profile DeFi and CeFi platforms collapsed. Among the more notable examples, the Terra/LUNA ecosystem imploded in May while major crypto exchange FTX collapsed in early November. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/financial-bubbles-expert-crypto-bubble-like-no-other-or-ponzi-scheme-he-right.htm"&gt;Read More: Financial Bubbles Expert: Crypto a Bubble Like No Other or a Ponzi Scheme. Is He Right?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Bubble</category><category>FTX</category><category>Terra</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/financial-bubbles-expert-crypto-bubble-like-no-other-or-ponzi-scheme-he-right.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100744/248987/bitcoin-bubble.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="159910"/></item><item><title>Zilliqa Price Prediction - Why Sharding Pioneer Is on Fire and Should You Buy Today?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/zilliqa-price-prediction-why-sharding-pioneer-is-on-fire-and-should-you-buy-today.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
Zilliqa’s ZIL token has been on an impressive roll this week, with its price rising considerably as more investors jump to catch its hot wave. However, why is its price on the rise, and what should investors know about it? ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/zilliqa-price-prediction-why-sharding-pioneer-is-on-fire-and-should-you-buy-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Zilliqa Price Prediction - Why Sharding Pioneer Is on Fire and Should You Buy Today?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/zilliqa-price-prediction-why-sharding-pioneer-is-on-fire-and-should-you-buy-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100735/248964/53bf2e.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="299373"/></item><item><title>3 Reasons Why Crypto is Breaking Out and the Rally Might Have Legs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/3-reasons-why-crypto-breaking-out-rally-might-legs.htm</link><description>The bullish breakout in crypto that started last week has seen investors beam with hope for a sustainable recovery. Bitcoin (BTC) and other cryptocurrencies struggled throughout 2022 amid internal and external uncertain events....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/3-reasons-why-crypto-breaking-out-rally-might-legs.htm"&gt;Read More: 3 Reasons Why Crypto is Breaking Out and the Rally Might Have Legs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/3-reasons-why-crypto-breaking-out-rally-might-legs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100729/248957/screenshot-71.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="120160"/></item><item><title>After Topping $15 Million, Dash 2 Trade Crypto Presale Will Sell Out in Hours - Big Gains in Exchange Listings Wednesday 11th January</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/after-topping-15-million-dash-2-trade-crypto-presale-will-sell-out-in-hours-big-gains-in-exchange-listings-wednesday-11th-january.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
D2T, the crypto token for the Dash 2 Trade ecosystem, has hit yet another milestone as it nears its final total of $15,421,600 before making its public debut on exchanges tomorrow, Wednesday, January 11th....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/after-topping-15-million-dash-2-trade-crypto-presale-will-sell-out-in-hours-big-gains-in-exchange-listings-wednesday-11th-january.htm"&gt;Read More: After Topping $15 Million, Dash 2 Trade Crypto Presale Will Sell Out in Hours - Big Gains in Exchange Listings Wednesday 11th January&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/after-topping-15-million-dash-2-trade-crypto-presale-will-sell-out-in-hours-big-gains-in-exchange-listings-wednesday-11th-january.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100726/248949/img-8936.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="106067"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 10th January – FGHT, APT, D2T, CHZ, CCHG, GALA, RIA, ZIL</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-10th-january-fght-apt-d2t-chz-cchg-gala-ria-zil.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has remained flat in the past 24 hours, after a much-needed rally yesterday. At $889 billion, its total cap has also risen by 6% in a week, although it is actually slightly down in the past month. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite today's lack of movement for the market as a whole, a number of altcoins have continued to beat averages. This article collects them in a list of the best crypto to buy today, while it also includes several very promising presale tokens....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-10th-january-fght-apt-d2t-chz-cchg-gala-ria-zil.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 10th January – FGHT, APT, D2T, CHZ, CCHG, GALA, RIA, ZIL&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-10th-january-fght-apt-d2t-chz-cchg-gala-ria-zil.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100694/248937/best-crypto-10th-jan.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="298459"/></item><item><title>Wintermute is Now One of the Biggest Market Makers in Crypto and Has Birthed 36 Millionaires</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wintermute-now-one-of-biggest-market-makers-crypto-birthed-36-millionaires.htm</link><description>Wintermute, a leading global crypto market maker, has paid its 36 British staff a total of $83 million in 2021, suggesting that the crypto company gave birth to 36 new millionaires.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to its newly filed annual report, Wintermute paid its 36 UK staff $83 million in 2021, meaning the firm had an average payout of $2.3 million for each employee. Furthermore, the crypto company paid a whopping $22.5 million to one director in the year. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wintermute-now-one-of-biggest-market-makers-crypto-birthed-36-millionaires.htm"&gt;Read More: Wintermute is Now One of the Biggest Market Makers in Crypto and Has Birthed 36 Millionaires&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Wintermute</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Millionaire</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wintermute-now-one-of-biggest-market-makers-crypto-birthed-36-millionaires.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100705/248931/wintermute-meta-1024-535.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="153551"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Pumps 10% And That Makes This New Meme Coin Gaming Platform More Valuable</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-pumps-10-that-makes-new-meme-coin-gaming-platform-more-valuable.htm</link><description>DOGE, the native token of the dog meme-inspired Dogecoin blockchain, has been pumping in tandem with a broader move higher in cryptocurrency markets in the last few days. Traders have been bidding up crypto prices in the hope that a weakening US economic outlook in the wake of last week’s soft US ISM surveys prevents the Fed from being too aggressive with rate hikes this year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-pumps-10-that-makes-new-meme-coin-gaming-platform-more-valuable.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Pumps 10% And That Makes This New Meme Coin Gaming Platform More Valuable&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>DOGE</category><category>TAMADOGE</category><category>TAMA</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-pumps-10-that-makes-new-meme-coin-gaming-platform-more-valuable.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100703/248926/tamadoge.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="833768"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Bithumb Hit With Tax Investigation, Prosecutors Grill ‘Major Shareholder’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bithumb-hit-with-tax-investigation-prosecutors-grill-major-shareholder.htm</link><description>The South Korean crypto exchange Bithumb has been hit with a double whammy from the South Korean tax and legal authorities – with the exchange made the subject of a “special” tax investigation. And prosecutors have summoned its suspected largest shareholder for questioning. &lt;br /&gt;
Chosun reported that the National Tax Service (NTS) has “launched a special tax investigation” into Bithumb Korea and Bithumb Holdings. The two companies operate the Bithumb trading platform....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bithumb-hit-with-tax-investigation-prosecutors-grill-major-shareholder.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Bithumb Hit With Tax Investigation, Prosecutors Grill ‘Major Shareholder’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bithumb</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bithumb-hit-with-tax-investigation-prosecutors-grill-major-shareholder.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100668/248876/adobestock-519554400-editorial-use-only.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1406147"/></item></channel></rss>
