<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Calvaria is the Best Play to Earn Game Since Splinterlands And its Raised Nearly $3m in Presale - Ending Soon</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/calvaria-is-the-best-play-to-earn-game-since-splinterlands-and-its-raised-nearly-3m-in-presale-ending-soon.htm</link><description>Calvaria: Duels of Eternity is an upcoming digital battle card game that is set to make waves in the GameFi space. The developers of Calvaria are hopeful that their new NFT-based battle card game will help spur crypto adoption rates. The play-to-earn mechanics allows players to earn rewards as they play, and by offering a free version of the game, players will be able to see how cryptocurrencies could improve their gameplay experience without spending a dime....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/calvaria-is-the-best-play-to-earn-game-since-splinterlands-and-its-raised-nearly-3m-in-presale-ending-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Calvaria is the Best Play to Earn Game Since Splinterlands And its Raised Nearly $3m in Presale - Ending Soon&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Calvaria</category><category>RIA</category><category>Web 3 Gaming</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>P2E</category><category>Splinterlands</category><category>Battle Card Game</category><category>Battle Cards</category><category>Nft Cards</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/calvaria-is-the-best-play-to-earn-game-since-splinterlands-and-its-raised-nearly-3m-in-presale-ending-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101609/250991/calvaria5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="961022"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Will Soon Have 100 Million Addresses With Non-Zero Balance – What This Milestone Means for ETH Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-will-soon-have-100-million-addresses-with-non-zero-balance-what-this-milestone-means-for-eth-price.htm</link><description>The number of Ethereum addresses holding a non-zero balance hit a new record high on Monday of 92.5 million. 2022’s bear market, which culminated in the collapse of one of the world’s former largest cryptocurrency exchanges in November, does not appear to have impacted growth in the number of non-zero balance addresses. &lt;br /&gt;
...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-will-soon-have-100-million-addresses-with-non-zero-balance-what-this-milestone-means-for-eth-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Will Soon Have 100 Million Addresses With Non-Zero Balance – What This Milestone Means for ETH Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-will-soon-have-100-million-addresses-with-non-zero-balance-what-this-milestone-means-for-eth-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101606/250969/adobestock-502340386-editorial-use-only.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2344060"/></item><item><title>Green Crypto Project to Drive Up EV Charging Payments Efficiency Raises $300k - How to Invest in C+Charge</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-project-to-drive-up-ev-charging-payments-efficiency-raises-300k-how-to-invest-in-ccharge.htm</link><description>The electric vehicle (EV) industry is experiencing a rapid growth and with it comes the need for a more efficient and convenient way to charge these vehicles. Enter C+Charge, a blockchain-based platform that aims to make EV charging more accessible and convenient for EV owners. The platform connects EV owners with charging networks and allows for easy payment transactions, all while helping EV drivers earn carbon credits and sustainable cryptocurrency rewards....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-project-to-drive-up-ev-charging-payments-efficiency-raises-300k-how-to-invest-in-ccharge.htm"&gt;Read More: Green Crypto Project to Drive Up EV Charging Payments Efficiency Raises $300k - How to Invest in C+Charge&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Sustainable Crypto</category><category>how to invest in C+charge</category><category>C+Charge</category><category>CCHG</category><category>Green Crypto</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-project-to-drive-up-ev-charging-payments-efficiency-raises-300k-how-to-invest-in-ccharge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101604/250966/how-to-invest-in-ccharge.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="305057"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Transactions Surge to 21 Month High – What This Means For BTC Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-transactions-surge-21-month-high-what-means-for-btc-price.htm</link><description>The number of transactions recorded on the Bitcoin blockchain jumped to nearly 300,000 on Saturday the 14 of January, its highest level since April 2021, according to data from crypto analytics firm Glassnode. Just a few weeks ago, daily transactions had been as low as 240,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-transactions-surge-21-month-high-what-means-for-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Transactions Surge to 21 Month High – What This Means For BTC Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Transactions</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-transactions-surge-21-month-high-what-means-for-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101600/250963/btcusd-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="773519"/></item><item><title>Are We Witnessing the Return of the Crypto Bulls or a Bear Market Bull Trap?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/are-we-witnessing-return-of-crypto-bulls-or-bear-market-bull-trap.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has been on a roller coaster ride in recent months, with Bitcoin and Ethereum prices experiencing significant fluctuations. After a period of relative stability, BTC's price catapulted by a remarkable 28% in January, leading to liquidations worth more than $500 million as exchanges closed traders' leveraged short positions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/are-we-witnessing-return-of-crypto-bulls-or-bear-market-bull-trap.htm"&gt;Read More: Are We Witnessing the Return of the Crypto Bulls or a Bear Market Bull Trap?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin Price</category><category>Bitcoin Price Prediction</category><category>Btc Price</category><category>Bitcoin Bull Trap</category><category>Bull Trap</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/are-we-witnessing-return-of-crypto-bulls-or-bear-market-bull-trap.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101591/250889/btc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="601829"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Digital Yuan Used to Buy Securities, Monex Group Interested in FTX Japan, Bitget Launches Copy Trading in Spot Market</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-digital-yuan-used-to-buy-securities-monex-group-interested-in-ftx-japan-bitget-launches-copy-trading-in-spot-market.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-digital-yuan-used-to-buy-securities-monex-group-interested-in-ftx-japan-bitget-launches-copy-trading-in-spot-market.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Digital Yuan Used to Buy Securities, Monex Group Interested in FTX Japan, Bitget Launches Copy Trading in Spot Market&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Securities</category><category>Legal</category><category>Vauld</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Bitget</category><category>FTX</category><category>Japan</category><category>Investment</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Thailand</category><category>SEC</category><category>Wallet</category><category>NFT</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Polkadot</category><category>Aave</category><category>Hedera</category><category>Mining</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-digital-yuan-used-to-buy-securities-monex-group-interested-in-ftx-japan-bitget-launches-copy-trading-in-spot-market.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101548/250668/adobestock-sielan-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="94037"/></item><item><title>Terra Classic Luna Price Slips Back 3% to $0.000176 - Can LUNC Really Reach $1 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-luna-price-slips-back-3-to-0000176-can-lunc-really-reach-1-in-2023.htm</link><description>Terra Classic price is building momentum to correct a 3% dip recorded in 24 hours. Before the pullback to 0.0001720, LUNC traded new 2023 highs of $0.0001936. With support at $0.0001720 staying intact, Terra Classic price might push for the resumption of the uptrend during the American session....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-luna-price-slips-back-3-to-0000176-can-lunc-really-reach-1-in-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Classic Luna Price Slips Back 3% to $0.000176 - Can LUNC Really Reach $1 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-luna-price-slips-back-3-to-0000176-can-lunc-really-reach-1-in-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101588/250848/screenshot-92.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="154584"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Strengthening on Upcoming Shibarium Layer 2 Beta Launch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-strengthening-upcoming-shibarium-layer-2-beta-launch.htm</link><description>Meme crypto Shiba Inu's price rallied more than most coins in the top 20 over the past week as the team announced that its Layer 2 network, Shibarium, is set to enter beta launch soon. The developers of the project insist that Shibarium has not been designed as a tool to manipulate the Shiba Inu price, but instead as a platform for achieving the vision and mission of their community....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-strengthening-upcoming-shibarium-layer-2-beta-launch.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Strengthening on Upcoming Shibarium Layer 2 Beta Launch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Shib Price</category><category>Shiba Inu Price</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Meme Crypto</category><category>Meme Cryptocurrency</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>DOGE</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-strengthening-upcoming-shibarium-layer-2-beta-launch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101578/250784/shib.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="673336"/></item><item><title>Tony Cheng, Managing Partner at Foresight Ventures, on Crypto Venture Capital and Investing in 2023 | Ep. 196</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/tony-cheng-managing-partner-at-foresight-ventures-crypto-venture-capital-investing-2023-ep-196.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Tony Cheng, Managing Partner at Foresight Ventures, talks about investing in China, investment trends of 2023, and various ways where the VC landscape changed in 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/tony-cheng-managing-partner-at-foresight-ventures-crypto-venture-capital-investing-2023-ep-196.htm"&gt;Read More: Tony Cheng, Managing Partner at Foresight Ventures, on Crypto Venture Capital and Investing in 2023 | Ep. 196&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/tony-cheng-managing-partner-at-foresight-ventures-crypto-venture-capital-investing-2023-ep-196.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101569/250689/tony-cheng-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="61120"/></item><item><title>Japanese Tax Agency Wants to Tax NFT Sales and Crypto Gaming Profits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-tax-agency-wants-tax-nft-sales-crypto-gaming-profits.htm</link><description>The Japanese tax body has signaled an intention to tax non-fungible token (NFT) sales and the profits earned by crypto and blockchain gamers. &lt;br /&gt;
In an FAQ-type document released by the National Tax Agency (NTA), the body explained “guidelines” for tax officers dealing with NFT-related “cases” where taxes such as consumption tax (Japan’s equivalent of VAT) should be applied....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-tax-agency-wants-tax-nft-sales-crypto-gaming-profits.htm"&gt;Read More: Japanese Tax Agency Wants to Tax NFT Sales and Crypto Gaming Profits&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Japan</category><category>NFT</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-tax-agency-wants-tax-nft-sales-crypto-gaming-profits.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101508/250593/3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="624053"/></item><item><title>Lazarus Group's Stolen 41,000 ETH from Harmony Bridge Hack is on The Move</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lazarus-groups-stolen-41000-eth-from-harmony-bridge-hack-move.htm</link><description>A whopping 41,000 ETH stolen by the North Korean hackers Lazarus Group are currently being deposited on crypto exchanges. &lt;br /&gt;
According to an analysis of the token movements shared online, the ETH was sent through the anonymity system Railgun before being consolidated in wallets and sent to three major crypto exchanges, possibly to be exchanged for fiat currency....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lazarus-groups-stolen-41000-eth-from-harmony-bridge-hack-move.htm"&gt;Read More: Lazarus Group's Stolen 41,000 ETH from Harmony Bridge Hack is on The Move&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Harmony</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lazarus-groups-stolen-41000-eth-from-harmony-bridge-hack-move.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101558/250667/harmony-bridge.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="116496"/></item><item><title>PancakeSwap Price Slips 3% to $3.71 - Should You Buy Dip in This Top DEX Coin?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pancakeswap-price-slips-3-to-371-should-you-buy-dip-in-this-top-dex-coin.htm</link><description>PancakeSwap price has started giving back the gains accrued from January 1, when it bottomed out at $3.15. CAKE is down slightly over 3% in 24 hours to trade at $3.72 at the time of writing. With this price analysis, investors will figure out if they should buy the dip or wait for PancakeSwap price to exhaust the pullback....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pancakeswap-price-slips-3-to-371-should-you-buy-dip-in-this-top-dex-coin.htm"&gt;Read More: PancakeSwap Price Slips 3% to $3.71 - Should You Buy Dip in This Top DEX Coin?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pancakeswap-price-slips-3-to-371-should-you-buy-dip-in-this-top-dex-coin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101546/250659/pancakeswap-on-bnb-cake-14-33-48-17-jan-2023.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1268595"/></item><item><title>Kevin O’Leary Says Crypto is Getting "Very Interesting" - Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-crypto-is-getting-very-interesting-heres-why.htm</link><description>Investor and Shark Tank star Kevin O'Leary has said crypto is getting "very interesting" as the recent events have forced lawmakers to push for a solid regulatory framework....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-crypto-is-getting-very-interesting-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Kevin O’Leary Says Crypto is Getting "Very Interesting" - Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Kevin O'Leary</category><category>FTX</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/kevin-oleary-says-crypto-is-getting-very-interesting-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101551/250661/kevinolary.JPG" type="image/jpeg" length="108868"/></item><item><title>Want to Buy Distressed Crypto Assets? 3AC Founders May Be Creating an Exchange For That Called GTX</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/want-buy-distressed-crypto-assets-3ac-founders-may-creating-an-exchange-for-that-called-gtx.htm</link><description>The founders of now-bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital and troubled crypto exchange CoinFlex have teamed up to create a new exchange focused on the claims of failed crypto projects. &lt;br /&gt;
Su Zhu and Kyle Davies, the founders of collapsed crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), in collaboration with Mark Lamb and Sudhu Arumugam, who founded CoinFlex, plan to launch GTX, a new crypto exchange focused on claims trading....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/want-buy-distressed-crypto-assets-3ac-founders-may-creating-an-exchange-for-that-called-gtx.htm"&gt;Read More: Want to Buy Distressed Crypto Assets? 3AC Founders May Be Creating an Exchange For That Called GTX&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/want-buy-distressed-crypto-assets-3ac-founders-may-creating-an-exchange-for-that-called-gtx.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101539/250653/su-zhu-amongst-creditors-files-5m-claim-against-website-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="92230"/></item><item><title>Former UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson Received £1 Million Donation From Thai Crypto Investor</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/former-uk-prime-minister-boris-johnson-received-ps1-million-donation-from-thai-crypto-investor.htm</link><description>Former UK prime minister Boris Johnson received a £1 million donation from a Thailand-based cryptocurrency investor, parliamentary documents have revealed. &lt;br /&gt;
The register of interests, published on Friday 13 January, showed that Johnson's company Boris Johnson Ltd., received the donation from Christopher Harborne. It also showed that Johnson earned £250,000 for a speech held at blockchain company ParallelChain Lab in Singapore....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/former-uk-prime-minister-boris-johnson-received-ps1-million-donation-from-thai-crypto-investor.htm"&gt;Read More: Former UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson Received £1 Million Donation From Thai Crypto Investor&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>People In Crypto</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/former-uk-prime-minister-boris-johnson-received-ps1-million-donation-from-thai-crypto-investor.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101535/250646/skynews-boris-johnson-5941280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="190433"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 17th January – CELO, MEMAG, CAVA, FGHT, CRO, CCHG, CVX, RIA, LRC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-17th-january-celo-memag-cava-fght-cro-cchg-cvx-ria-lrc.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has enjoyed another day of gains, with its total cap rising by 1% in 24 hours, to $1.03 trillion. This marks more or less a week of uninterrupted increases, with the publication of more positive US inflation figures serving to set off a wave of renewed optimism from investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-17th-january-celo-memag-cava-fght-cro-cchg-cvx-ria-lrc.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 17th January – CELO, MEMAG, CAVA, FGHT, CRO, CCHG, CVX, RIA, LRC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-17th-january-celo-memag-cava-fght-cro-cchg-cvx-ria-lrc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101510/250644/best-crypto-to-buy-today-17th-january.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="364355"/></item></channel></rss>
