<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 04:50:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Introducing DigiToads: The Top Meme Coin of 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/introducing-digitoads-the-top-meme-coin-of-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-613.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-613.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-613.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/introducing-digitoads-the-top-meme-coin-of-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies evolve daily, owing to the rapid transformation of the digital space. As Tokens emerge, some do so with exciting features for the modern world. At the heart of these transformations is DigiToads&ndash;a platform that is set to revolutionize how people interact with meme coins. The stake-to-earn feature and play-to-earn are all standouts of DigiToads, which will provide opportunities for investors as the platform takes new steps towards its launch.</p>
<p>Step Into the World of TOADS</p>
<p>The core of the coin is the new web3 which promises an immersive online experience. Indeed, DigiToads enables interactions in the web-3 using its native coin TOADS. The coin is critical to NFT staking, and the P2E feature is set to become central to DigiToads' growth. Users will collect more NFTs in the metaverse, nature them in interactive gaming, and finally use them to battle other players within the DigiToads ecosystem for more prizes.</p>
<p>While in the competitive state of gaming, NFT owners will have the opportunity to maximize their character&rsquo;s strengths by spending more TOADS. In doing so, they increase their chances of winning, and at the same time create a prize pool key in rewarding other potential investors wanting to put their money in DigiToads.</p>
<p>Deflationary Economics</p>
<p>Memecoins combine a series of ways to sustain their existence for a long time. DigiToads has a thought-out plan that combines interactive gaming and prize pools to keep people invested in TOADS. So far, the strategy has enabled a pre-funding revenue of about $4.25 million. Indeed, as the token price continues to grow, it will need other strategies to keep up with the competition, and that is where deflationary tokenomics comes in.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The economy of DigiToads works to limit the supply of TOADS over time to make them scarce, hence more valuable. So far, at the presale price of $0.036, TOADS&rsquo; early adopters are up by over 170%. This strategy means that early participants who went in at a low price point have the potential to reap enormous benefits when the coin becomes a big hit as it gains traction. A noteworthy aspect is the massive discounts that set the entry price even lower.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Financial Sound Model</p>
<p>Some scary bits of the crypto world unfolded in 2022. Notable names in the crypto ecosystem experienced turbulent periods that posed a danger to their existence. Such events are likely in the financial markets and are more common due to outside factors beyond the control of crypto platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the DigiToads ecosystem has been designed to help prevent such catastrophes. The treasury oversees every element of the coin. It works by looking at viable investments to pursue by maintaining a working liquidity pool. The pool benefits from multiple stakes from play to earn and a percentage of the profits derived by the sale of TOADS. &nbsp;</p>
<p>While the model seems normal by crypto standards, it takes motivation from the remarkable presale DigiToads has had so far. The quick adoption of TOADS by the public and crypto fanatics is enough confidence that the treasury will step in whenever required.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>The Dynamic Crypto Landscape</p>
<p>DigiToads launch comes amidst a multitude of contentions trying to take the attention of investors seeking to take positions in the bustling crypto market. However, in 2023, DigiToads is at the top of other newer coins vying for attention. Its multi-use case, that is, existing as a utility coin that will power the future internet&ndash;web3&ndash;and the ability to appeal as a meme-coin is what makes it a strong contender.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pure meme coins depend on FOMO to have credibility in the markets. While this model is impressive, it often loses steam after a while. DigiToads can ride on this too while clinging to its NFT staking features, play-to-earn, and its initiatives towards the environment to have a stronger position to take on future challenges that threaten the crypto market.</p>
<p>Bottom Line</p>
<p>Meme coins have existed for a while, and their popularity as memes has been a root for their rise. The multi-case for DigiToads makes it ripe for investors, as it provides the best of both. The current pre-sale that is ongoing makes it a must-have because of prizes, heavy discounts, and the potential returns once the coin fully launches and the price surges.</p>
<p>For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies evolve daily, owing to the rapid transformation of the digital space. As Tokens emerge, some do so with exciting features for the modern world. At the heart of these transformations is DigiToads&ndash;a platform that is set to revolutionize how people interact with meme coins. The stake-to-earn feature and play-to-earn are all standouts of DigiToads, which will provide opportunities for investors as the platform takes new steps towards its launch.</p>
<p>Step Into the World of TOADS</p>
<p>The core of the coin is the new web3 which promises an immersive online experience. Indeed, DigiToads enables interactions in the web-3 using its native coin TOADS. The coin is critical to NFT staking, and the P2E feature is set to become central to DigiToads' growth. Users will collect more NFTs in the metaverse, nature them in interactive gaming, and finally use them to battle other players within the DigiToads ecosystem for more prizes.</p>
<p>While in the competitive state of gaming, NFT owners will have the opportunity to maximize their character&rsquo;s strengths by spending more TOADS. In doing so, they increase their chances of winning, and at the same time create a prize pool key in rewarding other potential investors wanting to put their money in DigiToads.</p>
<p>Deflationary Economics</p>
<p>Memecoins combine a series of ways to sustain their existence for a long time. DigiToads has a thought-out plan that combines interactive gaming and prize pools to keep people invested in TOADS. So far, the strategy has enabled a pre-funding revenue of about $4.25 million. Indeed, as the token price continues to grow, it will need other strategies to keep up with the competition, and that is where deflationary tokenomics comes in.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The economy of DigiToads works to limit the supply of TOADS over time to make them scarce, hence more valuable. So far, at the presale price of $0.036, TOADS&rsquo; early adopters are up by over 170%. This strategy means that early participants who went in at a low price point have the potential to reap enormous benefits when the coin becomes a big hit as it gains traction. A noteworthy aspect is the massive discounts that set the entry price even lower.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Financial Sound Model</p>
<p>Some scary bits of the crypto world unfolded in 2022. Notable names in the crypto ecosystem experienced turbulent periods that posed a danger to their existence. Such events are likely in the financial markets and are more common due to outside factors beyond the control of crypto platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the DigiToads ecosystem has been designed to help prevent such catastrophes. The treasury oversees every element of the coin. It works by looking at viable investments to pursue by maintaining a working liquidity pool. The pool benefits from multiple stakes from play to earn and a percentage of the profits derived by the sale of TOADS. &nbsp;</p>
<p>While the model seems normal by crypto standards, it takes motivation from the remarkable presale DigiToads has had so far. The quick adoption of TOADS by the public and crypto fanatics is enough confidence that the treasury will step in whenever required.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>The Dynamic Crypto Landscape</p>
<p>DigiToads launch comes amidst a multitude of contentions trying to take the attention of investors seeking to take positions in the bustling crypto market. However, in 2023, DigiToads is at the top of other newer coins vying for attention. Its multi-use case, that is, existing as a utility coin that will power the future internet&ndash;web3&ndash;and the ability to appeal as a meme-coin is what makes it a strong contender.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pure meme coins depend on FOMO to have credibility in the markets. While this model is impressive, it often loses steam after a while. DigiToads can ride on this too while clinging to its NFT staking features, play-to-earn, and its initiatives towards the environment to have a stronger position to take on future challenges that threaten the crypto market.</p>
<p>Bottom Line</p>
<p>Meme coins have existed for a while, and their popularity as memes has been a root for their rise. The multi-case for DigiToads makes it ripe for investors, as it provides the best of both. The current pre-sale that is ongoing makes it a must-have because of prizes, heavy discounts, and the potential returns once the coin fully launches and the price surges.</p>
<p>For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[InQubeta Set To Revolutionize Investment For AI Start-ups]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/inqubeta-set-to-revolutionize-investment-for-ai-start-ups</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-614.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-614.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-614.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/inqubeta-set-to-revolutionize-investment-for-ai-start-ups</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Artificial intelligence (AI) start-ups emerge as the catalysts of change in the fast-growing world of technology. Where innovation is leading the global economy, artificial intelligence (AI) startups emerge as the catalysts of change. However, the path to success for these budding enterprises is often challenging, particularly when securing the necessary funding to fuel their growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recognizing this critical need, a groundbreaking initiative called InQubeta (QUBE) has arrived on the scene, poised to revolutionize investment for AI start-ups and redefine the landscape of technological advancement.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a DeFi crypto, InQubeta proposes unique value with a cutting-edge investment strategy to bridge the gap between visionary AI start-ups and eager investors seeking the next big breakthrough. While experts have estimated the global Al market size to hit $1,6 billion by 2030, many savvy investors are already joining the QUBE presale as they consider the coin the best crypto to invest in.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let's discover how InQubeta seeks to revolutionize investment for Al startups.</p>
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) Can Become The Major Catalyst For The Emerging AI Start-ups Growth</p>
<p>InQubeta is a new crypto project with much attention from investors and AI startups. While built on the ERC20 Ethereum blockchain, the InQubeta platform allows investors to gain unprecedented access to diverse AI startups, each presenting an opportunity to be at the forefront of technological disruption.</p>
<p>QUBE is the world's first cryptocurrency that seeks to revolutionize investment for Al start-ups. As such, the platform uses the concept of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) to link investors and Al startups through the NFT marketplace. While investors search through the NFT marketplace for the best NFTs to buy, startups can create and list NFTs representing various rewards and or equity in their company. The NFTs create mutual benefits to help startups raise funds and offer a unique and lucrative opportunity for investors simultaneously.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its fractional investment opportunity, InQubeta could be the best crypto to invest in 2023 as it allows investors to own a share of any AI startup within the ecosystem. Investors can purchase the NFTs they choose with the ERC20 QUBE token, the in-house currency. This is to ensure&nbsp; seamless, secure, and transparent transactions in the InQubeta ecosystem. With the opportunities and growth trajectory of AI technology, InQubeta could be the best crypto for beginners and experts who want to invest in the future of AI start-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) Thrilled Investors With Exceptional Opportunities&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aside from its innovative investment strategy, InQubeta also allows investors to earn residual income. By joining the InQubeta staking pool, investors can leverage DeFi crypto to generate a sustainable income flow. 5% of the buy and sell tax generated from transactions is sent to the reward pool to form a reward for investors in the staking pool.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the adoption of deflationary traits, QUBE is seen among investors as a promising crypto investment. This is tied to the reason that the platform pushes 2% of the buy and sell tax to the burn wallet to create a scarcity of QUBE tokens with the hope of increasing its value over time.</p>
<p>With the ERC20 QUBE token, InQubeta allows for an inclusive governance system that supports an efficient, transparent, decentralized authority in the InQubeta ecosystem. With this, QUBE can be seen as the best crypto for beginners and experienced investors alike, as every token holder can contribute their voice to the platform's growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>As the world witnesses the rapid advancement of AI technology, InQubeta stands poised to make a profound impact. By revolutionizing the investment landscape for AI start-ups, QUBE offers a gateway to a future where disruptive ideas become transformative realities. Of course, with the estimation of a $1.6 billion AI market size, QUBE stands as a crypto that can generate massive revenue for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While currently on its presale, investors can purchase QUBE tokens at an affordable rate and gain access to the NFT marketplace to browse for the best NTFS to buy. While InQubeta catalyzes AI start-ups' growth, join investors now to make the change. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Join InQubeta Communities</p>
<p>Keywords: InQubeta, QUBE, DeFi crypto, best crypto to invest in, ERC20, best NFTs, credible crypto, best crypto for beginners</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Artificial intelligence (AI) start-ups emerge as the catalysts of change in the fast-growing world of technology. Where innovation is leading the global economy, artificial intelligence (AI) startups emerge as the catalysts of change. However, the path to success for these budding enterprises is often challenging, particularly when securing the necessary funding to fuel their growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recognizing this critical need, a groundbreaking initiative called InQubeta (QUBE) has arrived on the scene, poised to revolutionize investment for AI start-ups and redefine the landscape of technological advancement.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a DeFi crypto, InQubeta proposes unique value with a cutting-edge investment strategy to bridge the gap between visionary AI start-ups and eager investors seeking the next big breakthrough. While experts have estimated the global Al market size to hit $1,6 billion by 2030, many savvy investors are already joining the QUBE presale as they consider the coin the best crypto to invest in.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let's discover how InQubeta seeks to revolutionize investment for Al startups.</p>
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) Can Become The Major Catalyst For The Emerging AI Start-ups Growth</p>
<p>InQubeta is a new crypto project with much attention from investors and AI startups. While built on the ERC20 Ethereum blockchain, the InQubeta platform allows investors to gain unprecedented access to diverse AI startups, each presenting an opportunity to be at the forefront of technological disruption.</p>
<p>QUBE is the world's first cryptocurrency that seeks to revolutionize investment for Al start-ups. As such, the platform uses the concept of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) to link investors and Al startups through the NFT marketplace. While investors search through the NFT marketplace for the best NFTs to buy, startups can create and list NFTs representing various rewards and or equity in their company. The NFTs create mutual benefits to help startups raise funds and offer a unique and lucrative opportunity for investors simultaneously.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its fractional investment opportunity, InQubeta could be the best crypto to invest in 2023 as it allows investors to own a share of any AI startup within the ecosystem. Investors can purchase the NFTs they choose with the ERC20 QUBE token, the in-house currency. This is to ensure&nbsp; seamless, secure, and transparent transactions in the InQubeta ecosystem. With the opportunities and growth trajectory of AI technology, InQubeta could be the best crypto for beginners and experts who want to invest in the future of AI start-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) Thrilled Investors With Exceptional Opportunities&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aside from its innovative investment strategy, InQubeta also allows investors to earn residual income. By joining the InQubeta staking pool, investors can leverage DeFi crypto to generate a sustainable income flow. 5% of the buy and sell tax generated from transactions is sent to the reward pool to form a reward for investors in the staking pool.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the adoption of deflationary traits, QUBE is seen among investors as a promising crypto investment. This is tied to the reason that the platform pushes 2% of the buy and sell tax to the burn wallet to create a scarcity of QUBE tokens with the hope of increasing its value over time.</p>
<p>With the ERC20 QUBE token, InQubeta allows for an inclusive governance system that supports an efficient, transparent, decentralized authority in the InQubeta ecosystem. With this, QUBE can be seen as the best crypto for beginners and experienced investors alike, as every token holder can contribute their voice to the platform's growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>As the world witnesses the rapid advancement of AI technology, InQubeta stands poised to make a profound impact. By revolutionizing the investment landscape for AI start-ups, QUBE offers a gateway to a future where disruptive ideas become transformative realities. Of course, with the estimation of a $1.6 billion AI market size, QUBE stands as a crypto that can generate massive revenue for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While currently on its presale, investors can purchase QUBE tokens at an affordable rate and gain access to the NFT marketplace to browse for the best NTFS to buy. While InQubeta catalyzes AI start-ups' growth, join investors now to make the change. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Join InQubeta Communities</p>
<p>Keywords: InQubeta, QUBE, DeFi crypto, best crypto to invest in, ERC20, best NFTs, credible crypto, best crypto for beginners</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Shiba Inu and Tradecurve journey to $1B market cap a closer look]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/shiba-inu-and-tradecurve-journey-to-1b-market-cap-a-closer-look</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-610.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-610.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-610.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/shiba-inu-and-tradecurve-journey-to-1b-market-cap-a-closer-look</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the significant meme token, has been making waves in the market since its launch, with its market cap going from $1M to $1B in only 279 days. However, as this rapid growth subsequently fell, one project currently in Stage 2 of its presale - Tradecurve (TCRV) could replicate this movement as it brings innovation, long-term growth potential and solves many problems the current online trading industry faces. Today, we will look at both of these projects and see how they compare.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) - incredible $1B market cap journey</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) was first released in August 2020. Within a year of its introduction, Shiba Inu had a market valuation of $1B. Amazingly, Shiba Inu grew from a market valuation of $1B in just 279 days. Shiba Inu became a well-known topic of conversation during this time as many notable celebrities, such as Ice-T and Antonio Brown, started backing this project. Notably, Shiba Inu outperformed Dogecoin (DOGE) in popularity and received wide acclaim in the second half of 2021.</p>
<p>As a result, the Shiba Inu community is still strong to this day. Currently, Shiba Inu has a value of $0.000008442 with a market cap of $4.9B, which is a decrease of 2.18% in the last day alone. Shiba Inu looks to have a bright future as many experts predict that its community will soon be the key to Shiba Inu jumping to $0.00001.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV) - what&rsquo;s in store for its market cap growth?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve has become a crypto sensation in the last few weeks as its presale has attracted countless individuals in hopes of long-term gains. This project could transform into a fan-favorite trading platform for millions of traders worldwide. It will introduce the first-ever private trading environment offering all derivatives on a single account with no KYC checks or FIAT payments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Not only that, Tradecurve will stand out as one of the few trading platforms that allows cryptocurrency to be used as collateral and for deposits. Users can create an account using their email, connect a crypto wallet to the account, and make one deposit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve will also offer high leverage starting at 500:1, automated trading &amp; artificial intelligence (AI) bots, the possibility to enroll in a metaverse trading academy, and more.</p>
<p></p>
<p>At the core of this platform and its expansive ecosystem will lie its utility token, TCRV, which will give holders access to various VIP statuses, discounts on subscription fees, passive income via staking, and governance voting rights. In Stage 2 of its presale, one TCRV currently has a value of only $0.012.</p>
<p>According to an IMARC impactful insights report, the value of the world foreign currency market was $753.2B in 2022. If Tradecurve taps into just 1% of this rising market, it could generate millions causing its market cap to grow. Currently, the Tradecurve market cap sits at $21.6M as there is a 1.8B TCRV token supply. This market cap could reach $1B fast as experts are bullish about this project, with some claiming it could see a value rise of 50x during its presale and 100x after its launch and subsequent Tier-1 CEX listing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since the market cap is so low, Tradecurve has all the potential to skyrocket after its launch and replicate the movement of Shiba Inu, with its market cap growing to $1B within one year or even sooner.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about the Tradecurve presale:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the significant meme token, has been making waves in the market since its launch, with its market cap going from $1M to $1B in only 279 days. However, as this rapid growth subsequently fell, one project currently in Stage 2 of its presale - Tradecurve (TCRV) could replicate this movement as it brings innovation, long-term growth potential and solves many problems the current online trading industry faces. Today, we will look at both of these projects and see how they compare.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) - incredible $1B market cap journey</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) was first released in August 2020. Within a year of its introduction, Shiba Inu had a market valuation of $1B. Amazingly, Shiba Inu grew from a market valuation of $1B in just 279 days. Shiba Inu became a well-known topic of conversation during this time as many notable celebrities, such as Ice-T and Antonio Brown, started backing this project. Notably, Shiba Inu outperformed Dogecoin (DOGE) in popularity and received wide acclaim in the second half of 2021.</p>
<p>As a result, the Shiba Inu community is still strong to this day. Currently, Shiba Inu has a value of $0.000008442 with a market cap of $4.9B, which is a decrease of 2.18% in the last day alone. Shiba Inu looks to have a bright future as many experts predict that its community will soon be the key to Shiba Inu jumping to $0.00001.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV) - what&rsquo;s in store for its market cap growth?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve has become a crypto sensation in the last few weeks as its presale has attracted countless individuals in hopes of long-term gains. This project could transform into a fan-favorite trading platform for millions of traders worldwide. It will introduce the first-ever private trading environment offering all derivatives on a single account with no KYC checks or FIAT payments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Not only that, Tradecurve will stand out as one of the few trading platforms that allows cryptocurrency to be used as collateral and for deposits. Users can create an account using their email, connect a crypto wallet to the account, and make one deposit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve will also offer high leverage starting at 500:1, automated trading &amp; artificial intelligence (AI) bots, the possibility to enroll in a metaverse trading academy, and more.</p>
<p></p>
<p>At the core of this platform and its expansive ecosystem will lie its utility token, TCRV, which will give holders access to various VIP statuses, discounts on subscription fees, passive income via staking, and governance voting rights. In Stage 2 of its presale, one TCRV currently has a value of only $0.012.</p>
<p>According to an IMARC impactful insights report, the value of the world foreign currency market was $753.2B in 2022. If Tradecurve taps into just 1% of this rising market, it could generate millions causing its market cap to grow. Currently, the Tradecurve market cap sits at $21.6M as there is a 1.8B TCRV token supply. This market cap could reach $1B fast as experts are bullish about this project, with some claiming it could see a value rise of 50x during its presale and 100x after its launch and subsequent Tier-1 CEX listing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since the market cap is so low, Tradecurve has all the potential to skyrocket after its launch and replicate the movement of Shiba Inu, with its market cap growing to $1B within one year or even sooner.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about the Tradecurve presale:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) Investors Rush to Grab Uwerx (WERX) Tokens in Current Market]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/uniswap-uni-and-aave-aave-investors-rush-to-grab-uwerx-werx-tokens-in-current-market</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-612.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-612.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-612.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/uniswap-uni-and-aave-aave-investors-rush-to-grab-uwerx-werx-tokens-in-current-market</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Uniwap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) have experienced an exponential increase since their launch. However, there has been a recent change in the crypto market so these coins are declining gradually. &nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result, Uniswap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) investors are seeking Uwerx (WERX) tokens; crypto analysts have predicted Uwerx (WERX) to increase above 8,000% by the end of 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Why are Uniswap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) investors shifting to Uwerx tokens? and What makes Uwerx so promising?</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) investors are seeking for alternative investments</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) has gained ground since its inception and has generated money for its investors. However, Uniswap (UNI) has been experiencing a sudden drop since June 2022, crashing more than $25,000 billion. This steep decline has caused investors to lose interest in Uniswap (UNI) and seek alternatives in stable crypto investments like Uwerx (WERX).</p>
<p>A Uniswap (UNI) token costs about $5.00, which is 80% lower than its peak price. Unfortunately, it may be difficult for Uniswap (UNI) to experience any notable increase for the rest of 2022 as a result of its continuous decrease.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aave (AAVE) investors aren&rsquo;t making an optimal profit</p>
<p>Aave (AAVE) runs on the Ethereum blockchain and is used to lend or borrow digital assets directly without any intermediary. Aave (AAVE) has had a good run since its creation. The Aave (AAVE) token is the 44th largest cryptocurrency, with a market value of over $1.09 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, although early Aave (AAVE) investors made a major profit initially, Aave (AAVE) is currently down more than 84% from $666, preventing investors from generating maximal profit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uwerx (WERX): A risk worth taking?</p>
<p>Uwerx is the first of its kind, blockchain based freelance platform that promises to revolutionise the freelance industry. It promises to provide lower fees and focuses on protecting intellectual property rights and transparency. It offers a fair and equal marketplace in comparison to Fiverr and Upwork. Uwerx will secure liquidity for 25 years after presale and has already received approval for its audit from the reputed InterFi Network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The WERX token is billed to see exponential growth in the coming years with predictions peaking at an astronomical $2 a in 2025. Investors have been presented with a unique opportunity and with the presale currently ongoing, it is a chance to get in on the ground floor of a project with a bright and prosperous future ahead. Currently, WERX is being sold for $0.0315 and the purchase bonus is at 20%, however this is likely to fall with the upcoming price increases.</p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uniwap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) have experienced an exponential increase since their launch. However, there has been a recent change in the crypto market so these coins are declining gradually. &nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result, Uniswap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) investors are seeking Uwerx (WERX) tokens; crypto analysts have predicted Uwerx (WERX) to increase above 8,000% by the end of 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Why are Uniswap (UNI) and Aave (AAVE) investors shifting to Uwerx tokens? and What makes Uwerx so promising?</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) investors are seeking for alternative investments</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) has gained ground since its inception and has generated money for its investors. However, Uniswap (UNI) has been experiencing a sudden drop since June 2022, crashing more than $25,000 billion. This steep decline has caused investors to lose interest in Uniswap (UNI) and seek alternatives in stable crypto investments like Uwerx (WERX).</p>
<p>A Uniswap (UNI) token costs about $5.00, which is 80% lower than its peak price. Unfortunately, it may be difficult for Uniswap (UNI) to experience any notable increase for the rest of 2022 as a result of its continuous decrease.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aave (AAVE) investors aren&rsquo;t making an optimal profit</p>
<p>Aave (AAVE) runs on the Ethereum blockchain and is used to lend or borrow digital assets directly without any intermediary. Aave (AAVE) has had a good run since its creation. The Aave (AAVE) token is the 44th largest cryptocurrency, with a market value of over $1.09 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, although early Aave (AAVE) investors made a major profit initially, Aave (AAVE) is currently down more than 84% from $666, preventing investors from generating maximal profit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uwerx (WERX): A risk worth taking?</p>
<p>Uwerx is the first of its kind, blockchain based freelance platform that promises to revolutionise the freelance industry. It promises to provide lower fees and focuses on protecting intellectual property rights and transparency. It offers a fair and equal marketplace in comparison to Fiverr and Upwork. Uwerx will secure liquidity for 25 years after presale and has already received approval for its audit from the reputed InterFi Network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The WERX token is billed to see exponential growth in the coming years with predictions peaking at an astronomical $2 a in 2025. Investors have been presented with a unique opportunity and with the presale currently ongoing, it is a chance to get in on the ground floor of a project with a bright and prosperous future ahead. Currently, WERX is being sold for $0.0315 and the purchase bonus is at 20%, however this is likely to fall with the upcoming price increases.</p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Currencies Set To Explode In Q3: Polkadot, Cosmos, Caged Beasts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/crypto-currencies-set-to-explode-in-q3-polkadot-cosmos-caged-beasts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-609.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-609.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-609.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/crypto-currencies-set-to-explode-in-q3-polkadot-cosmos-caged-beasts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The third quarter of this year holds great promise for the crypto market as several tokens are poised to make a significant impact. Among them, Polkadot, Cosmos, and Caged Beasts (BEASTS) stand out with their unique advantages and potential for explosive growth. Let's delve into the advantages of these tokens and why they deserve your attention.</p>
<p>Polkadot: Unleashing Interoperability and Scalability</p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT) stands out in the crypto market by offering unparalleled interoperability and scalability. Its core technology, known as the Polkadot Relay Chain, enables different blockchains to communicate and share information securely. This revolutionary feature allows for seamless interaction between chains, fostering collaboration and enabling the transfer of assets and data across various networks. With Polkadot's interoperability, developers can build decentralized applications that leverage the strengths of multiple blockchains, leading to enhanced functionality and efficiency. Additionally, Polkadot's scalable architecture ensures that as the network grows, it can handle increased transaction volumes without compromising performance.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Cosmos: Empowering A Connected Blockchain Ecosystem</p>
<p>Cosmos (ATOM) takes a unique approach to blockchain by creating an interconnected ecosystem. It achieves this through the Cosmos Hub, a central hub that connects multiple independent blockchains, known as zones, through the Inter-Blockchain Communication (IBC) protocol. This innovative solution allows for seamless communication and interoperability between different blockchains, enabling the transfer of assets and data across the network. Cosmos' modular architecture and developer-friendly tools make it easy for developers to create and customize their own blockchains within the ecosystem. By empowering a connected blockchain ecosystem, Cosmos opens up new possibilities for cross-chain applications, decentralized finance (DeFi), and decentralized exchanges (DEXs), driving innovation and fostering collaboration among blockchain projects.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Caged Beasts: Embracing Community, Transparency, And Growth</p>
<p>Caged Beasts (BEASTS) stands out in the meme coin realm with its strong focus on community, transparency, and growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>This token prioritizes engaging its community members through various programs and initiatives. Competitions, bonuses, events, and voting opportunities are just some of the avenues that Caged Beasts provides for its community to participate and earn rewards. By fostering an immersive experience, Caged Beasts aims to create an active and vibrant community that shares a common interest in the token's success.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Transparency is another key aspect of Caged Beasts, as the project team provides access to observe locked-up funds, ensuring trust and confidence among investors. Furthermore, Caged Beasts has a clear growth strategy in place, allocating a significant portion of its funds to a marketing wallet. This allocation is aimed at expanding the coin's reach, driving adoption, and establishing a strong presence in the market. With its community-centric approach, transparency, and growth-oriented mindset, Caged Beasts seeks to differentiate itself and offer a compelling investment opportunity in the meme coin space.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>As we enter the third quarter of the year, the crypto market is primed for explosive growth, and tokens like Polkadot, Cosmos, and Caged Beasts are leading the charge. Polkadot's interoperability, Cosmos' connected blockchain ecosystem, and Caged Beasts' community-centric approach make them compelling choices for investors and developers alike. By leveraging their unique advantages, these tokens are set to redefine the crypto landscape and open up new possibilities for innovation and financial opportunities. Keep a close eye on these tokens as they aim to make waves and shape the future of the crypto world in the coming months.</p>
<p>For More On Caged BeastsWebsite: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The third quarter of this year holds great promise for the crypto market as several tokens are poised to make a significant impact. Among them, Polkadot, Cosmos, and Caged Beasts (BEASTS) stand out with their unique advantages and potential for explosive growth. Let's delve into the advantages of these tokens and why they deserve your attention.</p>
<p>Polkadot: Unleashing Interoperability and Scalability</p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT) stands out in the crypto market by offering unparalleled interoperability and scalability. Its core technology, known as the Polkadot Relay Chain, enables different blockchains to communicate and share information securely. This revolutionary feature allows for seamless interaction between chains, fostering collaboration and enabling the transfer of assets and data across various networks. With Polkadot's interoperability, developers can build decentralized applications that leverage the strengths of multiple blockchains, leading to enhanced functionality and efficiency. Additionally, Polkadot's scalable architecture ensures that as the network grows, it can handle increased transaction volumes without compromising performance.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Cosmos: Empowering A Connected Blockchain Ecosystem</p>
<p>Cosmos (ATOM) takes a unique approach to blockchain by creating an interconnected ecosystem. It achieves this through the Cosmos Hub, a central hub that connects multiple independent blockchains, known as zones, through the Inter-Blockchain Communication (IBC) protocol. This innovative solution allows for seamless communication and interoperability between different blockchains, enabling the transfer of assets and data across the network. Cosmos' modular architecture and developer-friendly tools make it easy for developers to create and customize their own blockchains within the ecosystem. By empowering a connected blockchain ecosystem, Cosmos opens up new possibilities for cross-chain applications, decentralized finance (DeFi), and decentralized exchanges (DEXs), driving innovation and fostering collaboration among blockchain projects.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Caged Beasts: Embracing Community, Transparency, And Growth</p>
<p>Caged Beasts (BEASTS) stands out in the meme coin realm with its strong focus on community, transparency, and growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>This token prioritizes engaging its community members through various programs and initiatives. Competitions, bonuses, events, and voting opportunities are just some of the avenues that Caged Beasts provides for its community to participate and earn rewards. By fostering an immersive experience, Caged Beasts aims to create an active and vibrant community that shares a common interest in the token's success.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Transparency is another key aspect of Caged Beasts, as the project team provides access to observe locked-up funds, ensuring trust and confidence among investors. Furthermore, Caged Beasts has a clear growth strategy in place, allocating a significant portion of its funds to a marketing wallet. This allocation is aimed at expanding the coin's reach, driving adoption, and establishing a strong presence in the market. With its community-centric approach, transparency, and growth-oriented mindset, Caged Beasts seeks to differentiate itself and offer a compelling investment opportunity in the meme coin space.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>As we enter the third quarter of the year, the crypto market is primed for explosive growth, and tokens like Polkadot, Cosmos, and Caged Beasts are leading the charge. Polkadot's interoperability, Cosmos' connected blockchain ecosystem, and Caged Beasts' community-centric approach make them compelling choices for investors and developers alike. By leveraging their unique advantages, these tokens are set to redefine the crypto landscape and open up new possibilities for innovation and financial opportunities. Keep a close eye on these tokens as they aim to make waves and shape the future of the crypto world in the coming months.</p>
<p>For More On Caged BeastsWebsite: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sparklo (SPRK) Brings New Innovation To Crypto Network As Neo (NEO) And Conflux (CFX) Witnesses Price Changes]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sparklo-sprk-brings-new-innovation-to-crypto-network-as-neo-neo-and-conflux-cfx-witnesses-price-changes</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-611.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-611.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-611.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sparklo-sprk-brings-new-innovation-to-crypto-network-as-neo-neo-and-conflux-cfx-witnesses-price-changes</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Amid the evolving cryptocurrency landscape, Sparklo stands out as a promising market entrant with its innovative concept and strong use case. Unlike Neo(NEO) and Conflux (CFX)), which have faced recent challenges, Sparklo is gaining recognition as an exciting contender ready to make significant strides in the dynamic cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Sparklo (SPRK): Revolutionizing blockchain investments through premium metals&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sparklo sets itself apart as an innovative investment platform on a mission to reshape the way traders interact with esteemed metals like gold, silver and platinum. Opening up exciting investment opportunities. By utilizing advanced blockchain technology, Sparklo creates a user-friendly and efficient trading environment specifically designed for precious metals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With an incredibly low presale price of just $0.026, Sparklo presents a promising investment opportunity. Investors can engage in fractionalized NFT trading, where each token is intrinsically backed by valuable metals.</p>
<p>Investors are drawn to Sparklo's transparent network as its smart contract undergoes audits conducted by InterFi. With projected growth potential estimated to be a remarkable 4,000 times, Sparklo has the potential to become one of the top 100 cryptocurrencies. This prospect magnetizes both crypto enthusiasts and investors, generating significant interest in the platform.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Conflux (CFX) recent partnerships push its price up slightly&nbsp;</p>
<p>New strategic alliances with TaskOn and Port3 Network have increased Conflux's (CFX) network's potential. Furthermore, Conflux (CFX) is enhancing its DeFi functionality through upcoming projects such as vSwap, Rime Finance, Mold Finance and Flux Fire.</p>
<p>These developments have garnered positive feedback from the Conflux community and have had a favorable impact on the Conflux (CFX) price. Currently trading at $0.29, the token has experienced a 1.91% increase in the last 24 hours, accompanied by a 22.31% rise in trading volume since yesterday. Conflux (CFX) is currently at a support level of $0.25; if it breaks this level, it could result in a price decline to $0.14.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neo (NEO) price pushed up as the network recently announced its support for AI&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neo (NEO) price experienced an upward drift on Monday, rising to $9.72, surpassing the weekend low of $8.67. The reason behind this increase in a low-volume environment remains unclear. However, Neo's (NEO) involvement in the rapidly growing field of artificial intelligence (AI) may have contributed to the price rise. Neo (NEO) recently announced the winners of its NeoChat ChatGPT launch competition, highlighting its investments in AI.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to CoinMarketCap, Neo (NEO) trading volume in the past 24 hours exceeded $87 million, slightly above the 7-day moving average. Despite this jump, Neo (NEO) price remains significantly lower than its year-to-date high of $15.68. Holders of Neo (NEO) are now recognizing the promising opportunities Sparklo presents.</p>
<p>Find out about the Sparklo presale using the links below</p>
<ul>
<li>Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</li>
<li>Website: https://sparklo.finance</li>
<li>Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</li>
<li>Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</li>
</ul>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the evolving cryptocurrency landscape, Sparklo stands out as a promising market entrant with its innovative concept and strong use case. Unlike Neo(NEO) and Conflux (CFX)), which have faced recent challenges, Sparklo is gaining recognition as an exciting contender ready to make significant strides in the dynamic cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Sparklo (SPRK): Revolutionizing blockchain investments through premium metals&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sparklo sets itself apart as an innovative investment platform on a mission to reshape the way traders interact with esteemed metals like gold, silver and platinum. Opening up exciting investment opportunities. By utilizing advanced blockchain technology, Sparklo creates a user-friendly and efficient trading environment specifically designed for precious metals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With an incredibly low presale price of just $0.026, Sparklo presents a promising investment opportunity. Investors can engage in fractionalized NFT trading, where each token is intrinsically backed by valuable metals.</p>
<p>Investors are drawn to Sparklo's transparent network as its smart contract undergoes audits conducted by InterFi. With projected growth potential estimated to be a remarkable 4,000 times, Sparklo has the potential to become one of the top 100 cryptocurrencies. This prospect magnetizes both crypto enthusiasts and investors, generating significant interest in the platform.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Conflux (CFX) recent partnerships push its price up slightly&nbsp;</p>
<p>New strategic alliances with TaskOn and Port3 Network have increased Conflux's (CFX) network's potential. Furthermore, Conflux (CFX) is enhancing its DeFi functionality through upcoming projects such as vSwap, Rime Finance, Mold Finance and Flux Fire.</p>
<p>These developments have garnered positive feedback from the Conflux community and have had a favorable impact on the Conflux (CFX) price. Currently trading at $0.29, the token has experienced a 1.91% increase in the last 24 hours, accompanied by a 22.31% rise in trading volume since yesterday. Conflux (CFX) is currently at a support level of $0.25; if it breaks this level, it could result in a price decline to $0.14.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neo (NEO) price pushed up as the network recently announced its support for AI&nbsp;</p>
<p>Neo (NEO) price experienced an upward drift on Monday, rising to $9.72, surpassing the weekend low of $8.67. The reason behind this increase in a low-volume environment remains unclear. However, Neo's (NEO) involvement in the rapidly growing field of artificial intelligence (AI) may have contributed to the price rise. Neo (NEO) recently announced the winners of its NeoChat ChatGPT launch competition, highlighting its investments in AI.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to CoinMarketCap, Neo (NEO) trading volume in the past 24 hours exceeded $87 million, slightly above the 7-day moving average. Despite this jump, Neo (NEO) price remains significantly lower than its year-to-date high of $15.68. Holders of Neo (NEO) are now recognizing the promising opportunities Sparklo presents.</p>
<p>Find out about the Sparklo presale using the links below</p>
<ul>
<li>Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</li>
<li>Website: https://sparklo.finance</li>
<li>Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</li>
<li>Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</li>
</ul>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Top Crypto Projects in 2023: Exploring P2E Potential of Big Eyes Coin, Decentraland, and The Sandbox]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/top-crypto-projects-in-2023-exploring-p2e-potential-of-big-eyes-coin-decentraland-and-the-sandbox</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-608.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-608.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-608.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/top-crypto-projects-in-2023-exploring-p2e-potential-of-big-eyes-coin-decentraland-and-the-sandbox</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As the popularity of cryptocurrencies continues to soar, the world of online gaming has embraced the trend, giving rise to an exciting genre known as crypto casinos. These platforms offer a unique blend of gambling and blockchain technology, allowing users to play and earn digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this comparative analysis, we delve into some of the top-rated play-to-earn crypto projects: Big Eyes Coin&rsquo;s (BIG) upcoming casino, Decentraland, and The Sandbox.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Join us as we explore the safety measures implemented by these platforms, ensuring a secure and enjoyable gaming experience for meme coin lovers and investors seeking meme coins with added utility.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin's Casino &mdash; Unleashing its Power as a Top-Rated P2E Crypto Project</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin, inspired by popular meme coins like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, has set its sights on revolutionizing the crypto gaming landscape. The forthcoming casino promises an immersive play-to-earn (P2E) experience, allowing users to both enjoy games and earn valuable tokens. Through decentralized governance and smart contract technology, Big Eyes Coin ensures transparency and fairness in its gaming ecosystem. Players will have access to over 4,000 P2E games when buying Big Eyes Coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By prioritizing security and user empowerment, Big Eyes Coin's casino aims to become a leading player in the crypto gaming industry.</p>
<p>Decentraland - Building a Virtual Metaverse</p>
<p>Decentraland, one of the pioneers in the crypto gaming space, has captured the imagination of users worldwide with its virtual metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Powered by blockchain technology, Decentraland offers a user-owned, decentralized virtual world where players can explore, interact, and monetize their creations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In terms of security, Decentraland implements robust cryptographic protocols to protect user identities and assets. Additionally, smart contracts govern the platform, ensuring the integrity of in-game transactions and preventing fraud. With a strong emphasis on decentralization and security, Decentraland has established itself as a prominent player in the crypto-gaming realm.</p>
<p></p>
<p>The Sandbox - Empowering Creators in a Virtual Universe</p>
<p>The Sandbox introduces a unique blend of gaming and creativity, allowing users to build, own, and monetize their virtual experiences within its blockchain-based metaverse. To ensure the security of user assets, The Sandbox employs non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and blockchain technology, providing users with verifiable ownership and protection against unauthorized modifications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform also features a robust marketplace for trading virtual assets, where security measures are in place to prevent fraudulent transactions. By empowering creators and prioritizing security, The Sandbox has carved a niche for itself in the crypto gaming landscape.</p>
<p>In Conclusion&hellip;</p>
<p>In this comparative analysis of crypto gaming platforms, we have explored the security features of some of the top-rated play-to-earn crypto projects. Each platform exhibits a solid commitment to user safety and data protection, employing cutting-edge technologies such as blockchain, smart contracts, and encryption protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As meme coin lovers and investors seeking meme coins with utility, it is essential to choose a platform that prioritizes security while offering an engaging play-to-earn experience. Whether you prefer the P2E approach of Big Eyes Coin's casino, the immersive metaverse of Decentraland, or the creative freedom of The Sandbox, it is evident that the crypto gaming industry is evolving rapidly, providing users with exciting opportunities to participate in the digital revolution.</p>
<p>To learn more about Big Eyes Coin's presale and immerse yourself in the world of crypto gaming, visit our presale website and join the community today.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin (BIG)</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL</p>
<p>Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/BigEyesCoin/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/BigEyesCoin&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the popularity of cryptocurrencies continues to soar, the world of online gaming has embraced the trend, giving rise to an exciting genre known as crypto casinos. These platforms offer a unique blend of gambling and blockchain technology, allowing users to play and earn digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this comparative analysis, we delve into some of the top-rated play-to-earn crypto projects: Big Eyes Coin&rsquo;s (BIG) upcoming casino, Decentraland, and The Sandbox.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Join us as we explore the safety measures implemented by these platforms, ensuring a secure and enjoyable gaming experience for meme coin lovers and investors seeking meme coins with added utility.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin's Casino &mdash; Unleashing its Power as a Top-Rated P2E Crypto Project</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin, inspired by popular meme coins like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, has set its sights on revolutionizing the crypto gaming landscape. The forthcoming casino promises an immersive play-to-earn (P2E) experience, allowing users to both enjoy games and earn valuable tokens. Through decentralized governance and smart contract technology, Big Eyes Coin ensures transparency and fairness in its gaming ecosystem. Players will have access to over 4,000 P2E games when buying Big Eyes Coin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By prioritizing security and user empowerment, Big Eyes Coin's casino aims to become a leading player in the crypto gaming industry.</p>
<p>Decentraland - Building a Virtual Metaverse</p>
<p>Decentraland, one of the pioneers in the crypto gaming space, has captured the imagination of users worldwide with its virtual metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Powered by blockchain technology, Decentraland offers a user-owned, decentralized virtual world where players can explore, interact, and monetize their creations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In terms of security, Decentraland implements robust cryptographic protocols to protect user identities and assets. Additionally, smart contracts govern the platform, ensuring the integrity of in-game transactions and preventing fraud. With a strong emphasis on decentralization and security, Decentraland has established itself as a prominent player in the crypto-gaming realm.</p>
<p></p>
<p>The Sandbox - Empowering Creators in a Virtual Universe</p>
<p>The Sandbox introduces a unique blend of gaming and creativity, allowing users to build, own, and monetize their virtual experiences within its blockchain-based metaverse. To ensure the security of user assets, The Sandbox employs non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and blockchain technology, providing users with verifiable ownership and protection against unauthorized modifications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform also features a robust marketplace for trading virtual assets, where security measures are in place to prevent fraudulent transactions. By empowering creators and prioritizing security, The Sandbox has carved a niche for itself in the crypto gaming landscape.</p>
<p>In Conclusion&hellip;</p>
<p>In this comparative analysis of crypto gaming platforms, we have explored the security features of some of the top-rated play-to-earn crypto projects. Each platform exhibits a solid commitment to user safety and data protection, employing cutting-edge technologies such as blockchain, smart contracts, and encryption protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As meme coin lovers and investors seeking meme coins with utility, it is essential to choose a platform that prioritizes security while offering an engaging play-to-earn experience. Whether you prefer the P2E approach of Big Eyes Coin's casino, the immersive metaverse of Decentraland, or the creative freedom of The Sandbox, it is evident that the crypto gaming industry is evolving rapidly, providing users with exciting opportunities to participate in the digital revolution.</p>
<p>To learn more about Big Eyes Coin's presale and immerse yourself in the world of crypto gaming, visit our presale website and join the community today.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin (BIG)</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL</p>
<p>Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/BigEyesCoin/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/BigEyesCoin&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Senator Cynthia Lummis Pushes Back Against Bidens Crypto Tax]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/senator-cynthia-lummis-pushes-back-against-bidens-crypto-tax</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lummis-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lummis-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lummis-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 08:12:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/senator-cynthia-lummis-pushes-back-against-bidens-crypto-tax</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>US Senator Cynthia Lummis has pushed back against the Biden Administration&rsquo;s proposal to tax cryptocurrency miners, stating that the administration is picking &ldquo;winners and losers.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Bitcoin mining is a very polarizing subject in the United States of America and has drawn considerable ire from the Biden administration.&nbsp;</p>
A Harsh Tax Regime&nbsp;
<p>Bitcoin mining has often drawn harsh criticism from governments thanks to its high energy consumption. In the latest example, the Joe Biden administration has outlined plans to impose harsh taxes on Bitcoin mining. According to reports, the tax in question is called the Digital Asset Mining Energy Excise Tax (DAME). It was proposed by the administration in its budget for the fiscal year 2024. Under the proposal, cryptocurrency mining firms would have to pay a tax equal to 30% of the cost of electricity consumed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The tax would come into effect next year and be gradually phased in over a period of three years at a fixed rate of 10% per year until it reaches the targeted 30% by the end of 2026.&nbsp;</p>
Significant Pushback&nbsp;
<p>The proposal has been subject to furious pushback from prominent members of the cryptocurrency community, who have argued that the administration&rsquo;s priorities are misplaced. However, prominent faces from the crypto community are not the only ones critical of the proposal. Robert F. Kennedy Jr, United States presidential candidate, has also roundly criticized the bill, calling it a &ldquo;bad idea.&rdquo; According to recent statements, Kennedy has chosen to publicly align himself with the Bitcoin community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another prominent voice against the proposal is that of Senator Cynthia Lummis, who has been vocal in her criticism of the bill. Lummis first spoke against the bill at the Bitcoin 2023 conference, telling the audience in attendance that the tax would not happen. She later tweeted about the conference and reiterated her opposition to the proposal, arguing that she would not let the government kill the crypto industry with taxes and oppose the proposal in Congress.</p>

<p>&ldquo;America must welcome innovation, and digital assets are the future of financial innovation. A 30% tax hike on any specific industry is a blatant attempt by the administration to pick winners and losers. I will not let President Biden tax the digital asset industry out of existence.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Cryptocurrency regulation and taxation has become a significant talking point in the US budget. Apart from the proposed 30% tax on crypto mining activities, the Biden government has also stated that it wants to eliminate tax loopholes for wealthy crypto traders. President Biden&rsquo;s comments have understandably sparked confusion within crypto circles. However, experts believe that he referred to a dearth of wash trading rules, allowing traders to engage in tax-loss harvesting. If the proposal is passed, it could lead to miners moving to other jurisdictions and putting significant uncertainty over the crypto industry in the United States in the face of growing regulatory pressure.&nbsp;</p>
Responsible Innovation Act To Be Reintroduced&nbsp;
<p>Senator Lumis, along with Democratic Senator Gillibrand of New York, has stated that there are plans to reintroduce the Responsible Innovations Act with some amendments, such as adding in greater customer protections. The bill was originally introduced last year and takes a comprehensive approach to regulating the crypto industry in the United States of America.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lummis and Gillibrand are working with the House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick T. McHenry, R-N.C., and Maxine Waters, D-Calif, with the group working to break the bill into different committees and get it passed. Lummis stated at the Bitcoin 2023 conference,</p>

<p>&ldquo;What we&rsquo;re apt to see is for the House to move a stablecoin bill first, then you&rsquo;ll probably see the introduction of Lummis Gillibrand in the Senate, which will remain comprehensive.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>US Senator Cynthia Lummis has pushed back against the Biden Administration&rsquo;s proposal to tax cryptocurrency miners, stating that the administration is picking &ldquo;winners and losers.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Bitcoin mining is a very polarizing subject in the United States of America and has drawn considerable ire from the Biden administration.&nbsp;</p>
A Harsh Tax Regime&nbsp;
<p>Bitcoin mining has often drawn harsh criticism from governments thanks to its high energy consumption. In the latest example, the Joe Biden administration has outlined plans to impose harsh taxes on Bitcoin mining. According to reports, the tax in question is called the Digital Asset Mining Energy Excise Tax (DAME). It was proposed by the administration in its budget for the fiscal year 2024. Under the proposal, cryptocurrency mining firms would have to pay a tax equal to 30% of the cost of electricity consumed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The tax would come into effect next year and be gradually phased in over a period of three years at a fixed rate of 10% per year until it reaches the targeted 30% by the end of 2026.&nbsp;</p>
Significant Pushback&nbsp;
<p>The proposal has been subject to furious pushback from prominent members of the cryptocurrency community, who have argued that the administration&rsquo;s priorities are misplaced. However, prominent faces from the crypto community are not the only ones critical of the proposal. Robert F. Kennedy Jr, United States presidential candidate, has also roundly criticized the bill, calling it a &ldquo;bad idea.&rdquo; According to recent statements, Kennedy has chosen to publicly align himself with the Bitcoin community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another prominent voice against the proposal is that of Senator Cynthia Lummis, who has been vocal in her criticism of the bill. Lummis first spoke against the bill at the Bitcoin 2023 conference, telling the audience in attendance that the tax would not happen. She later tweeted about the conference and reiterated her opposition to the proposal, arguing that she would not let the government kill the crypto industry with taxes and oppose the proposal in Congress.</p>

<p>&ldquo;America must welcome innovation, and digital assets are the future of financial innovation. A 30% tax hike on any specific industry is a blatant attempt by the administration to pick winners and losers. I will not let President Biden tax the digital asset industry out of existence.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Cryptocurrency regulation and taxation has become a significant talking point in the US budget. Apart from the proposed 30% tax on crypto mining activities, the Biden government has also stated that it wants to eliminate tax loopholes for wealthy crypto traders. President Biden&rsquo;s comments have understandably sparked confusion within crypto circles. However, experts believe that he referred to a dearth of wash trading rules, allowing traders to engage in tax-loss harvesting. If the proposal is passed, it could lead to miners moving to other jurisdictions and putting significant uncertainty over the crypto industry in the United States in the face of growing regulatory pressure.&nbsp;</p>
Responsible Innovation Act To Be Reintroduced&nbsp;
<p>Senator Lumis, along with Democratic Senator Gillibrand of New York, has stated that there are plans to reintroduce the Responsible Innovations Act with some amendments, such as adding in greater customer protections. The bill was originally introduced last year and takes a comprehensive approach to regulating the crypto industry in the United States of America.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lummis and Gillibrand are working with the House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick T. McHenry, R-N.C., and Maxine Waters, D-Calif, with the group working to break the bill into different committees and get it passed. Lummis stated at the Bitcoin 2023 conference,</p>

<p>&ldquo;What we&rsquo;re apt to see is for the House to move a stablecoin bill first, then you&rsquo;ll probably see the introduction of Lummis Gillibrand in the Senate, which will remain comprehensive.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi Set to Launch Trading Service in Hong Kong]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/huobi-set-to-launch-trading-service-in-hong-kong</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1685121401jyWCm2b0F2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1685121401jyWCm2b0F2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1685121401jyWCm2b0F2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 19:20:47 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/huobi-set-to-launch-trading-service-in-hong-kong</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 26th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Huobi announced the launch of Huobi HK and stated that they will provide cryptocurrency trading services to users in HK. Huobi HK will play a significant role in driving Hong Kong towards becoming the global hub for Web3.</p><p>In the future, users will be able to buy, sell, and hold mainstream cryptocurrencies such as BTC and ETH, as well as other major cryptocurrencies listed on the independent index through Huobi HK. Huobi aims to deliver an excellent trading experience to Web3 users in Hong Kong.</p><p>Hong Kong has been gradually implementing crypto-friendly policies since last year and recently announced the introduction of "crypto regulations." The Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has also announced that more details regarding virtual asset trading regulations will come into light starting June 1st, and retail investors may be able to trade digital assets on licensed platforms as early as the second half of 2023.</p><p>As a cryptocurrency exchange platform with a decade-long history, Huobi is actively involved in the development and construction of Hong Kong's Web3 ecosystem. It is worth noting that during this year's Hong Kong Web3 Carnival, Huobi became a significant contributor to Hong Kong's first Web3 ecosystem fund. Additionally, Huobi is actively preparing to apply for a cryptocurrency trading license in Hong Kong. Huobi aims to open the Hong Kong market in a compliant and regulated manner that will accelerate the development of Hong Kong's Web3 ecosystem.</p><p>A representative from Huobi stated, "Regulation of Web3 in Hong Kong will contribute to the widespread adoption of cryptocurrencies on a global scale. Huobi will continue to collaborate with regulatory authorities in Hong Kong to support the development of a vibrant Web3 hub."</p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 26th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Huobi announced the launch of Huobi HK and stated that they will provide cryptocurrency trading services to users in HK. Huobi HK will play a significant role in driving Hong Kong towards becoming the global hub for Web3.</p><p>In the future, users will be able to buy, sell, and hold mainstream cryptocurrencies such as BTC and ETH, as well as other major cryptocurrencies listed on the independent index through Huobi HK. Huobi aims to deliver an excellent trading experience to Web3 users in Hong Kong.</p><p>Hong Kong has been gradually implementing crypto-friendly policies since last year and recently announced the introduction of "crypto regulations." The Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has also announced that more details regarding virtual asset trading regulations will come into light starting June 1st, and retail investors may be able to trade digital assets on licensed platforms as early as the second half of 2023.</p><p>As a cryptocurrency exchange platform with a decade-long history, Huobi is actively involved in the development and construction of Hong Kong's Web3 ecosystem. It is worth noting that during this year's Hong Kong Web3 Carnival, Huobi became a significant contributor to Hong Kong's first Web3 ecosystem fund. Additionally, Huobi is actively preparing to apply for a cryptocurrency trading license in Hong Kong. Huobi aims to open the Hong Kong market in a compliant and regulated manner that will accelerate the development of Hong Kong's Web3 ecosystem.</p><p>A representative from Huobi stated, "Regulation of Web3 in Hong Kong will contribute to the widespread adoption of cryptocurrencies on a global scale. Huobi will continue to collaborate with regulatory authorities in Hong Kong to support the development of a vibrant Web3 hub."</p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  26351 Bids Supportive - 27 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-26351-bids-supportive-27-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-26-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-26-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-26-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-26351-bids-supportive-27-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Remains Below 26763:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 27 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained in a relatively narrow range early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 26763.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 29850 to 25810.&nbsp; &nbsp;Decent technical support has recently emerged around the 26351 level, a downside price objective associated with recent selling pressure around the 28334.75 and 27647.82 levels.&nbsp; The recent move lower also represented a test of the 25882.35 area, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that intensified around the same levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25604.43 and 25124.80 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 26810, 27046, 27429, 27811, 28430, 29048, 29143, and 29813 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 27981, 28095, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels. Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26818.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26351.17.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Remains Below 26763:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 27 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained in a relatively narrow range early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 26763.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 29850 to 25810.&nbsp; &nbsp;Decent technical support has recently emerged around the 26351 level, a downside price objective associated with recent selling pressure around the 28334.75 and 27647.82 levels.&nbsp; The recent move lower also represented a test of the 25882.35 area, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that intensified around the same levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25604.43 and 25124.80 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 26810, 27046, 27429, 27811, 28430, 29048, 29143, and 29813 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 27981, 28095, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels. Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26818.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26351.17.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Dogecoin(DOGE) and Uwerx Look Promising for the Next Crypto Boom]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/dogecoindoge-and-uwerx-look-promising-for-the-next-crypto-boom</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-153601.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-153601.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-153601.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/dogecoindoge-and-uwerx-look-promising-for-the-next-crypto-boom</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s4">Dogecoin (DOGE) remains the torchbearer of all meme coins with certain fluctuations and downfalls. A strong community of supporters and influence from noteworthy personnel still keeps the crypto in the top 10. Dogecoin has been showing impressive performance, despite multiple setbacks.</p>
<p class="s4">And it continues to inch toward the $0.1 milestone within months, predicted to reach even the $1.0 mark in 2023. DOGE's achievement of such a price means excellent profits for traders and investors.</p>
<p class="s4">However, the market value now remains over $0.07, requiring a significant boost in the meme coin. Recent growth in capital and reduction of crypto market outflows will likely take a bullish turn soon. Therefore, an enormous increment in value is possible in the coming months.</p>
<p class="s4">The crypto keeps struggling around the $0.07 mark for about a month, dipping significantly initially. Yet, within weeks, it recovered a significant share of the lost market cap. And the daily transaction numbers reached an all-time high due to the near-bullish forecast of the market.</p>
<p class="s4">Meantime, the first-ever blockchain-supported freelancing platform, Uwerx, doesn't fall behind. Its native crypto, WERX, currently values a mere $0.0315 at the presales. But analysts recognized the potential, predicting an exponential price rise to reach as much as $0.3 by Q3 of 2023.</p>
<p class="s4">The ongoing presales have already entered the fourth stage, completing the first in 17 days and the second in 8 days. Freelancers, investors, and analysts look forward to Uwerx's mainstream success as the platform integrates some unique features for target users.</p>
<p class="s8">Why Does Uwerx Matter So Much?</p>
<p class="s4">Uwerx allows freelancers to earn a minimal 1% transaction fee, considerably lower than traditional platforms. Freelancers will receive payments directly to their WERX hubs, letting them interact with the crypto space. And it'll unveil a new door to crypto-related businesses.</p>
<p class="s4">An audit by InterFi Network and SolidProof already set the foundation of top-tier security. The platform already introduced a custom vault to lock up the tokens in the 25-year liquidity pool. So, all clients' and freelancers' assets and intellectual properties will have a steady backup for security.</p>
<p class="s4">There are advanced features like gamification and incentivization to avoid dull, monotonous, and tiresome work. It should keep the freelancers motivated and enthusiastic to take on new challenges. Analysts and investors also recognized these benefits, counting on the innovative blockchain system.</p>
<p class="s4">A lot is happening within Uwerx as many development tasks are underway to become accessible to the public. It'll start with the release of Uwerx's Alpha version on May 19, 2023, featuring the landing and signup pages. The team plans to continue releasing the next versions based on user feedback.</p>
<p class="s4">The much-hyped presales will end on July 31, 2023, and the Team Lock of tokens will happen before that. A recent Twitter poll revealed 82.8% of voters opted for immediately locking the tokens. And the Uwerx team is getting ready to announce the possible date following the scheduled Test Airdrop.</p>
<p class="s4">The listing of WERX is also gaining momentum as CoinSniper already recognized the token. Uniswap will likely introduce the crypto in its portfolio by August 01, 2023. Launching in centralized exchanges should let the platform initiate the renouncement of contract ownership, lessening tax worries.</p>
<p class="s4">The WERX presales exceeded expectations in every aspect, gaining much appreciation from the crypto space. And the demand keeps increasing as the forecast indicates exploding surges in price. The Uwerx team also understands the impulse, changing five token allocations as follows &ndash;</p>
 Presale: An increase to 57% from 45% to renew confidence.
 Founding Team: A reduction to 7% from 8% to prioritize user benefits.
 Partnership incentives: A reduction to 3% from 7.5% after reviewing new information.
 User performance incentives: A decrease to 6.5% from 15%.
 Joining incentives: An increase to 6.5% from 4.5% to attract more users.
<p class="s4">New investors/customers/users can achieve a 20% bonus on every purchase during the presales. It also sparked the popularity and checkups on this innovative, promising, and beneficial platform. Uwerx has already gained over 5,000 signups with over 1000 members in its Telegram community.</p>
<p class="s4">Grab your opportunity with Uwerx using either of the links mentioned below &ndash;</p>
<p class="s4">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s4">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p class="s4">&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s4">Dogecoin (DOGE) remains the torchbearer of all meme coins with certain fluctuations and downfalls. A strong community of supporters and influence from noteworthy personnel still keeps the crypto in the top 10. Dogecoin has been showing impressive performance, despite multiple setbacks.</p>
<p class="s4">And it continues to inch toward the $0.1 milestone within months, predicted to reach even the $1.0 mark in 2023. DOGE's achievement of such a price means excellent profits for traders and investors.</p>
<p class="s4">However, the market value now remains over $0.07, requiring a significant boost in the meme coin. Recent growth in capital and reduction of crypto market outflows will likely take a bullish turn soon. Therefore, an enormous increment in value is possible in the coming months.</p>
<p class="s4">The crypto keeps struggling around the $0.07 mark for about a month, dipping significantly initially. Yet, within weeks, it recovered a significant share of the lost market cap. And the daily transaction numbers reached an all-time high due to the near-bullish forecast of the market.</p>
<p class="s4">Meantime, the first-ever blockchain-supported freelancing platform, Uwerx, doesn't fall behind. Its native crypto, WERX, currently values a mere $0.0315 at the presales. But analysts recognized the potential, predicting an exponential price rise to reach as much as $0.3 by Q3 of 2023.</p>
<p class="s4">The ongoing presales have already entered the fourth stage, completing the first in 17 days and the second in 8 days. Freelancers, investors, and analysts look forward to Uwerx's mainstream success as the platform integrates some unique features for target users.</p>
<p class="s8">Why Does Uwerx Matter So Much?</p>
<p class="s4">Uwerx allows freelancers to earn a minimal 1% transaction fee, considerably lower than traditional platforms. Freelancers will receive payments directly to their WERX hubs, letting them interact with the crypto space. And it'll unveil a new door to crypto-related businesses.</p>
<p class="s4">An audit by InterFi Network and SolidProof already set the foundation of top-tier security. The platform already introduced a custom vault to lock up the tokens in the 25-year liquidity pool. So, all clients' and freelancers' assets and intellectual properties will have a steady backup for security.</p>
<p class="s4">There are advanced features like gamification and incentivization to avoid dull, monotonous, and tiresome work. It should keep the freelancers motivated and enthusiastic to take on new challenges. Analysts and investors also recognized these benefits, counting on the innovative blockchain system.</p>
<p class="s4">A lot is happening within Uwerx as many development tasks are underway to become accessible to the public. It'll start with the release of Uwerx's Alpha version on May 19, 2023, featuring the landing and signup pages. The team plans to continue releasing the next versions based on user feedback.</p>
<p class="s4">The much-hyped presales will end on July 31, 2023, and the Team Lock of tokens will happen before that. A recent Twitter poll revealed 82.8% of voters opted for immediately locking the tokens. And the Uwerx team is getting ready to announce the possible date following the scheduled Test Airdrop.</p>
<p class="s4">The listing of WERX is also gaining momentum as CoinSniper already recognized the token. Uniswap will likely introduce the crypto in its portfolio by August 01, 2023. Launching in centralized exchanges should let the platform initiate the renouncement of contract ownership, lessening tax worries.</p>
<p class="s4">The WERX presales exceeded expectations in every aspect, gaining much appreciation from the crypto space. And the demand keeps increasing as the forecast indicates exploding surges in price. The Uwerx team also understands the impulse, changing five token allocations as follows &ndash;</p>
 Presale: An increase to 57% from 45% to renew confidence.
 Founding Team: A reduction to 7% from 8% to prioritize user benefits.
 Partnership incentives: A reduction to 3% from 7.5% after reviewing new information.
 User performance incentives: A decrease to 6.5% from 15%.
 Joining incentives: An increase to 6.5% from 4.5% to attract more users.
<p class="s4">New investors/customers/users can achieve a 20% bonus on every purchase during the presales. It also sparked the popularity and checkups on this innovative, promising, and beneficial platform. Uwerx has already gained over 5,000 signups with over 1000 members in its Telegram community.</p>
<p class="s4">Grab your opportunity with Uwerx using either of the links mentioned below &ndash;</p>
<p class="s4">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s4">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p class="s4">&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC to USDT: Is More Volatility on the Horizon? Trade the Global Markets with Hybrid Exchange Tradecurve]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-to-usdt-is-more-volatility-on-the-horizon-trade-the-global-markets-with-hybrid-exchange-tradecurve</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-78.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-78.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-78.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-to-usdt-is-more-volatility-on-the-horizon-trade-the-global-markets-with-hybrid-exchange-tradecurve</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the BTC halving approaching and the markets going through another bearish move, what does this mean for hodlers, and when is the next halving scheduled? Tradecurve offers a convenient trading solution that covers multiple markets using just one wallet, and perhaps the best part is that no KYC is required.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Bitcoin's Halving: What You Need to Know</p>
<p>BTC-USD is the most widely traded cryptocurrency pair in the world. Since its introduction in 2009, BTC has experienced several cycles that have shaped its price and value. One of the most significant events is the halving, which occurs approximately every 4 years or every 210,000 blocks created. The next halving is expected to take place around April 2024. During the halving, the mining rate decreases from 6.25 BTC per block to 3.125 BTC per block.</p>
<p>The halving is a major event because it reduces the rate at which new Bitcoins are introduced into circulation. With a fixed supply of 21 million coins, reducing the supply of new coins through the halving can increase the scarcity and value of Bitcoin over time.</p>
<p>Bitcoin mining involves powerful computers competing to solve complex mathematical problems and add new blocks to the blockchain. The halving cuts these rewards in half, which means miners have to work twice as hard to earn the same amount of BTC.</p>
<p>If history is any indication, the halving is a bullish event for BTC, and Bitcoin holders can expect significant volatility after the next halving in April 2024.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tradecurve.io: A Ground-Breaking, Borderless Trading Platform</p>
<p>Thanks to DeFi and blockchain technology, everyone has the option to have their wallet keys and maintain control over their investments. Tradecurve takes advantage of this by offering a trading platform created by traders for traders. It combines the best features of centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>Tradecurve stands out with its cutting-edge trading platform, high leverage, and minimal trading fees. The registration process is simple, and there's no need for KYC verification. Customers can seamlessly join an international ecosystem.</p>
<p>Using Tradecurve's brokerage services, people can use cryptocurrency deposits as collateral for trading derivatives and access multiple markets from a single account.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Staking pools enable TCRV owners to generate additional passive income. Leverage trading starts at 500:1, and a comprehensive metaverse academy offers numerous options for self-development. The expanding user base enjoys round-the-clock customer service and a regularly updated FAQ section.</p>
<p>Token allocation demonstrates a respectable distribution, with 40% of the total supply reserved for presale, 15% for the Tradecurve team, 14% for reserves, 9% for burning, and the remainder for legal advice and listings.</p>
<p>Investors are intrigued by Tradecurve's potential, and during the second stage of its presale, TCRV is listed at $0.012. Analysts predict gains of up to 800% for TCRV in the coming month as it gets listed on Uniswap and other major exchanges, and gains of 100x after it launches on Tier 1 exchanges.</p>
<p>For more information about TCRV presale tokens:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the BTC halving approaching and the markets going through another bearish move, what does this mean for hodlers, and when is the next halving scheduled? Tradecurve offers a convenient trading solution that covers multiple markets using just one wallet, and perhaps the best part is that no KYC is required.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Bitcoin's Halving: What You Need to Know</p>
<p>BTC-USD is the most widely traded cryptocurrency pair in the world. Since its introduction in 2009, BTC has experienced several cycles that have shaped its price and value. One of the most significant events is the halving, which occurs approximately every 4 years or every 210,000 blocks created. The next halving is expected to take place around April 2024. During the halving, the mining rate decreases from 6.25 BTC per block to 3.125 BTC per block.</p>
<p>The halving is a major event because it reduces the rate at which new Bitcoins are introduced into circulation. With a fixed supply of 21 million coins, reducing the supply of new coins through the halving can increase the scarcity and value of Bitcoin over time.</p>
<p>Bitcoin mining involves powerful computers competing to solve complex mathematical problems and add new blocks to the blockchain. The halving cuts these rewards in half, which means miners have to work twice as hard to earn the same amount of BTC.</p>
<p>If history is any indication, the halving is a bullish event for BTC, and Bitcoin holders can expect significant volatility after the next halving in April 2024.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tradecurve.io: A Ground-Breaking, Borderless Trading Platform</p>
<p>Thanks to DeFi and blockchain technology, everyone has the option to have their wallet keys and maintain control over their investments. Tradecurve takes advantage of this by offering a trading platform created by traders for traders. It combines the best features of centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>Tradecurve stands out with its cutting-edge trading platform, high leverage, and minimal trading fees. The registration process is simple, and there's no need for KYC verification. Customers can seamlessly join an international ecosystem.</p>
<p>Using Tradecurve's brokerage services, people can use cryptocurrency deposits as collateral for trading derivatives and access multiple markets from a single account.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Staking pools enable TCRV owners to generate additional passive income. Leverage trading starts at 500:1, and a comprehensive metaverse academy offers numerous options for self-development. The expanding user base enjoys round-the-clock customer service and a regularly updated FAQ section.</p>
<p>Token allocation demonstrates a respectable distribution, with 40% of the total supply reserved for presale, 15% for the Tradecurve team, 14% for reserves, 9% for burning, and the remainder for legal advice and listings.</p>
<p>Investors are intrigued by Tradecurve's potential, and during the second stage of its presale, TCRV is listed at $0.012. Analysts predict gains of up to 800% for TCRV in the coming month as it gets listed on Uniswap and other major exchanges, and gains of 100x after it launches on Tier 1 exchanges.</p>
<p>For more information about TCRV presale tokens:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Investors Showing Interest in InQubeta (QUBE) Presale, While Arbitrum (ARB) Community Continues to See Losses]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/investors-showing-interest-in-inqubeta-qube-presale-while-arbitrum-arb-community-continues-to-see-losses</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-151108.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-151108.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-151108.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/investors-showing-interest-in-inqubeta-qube-presale-while-arbitrum-arb-community-continues-to-see-losses</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Investors are increasingly showing interest in the InQubeta (QUBE) presale, while Arbitrum(ARB) holders continue to see the value of their holdings drop. Presales and initial coin offerings (ICO) are known to excite investors, but InQubeta&rsquo;s presale is generating unprecedented interest as investors look to capitalize on a barrier-free opportunity to purchase equity in promising Artificial Intelligence (AI) startups.</p>
<p>AI is one of the fastest-growing technology fields, with total investments in the industry rising by over $80 billion from 2015 to 2021. That&rsquo;s a clear indicator that many traditional investors expect AI to be a significant part of everyday life in the future.</p>
<p>Many AI-powered devices that were once nothing more than a fantasy of novelists are now a common reality. AI-powered devices now clean floors in many homes, while some vehicle manufacturers have added self-driving features to their products. All this has occurred while AI technology still remains in its infancy.</p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta keeps trending upwards while other altcoins like Arbitrum lose value</p>
<p>InQubeta&rsquo;s unique platform deserves credit for the growth enjoyed during its presale. It allows anyone, to invest in AI startups without a need for Silicon Valley connections or other barriers associated with mainstream investment firms. The platform also makes it easier for AI startups to secure the funding needed for their projects.</p>
<p>Startups raise capital on InQubeta&rsquo;s platform by creating ERC20 QUBE tokens. These are fractionalized, deflationary non-fungible tokens (NFTs) that represent equity and other rewards in their companies. These tokens are then listed on the InQubeta marketplace where investors find and research startups with potential to invest in.</p>
<p>Investors purchase fractionalized QUBE tokens of startups they link with $QUBE tokens, the platform's native currency. This gives them equity in the company and other rewards like profit-sharing in some cases.</p>
<p>InQubeta&rsquo;s platform has deflationary protocols that help to push prices upwards. Buy and sell transactions with QUBE tokens are taxed at a 2% rate. The taxes generated are sent to a burn wallet to reduce the total number of available coins. The tax rate is 5% for $QUBE transactions, and it&rsquo;s used to fund a dedicated reward pool for investors who stake their coins.</p>
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) also allows investors to be part of the platform's governance, with the size of each investor&rsquo;s holdings deciding the authority of their voice. Investors can propose, discuss, and vote on ideas that affect the platform's protocols and future.</p>
<p class="s11">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s8">Arbitrum (ARB) release hasn&rsquo;t gone as planned</p>
<p>Arbitrum is built around the Ethereum (ETH) network &ndash; the second most popular cryptocurrency worldwide. ETH &nbsp;has lots of things going on for it like supporting smart contracts. However, Ethereum transaction fees have gotten outrageously high as its value grows.</p>
<p>Arbitrum has created a third-party solution for Ethereum&rsquo;s problems by building its platform on Ethereum&rsquo;s blockchain to speed up transactions and lower fees. It&rsquo;s emerged as a popular place for ETH holders to complete transactions.</p>
<p>Arbitrum released its new ARB governance token in March 2023, but the token hasn&rsquo;t seen significant growth since. Instead, prices have dropped by over 50% since setting an all-time high of $1.77 in April. Altcoins like Arbitrum have struggled to grow since the start of the InQubetapresale as investors can&rsquo;t resist the urge to be part of the AI revolution going on. Artificial intelligence has the potential to surpass the internet regarding its effects on how the world works, leading to a steady flow of investment capital into the industry and services that help its growth.</p>
<p class="s8">Summary</p>
<p>Many cryptocurrencies are predicted to experience significant growth this year, but Arbitrummight not be one of them despite making Ethereum transactions faster and cheaper. Other promising altcoins like InQubeta are drawing significant investments, keeping investments in coins like ARB low for now.</p>
<p class="s11">Join InQubeta Communities&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investors are increasingly showing interest in the InQubeta (QUBE) presale, while Arbitrum(ARB) holders continue to see the value of their holdings drop. Presales and initial coin offerings (ICO) are known to excite investors, but InQubeta&rsquo;s presale is generating unprecedented interest as investors look to capitalize on a barrier-free opportunity to purchase equity in promising Artificial Intelligence (AI) startups.</p>
<p>AI is one of the fastest-growing technology fields, with total investments in the industry rising by over $80 billion from 2015 to 2021. That&rsquo;s a clear indicator that many traditional investors expect AI to be a significant part of everyday life in the future.</p>
<p>Many AI-powered devices that were once nothing more than a fantasy of novelists are now a common reality. AI-powered devices now clean floors in many homes, while some vehicle manufacturers have added self-driving features to their products. All this has occurred while AI technology still remains in its infancy.</p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta keeps trending upwards while other altcoins like Arbitrum lose value</p>
<p>InQubeta&rsquo;s unique platform deserves credit for the growth enjoyed during its presale. It allows anyone, to invest in AI startups without a need for Silicon Valley connections or other barriers associated with mainstream investment firms. The platform also makes it easier for AI startups to secure the funding needed for their projects.</p>
<p>Startups raise capital on InQubeta&rsquo;s platform by creating ERC20 QUBE tokens. These are fractionalized, deflationary non-fungible tokens (NFTs) that represent equity and other rewards in their companies. These tokens are then listed on the InQubeta marketplace where investors find and research startups with potential to invest in.</p>
<p>Investors purchase fractionalized QUBE tokens of startups they link with $QUBE tokens, the platform's native currency. This gives them equity in the company and other rewards like profit-sharing in some cases.</p>
<p>InQubeta&rsquo;s platform has deflationary protocols that help to push prices upwards. Buy and sell transactions with QUBE tokens are taxed at a 2% rate. The taxes generated are sent to a burn wallet to reduce the total number of available coins. The tax rate is 5% for $QUBE transactions, and it&rsquo;s used to fund a dedicated reward pool for investors who stake their coins.</p>
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) also allows investors to be part of the platform's governance, with the size of each investor&rsquo;s holdings deciding the authority of their voice. Investors can propose, discuss, and vote on ideas that affect the platform's protocols and future.</p>
<p class="s11">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s8">Arbitrum (ARB) release hasn&rsquo;t gone as planned</p>
<p>Arbitrum is built around the Ethereum (ETH) network &ndash; the second most popular cryptocurrency worldwide. ETH &nbsp;has lots of things going on for it like supporting smart contracts. However, Ethereum transaction fees have gotten outrageously high as its value grows.</p>
<p>Arbitrum has created a third-party solution for Ethereum&rsquo;s problems by building its platform on Ethereum&rsquo;s blockchain to speed up transactions and lower fees. It&rsquo;s emerged as a popular place for ETH holders to complete transactions.</p>
<p>Arbitrum released its new ARB governance token in March 2023, but the token hasn&rsquo;t seen significant growth since. Instead, prices have dropped by over 50% since setting an all-time high of $1.77 in April. Altcoins like Arbitrum have struggled to grow since the start of the InQubetapresale as investors can&rsquo;t resist the urge to be part of the AI revolution going on. Artificial intelligence has the potential to surpass the internet regarding its effects on how the world works, leading to a steady flow of investment capital into the industry and services that help its growth.</p>
<p class="s8">Summary</p>
<p>Many cryptocurrencies are predicted to experience significant growth this year, but Arbitrummight not be one of them despite making Ethereum transactions faster and cheaper. Other promising altcoins like InQubeta are drawing significant investments, keeping investments in coins like ARB low for now.</p>
<p class="s11">Join InQubeta Communities&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Should You Buy Ethereum on eToro, or Buy the Collateral Network (COLT) Presale?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/should-you-buy-ethereum-on-etoro-or-buy-the-collateral-network-colt-presale</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-151918.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-151918.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-151918.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/should-you-buy-ethereum-on-etoro-or-buy-the-collateral-network-colt-presale</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH) has solidified itself as one of the market's most popular and desirable crypto coins. However, as the recent lockup of ETH tokens hits new highs, investors are wondering about the coin's future movements.</p>
<p>While this is happening, a new player on the market &ndash; Collateral Network (COLT), is turning heads and making waves, with experts predicting a 3500% growth even while the token is still in its public presale.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY COLT TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Collateral Network Blows Investors Away with Incredible Gains</p>
<p>Collateral Network is one of the hottest projects in the crypto sphere right now. Set to revolutionize the lending industry, Collateral Network is the first decentralized lending platform on the blockchain that allows people to leverage their real-world assets in exchange for loans.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let's say you need to get a loan to fund an upcoming project, and you have a $10,000 watch. You can send that watch over to Collateral Network, where it will be valued and stored securely in a vault. Collateral Network will mint a 100% asset-backed NFT from your watch and sell it in fractions to other Collateral Network holders. Once you repay your loan, you'll get the watch back, and the NFT will be burned.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the people who fund the loans, i.e., buy fractions of the asset-backed NFTs, can create a diversified portfolio of multiple small loans and receive fixed-interest weekly payments from each loan. So, Collateral Network also allows lenders to create streams of passive income with competitive rates.</p>
<p>At the moment, this token is still in its public presale. Nonetheless, it's already providing gains for holders, as its initial presale price has already jumped from $0.01 to $0.014 in just a few weeks. Experts and analysts are predicting 3500% gains for the coin in the near future and an incredible 100x increase once the coin hits exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Is Buying Ethereum on eToro Worth It?</p>
<p>The Ethereum (ETH) price is continuing to see bearish reactions as the Ethereum lockup continues to rise. In an effort to boost the Ethereum value, Ethereum holders have been locking up their Ethereum coins in the past few weeks. Now, the total locked amount has reached a new high, with 19,375,242 Ethereum coins being locked away.</p>
<p>However, the lockup trend has yet to achieve its goal of boosting Ethereum value, and now investors are unsure where all of this will lead. Some experts are predicting a further decline in Ethereum prices in the future, with some saying that it could fall from its current trading price of $1,788.05 to $1,462.</p>
<p>If you want to wait for the expected dip once it comes, you can buy Ethereum on eToro. However, at this time, it's not recommendable that you do so, as predictions aren't so good for the coin. So, you'll be much better off investing in the Collateral Network presale if you want to get maximum gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on Collateral Network visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Collateral Network presale here:</p>
<p>Website: https://www.collateralnetwork.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.collateralnetwork.io/login</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/collateralnwk&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Collateralnwk&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH) has solidified itself as one of the market's most popular and desirable crypto coins. However, as the recent lockup of ETH tokens hits new highs, investors are wondering about the coin's future movements.</p>
<p>While this is happening, a new player on the market &ndash; Collateral Network (COLT), is turning heads and making waves, with experts predicting a 3500% growth even while the token is still in its public presale.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY COLT TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Collateral Network Blows Investors Away with Incredible Gains</p>
<p>Collateral Network is one of the hottest projects in the crypto sphere right now. Set to revolutionize the lending industry, Collateral Network is the first decentralized lending platform on the blockchain that allows people to leverage their real-world assets in exchange for loans.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let's say you need to get a loan to fund an upcoming project, and you have a $10,000 watch. You can send that watch over to Collateral Network, where it will be valued and stored securely in a vault. Collateral Network will mint a 100% asset-backed NFT from your watch and sell it in fractions to other Collateral Network holders. Once you repay your loan, you'll get the watch back, and the NFT will be burned.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the people who fund the loans, i.e., buy fractions of the asset-backed NFTs, can create a diversified portfolio of multiple small loans and receive fixed-interest weekly payments from each loan. So, Collateral Network also allows lenders to create streams of passive income with competitive rates.</p>
<p>At the moment, this token is still in its public presale. Nonetheless, it's already providing gains for holders, as its initial presale price has already jumped from $0.01 to $0.014 in just a few weeks. Experts and analysts are predicting 3500% gains for the coin in the near future and an incredible 100x increase once the coin hits exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Is Buying Ethereum on eToro Worth It?</p>
<p>The Ethereum (ETH) price is continuing to see bearish reactions as the Ethereum lockup continues to rise. In an effort to boost the Ethereum value, Ethereum holders have been locking up their Ethereum coins in the past few weeks. Now, the total locked amount has reached a new high, with 19,375,242 Ethereum coins being locked away.</p>
<p>However, the lockup trend has yet to achieve its goal of boosting Ethereum value, and now investors are unsure where all of this will lead. Some experts are predicting a further decline in Ethereum prices in the future, with some saying that it could fall from its current trading price of $1,788.05 to $1,462.</p>
<p>If you want to wait for the expected dip once it comes, you can buy Ethereum on eToro. However, at this time, it's not recommendable that you do so, as predictions aren't so good for the coin. So, you'll be much better off investing in the Collateral Network presale if you want to get maximum gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on Collateral Network visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Collateral Network presale here:</p>
<p>Website: https://www.collateralnetwork.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.collateralnetwork.io/login</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/collateralnwk&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Collateralnwk&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitfinex to List Pepe (PEPE), Shiba Inu (SHIB) Gets New NFT Hoodies, Sparklo (SPRK) Presale Explodes]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitfinex-to-list-pepe-pepe-shiba-inu-shib-gets-new-nft-hoodies-sparklo-sprk-presale-explodes</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-152529.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-152529.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-152529.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitfinex-to-list-pepe-pepe-shiba-inu-shib-gets-new-nft-hoodies-sparklo-sprk-presale-explodes</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">As initial hype fades, Pepe (PEPE) has now maintained a new red color, while Shiba Inu (SHIB) continues its long-term battle with the bears. In light of the recent struggles of meme coins, investors have become increasingly cautious when considering investment opportunities. One project that has stood out from the pack because of its utility is Sparklo.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">Sparklo (SPRK) offers unrivaled utility to investors</p>
<p class="s7">Sparklo is developing the first blockchain platform that will allow both low and high-income earners to assess the precious metals industry by eliminating the obstacles that plague the traditional investment market. Using fractional NFTs, Sparklo will give investors the chance to own gold, silver, and platinum.</p>
<p class="s7">At current prices, gold has a market cap of $13.02 trillion, silver $1.3 trillion, and platinum$267.92 billion. Exploring these markets gives Sparklo an unrivaled utility. Sparklo will also collaborate with jewelry stores to provide investors with early access to some jewelry products before they are made available on the market.</p>
<p class="s7">Now in the second presale stage, Sparklo (SPRK) currently trades at $0.026 with up to 50% rewards on purchases. Given the potential of Sparklo, experts have predicted a price jump of up to 40x within the first year of launch.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">The red Pepe (PEPE) color despite Bitfinex listing</p>
<p class="s7">Following an explosive performance early this month, Pepe (PEPE) has been sliding deeper into bear territory. As a popular meme coin, Pepe (PEPE) continues to receive support from crypto exchanges. Bitfinex has announced that Pepe (PEPE) will be listed on the exchange on May 22. Trading Pepe (PEPE) against US Dollar and Tether (USDT) pairs will open on May 24. </p>
<p class="s7">The massive Pepe (PEPE) rally was followed by an even bigger dump as investors cashed out their gains. Despite Bifinex announcing the listing of Pepe (PEPE) has lost more than 5% of its value in the last 24 hours. Over the last week, the price of Pepe (PEPE) has declined by 13%, making it one of the biggest losers. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">John Richmond teases new Shiba Inu (SHIB) NFT hoodie</p>
<p class="s7">An equally popular meme coin, Shiba Inu (SHIB) continues to see more developments than Pepe (PEPE). John Richmond, the famous Italian-English fashion designer has announced that he will launch a new NFT hoodie collection exclusively for the Shiba Inu (SHIB) community. According to Richmond, the hoodies are part of the Cyberpunk LegendsLiveForever collection.</p>
<p class="s7">Like NFTs, each hoodie will be unique. The announcement has turned the negative sentiments of Shiba Inu (SHIB) positive. Over the last 24 hours, the price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) has gained 2.7%, pushing its price up to $0.000008778. However, in the long term, Shiba Inu (SHIB) remains bearish, losing 16% of its value in the last 30 days. The poor performance of meme coins has fueled the migration of investors to projects with more utility like Sparklo. </p>
<p class="s7">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s13">Find out about the Sparklo (SPRK) presale using the links below:</p>
<p class="s15">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s15">Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s15">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s15">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">As initial hype fades, Pepe (PEPE) has now maintained a new red color, while Shiba Inu (SHIB) continues its long-term battle with the bears. In light of the recent struggles of meme coins, investors have become increasingly cautious when considering investment opportunities. One project that has stood out from the pack because of its utility is Sparklo.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">Sparklo (SPRK) offers unrivaled utility to investors</p>
<p class="s7">Sparklo is developing the first blockchain platform that will allow both low and high-income earners to assess the precious metals industry by eliminating the obstacles that plague the traditional investment market. Using fractional NFTs, Sparklo will give investors the chance to own gold, silver, and platinum.</p>
<p class="s7">At current prices, gold has a market cap of $13.02 trillion, silver $1.3 trillion, and platinum$267.92 billion. Exploring these markets gives Sparklo an unrivaled utility. Sparklo will also collaborate with jewelry stores to provide investors with early access to some jewelry products before they are made available on the market.</p>
<p class="s7">Now in the second presale stage, Sparklo (SPRK) currently trades at $0.026 with up to 50% rewards on purchases. Given the potential of Sparklo, experts have predicted a price jump of up to 40x within the first year of launch.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">The red Pepe (PEPE) color despite Bitfinex listing</p>
<p class="s7">Following an explosive performance early this month, Pepe (PEPE) has been sliding deeper into bear territory. As a popular meme coin, Pepe (PEPE) continues to receive support from crypto exchanges. Bitfinex has announced that Pepe (PEPE) will be listed on the exchange on May 22. Trading Pepe (PEPE) against US Dollar and Tether (USDT) pairs will open on May 24. </p>
<p class="s7">The massive Pepe (PEPE) rally was followed by an even bigger dump as investors cashed out their gains. Despite Bifinex announcing the listing of Pepe (PEPE) has lost more than 5% of its value in the last 24 hours. Over the last week, the price of Pepe (PEPE) has declined by 13%, making it one of the biggest losers. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s10">John Richmond teases new Shiba Inu (SHIB) NFT hoodie</p>
<p class="s7">An equally popular meme coin, Shiba Inu (SHIB) continues to see more developments than Pepe (PEPE). John Richmond, the famous Italian-English fashion designer has announced that he will launch a new NFT hoodie collection exclusively for the Shiba Inu (SHIB) community. According to Richmond, the hoodies are part of the Cyberpunk LegendsLiveForever collection.</p>
<p class="s7">Like NFTs, each hoodie will be unique. The announcement has turned the negative sentiments of Shiba Inu (SHIB) positive. Over the last 24 hours, the price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) has gained 2.7%, pushing its price up to $0.000008778. However, in the long term, Shiba Inu (SHIB) remains bearish, losing 16% of its value in the last 30 days. The poor performance of meme coins has fueled the migration of investors to projects with more utility like Sparklo. </p>
<p class="s7">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s13">Find out about the Sparklo (SPRK) presale using the links below:</p>
<p class="s15">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s15">Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s15">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s15">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC Whales are investing heavily into TOADS to diversify their wealth]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-whales-are-investing-heavily-into-toads-to-diversify-their-wealth</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-150907.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-150907.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-26-at-150907.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-whales-are-investing-heavily-into-toads-to-diversify-their-wealth</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Whether by luck, good timing, or a fundamental belief in decentralized finance, hundreds, if not thousands of people, bought large amounts of Bitcoin and still hold them to date. As they are commonly known, Bitcoin whales exert significant influence over the market, with their activity influencing prices. </p>
<p>Bitcoin whales are always on the hunt for the next big thing. Many of them are now circling DigiToads, a unique memecoin that offers utility to users. The activity of whales is felt even for major coins with significant liquidity spread globally. Therefore, their entry into the memecoinspace with interest in DigiToads is noticeable. </p>
<p>Focus on DigiToads</p>
<p>This project is currently conducting a presale as it looks to proceed toward full launch. DigiToads is fast gathering momentum in the memecoin space as it looks to dislodge more established competitors. </p>
<p>At press time, DigiToads had raised over $4.25 million in the presale, which only commenced recently. This amount indicates the interest of some significant players in the crypto landscape in this emerging memecoin. </p>
<p>It might have a lot to do with DigiToads gradual increase in token pricing through the presale as it prepares for launch. Since the token sale started, prices have risen over 140%, with more planned increases in the pipeline. As they say, the early bird catches the worm. Crypto whales who have bought TOADS tokens are probably looking at the big picture in acquiring the coin in its early stages. </p>
<p>Memecoins are having a moment; again. Those who followed the last crypto rally two years ago remember how Dogecoin blew established projects off the ballpark in a short window. Well, Pepecoin has had a significant surge in the past month before tapering off a week ago. DigiToadsseeks to take up the mantle and take memecoins up a notch.</p>
<p>DigiToads Utility</p>
<p>The key to DigiToads aims is the addition of utility to the standard operating procedure of memecoins. Typical memecoins ride on the meme's popularity. it is pegged on to its logical conclusion. Pepecoin is a subset of the &ldquo;Pepe the Frog'' meme that has been a staple on the internet for a decade or more, especially on right-wing chat boards. This token took up the notoriety of this meme and got hot a few weeks ago, and has experienced some correction lately. </p>
<p>For DigiToads, the meme aspect holds but is not the end all be all of the projects. The team behind the project conceptualized a pay-to-earn (P2E) gaming ecosystem with the TOADS token at the heart of this ecosystem. TOADS is an ERC-20 token, meaning broad compatibility with Ethereum wallets and ease of trading. </p>
<p>The game itself takes place in a swamp metaverse where toads live. These toads catch flies for their nourishment and engage in various battles to secure their habitat. The battles can be intense, and the player must ensure they nourish their toads to be as strong as possible in preparation. Success in these battles means rewards to the player in the form of TOADs hence the play-to-earn concept. </p>
<p>Additionally, the players have a chance to accumulate several Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) collectibles as they navigate the game. These NFTs are unique and have inherent value. To protect the value of the NFTs collectively, DigiToads allows gamers to stake their NFTs in exchange for a small percentage of TOADS transaction fees collected by the project. Staking TOADS is also an option to ensure that one can participate in project governance moving forward. </p>
<p>Governance will be through a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), ensuring DigiToads retains a distributed network governance model. Besides sustainable governance, the project also has a commitment to real-world sustainability, with some of the profits donated to charities committed to saving rainforests. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Markets follow whales</p>
<p>In an ocean, the big fish change the behavior of other fish when they come into an area. Whales may not have the stereotypical fear of sharks but are large enough to cause a reaction in the surrounding waters. </p>
<p>Whether you think the role of crypto whales in the markets is positive or not, there is no doubt that their activity moves markets. For instance, the activity of the four biggest Bitcoin wallets that collectively own over 3 % of all Bitcoin in circulation is enough to tilt markets. Notably, these four are rarely active and have not rocked Bitcoin prices as much as possible. Interest in a new token like TOADS is an endorsement of the fundamentals of this project. The markets will certainly be watching this space for their subsequent moves. </p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>Whales purchasing TOADS tokens is indicative of the potential of these projects. Rarely do these crypto powerhouses act for charitable ends, and their moves often come upon calculated projections. The DigiToads launch is certainly something to look forward to shortly. </p>
<p class="s12">For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether by luck, good timing, or a fundamental belief in decentralized finance, hundreds, if not thousands of people, bought large amounts of Bitcoin and still hold them to date. As they are commonly known, Bitcoin whales exert significant influence over the market, with their activity influencing prices. </p>
<p>Bitcoin whales are always on the hunt for the next big thing. Many of them are now circling DigiToads, a unique memecoin that offers utility to users. The activity of whales is felt even for major coins with significant liquidity spread globally. Therefore, their entry into the memecoinspace with interest in DigiToads is noticeable. </p>
<p>Focus on DigiToads</p>
<p>This project is currently conducting a presale as it looks to proceed toward full launch. DigiToads is fast gathering momentum in the memecoin space as it looks to dislodge more established competitors. </p>
<p>At press time, DigiToads had raised over $4.25 million in the presale, which only commenced recently. This amount indicates the interest of some significant players in the crypto landscape in this emerging memecoin. </p>
<p>It might have a lot to do with DigiToads gradual increase in token pricing through the presale as it prepares for launch. Since the token sale started, prices have risen over 140%, with more planned increases in the pipeline. As they say, the early bird catches the worm. Crypto whales who have bought TOADS tokens are probably looking at the big picture in acquiring the coin in its early stages. </p>
<p>Memecoins are having a moment; again. Those who followed the last crypto rally two years ago remember how Dogecoin blew established projects off the ballpark in a short window. Well, Pepecoin has had a significant surge in the past month before tapering off a week ago. DigiToadsseeks to take up the mantle and take memecoins up a notch.</p>
<p>DigiToads Utility</p>
<p>The key to DigiToads aims is the addition of utility to the standard operating procedure of memecoins. Typical memecoins ride on the meme's popularity. it is pegged on to its logical conclusion. Pepecoin is a subset of the &ldquo;Pepe the Frog'' meme that has been a staple on the internet for a decade or more, especially on right-wing chat boards. This token took up the notoriety of this meme and got hot a few weeks ago, and has experienced some correction lately. </p>
<p>For DigiToads, the meme aspect holds but is not the end all be all of the projects. The team behind the project conceptualized a pay-to-earn (P2E) gaming ecosystem with the TOADS token at the heart of this ecosystem. TOADS is an ERC-20 token, meaning broad compatibility with Ethereum wallets and ease of trading. </p>
<p>The game itself takes place in a swamp metaverse where toads live. These toads catch flies for their nourishment and engage in various battles to secure their habitat. The battles can be intense, and the player must ensure they nourish their toads to be as strong as possible in preparation. Success in these battles means rewards to the player in the form of TOADs hence the play-to-earn concept. </p>
<p>Additionally, the players have a chance to accumulate several Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) collectibles as they navigate the game. These NFTs are unique and have inherent value. To protect the value of the NFTs collectively, DigiToads allows gamers to stake their NFTs in exchange for a small percentage of TOADS transaction fees collected by the project. Staking TOADS is also an option to ensure that one can participate in project governance moving forward. </p>
<p>Governance will be through a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), ensuring DigiToads retains a distributed network governance model. Besides sustainable governance, the project also has a commitment to real-world sustainability, with some of the profits donated to charities committed to saving rainforests. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Markets follow whales</p>
<p>In an ocean, the big fish change the behavior of other fish when they come into an area. Whales may not have the stereotypical fear of sharks but are large enough to cause a reaction in the surrounding waters. </p>
<p>Whether you think the role of crypto whales in the markets is positive or not, there is no doubt that their activity moves markets. For instance, the activity of the four biggest Bitcoin wallets that collectively own over 3 % of all Bitcoin in circulation is enough to tilt markets. Notably, these four are rarely active and have not rocked Bitcoin prices as much as possible. Interest in a new token like TOADS is an endorsement of the fundamentals of this project. The markets will certainly be watching this space for their subsequent moves. </p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>Whales purchasing TOADS tokens is indicative of the potential of these projects. Rarely do these crypto powerhouses act for charitable ends, and their moves often come upon calculated projections. The DigiToads launch is certainly something to look forward to shortly. </p>
<p class="s12">For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[DCG Closes Institutional Trading Platform TradeBlock]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/dcg-closes-institutional-trading-platform-tradeblock</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dcg-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dcg-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dcg-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:59:55 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/dcg-closes-institutional-trading-platform-tradeblock</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>DCG announced on Thursday the closure of its prime brokerage subsidiary TradeBlock. The company cites broad economic concerns and the uncertain regulatory climate in the US. </p>
<p>Digital Currency Group (DCG) announced on Thursday that it would officially start the process of shutting down its institutional trading platform on May 31, Bloomberg reports.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Barry Silbert&rsquo;s crypto conglomerate, Digital Currency Group, is shuttering its TradeBlock institutional trading platform https://t.co/duE4YnknrR</p>
&mdash; Bloomberg Crypto (@crypto) May 25, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the venture capital conglomerate told Bloomberg that concerns over the broader economic climate and an uncertain regulatory environment for cryptocurrencies in the US drove the decision to shutter TradeBlock&rsquo;s operations.</p>

<p>Due to the state of the broader economy and prolonged crypto winter, along with the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the US, we made the decision to sunset the institutional trading platform side of the business.</p>

Challenging Times for DCG
<p>Established in 2011, the company was acquired by DCG&rsquo;s crypto-focused media platform CoinDesk in 2021. CoinDesk retained only its index data business which it later rebranded to CoinDesk Indices, Finance Magnates reports.</p>
<p>DCG has been under severe pressure after one of its subsidiaries, Genesis Global Trading, halted customer withdrawals in November and went bankrupt, reportedly owing creditors $3 billion.</p>
<p>The company is further facing pressure over a lending product called &ldquo;Earn&rdquo;, which Genesis offered in partnership with crypto exchange Gemini.</p>
<p>Earlier in the week, it was reported that DCG missed a payment concerning a $900 million loan made by Gemini to Genesis. The crypto exchange warned earlier in the month that if DCG could not make the required loan repayment or restructure its debt, the company would be at risk of defaulting on its obligations.</p>
<p>The conglomerate further revealed in its Q4 2022 investor report that it suffered losses worth $1.1 billion due to the collapse of Three Arrows Capital. DCG is reportedly 3AC&rsquo;s largest creditor, which owes around $2.36 billion in funds.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DCG announced on Thursday the closure of its prime brokerage subsidiary TradeBlock. The company cites broad economic concerns and the uncertain regulatory climate in the US. </p>
<p>Digital Currency Group (DCG) announced on Thursday that it would officially start the process of shutting down its institutional trading platform on May 31, Bloomberg reports.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Barry Silbert&rsquo;s crypto conglomerate, Digital Currency Group, is shuttering its TradeBlock institutional trading platform https://t.co/duE4YnknrR</p>
&mdash; Bloomberg Crypto (@crypto) May 25, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>A spokesperson for the venture capital conglomerate told Bloomberg that concerns over the broader economic climate and an uncertain regulatory environment for cryptocurrencies in the US drove the decision to shutter TradeBlock&rsquo;s operations.</p>

<p>Due to the state of the broader economy and prolonged crypto winter, along with the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the US, we made the decision to sunset the institutional trading platform side of the business.</p>

Challenging Times for DCG
<p>Established in 2011, the company was acquired by DCG&rsquo;s crypto-focused media platform CoinDesk in 2021. CoinDesk retained only its index data business which it later rebranded to CoinDesk Indices, Finance Magnates reports.</p>
<p>DCG has been under severe pressure after one of its subsidiaries, Genesis Global Trading, halted customer withdrawals in November and went bankrupt, reportedly owing creditors $3 billion.</p>
<p>The company is further facing pressure over a lending product called &ldquo;Earn&rdquo;, which Genesis offered in partnership with crypto exchange Gemini.</p>
<p>Earlier in the week, it was reported that DCG missed a payment concerning a $900 million loan made by Gemini to Genesis. The crypto exchange warned earlier in the month that if DCG could not make the required loan repayment or restructure its debt, the company would be at risk of defaulting on its obligations.</p>
<p>The conglomerate further revealed in its Q4 2022 investor report that it suffered losses worth $1.1 billion due to the collapse of Three Arrows Capital. DCG is reportedly 3AC&rsquo;s largest creditor, which owes around $2.36 billion in funds.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Launches NFT Loan Feature]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-launches-nft-loan-feature</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-new-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-new-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-new-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-launches-nft-loan-feature</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Binance crypto exchange has started its NFT journey by launching a loan feature, which will allow users to use their NFTs as collateral to borrow cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
Borrow Crypto Against NFT
<p>The move marks the entry of the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange into the NFT lending space. After launching its NFT marketplace in June 2021, the latest NFT lending feature will give users easy and quick access to funds without having to sell their NFTs, allowing them to borrow cryptocurrencies by just putting their digital assets as collateral.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Head of Product at Binance, Mayur Kama, announced the news, saying,</p>

<p>&ldquo;Binance NFT is building! We&rsquo;ve added many features that make it a one-stop shop for NFT trading and financial services for our community. We already have low fees and the Binance peace of mind; now NFT Loans will add a new form of liquidity for NFT holders, allowing them to participate in the market without letting go of their precious NFTs.&rdquo;</p>

DeFi Benefits For Users
<p>The feature will allow users to initially borrow only Ether (ETH) against NFTs that have been marked as &ldquo;blue-chip.&rdquo; These include popular digital asset collections like the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC), Azuki, and Doodles. Collectors with NFTs from any of these collections will be able to put their assets as collateral and borrow ETH.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement from the company has claimed that more NFT collections will be added to the &ldquo;blue-chip&rdquo; list, broadening the borrowing opportunities for its users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The feature also allows users to tap into the DeFi-related benefits in the Binance NFT community, as it operates on a &ldquo;Peer to Pool&rdquo; mechanism, where data is sourced from multiple providers, including the oracle service Chainlink and the OpenSea NFT marketplace. The Binance NFT marketplace acts like a loan pool, and the floor price of the collateralized NFTs decides the amount of ETH a user can borrow.&nbsp;</p>
No Gas fees
<p>One notable advantage of the Binance NFT loan feature is the absence of gas fees or Ethereum transaction fees, making it a cost-effective solution for users seeking liquidity. In addition, the interest rates on NFT loans currently stand at 7.91% per annum, with loan-to-value ratios ranging from 40% to 60%, as stated on the Binance NFT website.</p>
<p>Binance's foray into NFT lending further expands its NFT offerings, complementing its NFT marketplace that was introduced in April 2021. Since its launch, Binance has continually added features to enhance user experience, including the recent integration of Ordinals, Bitcoin-based NFTs, alongside existing blockchain support for Ethereum, Polygon, and Binance's native BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Binance crypto exchange has started its NFT journey by launching a loan feature, which will allow users to use their NFTs as collateral to borrow cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
Borrow Crypto Against NFT
<p>The move marks the entry of the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange into the NFT lending space. After launching its NFT marketplace in June 2021, the latest NFT lending feature will give users easy and quick access to funds without having to sell their NFTs, allowing them to borrow cryptocurrencies by just putting their digital assets as collateral.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Head of Product at Binance, Mayur Kama, announced the news, saying,</p>

<p>&ldquo;Binance NFT is building! We&rsquo;ve added many features that make it a one-stop shop for NFT trading and financial services for our community. We already have low fees and the Binance peace of mind; now NFT Loans will add a new form of liquidity for NFT holders, allowing them to participate in the market without letting go of their precious NFTs.&rdquo;</p>

DeFi Benefits For Users
<p>The feature will allow users to initially borrow only Ether (ETH) against NFTs that have been marked as &ldquo;blue-chip.&rdquo; These include popular digital asset collections like the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC), Azuki, and Doodles. Collectors with NFTs from any of these collections will be able to put their assets as collateral and borrow ETH.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement from the company has claimed that more NFT collections will be added to the &ldquo;blue-chip&rdquo; list, broadening the borrowing opportunities for its users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The feature also allows users to tap into the DeFi-related benefits in the Binance NFT community, as it operates on a &ldquo;Peer to Pool&rdquo; mechanism, where data is sourced from multiple providers, including the oracle service Chainlink and the OpenSea NFT marketplace. The Binance NFT marketplace acts like a loan pool, and the floor price of the collateralized NFTs decides the amount of ETH a user can borrow.&nbsp;</p>
No Gas fees
<p>One notable advantage of the Binance NFT loan feature is the absence of gas fees or Ethereum transaction fees, making it a cost-effective solution for users seeking liquidity. In addition, the interest rates on NFT loans currently stand at 7.91% per annum, with loan-to-value ratios ranging from 40% to 60%, as stated on the Binance NFT website.</p>
<p>Binance's foray into NFT lending further expands its NFT offerings, complementing its NFT marketplace that was introduced in April 2021. Since its launch, Binance has continually added features to enhance user experience, including the recent integration of Ordinals, Bitcoin-based NFTs, alongside existing blockchain support for Ethereum, Polygon, and Binance's native BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Gemini To Establish European Headquarters in Ireland]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/gemini-to-establish-european-headquarters-in-ireland</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:56:16 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/gemini-to-establish-european-headquarters-in-ireland</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Winklevoss-owned crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co. will establish its European headquarters in Dublin, Ireland. </p>
<p>US-based Gemini announced it will run its European operations out of Dublin, Ireland. Cameron Winklevoss shared the news via his Twitter feed on Thursday as American crypto exchanges scramble to widen operations amid the intensifying regulatory crackdown in the US.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Awesome meeting this morning with @LeoVaradkar, the Prime Minister of Ireland. We talked about the profound promise of crypto and the importance of common sense regulation to realize that promise. We believe MiCA is that common sense regulation. We also announced that @Gemini has&hellip; pic.twitter.com/Iv3NmPTmju</p>
&mdash; Cameron Winklevoss (@cameron) May 25, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Bloomberg reports Gemini cited Dublin&rsquo;s thriving start-up culture as a pull factor for the exchange to set up its European operations there. After the European Union&rsquo;s Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation was approved last week, several crypto firms are considering a shift away from the US.</p>
Gemini Is the First Crypto Exchange to Register as a VASP in Ireland
<p>Leo Varadkar, Prime Minister of Ireland, congratulated Gemini on Twitter.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Congratulations @Gemini -the first firm registered by the Central Bank of Ireland as a Virtual Asset Service Provider. This is significant for Ireland as the Government focuses on innovation as a driver of growth. I wish Gemini every success as they build their team in Ireland. pic.twitter.com/Y3WULIqwNc</p>
&mdash; Leo Varadkar (@LeoVaradkar) May 25, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The PM further said Gemini&rsquo;s decision to establish its headquarters in Ireland points towards the Irish government&rsquo;s dedication to innovation.</p>
<p>Varadkar said:</p>

<p>Gemini&rsquo;s decision to locate in Ireland highlights our competitive offering for the international financial services sector. I wish Gemini every success as they build their team in Ireland.</p>

<p>In July 2022, Gemini became the first cryptocurrency exchange to register as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) by the Central Bank of Ireland. The exchange also secured the Bank&rsquo;s Electronic Money Institution (EMI) license in February 2022.</p>
Gemini Launches Offshore Crypto Derivatives Exchange
<p>Less than a month ago, Gemini launched Gemini Foundation, an offshore cryptocurrency derivative platform. The new exchange launched in 30 countries but is not available to US, UK, or EU users.</p>
<p>Gemini said the platform would allow users to begin trading with Bitcoin perpetual contracts, denominated in Gemini Dollar (GUSD) and offers 100x leverage.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Winklevoss-owned crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co. will establish its European headquarters in Dublin, Ireland. </p>
<p>US-based Gemini announced it will run its European operations out of Dublin, Ireland. Cameron Winklevoss shared the news via his Twitter feed on Thursday as American crypto exchanges scramble to widen operations amid the intensifying regulatory crackdown in the US.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Awesome meeting this morning with @LeoVaradkar, the Prime Minister of Ireland. We talked about the profound promise of crypto and the importance of common sense regulation to realize that promise. We believe MiCA is that common sense regulation. We also announced that @Gemini has&hellip; pic.twitter.com/Iv3NmPTmju</p>
&mdash; Cameron Winklevoss (@cameron) May 25, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Bloomberg reports Gemini cited Dublin&rsquo;s thriving start-up culture as a pull factor for the exchange to set up its European operations there. After the European Union&rsquo;s Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation was approved last week, several crypto firms are considering a shift away from the US.</p>
Gemini Is the First Crypto Exchange to Register as a VASP in Ireland
<p>Leo Varadkar, Prime Minister of Ireland, congratulated Gemini on Twitter.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Congratulations @Gemini -the first firm registered by the Central Bank of Ireland as a Virtual Asset Service Provider. This is significant for Ireland as the Government focuses on innovation as a driver of growth. I wish Gemini every success as they build their team in Ireland. pic.twitter.com/Y3WULIqwNc</p>
&mdash; Leo Varadkar (@LeoVaradkar) May 25, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The PM further said Gemini&rsquo;s decision to establish its headquarters in Ireland points towards the Irish government&rsquo;s dedication to innovation.</p>
<p>Varadkar said:</p>

<p>Gemini&rsquo;s decision to locate in Ireland highlights our competitive offering for the international financial services sector. I wish Gemini every success as they build their team in Ireland.</p>

<p>In July 2022, Gemini became the first cryptocurrency exchange to register as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) by the Central Bank of Ireland. The exchange also secured the Bank&rsquo;s Electronic Money Institution (EMI) license in February 2022.</p>
Gemini Launches Offshore Crypto Derivatives Exchange
<p>Less than a month ago, Gemini launched Gemini Foundation, an offshore cryptocurrency derivative platform. The new exchange launched in 30 countries but is not available to US, UK, or EU users.</p>
<p>Gemini said the platform would allow users to begin trading with Bitcoin perpetual contracts, denominated in Gemini Dollar (GUSD) and offers 100x leverage.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Hong Kong soon to open for crypto but companies must comply]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/hong-kong-soon-to-open-for-crypto-but-companies-must-comply</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:10:35 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/hong-kong-soon-to-open-for-crypto-but-companies-must-comply</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong's Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has recently introduced a series of stringent rules that are set to reshape the landscape of virtual asset trading within the city.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While offering a pathway for platforms to apply for licences starting June 1, the SFC also imposed restrictions on air drops and stablecoins, along with other requirements such as a 12-month track record for tokens and increased capital regulations for exchanges. As Hong Kong strives to establish itself as a global hub for virtual assets it is committed to a tight regulatory regime.</p>
Opening Doors for Virtual Asset Trading
<p>Effective from June 1, the SFC's new rules dictate that platforms engaged in virtual asset trading can now apply for licences. This move aims to establish a more structured and regulated environment for investors and traders. However, the SFC has also made it clear that virtual asset service providers (VASPs) who do not plan to obtain licences should initiate an orderly closure of their operations in Hong Kong.</p>
Striving for Transparency
<p>To ensure investor protection, tokens seeking listing on exchanges must now have a minimum 12-month track record. This requirement serves as a gatekeeping measure to ensure that only established and reputable tokens find their way into the trading ecosystem. Additionally, VASPs are now obligated to conduct thorough due diligence on tokens before listing them, enhancing transparency and mitigating risks.</p>
Capital Requirements and Reporting Obligations
<p>The new regulations introduce capital requirements for exchanges, mandating a minimum capital of HK$5,000,000 (US$640,000). Furthermore, exchanges must disclose their available and required liquid capital, outstanding bank loans, advances, and credit facilities, as well as provide a monthly profit and loss analysis to the SFC. These measures aim to enhance financial stability and promote responsible operations within the virtual asset trading space.</p>
Towards a Global Virtual Assets Hub
<p>Hong Kong's recent regulatory actions are part of a larger strategy to position itself as a prominent global hub for virtual assets. Investors will be closely observing how these regulations shape the market and also serve as an indicator of China's willingness to engage with the wider crypto industry. While crypto remains banned in mainland China, Hong Kong's progress may provide insights into potential shifts in China's regulatory landscape.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong's Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) has recently introduced a series of stringent rules that are set to reshape the landscape of virtual asset trading within the city.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While offering a pathway for platforms to apply for licences starting June 1, the SFC also imposed restrictions on air drops and stablecoins, along with other requirements such as a 12-month track record for tokens and increased capital regulations for exchanges. As Hong Kong strives to establish itself as a global hub for virtual assets it is committed to a tight regulatory regime.</p>
Opening Doors for Virtual Asset Trading
<p>Effective from June 1, the SFC's new rules dictate that platforms engaged in virtual asset trading can now apply for licences. This move aims to establish a more structured and regulated environment for investors and traders. However, the SFC has also made it clear that virtual asset service providers (VASPs) who do not plan to obtain licences should initiate an orderly closure of their operations in Hong Kong.</p>
Striving for Transparency
<p>To ensure investor protection, tokens seeking listing on exchanges must now have a minimum 12-month track record. This requirement serves as a gatekeeping measure to ensure that only established and reputable tokens find their way into the trading ecosystem. Additionally, VASPs are now obligated to conduct thorough due diligence on tokens before listing them, enhancing transparency and mitigating risks.</p>
Capital Requirements and Reporting Obligations
<p>The new regulations introduce capital requirements for exchanges, mandating a minimum capital of HK$5,000,000 (US$640,000). Furthermore, exchanges must disclose their available and required liquid capital, outstanding bank loans, advances, and credit facilities, as well as provide a monthly profit and loss analysis to the SFC. These measures aim to enhance financial stability and promote responsible operations within the virtual asset trading space.</p>
Towards a Global Virtual Assets Hub
<p>Hong Kong's recent regulatory actions are part of a larger strategy to position itself as a prominent global hub for virtual assets. Investors will be closely observing how these regulations shape the market and also serve as an indicator of China's willingness to engage with the wider crypto industry. While crypto remains banned in mainland China, Hong Kong's progress may provide insights into potential shifts in China's regulatory landscape.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
