<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 09:38:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>92% of Global Respondents Have Basic Knowledge of Crypto: Survey</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/92-of-global-respondents-have-basic-knowledge-of-crypto-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 22:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigeria]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257551</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/Cryptocurrencies-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/Cryptocurrencies-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Nigerians and Argentines seem to be the most optimistic about crypto's future, compared to Japanese, Americans, and Brits, who predominantly disagree.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A joint research conducted by Consensys and YouGov estimated that 92% of the participants are aware of cryptocurrencies. 37% see the asset class as the future money, whereas 26% are on the opposite corner, viewing it as a scam.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Residents of the United States and the United Kingdom are more likely to associate digital currencies with fraudulent schemes.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Sentiment Toward Crypto and NFTs</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The survey, which spread across the Americas, Asia, Europe, and Africa and questioned over 15,000 individuals, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://consensys.io/blog/global-survey-on-crypto-and-web3-press-release" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">showed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that most respondents are aware of cryptocurrencies, with many seeing a bright future for the industry.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nearly 40% of the participants believe the asset class could emerge as the future of money, while 31% see it as the future of digital ownership. Every fourth gives the sector the evil eye, comparing it to a scam.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nigerians (65%) and Argentines (56%) are most motivated to hold digital assets as a means to store value. This could be explained by the instability of their financial system and local currencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nigerians are also the most inclined to associate crypto with the future of money. South Africans and Mexicans are, respectively, second and third. On the other hand, only 15% of Brits and 17% of Germans agree with that thesis.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The survey touched upon the environmental impact which the technology has on the planet. 57% of Brazilians believe it is not harmful, whereas just 25% of the French respondents think the same.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, the analysis revealed that Nigeria, South Africa, and Vietnam are the countries most familiar with non-fungible tokens (NFTs). 76% of the Brits who are aware of digital collectibles have never owned any, compared to 24% of Vietnamese.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Results reveal that people worldwide are motivated to build and believe they are making valuable contributions online. This evolution indicates a shift in user behavior toward active participation, empowerment, and broader community ownership, characterized by Web3,&#8221; Consensys and YouGov concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Closer Look at Nigeria and Argentina</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The economic turbulence, most specifically the depreciation of their official currencies, could be a leading pro-crypto factor for Nigerians and Argentines. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/nigerians-rush-to-buy-bitcoin-amid-economy-collapse-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last summer, some residents of the African country started looking for alternative investments such as bitcoin and stablecoins amid a severe crash of the naira. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For their part, Argentines have opened their arms toward the asset class due to the nation&#8217;s political chaos and financial disturbance. The price of USDT measured in Argentine peso </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/argentines-embrace-crypto-following-resignation-of-economy-minister/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">soared</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on multiple exchanges in 2022 when Martin Guzman resigned as a Minister of Economy. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/92-of-global-respondents-have-basic-knowledge-of-crypto-survey/" rel="nofollow">92% of Global Respondents Have Basic Knowledge of Crypto: Survey</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>50% of German Crypto Investors View Digital Assets as Long-Term Investment (Survey)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/50-of-german-crypto-investors-view-digital-assets-as-long-term-investment-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 19:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257904</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Germany-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Germany-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[22% of German cryptocurrency investors think digital currencies could help them get rich overnight.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a KuCoin research, 49% of German crypto investors believe digital currencies could help them achieve long-term wealth accumulation plans. Every fourth thinks the asset class could serve as a store of value amid the current economic turbulence.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Most German crypto investors fall in the Generation Y demographic group, also known as Millennials (those born between the 1980s and the late 1990s).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Closer Look</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The survey </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.kucoin.com/blog/kucoin-s-into-the-cryptoverse-report-reveals-german-users-love-for-versatile-crypto-projects" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that Millennials account for 51% of the total number of cryptocurrency investors in Germany, while Generation X (those in their 40s and 50s) is second with 30%. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Digital assets are usually an interesting matter for youngsters as they are more open-minded toward innovations. However, Generation Z (those aged 18-25) represents only 19% of all Germans with exposure to the crypto market. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The biggest share of people hopped on the bandwagon less than three months ago, whereas 15% have done so in the past half a year. One possible reason behind that interest could be crypto&#8217;s revival since the start of 2023. Bitcoin, for example, finished 2022 at around $16,500, while currently, it is well above the $30,000 level. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Every fourth German crypto investor entered the ecosystem to diversify their portfolios. 30% find investing in digital assets &#8220;convenient,&#8221; whereas 22% want to get rich overnight. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The most popular use cases for crypto in Germany include trading, online shopping, purchasing non-fungible tokens (NFTs), HODLing/staking, accepting/paying salaries, and others.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unsurprisingly, Bitcoin (BTC) is the primary crypto investment choice for locals, with 64% of the investors having exposure to it. 40% have bought Ethereum (ETH), while 26% have bought NFTs.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">KuCoin believes the cryptocurrency landscape in Germany is &#8220;evolving.&#8221; It sees this as a &#8220;promising sign, considering the rapid pace at which the crypto market develops and adopts emerging technologies, such as artificial intelligence (AI), augmented reality (AR), virtual reality (VR), and more.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, the company argued that interest in Ethereum and other similar projects indicates the potential of an upcoming Web3 revolution in Europe&#8217;s strongest economy.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Germany&#8217;s Pro-Crypto Stance</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another survey carried out by Coincub </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/germany-is-the-most-crypto-friendly-nation-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">estimated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the European country is the most crypto-friendly nation for Q1 2022. Germany&#8217;s acceptance of the asset class and its &#8220;groundbreaking decision&#8221; to allow investments helped for the top position, the entity outlined.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Shortly after, the German authorities doubled down by </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/germany-no-taxes-for-selling-btc-and-eth-if-held-for-over-a-year/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">making</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the sale of BTC and ETH tax-free if those assets were held for over 12 months. Prior to that, people had to keep such holdings for ten years to be exempt from taxation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlike other European countries, Germany has imposed some regulations in the past few years. Legislation that was approved in 2020 requires all cryptocurrency exchanges operating inside the nation&#8217;s borders to secure a license from the Federal Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin). Such entities must also hold a minimum amount of capital and comply with anti-money laundering policies. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/50-of-german-crypto-investors-view-digital-assets-as-long-term-investment-survey/" rel="nofollow">50% of German Crypto Investors View Digital Assets as Long-Term Investment (Survey)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man Who Paid $20K in BTC to Hitman to Kill a Child Goes to Prison for 6 Years (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/man-who-paid-20k-in-btc-to-hitman-to-kill-a-child-goes-to-prison-for-6-years-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 16:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257510</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Prison-min-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Prison-min-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Musbach avoided the maximum sentence of ten years.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">John Michael Musbach &#8211; a 34-year-old resident of Haddonfield, New Jersey &#8211; was reportedly sentenced to six and a half years in jail for hiring a hitman to commit a murder.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He transferred $20,000 worth of BTC to the &#8220;executor&#8221; to kill a kid that was about to testify against him in a child-pornography case. Moreover, the youngster was the victim. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Gruesome Crime That Led to the Punishment</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://patch.com/new-jersey/haddon/haddonfield-man-who-paid-hitman-kill-kid-sentenced-prison" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Musbach exchanged sexually explicit videos and photographs with a 13-year-old child in the summer of 2015. The victim&#8217;s parents learned about the offense and contacted law enforcement agents. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">New York&#8217;s police identified that Musbach was behind the crime. The authorities collaborated with the Atlantic County Prosecutor&#8217;s office, which arrested him in March 2016. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition to the pornography charges, the investigators discovered that Musbach had even more horrid intentions. Upon searching his home, they detected he was looking for a hitman on the Dark Web that could kill the child so it won&#8217;t testify against him. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The man asked one potential &#8220;killer&#8221; whether murdering a 14-year-old would be an issue. He was assured that the target&#8217;s age was not a problem and paid approximately 40 BTC (equaling around $20,000 at the time).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Musbach pleaded guilty in 2017 to endangering the welfare of a child by sexual contact. He received a two-year suspended sentence with parole supervision for life. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After finding out about his murder plans, though, the Camden federal court changed the punishment to six and a half years. He faced a maximum sentence of ten years behind bars.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Surprisingly, not the First Case</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scott Quinn Berkett &#8211; a 26-year-old resident of Beverly Hills, Los Angeles &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/california-man-pays-a-hitman-13k-in-bitcoin-to-kill-his-ex-girlfriend-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pleaded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> guilty last summer to sending $13K in bitcoin to a hitman on the Dark Web whose task was to kill Berkett&#8217;s ex-girlfriend.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Undercover agents discovered the crime and contacted the offender introducing themselves as the killer. Berkett confirmed his intentions and even sent additional money to the detectives. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prosecutors have initially aimed at a ten-year prison sentence. However, they later recommended a five-year one because Berkett&#8217;s &#8220;mental health condition is a mitigating factor.&#8221; Judge Scarsi followed that guidance and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://lawandcrime.com/crime/a-man-paid-bitcoin-to-a-scam-dark-web-murder-for-hire-service-to-kill-a-woman-who-rejected-his-advances-now-hes-going-to-federal-prison/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sent</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> him to prison for 60 months.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/man-who-paid-20k-in-btc-to-hitman-to-kill-a-child-goes-to-prison-for-6-years-report/" rel="nofollow">Man Who Paid $20K in BTC to Hitman to Kill a Child Goes to Prison for 6 Years (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Not Just BlackRock: These Companies Have Also Filed for Spot Bitcoin ETF in the US</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 14:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258007</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/bitcoinetf_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/bitcoinetf_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BlackRock’s filing renewed the hopes of several U.S. traditional finance firms. Here's the list of companies that have resubmitted their applications. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past two weeks, there has been a series of spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applications from different traditional finance giants in the United States.</p>
<p>The frenzy started after BlackRock, the world’s biggest asset manager with over $9 trillion in AUM, submitted its spot Bitcoin ETF filing with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on June 15.</p>
<h2>A Bitcoin Spot ETF Frenzy</h2>
<p>BlackRock’s move spurred several Bitcoin ETF hopefuls to make fresh applications despite repeated rejections from the SEC in the past. The development also triggered a BTC rally that caused the leading crypto asset to soar past $30,000 and chart a multi-month peak.</p>
<p>An ETF is an investment vehicle that tracks the value of an underlying asset. A Bitcoin ETF would expose investors to the cryptocurrency without the burden of physically buying and holding the digital asset. It also relieves them of the stress of understanding the complexities of crypto exchanges, private keys, and crypto wallets.</p>
<p>A spot Bitcoin ETF directly tracks the price of BTC, while a futures Bitcoin ETF would follow the price of the asset’s futures contracts.</p>
<p>The SEC has rejected dozens of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the past, arguing that the proposals did not meet anti-fraud and investor protection standards. The regulator also mentioned the potential for market manipulation of the underlying crypto asset.</p>
<p>However, BlackRock’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-for-bitcoin-spot-etf-btc-dropped-to-3-month-low-as-fed-pauses-interest-rate-hikes-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">application</a> has renewed the hopes of several traditional firms in the U.S.</p>
<h2>U.S. Companies That Have Filed for Spot Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>Shortly after BlackRock’s ETF application, which mentioned Coinbase Custody as its crypto custodian and BNY Mellon as its cash custodian, New York-based asset manager WisdomTree <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-blackrock-two-more-asset-managers-file-to-launch-a-btc-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">resubmitted</a> its filing for approval on June 20. The SEC previously rejected WisdomTree’s spot filing twice, in 2021 and 2022; hence, this is the firm’s third attempt.</p>
<p>Investment management company Invesco also submitted its second spot Bitcoin ETF application on the same day as WisdomTree. The firm and Galaxy Digital initially filed a joint application in September 2021.</p>
<p>Shortly after, financial services firm Valkyrie rejoined the queue, filing for the Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund on June 21. The company’s initial filing was rejected around Christmas 2021.</p>
<p>Up next was investment manager VanEck’s refiling on June 22 after two <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">rejections</a> in 2021 and March 2023.</p>
<p>On June 29, Fidelity Digital Assets tried again with a spot Bitcoin ETF filing after modifications to make the document identical to BlackRock’s submission.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest and Swiss-based ETF provider 21Shares <a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-028.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">submitted</a> their <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf-rejected-by-the-sec-once-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">third application</a> on April 25 to launch the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" rel="nofollow">Not Just BlackRock: These Companies Have Also Filed for Spot Bitcoin ETF in the US</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity, VanEck, Invesco Amend Bitcoin Spot ETF Filings Following SEC&#8217;s Warning (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-vaneck-invesco-amend-bitcoin-spot-etf-filings-following-secs-warning-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258130</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/FidelitySEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/FidelitySEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase now plays a key role in almost all Bitcoin Spot ETF filings. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several financial giants, including Fidelity, 21Shares, and WisdomTree, have changed their filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission in regard to their applications for Bitcoin Spot ETFs.</p>
<p>This comes just hours after the US securities regulator reportedly warned that all recent filings for such products were &#8220;inadequate.&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>BlackRock <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" data-wpel-link="internal">splashed the waters</a> two weeks ago when it filed with the SEC to launch a Bitcoin Spot exchange-traded fund. While it was definitely not the first to try its luck, it was unquestionably the largest financial entity to do so.</li>
<li>The move was mimicked by several other notable players, including Fidelity, which copied BlackRock&#8217;s application, while Ark Invest changed its own to be the same as the world&#8217;s largest asset manager.</li>
<li>However, the Wall Street Journal <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal">cited</a> people familiar with the matter that said the SEC was not impressed by the recent filings as they were not “sufficiently clear and comprehensive.”</li>
<li>Aside from the negative effects on BTC&#8217;s price, the SEC&#8217;s warning resulted in immediate actions from the companies that have active applications for such a product.</li>
<li>As <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/fidelity-leads-flurry-of-bitcoin-etf-refilings-to-answer-sec-1.1940300" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by Bloomberg, some of the names include Fidelity Investments, Invesco, 21Shares, WisdomTree, and VanEck.</li>
<li>All changes involve Coinbase, as the largest US exchange has now been named as custodian of the funds and will provide market surveillance. The SEC has previously rejected all Spot Bitcoin ETF applications alleging that they failed to provide clear information on how the products aim to protect investors from market manipulation.</li>
<li>It&#8217;s worth noting, though, that the Commission has its own legal issues with Coinbase, as it sued the latter for selling unregistered securities. The exchange denied the allegations and most recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-request-for-dismissal-of-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> to have all charges dropped.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-vaneck-invesco-amend-bitcoin-spot-etf-filings-following-secs-warning-report/" rel="nofollow">Fidelity, VanEck, Invesco Amend Bitcoin Spot ETF Filings Following SEC&#8217;s Warning (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Eyes $20 After 5% Daily Jump, Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $30K: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/solana-sol-eyes-20-after-5-daily-jump-bitcoin-btc-maintains-30k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 08:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258184</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Solana_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Solana_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Flow is today's top performer following a massive 20% surge that drove it to above $0.65.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has calmed after the Friday rollercoaster that drove it up and down by over a grand and remains relatively still at $30,500.</p>
<p>The altcoins are also less volatile today, as it typically happens during the weekends, with SOL emerging as the most substantial gainer from the larger caps.</p>
<h2>BTC Above $30K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin went on a tear last week when it jumped from $26,500 to over $31,000 to register a new multi-month high. The bears tried to intervene but only managed to halt BTC&#8217;s price surge, and the asset remained stuck in a range between $30,000 and $31,000 for the past seven days or so.</p>
<p>That all changed on Friday following <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal">reports</a> that the SEC could reject the most recent Bitcoin Spot ETF applications filed by the likes of BlackRock, Fidelity, and others as they supposedly lacked critical information.</p>
<p>BTC reacted with an immediate nosedive that took it from over $31,000 to a 10-day low of $29,500 (on Bitstamp). However, the bulls stepped up and pushed the cryptocurrency north shortly after, resulting in a recovery to $30,500 on Saturday.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours have been quite calm, with the asset remaining at around that time. As such, its market cap is still just under $600 billion, and its dominance over the altcoins is shy of 50%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258185" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258185" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-258185" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258185" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SOL Eyes $20</h2>
<p>The altcoins also experienced impressive price increases over the past few weeks, with some standing out the most. Such was the case with Bitcoin Cash which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-explodes-33-to-14-month-high-solana-and-litecoin-soar-15-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">exploded</a> by over 100% weekly at one point and registered a 14-month high above $320 earlier this week.</p>
<p>The case with LTC was similar yesterday as it also had a new <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-ltc-soars-to-14-month-high-above-100-bitcoin-btc-reclaims-30k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">14-month peak</a> at over $110. However, the landscape is less volatile now, with LTC, DOGE, ETH, TRX, DOT, BCH, and SHIB charting insignificant losses.</p>
<p>In contrast, XRP is up by almost 3% but still stands under $0.5, and SOL jumped by roughly 5% to over $19.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has added less than $10 billion in a day but has managed to tap $1.2 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258186" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258186" style="width: 1881px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-258186" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1881" height="841" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1.jpg 1881w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1-1024x458.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1-768x343.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1-1536x687.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1881px) 100vw, 1881px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258186" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-sol-eyes-20-after-5-daily-jump-bitcoin-btc-maintains-30k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Solana (SOL) Eyes $20 After 5% Daily Jump, Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $30K: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Global Race to CBDCs: 130 Countries Already Exploring (Research)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-global-race-to-cbdcs-130-countries-already-exploring-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 04:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257724</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/CBDC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/CBDC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Asian nations seem most inclined to hop on the CBDC bandwagon, while many African countries are still standing aside.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">An analysis conducted by Atlantic Council revealed that 130 nations, or 98% of the global GDP, are &#8220;exploring&#8221; a central bank digital currency (CBDC). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">11 countries have fully launched one, with China being an example.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Closer Look at the CBDC Trends</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The research <a href="https://www.atlanticcouncil.org/cbdctracker/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">estimated </a>that 95 counties had joined the CBDC race in the past three years. As of the moment, 130 nations have introduced some programs, with many being developed economies, such as Japan, South Korea, Australia, the UK, and more. Most countries (46) are currently in the &#8220;research&#8221; phase, whereas 21 have launched pilot tests.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_257755" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257755" style="width: 1337px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC-.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257755" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC-.png" alt="Number of Countries That are Exploring CBDC" width="1337" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC-.png 1621w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC--300x90.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC--1024x306.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC--768x230.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC--1536x460.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CBDC--50x15.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1337px) 100vw, 1337px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257755" class="wp-caption-text">Number of Countries That are Exploring CBDC, Source: Atlantic Council</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Almost every G20 country &#8220;has made significant progress and invested new resources in these projects over the past six months,&#8221; Atlantic Council stated. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The nations that seem most determined to issue a digital version of their official currencies include China, Nigeria, the Bahamas, Jamaica, and other Caribbean islands.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Chinese authorities have introduced several initiatives to popularize the digital yuan. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Major local cities such as Shenzhen, Jinan, and Lianyungan <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-cities-introduce-digital-yuan-payments-during-the-spring-festival-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">offered</a> numerous activities for this year&#8217;s Spring Festival to encourage the usage of the CBDC. Prior to that, the officials allowed digital yuan payments during the 2022 Winter Olympic Games held in Beijing. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the analysis, the progress on retail CBDC in the United States of America &#8220;has stalled.&#8221; On the other hand, the world&#8217;s largest economy has moved forward on a wholesale (bank-to-bank) CBDC.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Since Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine and the G7 sanctions response, wholesale CBDC developments have doubled,&#8221; the company behind the study claimed.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other leading economies like Japan and the United Kingdom are developing prototypes and are considering consulting the public on the eventual release of a CBDC.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The European Central Bank has also displayed intentions to introduce a digital euro. The European Commission recently shed more light on the project, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.euronews.com/my-europe/2023/06/28/brussels-unveils-plans-for-a-digital-euro-promising-complete-privacy" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">describing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it as an alternative wide-payment solution employed in online and offline trading. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For their part, Brazil and India intend to launch their CBDCs next year. Banco Central do Brasil recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/mercado-bitcoin-to-support-brazils-cbdc-efforts-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">authorized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Mercado Bitcoin to participate in the project alongside the financial software fintech Sinqia, the brokerage firm Genial, and others.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Pros and Cons of CBDCs</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">There are different reasons why a central bank would seek the launch of such a product. Atlantic Council believes CBDCs could promote financial inclusion by providing money access to the unbanked population, introducing competition in the local monetary markets, increasing the efficiency of settlements, and lower transaction fees. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, CBDCs are much different than cryptocurrencies. The latter are famous for their decentralized nature.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CBDCs will be issued and controlled by central banks, meaning they could work against people&#8217;s privacy. Numerous individuals have warned about the release of those products. Ron DeSantis &#8211; Governor of Florida &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-cbdc-in-florida-says-governor-ron-desantis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">blasted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that technology as a surveillance tool, voicing support for a ban within the southern state.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy, who announced his run for President of the US, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robert-f-kennedy-to-enforce-pro-bitcoin-laws-should-he-become-president/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">labeled</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> CBDCs as products used for &#8220;oppression.&#8221; </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-global-race-to-cbdcs-130-countries-already-exploring-research/" rel="nofollow">The Global Race to CBDCs: 130 Countries Already Exploring (Research)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 60% of Institutional Investors Bullish on Crypto for Next 12 Months: Survey</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/over-60-of-institutional-investors-bullish-on-crypto-for-next-12-months-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 22:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257937</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Institutions.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Institutions.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Institutional investors expressed their belief in more real-world use cases and improvements in regulatory clarity, fueling the drive for crypto adoption.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new survey by Binance Research, the research arm of the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, found that most institutional investors are optimistic about the outlook of cryptocurrencies for the next 12 months.</p>
<p>Binance Research conducted the survey from March 31 to May 15, 2023, with 208 global institutional clients and VIP users as the respondents. The study, dubbed the &#8220;<a href="https://research.binance.com/en/analysis/institutional-crypto-outlook-survey-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Institutional Crypto Outlook Survey</a>,&#8221; explored the respondents&#8217; attitudes, preferences, motivations, and adoption toward crypto investments.</p>
<h2>A Positive Crypto Outlook</h2>
<p>The respondents comprised a diverse mix of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutional-investors-are-still-buying-crypto-according-to-a-coinbase-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">institutional investors</a> with various levels of experience and assets under management (AUM). More than 48% of the participants have over five years of crypto investing experience. Funds with crypto AUM below $25 million made up 52.4% of the surveyees, while those with AUM above $100 million accounted for 22.6%.</p>
<p>In the outlook category, 63.5% of the respondents expressed optimism for the crypto sector over the next 12 months. And when the time frame was extended to a decade, 88% of the surveyees indicated a positive outlook for crypto.</p>
<p>Regarding allocation, 47.1% of the participants disclosed that they maintained their crypto holdings over the past year, while 35.6% increased theirs within the same period. About half of the respondents expect to increase their crypto possessions with time, while 4.3% would do the opposite in the next year.</p>
<p>Investors&#8217; interests were focused on layer-1 and layer-2 sectors and infrastructure. Roughly 54% of participants found infrastructure most important to them or their fund, followed by layer-1 and layer-2 sectors at 48.1% and 43.8%. Decentralized applications (dApps) were discovered to be the most used in recent months.</p>
<h2>Driving Crypto Adoption</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the respondents expressed their belief in more real-world use cases and improvements in regulatory clarity fueling the drive for crypto adoption. Approximately 27% demanded more real-world use cases, while 25.3% asked for regulatory clarity.</p>
<p>The need for increased institutional participation through banks and other financial institutions also emerged as another driver of crypto <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutional-adoption-of-defi-is-many-years-away-says-blackrock-executive/" data-wpel-link="internal">adoption</a>, followed by stronger security like fraud detection and custody solutions.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The results highlight institutional investors&#8217; belief in broad ecosystem developments rather than short-term price action in driving widespread crypto adoption,&#8221; the report stated.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-60-of-institutional-investors-bullish-on-crypto-for-next-12-months-survey/" rel="nofollow">Over 60% of Institutional Investors Bullish on Crypto for Next 12 Months: Survey</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>$7.8 Billion Lost to Crypto Ponzi Schemes in 2022: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/7-8-billion-lost-to-crypto-ponzi-schemes-in-2022-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 18:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257908</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/ponzi_pyramid_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/ponzi_pyramid_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Once cyberattacks are added to the mix, a total of $11.5 billion worth of crypto has been lost to bad actors last year.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TRM Labs, a leading blockchain analysis firm focused on preventing cybercrime, has released a comprehensive report on the illicit sums lost to bad actors in the crypto space in 2022.</p>
<p>The figures are quite notable, especially given the declining prices and interest in the market last year.</p>
<h2>Improved Cybersecurity Measures</h2>
<p>In spite of the plummeting value of various digital assets due to crypto winter and the myriad collapses that accompanied it, the number of scams and thefts in the industry has not decreased significantly, at most staying in proportion to similar cases in previous years.</p>
<p>For instance, over $12 billion were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/overall-losses-from-defi-exploits-exceed-12-billion-in-2021-elliptic-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">lost</a> to DeFi exploits in 2021. Although this figure dwarfs the $3.7 billion lost to exploits in 2022, it’s worth noting that those $12 billion represent a sevenfold increase in DeFi exploits over the prior year, making 2022 an outlier by any measure.</p>
<p>In 2022, $3.7 billion was stolen across over 175 incidents, each of which resulted in an <a href="https://www.trmlabs.com/illicit-crypto-ecosystem-report-2023#Theft" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">average loss</a> of $20 million for the investors of the exploited projects. It’s worth noting that the smart contracts that were the main target of DeFi exploits in 2021 seem to have improved – only about 10% of cyberattacks in 2022 were protocol exploits, with the remaining 90% targeting the rest of the platforms’ infrastructure.</p>
<h2>Investors Still Enticed by Illicit Platforms</h2>
<p>About $7.8 billion were lost to pyramid schemes and similar Ponzi platforms in 2022. If other scams – such as romance frauds and phishing attacks – are taken into calculation, the crypto community lost over $9 billion in 2022 alone.</p>
<p>Although the pyramid scheme-type frauds at least provided some sort of value to investors until they ignominiously collapsed, the rate of fraudulent investment platforms and tokens – often offering a mere pipe dream – doubled in 2022, resulting in a total of $2.57 billion worth of crypto outright stolen from investors worldwide.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, pyramid schemes made up the lion’s share of ill-begotten gains, with about $7.8 billion in value disappearing overnight once they were no longer able to recruit new gullible marks.</p>
<p>The top 10 pyramid schemes accounted for 54% of the total take. The largest ones to collapse in 2022 were Forsage and the Trade Coin Club, with <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/victims-of-2-4b-bitconnect-ponzi-to-receive-17m-in-restitution/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitconnect</a> following close behind them.</p>
<p>About 40% of pyramid schemes in 2022 took place on the TRON network, mostly involving USDT. The report also touches on the sums involved in illicit markets, which, although very illegal, only generated about $1.5 billion in revenue for bad actors, far less than the amount generated by outright fraud.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/7-8-billion-lost-to-crypto-ponzi-schemes-in-2022-report/" rel="nofollow">$7.8 Billion Lost to Crypto Ponzi Schemes in 2022: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI TalentGPT Stands Tall Against Memes Like Doge, Shiba, and Pepe</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ai-talentgpt-stands-tall-against-memes-like-doge-shiba-and-pepe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258157</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-5.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-5.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There is an evident pattern in the crypto market when it comes to Meme tokens like Doge, Shiba, and Pepe. They all have a hype that only a few cashed on, and the rest are trying to onboard the passed bus. Unlike them, utility tokens tend to come with slower growth, less hype, but also [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is an evident pattern in the crypto market when it comes to Meme tokens like Doge, Shiba, and Pepe.</p>
<p>They all have a hype that only a few cashed on, and the rest are trying to onboard the passed bus. Unlike them, utility tokens tend to come with slower growth, less hype, but also with long-term potential.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258160" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3.png" alt="aitgpt" width="2560" height="1440" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3.png 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3-1536x864.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3-2048x1152.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Telegram-3-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h2>Utility vs Meme Tokens</h2>
<p>In the world of cryptocurrencies, the clash between utility tokens and meme tokens has captured significant attention. Meme tokens, like ike Doge, Shiba, and Pepe, characterized by their explosive but oftentimes short-lived hype, often leave investors high and dry.</p>
<p>On the other hand, utility tokens like AI TalentGPT (AITGPT) present a different narrative, offering real-world value and long-term potential. This article explores the presale of AI TalentGPT, delving into the advantages of utility tokens over meme tokens and how AI TalentGPT stands out as a promising solution that reshapes the crypto landscape.</p>
<p>In contrast, Utility tokens demonstrate a more gradual growth trajectory, characterized by lesser hype and a focus on long-term potential. Unlike Meme tokens, Utility tokens offer tangible value and real-world utility, which contributes to their sustained and meaningful development over time. This divergence in approach highlights the importance of considering the underlying value and utility of a token when assessing its long-term prospects in the crypto market.</p>
<h2>The Lifecycle of Meme Tokens</h2>
<p>In recent times, the cryptocurrency market has witnessed a surge of meme tokens like Doge, Shiba, and Pepe that gain popularity overnight, driven by social media buzz and celebrity endorsements. Investors are enticed by the promise of quick and astronomical returns, lured into the frenzy by the allure of easy profits.</p>
<p>However, the reality often proves harsh, as meme tokens are highly volatile and susceptible to pump-and-dump schemes. Once the hype subsides, these tokens rapidly plummet in value, leaving investors with substantial losses.</p>
<h2>The Value Proposition of Utility Tokens</h2>
<p>In contrast, utility tokens like AI TalentGPT (AITGPT) operate on a different principle. Rather than relying solely on speculative fervor, utility tokens derive their worth from the tangible benefits they offer within their respective ecosystems. AI TalentGPT (AITGPT) serves as the fuel that powers the AI TalentGPT platform, providing users with access to premium features, services, and participation in the platform&#8217;s governance. These tokens are rooted in real-world applications, addressing genuine problems and driving meaningful innovation.</p>
<h2>AI TalentGPT: Revolutionizing the Crypto Space</h2>
<p>AI TalentGPT (AITGPT) is poised to revolutionize the crypto space by merging the power of AI and utility tokens. The platform offers a novel approach to talent acquisition, employing AI technology to streamline the recruitment process and connect job seekers with suitable opportunities. By leveraging the AI TalentGPT ecosystem, users can access premium features, contribute to AI training tasks, and engage in knowledge exchange.</p>
<p>The presale of <a href="https://www.aitalentgpt.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">AI TalentGPT (AITGPT)</a> presents a unique opportunity for investors. Unlike meme tokens that fade into obscurity, AI TalentGPT is driven by a genuine need for AI-powered recruitment solutions, ensuring sustained demand and utility. The presale participants not only become early adopters but also gain voting rights, allowing them to actively shape the future of the platform.</p>
<h2>Utility of AI TalentGPT (AITGPT)</h2>
<p>The primary motive of <a href="https://www.aitalentgpt.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AI TalentGPT (AITGPT)</a> tokens is to incentivize user engagement in MyBeamery Platform to facilitate AI training by completing simple tasks and earn. Also, this token will help to ensure long-term sustainability of AI TalentGPT Platform (ChatGPT-based AI Recruitment Platform).  The support team will work for the tokens, and users can trade it making AI talentGPT an open community-based platform. People who hold this token will also get to vote for the features and updates.</p>
<h2>What We Have Learnt</h2>
<p>As the battle between utility and meme tokens rages on, AI TalentGPT (AITGPT) emerges as a standout player in the crypto space. By focusing on utility, real-world applications, and long-term value creation, AI TalentGPT sets itself apart from the short-term hype associated with meme tokens like Doge, Shiba, and Pepe.</p>
<p>The presale of AI TalentGPT offers investors the opportunity to support an innovative platform that addresses the job market&#8217;s needs while positioning themselves for potential long-term gains. As the utility token revolution continues, AI TalentGPT paves the way for a more sustainable and promising future in the crypto industry.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.aitalentgpt.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Presale: Here</a><br />
<a href="https://twitter.com/aitalentgpt" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Twitter: Here</a><br />
<a href="https://t.me/aitalentgpt" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Telegram: Here</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ai-talentgpt-stands-tall-against-memes-like-doge-shiba-and-pepe/" rel="nofollow">AI TalentGPT Stands Tall Against Memes Like Doge, Shiba, and Pepe</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
