<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>House Financial Services Chair Wants To Vote on Digital Asset Bill Next Month</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-financial-services-chair-wants-vote-digital-asset-bill-next-month.htm</link><description>US House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick T. McHenry plans to hold a vote on a bill that would regulate digital assets by mid July. &lt;br /&gt;
The draft legislation in question, the Digital Asset Market Structure Discussion Draft, would classify cryptocurrencies as a security or a commodity and regulate exchanges among other measures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/house-financial-services-chair-wants-vote-digital-asset-bill-next-month.htm"&gt;Read More: House Financial Services Chair Wants To Vote on Digital Asset Bill Next Month&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-financial-services-chair-wants-vote-digital-asset-bill-next-month.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116814/312838/adobestock-230599906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="533273"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Hover Near $26,000 Ahead of Key Fed Policy Announcement – Here’s How the BTC Price Might React</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-hover-near-26000-ahead-of-key-fed-policy-announcement-heres-how-btc-price-might-react.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin (BTC) price is hovering close to $26,000, well within its recent intra-day ranges in the lead-up to Wednesday’s key US Federal Reserve policy announcement. &lt;br /&gt;
The US central bank is expected to pause its cycle of aggressive interest rate hikes that began last March and have seen the bank lift rates by 500 bps (to 5.0-5.25%) in the last 10 meetings....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-hover-near-26000-ahead-of-key-fed-policy-announcement-heres-how-btc-price-might-react.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Hover Near $26,000 Ahead of Key Fed Policy Announcement – Here’s How the BTC Price Might React&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Fed</category><category>Interest Rates</category><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 02:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-hover-near-26000-ahead-of-key-fed-policy-announcement-heres-how-btc-price-might-react.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116829/312868/btc-6.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="255668"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 13 June – Terra Luna Classic, GMX, Fantom</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-13-june-terra-luna-classic-gmx-fantom.htm</link><description>The United States inflation rate has slowed down, with May recording a 4% rate--the lowest yearly figure since March 2021. &lt;br /&gt;
The drop in inflation may prompt the U.S. Federal Reserve to avoid raising interest rates during its upcoming Wednesday conference, prompting market observers to closely monitor the situation. &lt;br /&gt;
With the current economic situation in mind, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-13-june-terra-luna-classic-gmx-fantom.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 13 June – Terra Luna Classic, GMX, Fantom&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>CPI</category><category>CPI numbers</category><category>U.S. Federal Reserve</category><category>WSM</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>GMX</category><category>YPRED</category><category>ATOM</category><category>FTM</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Cosmos</category><category>Fantom</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Freelancing</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFTs</category><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-13-june-terra-luna-classic-gmx-fantom.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116826/312850/best-crypto-13june.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="310601"/></item><item><title>Brazil Central Bank Unveils CBDC, Tokenization ‘Events’ – Digital Real Rollout Imminent?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazil-central-bank-unveils-cbdc-tokenization-events-digital-real-rollout-imminent.htm</link><description>Brazil’s Central Bank, the Banco Central do Brasil (BCB), has unveiled a “roadmap” of events ahead of the nation’s CBDC rollout. &lt;br /&gt;
In an official BCB release, the bank stated that it would also begin assessing the possibility of enabling the launch of tokenized assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The BCB unveiled a list of “monthly webinars” as part of its digital real platform development....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazil-central-bank-unveils-cbdc-tokenization-events-digital-real-rollout-imminent.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazil Central Bank Unveils CBDC, Tokenization ‘Events’ – Digital Real Rollout Imminent?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazil-central-bank-unveils-cbdc-tokenization-events-digital-real-rollout-imminent.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116725/312726/brazil-12006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="323289"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Inflation Rate Data is Announced – Is the Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-inflation-rate-data-announced-is-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>The latest data on the US inflation rate indicates that consumer prices increased by 4% from a year earlier, marking a decrease from April's 4.9% and a significant drop from last June's 40-year high of 9.1%.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Labor Department's consumer price index reveals that this is the smallest yearly increase since March 2021.  &lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, on a monthly basis, prices saw a modest rise of 0.1% compared to April's 0.4% increase. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-inflation-rate-data-announced-is-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Inflation Rate Data is Announced – Is the Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-inflation-rate-data-announced-is-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116816/312841/13.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="483211"/></item><item><title>Sturdy Finance DeFi Protocol Faces Exploit, Loses More Than $750,000</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sturdy-finance-defi-protocol-faces-exploit-loses-more-than-750000.htm</link><description>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Sturdy Finance has been exploited, but the team has promised that no further action will be taken against the hackers if the money is returned. &lt;br /&gt;
Writing on Twitter on Tuesday, Sturdy Finance founder Sam Forman said his team has told the exploiter that they are offering a $100,000 bounty if all funds are returned to the protocol....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sturdy-finance-defi-protocol-faces-exploit-loses-more-than-750000.htm"&gt;Read More: Sturdy Finance DeFi Protocol Faces Exploit, Loses More Than $750,000&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>hacking</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sturdy-finance-defi-protocol-faces-exploit-loses-more-than-750000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116800/312821/hacking.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="154780"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Sui? SUI Price Bounces 34% From Recent Bottom and This New Penny Crypto Could Reach $1 Million Soon – What Does it Do?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-sui-sui-price-bounces-34-from-recent-bottom-new-penny-crypto-could-reach-1-million-soon-what-does-it-do.htm</link><description>Despite not being named a security in the SEC’s Binance and Coinbase lawsuits, the SUI price has dropped from a high of $0.96 to $0.51 in the days that followed. &lt;br /&gt;
SUI broke to the south of a short-term downtrend and lost almost 50% of its value – significantly more than most other altcoins in the same time frame. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-sui-sui-price-bounces-34-from-recent-bottom-new-penny-crypto-could-reach-1-million-soon-what-does-it-do.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Sui? SUI Price Bounces 34% From Recent Bottom and This New Penny Crypto Could Reach $1 Million Soon – What Does it Do?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SUI</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-sui-sui-price-bounces-34-from-recent-bottom-new-penny-crypto-could-reach-1-million-soon-what-does-it-do.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116809/312834/sui.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="220999"/></item><item><title>Bank of China Uses Ethereum Blockchain for $28 Million Digital Structured Notes – Crypto Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-china-uses-ethereum-blockchain-for-28-million-digital-structured-notes-crypto-adoption-rise.htm</link><description>Bank of China's investment arm BOCI has utilized the Ethereum blockchain network to issue $28 million worth of digital structured notes.  &lt;br /&gt;
The bank has become the first Chinese institution to issue this type of tokenized security in Hong Kong, global investment bank UBS said in a recent press release.  &lt;br /&gt;
The notes, which were worth CNH 200 million, were initiated by UBS and distributed to clients in the Asia-Pacific region. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-china-uses-ethereum-blockchain-for-28-million-digital-structured-notes-crypto-adoption-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of China Uses Ethereum Blockchain for $28 Million Digital Structured Notes – Crypto Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>China</category><category>Bank of China</category><category>UBS</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-china-uses-ethereum-blockchain-for-28-million-digital-structured-notes-crypto-adoption-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116808/312833/shanghai-g6de5da022-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="280594"/></item><item><title>The Sandbox is Going to Zero as the SEC Deems SAND to be a Security but This New AI Crypto Signals Platform May Be the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sandbox-going-zero-as-sec-deems-sand-security-but-new-ai-crypto-signals-platform-may-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</link><description>SAND, the native token that powers The Sandbox’s decentralized crypto, non-fungible token (NFT) and blockchain-powered metaverse, took an absolute beating last week. &lt;br /&gt;
When it hit fresh lows for the year just above $0.33 per token, the crypto token had lost a stunning nearly 50% of its value in less than seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
Ultimately, SAND ended the week with losses of around 35% in the $0.38 area, the cryptocurrency’s worst week since January 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sandbox-going-zero-as-sec-deems-sand-security-but-new-ai-crypto-signals-platform-may-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: The Sandbox is Going to Zero as the SEC Deems SAND to be a Security but This New AI Crypto Signals Platform May Be the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>The Sandbox</category><category>SAND</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>AI</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sandbox-going-zero-as-sec-deems-sand-security-but-new-ai-crypto-signals-platform-may-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116807/312832/sand.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="587324"/></item><item><title>The US Treasury Is Looking Into Privacy in Studying the Potential of a CBDC, Official Says</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-looking-into-privacy-studying-potential-of-cbdc-official-says.htm</link><description>The US Department of the Treasury is looking into privacy behind the potential of a future retail central bank digital currency, a Treasury official said on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
A retail CBDC has pros and cons, said Graham Steele, assistant secretary for financial institutions at US Treasury, on Tuesday at the Transform Payments US 2023 Conference in Texas.  &lt;br /&gt;
One challenge of a retail CBDC could be privacy, Steele said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-looking-into-privacy-studying-potential-of-cbdc-official-says.htm"&gt;Read More: The US Treasury Is Looking Into Privacy in Studying the Potential of a CBDC, Official Says&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Treasury</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-treasury-looking-into-privacy-studying-potential-of-cbdc-official-says.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116804/312829/adobestock-19789947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="433501"/></item><item><title>Blockstream CEO Adam Back: Bitcoin's Antifragility Will Prevail Amid Regulatory Pressures</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockstream-ceo-adam-back-bitcoins-antifragility-will-prevail-amid-regulatory-pressures.htm</link><description>Despite the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s crackdown against the biggest companies in crypto, one Bitcoin diehard isn't breaking a sweat. &lt;br /&gt;
Adam Back – CEO of Blockstream and popular cypherpunk – believes the crypto industry will simply adapt and relocate if it can’t find a home within the United States. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockstream-ceo-adam-back-bitcoins-antifragility-will-prevail-amid-regulatory-pressures.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockstream CEO Adam Back: Bitcoin's Antifragility Will Prevail Amid Regulatory Pressures&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockstream-ceo-adam-back-bitcoins-antifragility-will-prevail-amid-regulatory-pressures.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116802/312825/adobestock-186133910.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="174586"/></item><item><title>Celebrities Guy Fieri and Sammy Hagar Launch NFT Loyalty Program via Their Tequila Brand</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/celebrities-guy-fieri-sammy-hagar-launch-nft-loyalty-program-via-their-tequila-brand.htm</link><description>Celebrity chef Guy Fieri and Rock and Roll Hall of Famer Sammy Hagar are getting into non-fungible tokens through a new loyalty program launched by a tequila company they co-founded. &lt;br /&gt;
Through the tequila brand Santo Spirits, the pair announced a new Web3 loyalty program called the Santos Spirits Club, which will offer rewards and special offers, such as a virtual tasting of a soon to be released Santo Añejo Tequila with both Fieri and Hagar, autographed guitars, among other rewards. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celebrities-guy-fieri-sammy-hagar-launch-nft-loyalty-program-via-their-tequila-brand.htm"&gt;Read More: Celebrities Guy Fieri and Sammy Hagar Launch NFT Loyalty Program via Their Tequila Brand&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>NFT</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/celebrities-guy-fieri-sammy-hagar-launch-nft-loyalty-program-via-their-tequila-brand.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116799/312820/screen-shot-2023-06-13-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="823875"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Hinman Documents Go Public – Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-hinman-documents-go-public-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm</link><description>XRP, the cryptocurrency that powers the XRP Ledger, a layer-1 blockchain protocol, has reversed lower following an earlier pump to fresh multi-month highs in the $0.565 area. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency, which ranks as the world’s sixth largest with a market capitalization of around $26.5 billion, was last changing hands just under $0.51.XRP is now down more than 3%, having previously traded as much as 7.5% up on the day....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-hinman-documents-go-public-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Hinman Documents Go Public – Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>Ripple</category><category>XRP Ledger</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>SEC</category><category>Hinman</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-hinman-documents-go-public-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116798/312818/xrp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="602090"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: US Inflation Falls, Apple Threatens Damus Removal, Ripple Hinman Documents Unsealed + More News</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-us-inflation-falls-apple-threatens-damus-removal-ripple-hinman-documents-unsealed-more-news.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-us-inflation-falls-apple-threatens-damus-removal-ripple-hinman-documents-unsealed-more-news.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: US Inflation Falls, Apple Threatens Damus Removal, Ripple Hinman Documents Unsealed + More News&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><category>Apple</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>hacking</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>DAO</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-us-inflation-falls-apple-threatens-damus-removal-ripple-hinman-documents-unsealed-more-news.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116792/312812/federal-reserve.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1567350"/></item><item><title>Judge Rules in Favor of Galaxy Digital in Case Against BitGo Over $1.2 Billion Deal Cancellation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-rules-favor-of-galaxy-digital-case-against-bitgo-over-12-billion-deal-cancellation.htm</link><description>In a recent development, a federal judge in Delaware has ruled in favor of Galaxy Digital, the crypto merchant bank led by Mike Novogratz. &lt;br /&gt;
The case pertains to the termination of a $1.2 billion acquisition deal with BitGo. The court dismissed BitGo's lawsuit, stating that Galaxy had a valid basis for ending the agreement due to non-compliant financial documents provided by BitGo. &lt;br /&gt;
Citing Delaware Chancery Court Vice Chancellor James Laster during the ruling:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-rules-favor-of-galaxy-digital-case-against-bitgo-over-12-billion-deal-cancellation.htm"&gt;Read More: Judge Rules in Favor of Galaxy Digital in Case Against BitGo Over $1.2 Billion Deal Cancellation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>BitGo</category><category>Galaxy Digital</category><category>Galaxy Digital Capital Management</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-rules-favor-of-galaxy-digital-case-against-bitgo-over-12-billion-deal-cancellation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116796/312816/bitgo.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="619702"/></item><item><title>Circle CEO Allaire Puts Pressure on House Lawmakers To Pass a Stablecoin Bill</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-ceo-allaire-puts-pressure-house-lawmakers-pass-stablecoin-bill.htm</link><description>The CEO of stablecoin issuer Circle has put pressure on lawmakers to pass a stablecoin bill and get it signed by President Joe Biden as other countries forge ahead. &lt;br /&gt;
Delivering a stablecoin bill to “President Biden’s desk should be a national priority,” said CEO Jeremy Allaire in his prepared remarks ahead of Tuesday’s House Financial Services Committee hearing. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-ceo-allaire-puts-pressure-house-lawmakers-pass-stablecoin-bill.htm"&gt;Read More: Circle CEO Allaire Puts Pressure on House Lawmakers To Pass a Stablecoin Bill&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Jeremy Allaire</category><category>Circle</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-ceo-allaire-puts-pressure-house-lawmakers-pass-stablecoin-bill.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116783/312800/jeremy-allaire.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="371741"/></item><item><title>Mike Silagadze, CEO of ether.fi, on ETH, Re-Staking, and Building Start-Ups | Ep. 238</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/mike-silagadze-ceo-of-etherfi-on-eth-re-staking-and-building-start-ups-ep-238.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Mike Silagadze, Founder and CEO of ether.fi, talks about the importance of self-custody in Ether staking, the future of ETH, and “re-staking”.  &lt;br /&gt;
Mike Silagadze is the founder and CEO of ether.fi, the first decentralized, delegated staking protocol that allows stakers to maintain full control of their keys – and by extension, their staked ETH – throughout the entire staking process....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/mike-silagadze-ceo-of-etherfi-on-eth-re-staking-and-building-start-ups-ep-238.htm"&gt;Read More: Mike Silagadze, CEO of ether.fi, on ETH, Re-Staking, and Building Start-Ups | Ep. 238&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/mike-silagadze-ceo-of-etherfi-on-eth-re-staking-and-building-start-ups-ep-238.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116746/312766/mike-silagadze-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="116424"/></item><item><title>Telecom Giant Taiwan Mobile in Talks for Crypto Platform Investment</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/telecom-giant-taiwan-mobile-talks-for-crypto-platform-investment.htm</link><description>Telecommunications giant Taiwan Mobile is in talks with local crypto platforms about potential partnerships and even an investment in one of the businesses.  &lt;br /&gt;
The government-licensed wireless service provider is exploring opportunities for collaboration with blockchain-enabled financial institutions, including Taiwan-based XREX, Bloomberg reported, citing people familiar with the matter.  &lt;br /&gt;
No decisions have been made, and a deal may not materialize, the report noted. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/telecom-giant-taiwan-mobile-talks-for-crypto-platform-investment.htm"&gt;Read More: Telecom Giant Taiwan Mobile in Talks for Crypto Platform Investment&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Telecommunication</category><category>Telecom</category><category>Taiwan Mobile</category><category>Taiwan</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/telecom-giant-taiwan-mobile-talks-for-crypto-platform-investment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116748/312770/dragon-g1a2d745b7-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="292209"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Chart Forms Golden Cross on Weekly Candles – Best Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-chart-forms-golden-cross-weekly-candles-best-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Ethereum (ETH) has barely moved in the past 24 hours, with its position at $1,750 representing a 3.5% loss in a week and an 8% dive in the past fortnight. &lt;br /&gt;
However, ETH remains up by a healthy 46% since the beginning of the year, while analysts have noted that the altcoin has formed a weekly golden cross, with its short-term moving average rising above its long-term average for the first time since 2019....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-chart-forms-golden-cross-weekly-candles-best-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Chart Forms Golden Cross on Weekly Candles – Best Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-chart-forms-golden-cross-weekly-candles-best-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116724/312749/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1226996"/></item><item><title>Crypto Storage Solution from Censo Brings Self-Custody to Mobile Phones – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-storage-solution-from-censo-brings-self-custody-to-mobile-phones-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>FinTech company Censo has launched a mobile-phone based self-custody crypto wallet for institutions and organizations. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Monday press release, the company detailed that its new wallet provides a "truly decentralized key management solution" that is expected to be easier to use and less expensive than existing technologies.  &lt;br /&gt;
Censo noted that it does not employ multiparty computation (MPC), a key-sharding technology often used in institutional crypto custody arenas. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-storage-solution-from-censo-brings-self-custody-to-mobile-phones-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Storage Solution from Censo Brings Self-Custody to Mobile Phones – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Crypto Wallet</category><category>Custody</category><category>Censo</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-storage-solution-from-censo-brings-self-custody-to-mobile-phones-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116731/312737/chart-g3303bdbfa-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="446597"/></item></channel></rss>
