<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) - The best long term crypto investment for January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/orbeon-protocol-orbn-the-best-long-term-crypto-investment-for-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-09-at-232111.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-09-at-232111.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-09-at-232111.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/orbeon-protocol-orbn-the-best-long-term-crypto-investment-for-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>While the crypto winter persists, investors are seeking profitable projects to put in their money. Experts recommend new crypto projects with practical uses like Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) for higher returns.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>What is the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN)?</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is a new crypto project created to reform the venture capital industry. Orbeon makes investment opportunities accessible to everyone. Both start-ups and retail investors benefit from the design of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN).</p>
<p>Companies seeking funds can mint their equity-backed NFTs on Orbeon Protocol. These NFTs are broken into fractions to encourage people to invest. In the end, unicorn companies raise needed funds faster and users get to invest with as little as $1.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) provides everyday investors with the opportunity to back highly promising companies at an early stage. Before Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), access to the world's outstanding companies was only available to venture capitalists. But with Orbeon, an everyday person gets the opportunity to back a brand they truly believe in and reap the benefits. The Orbeon Protocol is here as a challenger VC.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>What do businesses benefit from the Orbeon Protocol?</p>
<p>With Orbeon, businesses are saved from facing rejections when sourcing for funds. Also, they don&rsquo;t have to complete any regulatory procedures to get needed funds.</p>
<p>Additionally, Orbeon connects businesses directly with the crypto community.</p>
<p>So, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) helps businesses to quickly access funds and also grow their communities.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>What investors benefit from Orbeon Protocol (ORBN)?</p>
<p>On Orbeon, investors get to put their money into vetted real-world businesses and crypto projects.</p>
<p>Also, there&rsquo;s a &lsquo;Fill or Kill&rsquo; mechanism that protects the interest of investors. It is included in the smart contract of the NFT created for client companies. Such that, investors automatically get their money back if a company fails to meet its funding goals. Additionally, the tokens allocated to the founding team are locked for one year, and are then released quarterly. Also, the liquidity pool is locked for 10 years to avoid the risk of a rug-pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Price Prediction&nbsp;</p>
<p>For $ORBN, analysts predict a 6,000% rise in price after the presale. Already, the coin has done 805%, moving from an initial price of $0.004 and now selling at $0.0362. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has completed two stages of presale. It is now in the third and final presale stage, and tokens are selling out fast.</p>
<p>Furthermore, holders of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) tokens enjoy governance and voting rights, priority access to up and coming funding rounds, staking rewards, and exclusive investor groups.</p>
<p>Find Out More About the Orbeon Protocol Presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the crypto winter persists, investors are seeking profitable projects to put in their money. Experts recommend new crypto projects with practical uses like Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) for higher returns.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>What is the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN)?</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is a new crypto project created to reform the venture capital industry. Orbeon makes investment opportunities accessible to everyone. Both start-ups and retail investors benefit from the design of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN).</p>
<p>Companies seeking funds can mint their equity-backed NFTs on Orbeon Protocol. These NFTs are broken into fractions to encourage people to invest. In the end, unicorn companies raise needed funds faster and users get to invest with as little as $1.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) provides everyday investors with the opportunity to back highly promising companies at an early stage. Before Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), access to the world's outstanding companies was only available to venture capitalists. But with Orbeon, an everyday person gets the opportunity to back a brand they truly believe in and reap the benefits. The Orbeon Protocol is here as a challenger VC.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>What do businesses benefit from the Orbeon Protocol?</p>
<p>With Orbeon, businesses are saved from facing rejections when sourcing for funds. Also, they don&rsquo;t have to complete any regulatory procedures to get needed funds.</p>
<p>Additionally, Orbeon connects businesses directly with the crypto community.</p>
<p>So, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) helps businesses to quickly access funds and also grow their communities.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>What investors benefit from Orbeon Protocol (ORBN)?</p>
<p>On Orbeon, investors get to put their money into vetted real-world businesses and crypto projects.</p>
<p>Also, there&rsquo;s a &lsquo;Fill or Kill&rsquo; mechanism that protects the interest of investors. It is included in the smart contract of the NFT created for client companies. Such that, investors automatically get their money back if a company fails to meet its funding goals. Additionally, the tokens allocated to the founding team are locked for one year, and are then released quarterly. Also, the liquidity pool is locked for 10 years to avoid the risk of a rug-pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Price Prediction&nbsp;</p>
<p>For $ORBN, analysts predict a 6,000% rise in price after the presale. Already, the coin has done 805%, moving from an initial price of $0.004 and now selling at $0.0362. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has completed two stages of presale. It is now in the third and final presale stage, and tokens are selling out fast.</p>
<p>Furthermore, holders of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) tokens enjoy governance and voting rights, priority access to up and coming funding rounds, staking rewards, and exclusive investor groups.</p>
<p>Find Out More About the Orbeon Protocol Presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US commercial bank closes crypto service over regulatory concerns]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-commercial-bank-closes-crypto-service-over-regulatory-concerns</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mcb.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mcb.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mcb.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 21:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-commercial-bank-closes-crypto-service-over-regulatory-concerns</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Metropolitan Commercial Bank has announced that it will be closing down its crypto business due to the regulatory environment.</p>
Uncertainty for banks
<p>The New York-based bank, which has been offering crypto services since 2015. The bank's move to shut down its crypto operations comes at a time when the regulatory landscape for digital currencies is in flux.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Earlier this year, the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) issued a statement clarifying that banks are allowed to provide custody services for cryptocurrencies. However, this guidance has not yet been implemented, leading to uncertainty for banks looking to enter the space.</p>
<p>Further uncertainty was fostered just recently, when the OCC made a joint statement with the Federal Reserve, and the FDIC, warning of the risks to banks of dealing with crypto companies.</p>
MCB closes crypto business
<p>In a statement, Metropolitan Commercial Bank said that it had:</p>

<p>"made the difficult decision to exit the cryptocurrency business due to the numerous regulatory hurdles and the evolving nature of the market."&nbsp;</p>

<p>The bank added that it will continue to serve its existing crypto clients until they have had a chance to transition to other providers.</p>
<p>Mark DiFazio, President and Chief Executive of the bank, was quoted in an article on the subject by American Banker. He said:</p>

<p>"Crypto-related clients, assets and deposits have never represented a material portion of the company's business and have never exposed the company to material financial risks,"&nbsp;</p>

<p>Also, according to the article, the bank only had four active crypto-related institutional clients, for whom the bank was providing &ldquo;debit card, payment, and account services.&rdquo; They were said to account for 1.5% of total revenue, and 6% of total deposits.</p>
Challenges for banks looking to offer crypto services
<p>The decision by Metropolitan Commercial Bank to close its crypto business is a reminder of the challenges facing banks looking to enter the digital currency space. While the OCC's guidance has opened the door for banks to offer crypto services, the lack of clear regulations has made it difficult for these institutions to navigate the space. Until there is greater clarity on the regulatory front, it is likely that other banks will also be hesitant to enter the crypto market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Metropolitan Commercial Bank has announced that it will be closing down its crypto business due to the regulatory environment.</p>
Uncertainty for banks
<p>The New York-based bank, which has been offering crypto services since 2015. The bank's move to shut down its crypto operations comes at a time when the regulatory landscape for digital currencies is in flux.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Earlier this year, the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) issued a statement clarifying that banks are allowed to provide custody services for cryptocurrencies. However, this guidance has not yet been implemented, leading to uncertainty for banks looking to enter the space.</p>
<p>Further uncertainty was fostered just recently, when the OCC made a joint statement with the Federal Reserve, and the FDIC, warning of the risks to banks of dealing with crypto companies.</p>
MCB closes crypto business
<p>In a statement, Metropolitan Commercial Bank said that it had:</p>

<p>"made the difficult decision to exit the cryptocurrency business due to the numerous regulatory hurdles and the evolving nature of the market."&nbsp;</p>

<p>The bank added that it will continue to serve its existing crypto clients until they have had a chance to transition to other providers.</p>
<p>Mark DiFazio, President and Chief Executive of the bank, was quoted in an article on the subject by American Banker. He said:</p>

<p>"Crypto-related clients, assets and deposits have never represented a material portion of the company's business and have never exposed the company to material financial risks,"&nbsp;</p>

<p>Also, according to the article, the bank only had four active crypto-related institutional clients, for whom the bank was providing &ldquo;debit card, payment, and account services.&rdquo; They were said to account for 1.5% of total revenue, and 6% of total deposits.</p>
Challenges for banks looking to offer crypto services
<p>The decision by Metropolitan Commercial Bank to close its crypto business is a reminder of the challenges facing banks looking to enter the digital currency space. While the OCC's guidance has opened the door for banks to offer crypto services, the lack of clear regulations has made it difficult for these institutions to navigate the space. Until there is greater clarity on the regulatory front, it is likely that other banks will also be hesitant to enter the crypto market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Reaffirms Goal of Becoming Crypto Hub]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/hong-kong-reaffirms-goal-of-becoming-crypto-hub</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-kong-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-kong-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-kong-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/hong-kong-reaffirms-goal-of-becoming-crypto-hub</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong has expressed its desire to become the world&rsquo;s leading crypto hub as the industry reels from the fallout of the collapsed crypto exchange FTX. </p>
<p>Hong Kong&rsquo;s financial secretary since 2017, Paul Chan, spoke at a Web3 forum recently and said that a region is a good place for cryptocurrency, financial technology, and other startups to set up shop despite what has occurred in the market recently. Chan says that Hong Kong remains committed to becoming a regional cryptocurrency hub. The city&rsquo;s financial secretary expressed these sentiments in October 2022, not long before Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s entire crypto empire collapsed and caused an industry-altering downturn and added that the city will do all within its power to attract new businesses within the industry from all over the world.</p>
<p>Singapore has previously been known to be somewhat of a crypto-haven but has backtracked on its stance by introducing many measures that make it difficult for crypto-related firms to set up shop &ndash; and Hong Kong is keen to step in and grab this opportunity. Chan said that since the city made its statements regarding the crypto industry, many leading technology firms and startups are considering moving their headquarters to the city or expanding there.</p>
<p>Chan said:</p>

<p>As certain crypto exchanges collapsed one after another, Hong Kong became a quality standing point for digital asset corporates.</p>

<p>He added to say that the city has a robust regulatory framework that &ldquo;matches international norms and standards&rdquo; while prohibiting those not complying with industry standards. Reports by Time indicate that the city is preparing to issue more licenses for digital asset trading firms and is planning a consultation on crypto platforms.</p>
Hong Kong Boosts Efforts to Attract Talent from China
<p>Secretary Chan spoke at w Web3-themed event at Cyberport on Monday, just two days after the borders between mainland China and Hong Kong reopened. According to reports by the South China Morning Post, Hong Kong is boosting its efforts to attract cryptocurrency talent from mainland China. Chan said:</p>

<p>I know that &hellip; some of you may have had doubts in the past about Hong Kong&rsquo;s development, but have recently heard many friends speak highly of new opportunities and development potential in Hong Kong, so have come to find out.</p>

<p>He added:</p>

<p>I can tell everyone that Hong Kong is at a new historical beginning of its development, and the Web3 ecosystem is also at a new stage of development. The combination of both brought us all together today to witness a golden new beginning of Web3 development.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong has expressed its desire to become the world&rsquo;s leading crypto hub as the industry reels from the fallout of the collapsed crypto exchange FTX. </p>
<p>Hong Kong&rsquo;s financial secretary since 2017, Paul Chan, spoke at a Web3 forum recently and said that a region is a good place for cryptocurrency, financial technology, and other startups to set up shop despite what has occurred in the market recently. Chan says that Hong Kong remains committed to becoming a regional cryptocurrency hub. The city&rsquo;s financial secretary expressed these sentiments in October 2022, not long before Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s entire crypto empire collapsed and caused an industry-altering downturn and added that the city will do all within its power to attract new businesses within the industry from all over the world.</p>
<p>Singapore has previously been known to be somewhat of a crypto-haven but has backtracked on its stance by introducing many measures that make it difficult for crypto-related firms to set up shop &ndash; and Hong Kong is keen to step in and grab this opportunity. Chan said that since the city made its statements regarding the crypto industry, many leading technology firms and startups are considering moving their headquarters to the city or expanding there.</p>
<p>Chan said:</p>

<p>As certain crypto exchanges collapsed one after another, Hong Kong became a quality standing point for digital asset corporates.</p>

<p>He added to say that the city has a robust regulatory framework that &ldquo;matches international norms and standards&rdquo; while prohibiting those not complying with industry standards. Reports by Time indicate that the city is preparing to issue more licenses for digital asset trading firms and is planning a consultation on crypto platforms.</p>
Hong Kong Boosts Efforts to Attract Talent from China
<p>Secretary Chan spoke at w Web3-themed event at Cyberport on Monday, just two days after the borders between mainland China and Hong Kong reopened. According to reports by the South China Morning Post, Hong Kong is boosting its efforts to attract cryptocurrency talent from mainland China. Chan said:</p>

<p>I know that &hellip; some of you may have had doubts in the past about Hong Kong&rsquo;s development, but have recently heard many friends speak highly of new opportunities and development potential in Hong Kong, so have come to find out.</p>

<p>He added:</p>

<p>I can tell everyone that Hong Kong is at a new historical beginning of its development, and the Web3 ecosystem is also at a new stage of development. The combination of both brought us all together today to witness a golden new beginning of Web3 development.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[What is Proof of Reserves and Why is it Important to the Crypto Industry?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/proof-of-reserves-and-why-is-it-important-to-the-crypto-industry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1cryptocurrency-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1cryptocurrency-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1cryptocurrency-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/proof-of-reserves-and-why-is-it-important-to-the-crypto-industry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Proof of reserves is a method used by cryptocurrency exchanges and other financial institutions to demonstrate that they hold a sufficient amount of assets in reserve to meet their customers' demands. This helps to build trust and confidence in the institution and ensures that customers can be confident that their funds are safe and secure.</p>
<p>There are several different ways that institutions can provide proof of reserves. One standard method is for the institution to provide a list of all its assets and evidence that it holds the private keys to those assets. This can be done through cryptographic proof, such as a Merkle tree, or by having a trusted third party audit the institution's reserves. Other methods of proof of reserve include providing regular reports on the institution's financial health and publicly disclosing its financial statements.</p>
Can the Proof of Reserves save the Cryptocurrency Industry?
<p>Proof of reserves is a mechanism that can help to build confidence and reduce the risk of fraud or mismanagement of funds by crypto exchanges or financial institutions. However, it is essential to note that proof of reserves alone is not the complete solution to the trust issues that can arise in the cryptocurrency space. Many other factors can contribute to a lack of trust, such as poor security practices, insider fraud, and regulatory uncertainties. A wide range of measures and best practices must be implemented to address these issues and build a more trusted and secure cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>
How can Regulators utilize Proof of Reserves to enhance Transparency?
<p>Regulators can make proof of reserves as a pre-requisite for exchanges and other financial institutions to reduce the risk of fraud or fund mismanagement. By establishing clear guidelines for what constitutes acceptable proof of reserves and by enforcing those guidelines through regular audits and other forms of oversight, regulators can help ensure that these institutions hold sufficient reserve assets to meet their customers' demands.</p>
<p>In addition, regulators can use proof of reserve to assess these institutions' overall financial health and stability. By reviewing the proof of reserve provided by financial institutions, regulators can better understand the assets they hold and the risks they might be exposed to. This can help regulators to identify potential problems or vulnerabilities in the industry and take action to address them before they become more serious.</p>
Is Proof of Reserves Important to Founders?
<p>For several reasons, proof of reserves can be necessary for founders of cryptocurrency exchanges and other financial institutions. By providing evidence that they hold sufficient assets in reserve to meet the demands of their customers, founders can help to establish their institution as a reliable and trustworthy place to carry out business. This can be especially important in the cryptocurrency industry, where there is often a lack of trust due to increased volatility, malicious scams, security issues, and regulatory concerns.</p>
<p>Another reason proof of reserve can be necessary for founders is that it can help reduce the risk of financial problems or mismanagement. By demonstrating that their institution holds sufficient assets in reserve, founders can help to reduce the risk of financial losses or other issues that could arise if the institution needs more assets to meet the demands of its customers. This can help founders to build a more stable and secure business, which can be especially important in the volatile and dynamic crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proof of reserves is a method used by cryptocurrency exchanges and other financial institutions to demonstrate that they hold a sufficient amount of assets in reserve to meet their customers' demands. This helps to build trust and confidence in the institution and ensures that customers can be confident that their funds are safe and secure.</p>
<p>There are several different ways that institutions can provide proof of reserves. One standard method is for the institution to provide a list of all its assets and evidence that it holds the private keys to those assets. This can be done through cryptographic proof, such as a Merkle tree, or by having a trusted third party audit the institution's reserves. Other methods of proof of reserve include providing regular reports on the institution's financial health and publicly disclosing its financial statements.</p>
Can the Proof of Reserves save the Cryptocurrency Industry?
<p>Proof of reserves is a mechanism that can help to build confidence and reduce the risk of fraud or mismanagement of funds by crypto exchanges or financial institutions. However, it is essential to note that proof of reserves alone is not the complete solution to the trust issues that can arise in the cryptocurrency space. Many other factors can contribute to a lack of trust, such as poor security practices, insider fraud, and regulatory uncertainties. A wide range of measures and best practices must be implemented to address these issues and build a more trusted and secure cryptocurrency ecosystem.</p>
How can Regulators utilize Proof of Reserves to enhance Transparency?
<p>Regulators can make proof of reserves as a pre-requisite for exchanges and other financial institutions to reduce the risk of fraud or fund mismanagement. By establishing clear guidelines for what constitutes acceptable proof of reserves and by enforcing those guidelines through regular audits and other forms of oversight, regulators can help ensure that these institutions hold sufficient reserve assets to meet their customers' demands.</p>
<p>In addition, regulators can use proof of reserve to assess these institutions' overall financial health and stability. By reviewing the proof of reserve provided by financial institutions, regulators can better understand the assets they hold and the risks they might be exposed to. This can help regulators to identify potential problems or vulnerabilities in the industry and take action to address them before they become more serious.</p>
Is Proof of Reserves Important to Founders?
<p>For several reasons, proof of reserves can be necessary for founders of cryptocurrency exchanges and other financial institutions. By providing evidence that they hold sufficient assets in reserve to meet the demands of their customers, founders can help to establish their institution as a reliable and trustworthy place to carry out business. This can be especially important in the cryptocurrency industry, where there is often a lack of trust due to increased volatility, malicious scams, security issues, and regulatory concerns.</p>
<p>Another reason proof of reserve can be necessary for founders is that it can help reduce the risk of financial problems or mismanagement. By demonstrating that their institution holds sufficient assets in reserve, founders can help to reduce the risk of financial losses or other issues that could arise if the institution needs more assets to meet the demands of its customers. This can help founders to build a more stable and secure business, which can be especially important in the volatile and dynamic crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto asset manager Osprey cuts most of its employees]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-asset-manager-osprey-cuts-most-of-its-employees</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/osprey.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/osprey.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/osprey.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-asset-manager-osprey-cuts-most-of-its-employees</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Digital asset manager Osprey Funds has laid off 15 employees and is currently operating with fewer than 10 employees, according to a source familiar with the matter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The news comes as the cryptocurrency market continues to struggle, with digital asset prices plunging and leading to the collapse of some heavily-leveraged investors. Despite the layoffs, Osprey CEO Greg King maintains that the company &ldquo;remains strong&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Osprey's Bitcoin Trust (OBTC), which is available at major online brokers like Fidelity, Charles Schwab, and TD Ameritrade, had approximately $46.9 million in assets under management as of January 6.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When including its trusts for BNB, Solana, Polkadot, and Algorand, the company has a total of $67.6 million in assets under management.</p>
<p>According to a report on Yahoo Finance, Osprey tried to launch a hedge fund back in August of 2022, but the attempt failed, and management informed its staff that the latest cuts were due to this failure.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market continues to face challenges, with investor appetite for risky assets shrinking and leading to a downturn in the industry. This has resulted in bankruptcies and layoffs, as well as a general decline in digital asset prices. It remains to be seen how Osprey and other companies in the space will navigate these challenges going forward.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital asset manager Osprey Funds has laid off 15 employees and is currently operating with fewer than 10 employees, according to a source familiar with the matter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The news comes as the cryptocurrency market continues to struggle, with digital asset prices plunging and leading to the collapse of some heavily-leveraged investors. Despite the layoffs, Osprey CEO Greg King maintains that the company &ldquo;remains strong&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Osprey's Bitcoin Trust (OBTC), which is available at major online brokers like Fidelity, Charles Schwab, and TD Ameritrade, had approximately $46.9 million in assets under management as of January 6.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When including its trusts for BNB, Solana, Polkadot, and Algorand, the company has a total of $67.6 million in assets under management.</p>
<p>According to a report on Yahoo Finance, Osprey tried to launch a hedge fund back in August of 2022, but the attempt failed, and management informed its staff that the latest cuts were due to this failure.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market continues to face challenges, with investor appetite for risky assets shrinking and leading to a downturn in the industry. This has resulted in bankruptcies and layoffs, as well as a general decline in digital asset prices. It remains to be seen how Osprey and other companies in the space will navigate these challenges going forward.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto sanctions reduce crypto-related crime]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-sanctions-reduce-crypto-related-crime</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sanc-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sanc-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sanc-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-sanctions-reduce-crypto-related-crime</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Chainalysis has published a report on the efficacy of OFAC adding crypto addresses to its SDN sanction list.</p>
OFAC includes cryptocurrency addresses on its SDN list for the first time
<p>In 2022, the U.S. Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) added several cryptocurrency addresses to its Specially Designated Nationals (SDN) list, which consists of individuals and entities that have been designated as sanctioned by the U.S. government.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This marked the first time that OFAC had included cryptocurrency addresses on the list, and the move was seen as a significant step in the agency's efforts to combat illicit activity in the crypto space.</p>
Chainalysis report shows significant decrease in volume of transactions associated with sanctioned entities
<p>According to a report by blockchain analysis firm Chainalysis, the OFAC's crypto-related designations had a noticeable impact on the level of cryptocurrency crime. The report found that the volume of cryptocurrency transactions associated with sanctioned entities decreased significantly after the OFAC designations were announced.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Prior to the designations, the volume of transactions associated with sanctioned entities was around $90 million per month. This figure dropped to just $9 million per month after the designations were announced.</p>
OFAC designations also impact wider crypto ecosystem and certain types of cryptocurrency crime
<p>The report also found that the OFAC designations had a wider impact on the crypto ecosystem, as many exchanges and other service providers took steps to delist or block transactions involving the designated addresses. This led to a decrease in the overall volume of transactions involving sanctioned entities, which fell from around 1% of all crypto transactions before the designations to just 0.1% after the designations.</p>
<p>The report noted that the OFAC's actions had a particularly strong impact on certain types of cryptocurrency crime, such as ransomware attacks and darknet market activity. The volume of ransomware payments declined significantly after the OFAC designations, falling from around $6 million per month to just $200,000 per month. Similarly, the volume of transactions associated with darknet markets fell from around $1.5 million per month to just $100,000 per month.</p>
<p>Overall, the report suggests that the OFAC's crypto-related designations were effective in disrupting illicit activity in the cryptocurrency space. By targeting specific addresses and entities, the agency was able to significantly reduce the volume of cryptocurrency transactions associated with sanctioned parties and disrupt the operations of many criminal groups.</p>
Privacy coins and international cooperation remain challenges in fight against cryptocurrency crime
<p>It is worth noting, however, that the OFAC's designations are just one tool in the fight against cryptocurrency crime. The report notes that the use of privacy coins, which can make it difficult to trace transactions, is on the rise and continues to present a challenge for law enforcement agencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, the report highlights the need for greater international cooperation in the fight against cryptocurrency crime, as many of the sanctioned entities were based in countries outside of the U.S.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainalysis has published a report on the efficacy of OFAC adding crypto addresses to its SDN sanction list.</p>
OFAC includes cryptocurrency addresses on its SDN list for the first time
<p>In 2022, the U.S. Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) added several cryptocurrency addresses to its Specially Designated Nationals (SDN) list, which consists of individuals and entities that have been designated as sanctioned by the U.S. government.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This marked the first time that OFAC had included cryptocurrency addresses on the list, and the move was seen as a significant step in the agency's efforts to combat illicit activity in the crypto space.</p>
Chainalysis report shows significant decrease in volume of transactions associated with sanctioned entities
<p>According to a report by blockchain analysis firm Chainalysis, the OFAC's crypto-related designations had a noticeable impact on the level of cryptocurrency crime. The report found that the volume of cryptocurrency transactions associated with sanctioned entities decreased significantly after the OFAC designations were announced.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Prior to the designations, the volume of transactions associated with sanctioned entities was around $90 million per month. This figure dropped to just $9 million per month after the designations were announced.</p>
OFAC designations also impact wider crypto ecosystem and certain types of cryptocurrency crime
<p>The report also found that the OFAC designations had a wider impact on the crypto ecosystem, as many exchanges and other service providers took steps to delist or block transactions involving the designated addresses. This led to a decrease in the overall volume of transactions involving sanctioned entities, which fell from around 1% of all crypto transactions before the designations to just 0.1% after the designations.</p>
<p>The report noted that the OFAC's actions had a particularly strong impact on certain types of cryptocurrency crime, such as ransomware attacks and darknet market activity. The volume of ransomware payments declined significantly after the OFAC designations, falling from around $6 million per month to just $200,000 per month. Similarly, the volume of transactions associated with darknet markets fell from around $1.5 million per month to just $100,000 per month.</p>
<p>Overall, the report suggests that the OFAC's crypto-related designations were effective in disrupting illicit activity in the cryptocurrency space. By targeting specific addresses and entities, the agency was able to significantly reduce the volume of cryptocurrency transactions associated with sanctioned parties and disrupt the operations of many criminal groups.</p>
Privacy coins and international cooperation remain challenges in fight against cryptocurrency crime
<p>It is worth noting, however, that the OFAC's designations are just one tool in the fight against cryptocurrency crime. The report notes that the use of privacy coins, which can make it difficult to trace transactions, is on the rise and continues to present a challenge for law enforcement agencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, the report highlights the need for greater international cooperation in the fight against cryptocurrency crime, as many of the sanctioned entities were based in countries outside of the U.S.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto benefits from weak dollar]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-benefits-from-weak-dollar</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/doll-4.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/doll-4.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/doll-4.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 16:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-benefits-from-weak-dollar</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The dollar is down today and the crypto ecosystem is making hay.</p>
Dollar rolling over
<p>Today dawned fair for crypto as the dollar waned against most other assets. USDT domination looks as though it might just be rolling over as it breaches a trendline active since the previous crypto top in November 2021.</p>
<p>The Dollar Index, which charts the strength of the dollar against a basket of other currencies has also taken a bit of a hit and is down 2.3% over the last couple of days. When this index goes down then cryptos will probably definitely be climbing.</p>
Bitcoin
<p>Bitcoin, the king of the cryptos, is up today, and is currently sitting at $17,275. If it keeps going, then perhaps it could reach a trendline that began in June 2022, and this would put it at around $19,000.</p>
<p>Where Bitcoin is slowly edging up, other cryptocurrencies are really starting to put on a bit of a spurt. Ethereum, the second biggest cryptocurrency by market cap, is up more than 2% this week already, and this follows a 6.7% rise from last week.</p>
Ethereum
<p>Last week&rsquo;s gain took Ethereum up through a downwards sloping trendline that has been in force since November of 2021, and if this week&rsquo;s price action keeps it above, then we are looking at a confirmed breakout.</p>
Solana
<p>Solana is the layer one blockchain that has really flown over these last couple of weeks or so. From a bottom of $8 it has climbed around 110% over just the last twelve days. $30 is the next strong level of resistance, as long as it can puncture through its own downsloping trendline from November 2021.</p>
Gala Games
<p>Looking at a slightly more exotic play, the Gala Games token $GALA is up more than 160% over the last four days and 42% currently today. Gala Games is a games studio with several play-to-earn games in its fold. Blockchain gaming is a sector that might see some huge growth over the long term.</p>
Total market cap
<p>The entire crypto market cap is back up to $893 billion, a $33 billion surge on the day. The market cap has met with resistance here, and it remains to be seen if this rally is more than just that, or if it is the first signs of the green shoots of a turn in the bear market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dollar is down today and the crypto ecosystem is making hay.</p>
Dollar rolling over
<p>Today dawned fair for crypto as the dollar waned against most other assets. USDT domination looks as though it might just be rolling over as it breaches a trendline active since the previous crypto top in November 2021.</p>
<p>The Dollar Index, which charts the strength of the dollar against a basket of other currencies has also taken a bit of a hit and is down 2.3% over the last couple of days. When this index goes down then cryptos will probably definitely be climbing.</p>
Bitcoin
<p>Bitcoin, the king of the cryptos, is up today, and is currently sitting at $17,275. If it keeps going, then perhaps it could reach a trendline that began in June 2022, and this would put it at around $19,000.</p>
<p>Where Bitcoin is slowly edging up, other cryptocurrencies are really starting to put on a bit of a spurt. Ethereum, the second biggest cryptocurrency by market cap, is up more than 2% this week already, and this follows a 6.7% rise from last week.</p>
Ethereum
<p>Last week&rsquo;s gain took Ethereum up through a downwards sloping trendline that has been in force since November of 2021, and if this week&rsquo;s price action keeps it above, then we are looking at a confirmed breakout.</p>
Solana
<p>Solana is the layer one blockchain that has really flown over these last couple of weeks or so. From a bottom of $8 it has climbed around 110% over just the last twelve days. $30 is the next strong level of resistance, as long as it can puncture through its own downsloping trendline from November 2021.</p>
Gala Games
<p>Looking at a slightly more exotic play, the Gala Games token $GALA is up more than 160% over the last four days and 42% currently today. Gala Games is a games studio with several play-to-earn games in its fold. Blockchain gaming is a sector that might see some huge growth over the long term.</p>
Total market cap
<p>The entire crypto market cap is back up to $893 billion, a $33 billion surge on the day. The market cap has met with resistance here, and it remains to be seen if this rally is more than just that, or if it is the first signs of the green shoots of a turn in the bear market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  17329 Tested - 10 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-17329-tested-10-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-17329-tested-10-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Above 17080:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its upward progress early in the Asian session as the pair traded as high as the 17292.94 area after Stops were elected above the 17080.17 area, a level that represents the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; BTC/USD bulls are pushing the pair higher to test the 17329.38 level, the 50% retracement of the same depreciating range, and retracement levels above this area include the 17578.59, 17886.94, and 17933.40 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 4.1% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16922.21 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 17030.83.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Above 17080:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its upward progress early in the Asian session as the pair traded as high as the 17292.94 area after Stops were elected above the 17080.17 area, a level that represents the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; BTC/USD bulls are pushing the pair higher to test the 17329.38 level, the 50% retracement of the same depreciating range, and retracement levels above this area include the 17578.59, 17886.94, and 17933.40 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 4.1% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16922.21 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 17030.83.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Astar Network Launches the XVM on Public Testnet, Enabling Truly Multichain Use Cases]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/astar-network-launches-the-xvm-on-public-testnet-enabling-truly-multichain-use-cases</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-01-07_00-16-57_1673272249ALpftYmyPN.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-01-07_00-16-57_1673272249ALpftYmyPN.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-01-07_00-16-57_1673272249ALpftYmyPN.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/astar-network-launches-the-xvm-on-public-testnet-enabling-truly-multichain-use-cases</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, 9th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of which language they are written with or which smart contract environment they use

Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, today announces the launch of its Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM) functionality on the public testnet Shibuya. It gives projects building on Astar Network, a Layer-1 blockchain, seamless interoperability between different smart contract environments such as the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) and WebAssembly (WASM).&nbsp;</p>
<p>XVM is a custom pallet and a set of interfaces that allow a smart contract in one virtual machine to communicate with another as if they are in the same environment. The XVM testnet is capable of making bi-directional calls between EVM and WASM smart contracts. It is the first major product launch as part of Astar Network&rsquo;s 2023 starmap.</p>
<p>WebAssembly is gaining favor among developers as it can be used with popular programming languages such as C/C++, GO, TypeScript and RUST, allowing them to get started with the languages they already know rather than learning specialized languages such as Solidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hoon Kim, Chief Technology Officer at Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We&rsquo;ve been working hard to create the foundation of the future, regardless of outside influences that are happening now. And today, I am proud to introduce one of our most important features to achieve the Astar Vision; the Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM). It will be the start of the next wave of innovation for dApps. Astar will not only have interoperability through XCM (Cross-chain Messaging) with other parachains but also have interoperability between different smart contract environments. &rdquo;</p>
<p>With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of which language they are written with or which smart contract environment they use. Developers will, for the first time, be able to build their cross-chain projects and experiment with the XVM developer toolkit. They can tap into the user bases and assets across multiple smart contract environments rather than being stuck with just one.</p>
<p>XVM allows developers to create a wide range of complex applications that do much more than merely bridging liquidity from EVM to WASM. For instance, users can prove ownership of assets in one smart contract environment from a different account scheme. It means developers don&rsquo;t need to create a new wallet for each environment to control the assets; Astar Network can create a universal asset controller with a single signer.</p>
About Astar Network
<p>Astar Network supports the building of dApps with EVM and WASM smart contracts and offers developers true interoperability, with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine (XVM). We are made by developers and for developers. Astar&rsquo;s unique Build2Earn model empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the code they write and dApps they build.</p>
<p>Astar&rsquo;s vibrant ecosystem has become Polkadot&rsquo;s leading Parachain globally, supported by all major exchanges and tier 1 VCs. Astar offers the flexibility of all Ethereum and WASM toolings for developers to start building their dApps.</p>
<p>For media queries, please contact: Maarten Henskens, press@astar.network</p>
<p>For more information, visit: Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | GitHub | Reddit
</p>ContactMaarten Henskenspress@astar.network]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, 9th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of which language they are written with or which smart contract environment they use

Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, today announces the launch of its Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM) functionality on the public testnet Shibuya. It gives projects building on Astar Network, a Layer-1 blockchain, seamless interoperability between different smart contract environments such as the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) and WebAssembly (WASM).&nbsp;</p>
<p>XVM is a custom pallet and a set of interfaces that allow a smart contract in one virtual machine to communicate with another as if they are in the same environment. The XVM testnet is capable of making bi-directional calls between EVM and WASM smart contracts. It is the first major product launch as part of Astar Network&rsquo;s 2023 starmap.</p>
<p>WebAssembly is gaining favor among developers as it can be used with popular programming languages such as C/C++, GO, TypeScript and RUST, allowing them to get started with the languages they already know rather than learning specialized languages such as Solidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hoon Kim, Chief Technology Officer at Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We&rsquo;ve been working hard to create the foundation of the future, regardless of outside influences that are happening now. And today, I am proud to introduce one of our most important features to achieve the Astar Vision; the Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM). It will be the start of the next wave of innovation for dApps. Astar will not only have interoperability through XCM (Cross-chain Messaging) with other parachains but also have interoperability between different smart contract environments. &rdquo;</p>
<p>With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of which language they are written with or which smart contract environment they use. Developers will, for the first time, be able to build their cross-chain projects and experiment with the XVM developer toolkit. They can tap into the user bases and assets across multiple smart contract environments rather than being stuck with just one.</p>
<p>XVM allows developers to create a wide range of complex applications that do much more than merely bridging liquidity from EVM to WASM. For instance, users can prove ownership of assets in one smart contract environment from a different account scheme. It means developers don&rsquo;t need to create a new wallet for each environment to control the assets; Astar Network can create a universal asset controller with a single signer.</p>
About Astar Network
<p>Astar Network supports the building of dApps with EVM and WASM smart contracts and offers developers true interoperability, with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine (XVM). We are made by developers and for developers. Astar&rsquo;s unique Build2Earn model empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the code they write and dApps they build.</p>
<p>Astar&rsquo;s vibrant ecosystem has become Polkadot&rsquo;s leading Parachain globally, supported by all major exchanges and tier 1 VCs. Astar offers the flexibility of all Ethereum and WASM toolings for developers to start building their dApps.</p>
<p>For media queries, please contact: Maarten Henskens, press@astar.network</p>
<p>For more information, visit: Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | GitHub | Reddit
</p>ContactMaarten Henskenspress@astar.network]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Will SBF Keep His Robinhood Shares? Crypto Daily TV 9/1/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/will-sbf-keep-his-robinhood-shares-crypto-daily-tv-9-1-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-sbf4.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-sbf4.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-sbf4.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/will-sbf-keep-his-robinhood-shares-crypto-daily-tv-9-1-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried seeks to keep Robinhood shares.</p>
<p>Ex-CEO of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, aka SBF, argued in his 5th January court filing that he should retain control of his Robinhood shares worth around $450 million.</p>
<p>U.S. subpoenas hedge funds in probe of Binance.</p>
<p>Federal prosecutors are examining American hedge funds&rsquo; dealings with cryptocurrency exchange Binance as part of a long-running investigation into potential violations of money-laundering rules at one of the world&rsquo;s leading crypto companies.</p>
<p>Crypto bank Juno chooses Zero Hash as new custodian.</p>
<p>Crypto bank Juno has chosen Zero Hash to serve as its new crypto custodian, the company announced in a blog post. The news follows Juno&rsquo;s warning last week advising clients to self-custody or sell their own crypto amid reports of its former custodian Wyre's turmoil.</p>
BTC/USD saw a minor rise of 0.1% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair made a minor upwards correction in the last session, rising 0.1%. The Williams indicator indicates an overbought market. Support is at 16892.6667 and resistance at 17022.6667.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD rose 0.5% in the last session.
<p>The last session saw the Ethereum rise 0.5% against the Dollar. The MACD is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 1255.8867 and resistance at 1274.9667.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
The last session saw XRP drop 0.8% against USD.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair fell 0.8% in the last session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.3397 and resistance at 0.3478.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar price remained largely unchanged in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 75.0667 and resistance at 77.3067.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US 6-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bills auctioned by US Department of Treasury. Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive. The US 6-Month Bill Auction will be released at 16:30 GMT, the Eurozone's Unemployment Rate at 10:00 GMT, Japan's Tokyo Consumer Price Index at 23:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market.</p>
<p>JP Tokyo Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Tokyo Consumer Price Index released by the Statistics Bureau is a measure of price movements obtained from the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>JP Overall Household Spending</p>
<p>The Overall Household Spending is an indicator that measures the total expenditures of households. The level of spending can be used as an indicator of consumer optimism. Japan's Overall Household Spending will be released at 23:30 GMT, the French Current Account at 07:45 GMT, and the US 3-Month Bill Auction at 16:30 GMT.</p>
<p>FR Current Account</p>
<p>The Current Account measures net flow of current transactions, including goods, services and interest payments into and out of the local economy.</p>
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried seeks to keep Robinhood shares.</p>
<p>Ex-CEO of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, aka SBF, argued in his 5th January court filing that he should retain control of his Robinhood shares worth around $450 million.</p>
<p>U.S. subpoenas hedge funds in probe of Binance.</p>
<p>Federal prosecutors are examining American hedge funds&rsquo; dealings with cryptocurrency exchange Binance as part of a long-running investigation into potential violations of money-laundering rules at one of the world&rsquo;s leading crypto companies.</p>
<p>Crypto bank Juno chooses Zero Hash as new custodian.</p>
<p>Crypto bank Juno has chosen Zero Hash to serve as its new crypto custodian, the company announced in a blog post. The news follows Juno&rsquo;s warning last week advising clients to self-custody or sell their own crypto amid reports of its former custodian Wyre's turmoil.</p>
BTC/USD saw a minor rise of 0.1% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair made a minor upwards correction in the last session, rising 0.1%. The Williams indicator indicates an overbought market. Support is at 16892.6667 and resistance at 17022.6667.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD rose 0.5% in the last session.
<p>The last session saw the Ethereum rise 0.5% against the Dollar. The MACD is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 1255.8867 and resistance at 1274.9667.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
The last session saw XRP drop 0.8% against USD.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair fell 0.8% in the last session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.3397 and resistance at 0.3478.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar price remained largely unchanged in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 75.0667 and resistance at 77.3067.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US 6-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bills auctioned by US Department of Treasury. Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive. The US 6-Month Bill Auction will be released at 16:30 GMT, the Eurozone's Unemployment Rate at 10:00 GMT, Japan's Tokyo Consumer Price Index at 23:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market.</p>
<p>JP Tokyo Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Tokyo Consumer Price Index released by the Statistics Bureau is a measure of price movements obtained from the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>JP Overall Household Spending</p>
<p>The Overall Household Spending is an indicator that measures the total expenditures of households. The level of spending can be used as an indicator of consumer optimism. Japan's Overall Household Spending will be released at 23:30 GMT, the French Current Account at 07:45 GMT, and the US 3-Month Bill Auction at 16:30 GMT.</p>
<p>FR Current Account</p>
<p>The Current Account measures net flow of current transactions, including goods, services and interest payments into and out of the local economy.</p>
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Conglomerate DCG Under Investigation by DOJ and SEC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-conglomerate-dcg-under-investigation-by-doj-and-sec</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dcg-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dcg-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dcg-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-conglomerate-dcg-under-investigation-by-doj-and-sec</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency conglomerate Digital Currency Group, or DCG, is reportedly under investigation by the United States Department of Justice (DOJ) and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The authorities are said to be mainly looking into internal transfers from DCG to its subsidiary Genesis. </p>
<p>Digital Currency Group is under investigation by the DOJ&rsquo;s Eastern District of New York and the SEC according to reports by Bloomberg. The investigation is reportedly focused on internal transfers between DCG and its subsidiary crypto lending firm Genesis Global Capital. The DOJ has already requested interviews and documents from both parties, while the SEC is undertaking a similar inquiry. As it stands, no indictment had been brought against any of the parties involved.</p>
<p>Among DCG&rsquo;s subsidiaries are Genesis, Grayscale Investments, media outlet CoinDesk, cryptocurrency exchange Luno, and Bitcoin mining company Foundry.</p>
Genesis Already in Trouble
<p>In June 2022, Genesis Trading was facing major losses following the fall of crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital, and later filed a claim for $1.2 billion &ndash; DCG assumed the claim for Genesis. The company has also been adversely affected by the collapse of FTX and according to the firm&rsquo;s disclosure, it had $175 million locked up in an FTX trading account.</p>
<p>The firm&rsquo;s lending unit also suspended withdrawals due to liquidity issues in November and undertook major layoffs over the past couple of months, nearly halving its headcounts since August, and talk of filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy has been rumored.</p>
<p>Genesis&rsquo; issues are further compounded as it owes $900 million to crypto exchange Gemini with who they operated a product called Gemini Earn in which investors can earn 8% interest on their crypto loans. According to reports, Gemini claims that DCG failed to repay Genesis, leading to the failure of payments to Gemini&rsquo;s clients.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency conglomerate Digital Currency Group, or DCG, is reportedly under investigation by the United States Department of Justice (DOJ) and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The authorities are said to be mainly looking into internal transfers from DCG to its subsidiary Genesis. </p>
<p>Digital Currency Group is under investigation by the DOJ&rsquo;s Eastern District of New York and the SEC according to reports by Bloomberg. The investigation is reportedly focused on internal transfers between DCG and its subsidiary crypto lending firm Genesis Global Capital. The DOJ has already requested interviews and documents from both parties, while the SEC is undertaking a similar inquiry. As it stands, no indictment had been brought against any of the parties involved.</p>
<p>Among DCG&rsquo;s subsidiaries are Genesis, Grayscale Investments, media outlet CoinDesk, cryptocurrency exchange Luno, and Bitcoin mining company Foundry.</p>
Genesis Already in Trouble
<p>In June 2022, Genesis Trading was facing major losses following the fall of crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital, and later filed a claim for $1.2 billion &ndash; DCG assumed the claim for Genesis. The company has also been adversely affected by the collapse of FTX and according to the firm&rsquo;s disclosure, it had $175 million locked up in an FTX trading account.</p>
<p>The firm&rsquo;s lending unit also suspended withdrawals due to liquidity issues in November and undertook major layoffs over the past couple of months, nearly halving its headcounts since August, and talk of filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy has been rumored.</p>
<p>Genesis&rsquo; issues are further compounded as it owes $900 million to crypto exchange Gemini with who they operated a product called Gemini Earn in which investors can earn 8% interest on their crypto loans. According to reports, Gemini claims that DCG failed to repay Genesis, leading to the failure of payments to Gemini&rsquo;s clients.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Logan Paul Withdraws Lawsuit Threat Over Crypto Scam Documentary]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/logan-paul-withdraws-lawsuit-threat-over-crypto-scam-documentary</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coffeezilla-paul-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coffeezilla-paul-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coffeezilla-paul-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/logan-paul-withdraws-lawsuit-threat-over-crypto-scam-documentary</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>YouTuber Logan Paul has promised to drop his threats of filing a defamation lawsuit over a three-part documentary that painted Paul&rsquo;s CryptoZoo project as a &ldquo;scam.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
No Lawsuit On Coffeezilla
<p>Controversial Youtube influencer Logan Paul is once again in the news over his crypto project, CryptoZoo. This time, he has taken back his threats to sue internet detective Stephen &ldquo;Coffeezilla&rdquo; Findeisen. Coffeezilla had produced and released a three-part documentary that highlighted Paul&rsquo;s CryptoZoo project and labeled it a scam. In response, Paul released a video in which he threatened to sue Coffeezilla. However, Paul has deleted that tweet since then, and according to Coffeezilla, also promised not to file the defamation lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coffeezilla tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Logan called me. He said he&rsquo;s deleting the two responses, and is dropping the lawsuit threats. I believe he&rsquo;s making a 3rd response, which I&rsquo;ll be delaying my video to include. Hopefully this time he takes accountability and refunds the victims of CryptoZoo. That&rsquo;s what matters.&rdquo;</p>

Logan Paul Apologizes
<p>The drama started after Coffeezilla dropped the first video of his three-part video series on December 17. In this video, he called out Logan Paul for being the face of an unscrupulous project, which, according to him, had engaged in business malpractices. Paul responded by accusing him of defamation and threatened him with a lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, according to Coffeezilla&rsquo;s recent tweets, the two Youtubers have hashed out their differences. In fact, Coffeezilla even shared a screenshot of a message from Paul&rsquo;s Discord server, where he apologized.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The excerpt from the screenshot reads,</p>

<p>&ldquo;It was rash and misaligned with the trust issue at hand, so I called him today and apologized. The war is not with Coffee. In fact, I&rsquo;m grateful he brought this to light. I will be taking accountability, apologizing, and coming forward with a plan in the near future,&rdquo;</p>

Problems With CryptoZoo
<p>Paul had touted the CryptoZoo project as a fun blockchain game that allows players to earn money as they play. The game, which is still in an unfinished stage introduces a new cryptocoin. Furthermore, players will also be buying and selling eggs that will hatch into animal-based NFTs, in order to breed and create new eggs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Findeisen had conducted a months-long investigation on the same, exposing significant issues in the P2E game. The video reports accused Paul and the development team of shady practices. Controversy has dogged the project from the start. One of the game&rsquo;s developers, Zech Kelling lied about the number of people working on the game. Reports claimed that Kelling has fled to Switzerland with the game&rsquo;s code.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>YouTuber Logan Paul has promised to drop his threats of filing a defamation lawsuit over a three-part documentary that painted Paul&rsquo;s CryptoZoo project as a &ldquo;scam.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
No Lawsuit On Coffeezilla
<p>Controversial Youtube influencer Logan Paul is once again in the news over his crypto project, CryptoZoo. This time, he has taken back his threats to sue internet detective Stephen &ldquo;Coffeezilla&rdquo; Findeisen. Coffeezilla had produced and released a three-part documentary that highlighted Paul&rsquo;s CryptoZoo project and labeled it a scam. In response, Paul released a video in which he threatened to sue Coffeezilla. However, Paul has deleted that tweet since then, and according to Coffeezilla, also promised not to file the defamation lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coffeezilla tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Logan called me. He said he&rsquo;s deleting the two responses, and is dropping the lawsuit threats. I believe he&rsquo;s making a 3rd response, which I&rsquo;ll be delaying my video to include. Hopefully this time he takes accountability and refunds the victims of CryptoZoo. That&rsquo;s what matters.&rdquo;</p>

Logan Paul Apologizes
<p>The drama started after Coffeezilla dropped the first video of his three-part video series on December 17. In this video, he called out Logan Paul for being the face of an unscrupulous project, which, according to him, had engaged in business malpractices. Paul responded by accusing him of defamation and threatened him with a lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, according to Coffeezilla&rsquo;s recent tweets, the two Youtubers have hashed out their differences. In fact, Coffeezilla even shared a screenshot of a message from Paul&rsquo;s Discord server, where he apologized.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The excerpt from the screenshot reads,</p>

<p>&ldquo;It was rash and misaligned with the trust issue at hand, so I called him today and apologized. The war is not with Coffee. In fact, I&rsquo;m grateful he brought this to light. I will be taking accountability, apologizing, and coming forward with a plan in the near future,&rdquo;</p>

Problems With CryptoZoo
<p>Paul had touted the CryptoZoo project as a fun blockchain game that allows players to earn money as they play. The game, which is still in an unfinished stage introduces a new cryptocoin. Furthermore, players will also be buying and selling eggs that will hatch into animal-based NFTs, in order to breed and create new eggs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Findeisen had conducted a months-long investigation on the same, exposing significant issues in the P2E game. The video reports accused Paul and the development team of shady practices. Controversy has dogged the project from the start. One of the game&rsquo;s developers, Zech Kelling lied about the number of people working on the game. Reports claimed that Kelling has fled to Switzerland with the game&rsquo;s code.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Solana RPC Endpoints Go Offline Following Bug In Latest Update]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/solana-rpc-endpoints-go-offline-following-bug-in-latest-update</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/solana-rpc-endpoints-go-offline-following-bug-in-latest-update</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to blockchain researcher and journalist Colin Wu, Solana&rsquo;s RPC Endpoints and Mainnet explorer are offline due to a bug in its latest release.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Solana has urged users operating on the impacted nodes to change to version 1.13.&nbsp;</p>
Network Still Functioning&nbsp;
<p>Solana Foundation-run Remote Procedure Call (RPC) endpoints are currently offline due to a bug in its latest test release, 1.14. While Solana has urged those operating on the impact nodes to change over to 1.13, the Solana Network remains unaffected, with block production taking place normally. This is due to the fact that other private RPCs by firms, such as Alchemy, QuickNode, and Triton, are still available to use. RPC endpoints are nodes connecting decentralized applications and wallets to the blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Journalist Colin Wu also updated Twitter followers, highlighting that the network was functioning normally despite the RPCs being offline.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Mainnet beta Explorer and Solana Foundation Public RPC endpoints are currently offline as RPC node software is upgraded, following a bug in test release 1.14. Block production has not been impacted, and the Solana network has not been impacted.&rdquo;</p>

Latest Upgrade To Blame&nbsp;
<p>Developers on Solana were able to pinpoint the latest test upgrade, version 1.14, as the primary cause of the failure. The upgrade was carried out by Solana Foundation node operators on their RPC endpoints and impacted the public RPC endpoints and the Mainnet beta explorer. The beta explorer is a tool that analyzes on-chain transactions and displays them to users in a simplified manner. Solana issued a statement on Twitter regarding the developments,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Mainnet beta Explorer and Solana Foundation Public RPC endpoints are currently offline as RPC node software is upgraded, following a bug in test release 1.14. Block production has not been impacted, and the Solana network has not been impacted. This bug impacted other nodes which had adopted the test release. If you are operating a node on a test release, please change over to 1.13.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Solana has faced a slew of network outages, with its history fraught with downtimes. In 2022 alone, the Solana network suffered 14 outages, which lasted for a total of 4 days, 12 hours, and 21 minutes. The last major outage on the Solana network occurred in October 2022 due to issues related to a node. The frequency of these outages has raised considerable concern among protocol users.&nbsp;</p>
Solana On The Road To Recovery&nbsp;
<p>Solana had a year to forget in 2022 but has started the new year on a brighter note. According to a tweet by Solana co-founder Raj Gokal, data from Artemis has shown that the network&rsquo;s daily addresses are ahead of those of its nearest rivals, namely Ethereum and Polygon, as of January 5th, 2023. Furthermore, the platform&rsquo;s native SOL token has seen its value jump considerably during the past week, rising by 37%, and is currently trading at just over $16, according to CoinMarketCap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The increase in price is a welcome development, considering SOL had dropped to $8 during the closing weeks of 2022. The token has also climbed up to being the 11th largest asset by market cap. Solana&rsquo;s community has also rallied around a new meme coin that is taking the network by storm. The new Bonk Inu token has surged over 1000% in the first week of the new year, attracting significant network activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to blockchain researcher and journalist Colin Wu, Solana&rsquo;s RPC Endpoints and Mainnet explorer are offline due to a bug in its latest release.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Solana has urged users operating on the impacted nodes to change to version 1.13.&nbsp;</p>
Network Still Functioning&nbsp;
<p>Solana Foundation-run Remote Procedure Call (RPC) endpoints are currently offline due to a bug in its latest test release, 1.14. While Solana has urged those operating on the impact nodes to change over to 1.13, the Solana Network remains unaffected, with block production taking place normally. This is due to the fact that other private RPCs by firms, such as Alchemy, QuickNode, and Triton, are still available to use. RPC endpoints are nodes connecting decentralized applications and wallets to the blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Journalist Colin Wu also updated Twitter followers, highlighting that the network was functioning normally despite the RPCs being offline.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Mainnet beta Explorer and Solana Foundation Public RPC endpoints are currently offline as RPC node software is upgraded, following a bug in test release 1.14. Block production has not been impacted, and the Solana network has not been impacted.&rdquo;</p>

Latest Upgrade To Blame&nbsp;
<p>Developers on Solana were able to pinpoint the latest test upgrade, version 1.14, as the primary cause of the failure. The upgrade was carried out by Solana Foundation node operators on their RPC endpoints and impacted the public RPC endpoints and the Mainnet beta explorer. The beta explorer is a tool that analyzes on-chain transactions and displays them to users in a simplified manner. Solana issued a statement on Twitter regarding the developments,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Mainnet beta Explorer and Solana Foundation Public RPC endpoints are currently offline as RPC node software is upgraded, following a bug in test release 1.14. Block production has not been impacted, and the Solana network has not been impacted. This bug impacted other nodes which had adopted the test release. If you are operating a node on a test release, please change over to 1.13.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Solana has faced a slew of network outages, with its history fraught with downtimes. In 2022 alone, the Solana network suffered 14 outages, which lasted for a total of 4 days, 12 hours, and 21 minutes. The last major outage on the Solana network occurred in October 2022 due to issues related to a node. The frequency of these outages has raised considerable concern among protocol users.&nbsp;</p>
Solana On The Road To Recovery&nbsp;
<p>Solana had a year to forget in 2022 but has started the new year on a brighter note. According to a tweet by Solana co-founder Raj Gokal, data from Artemis has shown that the network&rsquo;s daily addresses are ahead of those of its nearest rivals, namely Ethereum and Polygon, as of January 5th, 2023. Furthermore, the platform&rsquo;s native SOL token has seen its value jump considerably during the past week, rising by 37%, and is currently trading at just over $16, according to CoinMarketCap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The increase in price is a welcome development, considering SOL had dropped to $8 during the closing weeks of 2022. The token has also climbed up to being the 11th largest asset by market cap. Solana&rsquo;s community has also rallied around a new meme coin that is taking the network by storm. The new Bonk Inu token has surged over 1000% in the first week of the new year, attracting significant network activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Akon's Akoin Vs DPA Token DPAT: The battle to be Africa's coin]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/akons-akoin-vs-dpa-token-dpat-the-battle-to-be-africas-coin</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-192351.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-192351.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-192351.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/akons-akoin-vs-dpa-token-dpat-the-battle-to-be-africas-coin</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The traditional banking and finance system is in danger because of how the cryptocurrency market works and the pace of global adoption. With over twenty thousand cryptocurrencies in the world today and an average of 100 cryptocurrencies created daily, it is surprising that Africa has a very small share in this market. African countries regularly rank in the top 10 of searches on Google Trends for the term &ldquo;cryptocurrency.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, two asset-backed projects are setting the pace for the African continent, hoping to inspire other crypto projects springing up across the vast region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this article, we shall seek to compare Akoin, the project launched by popular hip hop artist Akon, and the Direct Property Africa Token DPAT to see which one can become Africa&rsquo;s coin. It all comes down to which project can balance providing access for a global investor market eager to profit from a lucrative and untapped location in a safe and transparent way, while giving Africans access to the global financial system needed for expansion and growth.</p>
<p>Use Cases</p>
<p>The Akoin token is meant to be used by all 54 African countries as a single currency. This means that Akoin will be operating as a multi-national currency that allows Africans to trade amongst themselves without having to worry about exchange rates or bank charges. The token is also designed to be used as the official currency for Akon City, a futuristic city yet to break ground, designed and created by the pop star.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, DPA Token DPAT is designed with the aim of creating an infrastructure token to help real estate developers, critical infrastructure builders, private/public initiatives and housing schemes access alternative capital from a truly global investor base allowing the international investor to access the lucrative African market in a transparent and decentralized way while helping to build a continent to spearhead growth by unlocking the clear potential of the people across the continent.</p>
<p>The token is backed by real estate and infrastructure projects run by trusted local developers in major African cities like Jacob West Ghana with the recently launched Khari project in Accra. The DPA Token team have built a custom platform so investors can purchase fractional shares in the form of NFTs representing the land under development and receive profits when the project or NFT is sold. Holders of the native DPAT coin will also receive natural price lifts as word of Africa's infrastructure token spreads.</p>
<p>Market Size</p>
<p>Africa's population is growing rapidly. Currently, the continent has 1.2 billion people and will soon reach 2 billion. As a result, Africa is the world's youngest continent&mdash;with more than half of its population under age 25&mdash;and it's one of the fastest urbanizing regions in the world with an estimated 200 million people expected to move to cities over the next five years.</p>
<p>This all bodes well for both projects especially considering DPAT is seeking to partner with global investors unsure of how to access lucrative African markets safely and securely. The projects funded and cities built will change the image of Africa and become crypto hubs for enthusiasts from all over the world to travel to build the next layer of the cryptoverse and spend their DPA Tokens.</p>
<p>Conclusion&nbsp;</p>
<p>Taking into account the above-listed and discussed points, it is safe to say that both projects have separate utilities but share the same goal to help Africa grow and spread crypto adoption. There is more than enough space for useful projects that help develop the engine of the world and promote a positive image of a continent growing at an incredible pace.</p>
<p>Although the Akoin project is bigger and more popular, dpatoken.io is not far behind and its international base of backers believe Africa is just the start of a global shift where the community get to decide what gets built - by whom, for whom, and where. Analysts are all saying DPAT is undervalued and is primed for huge growth in 2023. In the next few years, it is likely to build a fortune for many crypto lovers across the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You can learn more and support the project here.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The traditional banking and finance system is in danger because of how the cryptocurrency market works and the pace of global adoption. With over twenty thousand cryptocurrencies in the world today and an average of 100 cryptocurrencies created daily, it is surprising that Africa has a very small share in this market. African countries regularly rank in the top 10 of searches on Google Trends for the term &ldquo;cryptocurrency.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, two asset-backed projects are setting the pace for the African continent, hoping to inspire other crypto projects springing up across the vast region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this article, we shall seek to compare Akoin, the project launched by popular hip hop artist Akon, and the Direct Property Africa Token DPAT to see which one can become Africa&rsquo;s coin. It all comes down to which project can balance providing access for a global investor market eager to profit from a lucrative and untapped location in a safe and transparent way, while giving Africans access to the global financial system needed for expansion and growth.</p>
<p>Use Cases</p>
<p>The Akoin token is meant to be used by all 54 African countries as a single currency. This means that Akoin will be operating as a multi-national currency that allows Africans to trade amongst themselves without having to worry about exchange rates or bank charges. The token is also designed to be used as the official currency for Akon City, a futuristic city yet to break ground, designed and created by the pop star.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, DPA Token DPAT is designed with the aim of creating an infrastructure token to help real estate developers, critical infrastructure builders, private/public initiatives and housing schemes access alternative capital from a truly global investor base allowing the international investor to access the lucrative African market in a transparent and decentralized way while helping to build a continent to spearhead growth by unlocking the clear potential of the people across the continent.</p>
<p>The token is backed by real estate and infrastructure projects run by trusted local developers in major African cities like Jacob West Ghana with the recently launched Khari project in Accra. The DPA Token team have built a custom platform so investors can purchase fractional shares in the form of NFTs representing the land under development and receive profits when the project or NFT is sold. Holders of the native DPAT coin will also receive natural price lifts as word of Africa's infrastructure token spreads.</p>
<p>Market Size</p>
<p>Africa's population is growing rapidly. Currently, the continent has 1.2 billion people and will soon reach 2 billion. As a result, Africa is the world's youngest continent&mdash;with more than half of its population under age 25&mdash;and it's one of the fastest urbanizing regions in the world with an estimated 200 million people expected to move to cities over the next five years.</p>
<p>This all bodes well for both projects especially considering DPAT is seeking to partner with global investors unsure of how to access lucrative African markets safely and securely. The projects funded and cities built will change the image of Africa and become crypto hubs for enthusiasts from all over the world to travel to build the next layer of the cryptoverse and spend their DPA Tokens.</p>
<p>Conclusion&nbsp;</p>
<p>Taking into account the above-listed and discussed points, it is safe to say that both projects have separate utilities but share the same goal to help Africa grow and spread crypto adoption. There is more than enough space for useful projects that help develop the engine of the world and promote a positive image of a continent growing at an incredible pace.</p>
<p>Although the Akoin project is bigger and more popular, dpatoken.io is not far behind and its international base of backers believe Africa is just the start of a global shift where the community get to decide what gets built - by whom, for whom, and where. Analysts are all saying DPAT is undervalued and is primed for huge growth in 2023. In the next few years, it is likely to build a fortune for many crypto lovers across the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You can learn more and support the project here.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKB, Flow (FLOW) and Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Touted as Best Crypto Investments for 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/okb-flow-flow-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-touted-as-best-crypto-investments-for-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-08-at-192136.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-08-at-192136.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-08-at-192136.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/okb-flow-flow-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-touted-as-best-crypto-investments-for-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the collapse of FTX behind us, OKB, the native token of rival cryptocurrency exchange OKX seems to outperform most other digital assets. Furthermore, we have Dapper Lab&rsquo;s FLOW token down over 97% from its all-time high but with great partnerships in place, and last but not least, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), a newcomer that managed to skyrocket over 805% in December of which analysts now predict it will surge by as much as 6,000% in Q1 2023.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>OKB Shines Bright After FTX Collapse Causes FTT Token to Drop Like a Brick</p>
<p>OKB, OKX&rsquo;s native token, enjoyed a significant uptrend from around $22 to over $27 last week. When compared to most other cryptocurrencies, OKB is one of the digital assets that seems to be the most stable in value, still trading at about half of its all-time high whilst other cryptocurrencies are trading at 80 to 90 percent discounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given that OKX is rapidly gaining users and its trading volume is increasing, it might be wise to add OKB to your cryptocurrency portfolio, especially because OKB reduces payable trading fees on the cryptocurrency exchange and allows investors to earn a passive income through staking.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With this in mind, OKB has seen increased attention as many investors flock to OKB for 2023. Along with its utility as an exchange token, OKB is likely to see further growth as time goes on.</p>
<p>Dapper Lab&rsquo;s Flow (FLOW) Down 97% Makes for Great Long-Term Buy</p>
<p>Flow (FLOW), the native currency of the Flow network and the keystone for a new, inclusive, and borderless digital economy, is currently trading at a whopping 97% discount compared to last year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Although FLOW is designed as a payment method and a long-term reserve asset for the Flow economy, to be used by both validators and developers, it couldn&rsquo;t withstand the hefty blows dealt by the FTX collapse, and its price took a nosedive, so to speak.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, don&rsquo;t let its low price of a mere $0.65 per token fool you! Dapper Labs, the creator of the Flow blockchain as well as the famous NFT project Cryptokitties, has partnerships in place with big and well-known names such as the NBA, Warner Music Group, and UFC. Notable investors in the project include Andreessen Horowitz, Coinbase, Zynga, and Google Ventures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With these strong fundamentals, Flow (FLOW) makes for a great long-term buy going into 2023, and our experts predict the token to recover sooner rather than later.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) - The Crypto Project That Will Disrupt Crowdfunding and Venture Capital Markets in 2023</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is gaining momentum and making headlines left, right, and sideways ever since it managed to skyrocket over 805% in December during the first two phases of its pre-sale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) aims to disrupt the crowdfunding and venture capital markets through the use of fractionalized NFTs. If a start-up company wants to raise funds through Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), they can mint equity-backed NFTs that represent investments in the start-up.</p>
<p>Users of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) can then buy these NFTs from as little as $1 and reap the rewards of early seed investing. For start-ups, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) greatly reduces costs and allows them to be in direct contact with their backers.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) will use a Fill-or-Kill mechanism that ensures all investors get a refund whenever a start-up fails to reach its funding goal, which takes the guesswork out of the equation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The project&rsquo;s native ORBN token is set to provide holders with benefits like staking bonuses, transaction fee discounts and governance rights. Investors can participate in the pre-sale at a price of $0.0362 per token, however based on ORBN&rsquo;s performance thus far analysts predict that ORBN will see a 6000% price increase to $0.24 in the coming months.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the collapse of FTX behind us, OKB, the native token of rival cryptocurrency exchange OKX seems to outperform most other digital assets. Furthermore, we have Dapper Lab&rsquo;s FLOW token down over 97% from its all-time high but with great partnerships in place, and last but not least, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), a newcomer that managed to skyrocket over 805% in December of which analysts now predict it will surge by as much as 6,000% in Q1 2023.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>OKB Shines Bright After FTX Collapse Causes FTT Token to Drop Like a Brick</p>
<p>OKB, OKX&rsquo;s native token, enjoyed a significant uptrend from around $22 to over $27 last week. When compared to most other cryptocurrencies, OKB is one of the digital assets that seems to be the most stable in value, still trading at about half of its all-time high whilst other cryptocurrencies are trading at 80 to 90 percent discounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given that OKX is rapidly gaining users and its trading volume is increasing, it might be wise to add OKB to your cryptocurrency portfolio, especially because OKB reduces payable trading fees on the cryptocurrency exchange and allows investors to earn a passive income through staking.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With this in mind, OKB has seen increased attention as many investors flock to OKB for 2023. Along with its utility as an exchange token, OKB is likely to see further growth as time goes on.</p>
<p>Dapper Lab&rsquo;s Flow (FLOW) Down 97% Makes for Great Long-Term Buy</p>
<p>Flow (FLOW), the native currency of the Flow network and the keystone for a new, inclusive, and borderless digital economy, is currently trading at a whopping 97% discount compared to last year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Although FLOW is designed as a payment method and a long-term reserve asset for the Flow economy, to be used by both validators and developers, it couldn&rsquo;t withstand the hefty blows dealt by the FTX collapse, and its price took a nosedive, so to speak.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, don&rsquo;t let its low price of a mere $0.65 per token fool you! Dapper Labs, the creator of the Flow blockchain as well as the famous NFT project Cryptokitties, has partnerships in place with big and well-known names such as the NBA, Warner Music Group, and UFC. Notable investors in the project include Andreessen Horowitz, Coinbase, Zynga, and Google Ventures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With these strong fundamentals, Flow (FLOW) makes for a great long-term buy going into 2023, and our experts predict the token to recover sooner rather than later.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) - The Crypto Project That Will Disrupt Crowdfunding and Venture Capital Markets in 2023</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is gaining momentum and making headlines left, right, and sideways ever since it managed to skyrocket over 805% in December during the first two phases of its pre-sale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) aims to disrupt the crowdfunding and venture capital markets through the use of fractionalized NFTs. If a start-up company wants to raise funds through Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), they can mint equity-backed NFTs that represent investments in the start-up.</p>
<p>Users of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) can then buy these NFTs from as little as $1 and reap the rewards of early seed investing. For start-ups, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) greatly reduces costs and allows them to be in direct contact with their backers.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) will use a Fill-or-Kill mechanism that ensures all investors get a refund whenever a start-up fails to reach its funding goal, which takes the guesswork out of the equation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The project&rsquo;s native ORBN token is set to provide holders with benefits like staking bonuses, transaction fee discounts and governance rights. Investors can participate in the pre-sale at a price of $0.0362 per token, however based on ORBN&rsquo;s performance thus far analysts predict that ORBN will see a 6000% price increase to $0.24 in the coming months.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Jetshare JETT$ Price Prediction (2023)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/jetshare-jett-price-prediction-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-191414.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-191414.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-191414.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/jetshare-jett-price-prediction-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Jetshare is one of the most exciting cryptocurrency projects on the blockchain today. With the fractional NFT concept fast becoming a craze for cryptocurrency lovers, there has been a high demand for the project in recent weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are still doubts about how big the Jetshare token can grow in the coming years. In this article, we take a look at Jetshare&rsquo;s price prediction for the next two years. This price prediction is based on current market movement and the strengths of the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Market Opportunities Available</p>
<p>With the average rate for private Jet hires sitting at between $1,300 and $3,000 hourly, one would expect that very few people will have an interest in using these flights.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, contrary to that, research shows that private Jet rentals have soared in numbers over the past years. Partly because of the effects of the COVID-19 pandemic and also for the ultimate desire for privacy, most people are now turning towards private Jets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most would think these people are either celebrities, millionaires, billionaires, or successful businessmen, however groups of private individuals are more likely to pull funds together to travel across the globe in comfort.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the industry moves to a more sustainable future with the advent of electrical systems and hybrid-electric propulsion over the coming years, one can only expect the demand for private Jets to go in an upward trajectory.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This will in turn increase the demand for Jetshare&rsquo;s native token JETT$. In the end, the underlying Jets for the project will see real-life usage, while the tokens themselves will also appreciate in price as holders use the token to book Jet charters, pay at private terminals and access international aviation events.</p>
<p>Actual Price Predictions</p>
<p>The big question again remains: How high can the price of JETT$ get? It is expected that when the Jetshare project officially launches after its pre-sales, the price of the token will take off at around 0.08USD landing somewhere close to $5 by year end.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, this value is expected as the token gets listed on other exchanges over the coming months and receives more attention from the general investing public.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the subsequent months, as the project adds more Jets to its fleet and announces partnerships with airports, charter businesses and flying schools around the globe, it is expected that more investors will get interested in the project and increase the buying pressure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is expected to cause some positive price action in the market. Based on this intel, Jetshare should see a price increase of between 300% to 350% within 18 months.</p>
<p>By the end of 2024, the price of the token is likely to be on its way to the moon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>The best way to make money from cryptocurrency is to invest in projects that have real value and are backed with assets. In today&rsquo;s crypto market, what's better than a token that allows you to fly where you want.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the price prediction in this post, you can already see where this project is headed in the near future.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Click here to register now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Follow on twitter: https://twitter.com/Jetshare_JETT&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jetshare is one of the most exciting cryptocurrency projects on the blockchain today. With the fractional NFT concept fast becoming a craze for cryptocurrency lovers, there has been a high demand for the project in recent weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are still doubts about how big the Jetshare token can grow in the coming years. In this article, we take a look at Jetshare&rsquo;s price prediction for the next two years. This price prediction is based on current market movement and the strengths of the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Market Opportunities Available</p>
<p>With the average rate for private Jet hires sitting at between $1,300 and $3,000 hourly, one would expect that very few people will have an interest in using these flights.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, contrary to that, research shows that private Jet rentals have soared in numbers over the past years. Partly because of the effects of the COVID-19 pandemic and also for the ultimate desire for privacy, most people are now turning towards private Jets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most would think these people are either celebrities, millionaires, billionaires, or successful businessmen, however groups of private individuals are more likely to pull funds together to travel across the globe in comfort.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the industry moves to a more sustainable future with the advent of electrical systems and hybrid-electric propulsion over the coming years, one can only expect the demand for private Jets to go in an upward trajectory.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This will in turn increase the demand for Jetshare&rsquo;s native token JETT$. In the end, the underlying Jets for the project will see real-life usage, while the tokens themselves will also appreciate in price as holders use the token to book Jet charters, pay at private terminals and access international aviation events.</p>
<p>Actual Price Predictions</p>
<p>The big question again remains: How high can the price of JETT$ get? It is expected that when the Jetshare project officially launches after its pre-sales, the price of the token will take off at around 0.08USD landing somewhere close to $5 by year end.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, this value is expected as the token gets listed on other exchanges over the coming months and receives more attention from the general investing public.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the subsequent months, as the project adds more Jets to its fleet and announces partnerships with airports, charter businesses and flying schools around the globe, it is expected that more investors will get interested in the project and increase the buying pressure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is expected to cause some positive price action in the market. Based on this intel, Jetshare should see a price increase of between 300% to 350% within 18 months.</p>
<p>By the end of 2024, the price of the token is likely to be on its way to the moon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>The best way to make money from cryptocurrency is to invest in projects that have real value and are backed with assets. In today&rsquo;s crypto market, what's better than a token that allows you to fly where you want.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the price prediction in this post, you can already see where this project is headed in the near future.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Click here to register now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Follow on twitter: https://twitter.com/Jetshare_JETT&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Lifted from 16903 - 9 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-lifted-from-16903-9-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-lifted-from-16903-9-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Retains Bullish Bias:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) retained its bullish bias early in the Asian session as the pair encountered buying pressure around the 16903.58 level after trading as high as the 17027.11 level, its strongest print since 20 December and another test of the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; &nbsp;The buying pressure that emerged was right around the 78.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 17060.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; BTC/USD bulls seek to see if BTC/USD can establish a constructive base above the 16880.44 area, representing a 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 17750, 18469, 19179, 20058, and 20190 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 2.6% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16916.87 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16886.77.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Retains Bullish Bias:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) retained its bullish bias early in the Asian session as the pair encountered buying pressure around the 16903.58 level after trading as high as the 17027.11 level, its strongest print since 20 December and another test of the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; &nbsp;The buying pressure that emerged was right around the 78.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 17060.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; BTC/USD bulls seek to see if BTC/USD can establish a constructive base above the 16880.44 area, representing a 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 17750, 18469, 19179, 20058, and 20190 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 2.6% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16916.87 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16886.77.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: Celsius And Huobi Drama And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-weekly-roundup-celsius-and-huobi-drama-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-1-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-1-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-1-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-weekly-roundup-celsius-and-huobi-drama-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firms continue to struggle even in the first week of the new year, with businesses laying off workforces and announcing bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s find out how crypto has been faring in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>In the wake of the devastating winter storm in Texas in December 2022, Bitcoin miners returned up to 1,500 megawatts of energy to the grid, enough to power over 1.5 million small homes.</p>
<p>According to an Mt Gox announcement, base and intermediate payments will be moved back from July to September 2023.</p>
<p>Investor Michael Burry has said that the US will have a recession and more inflation in 2023. He thinks that inflation is currently very high, but it will not remain so.</p>
<p>Eric Voorhees, founder and CEO of crypto exchange Shapeshifter, says he cannot call the next bull market with any exactitude, but it would come in the next 6 months to 3 years.</p>
DeFi
<p>DeFi protocol Balancer has warned LPs on the protocol to withdraw their liquidity immediately due to an ongoing issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uniswap's newly implemented bug bounty program has uncovered and subsequently resolved an existing vulnerability in its Universal Router smart contract.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol SushiSwap has announced it would be shutting down its lending protocol, Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>South Korean tech giant LG Electronics has announced a partnership with the cloud-based technology platform Oorbit to bring the metaverse directly into the living room of TV viewers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A hack that exploited and drained GMX tokens from a whale enabled the perpetrator to exchange the assets for 2,627 Ether.</p>
<p>Crypto suffered its worst-ever year for hacks in 2022, with most of them affecting DeFi platforms which saw a third of all such activity in the last year.</p>
Business
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>Tron founder Justin Sun made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Customers of crypto-focused US bank Silvergate have withdrawn over $8 billion of their crypto-linked deposits, resulting in a drop in its share value.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the latest court ruling, Celsius Network has been rewarded the rights to interest-bearing accounts, pushing actual account holders to the end of the repayment queue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The US government has seized hundreds of millions of dollars worth of shares in Robinhood Markets Inc. as part of the fraud case against Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>With the crypto winter showing no signs of abating, crypto payment companies Wyre and EmpireDAO have become its latest casualties.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Core Scientific has come to an agreement with Celsius Network to shut down the 37,000 mining rigs that it was hosting for the latter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Indonesia is set to launch a cryptocurrency exchange in 2023 as part of a financial reform plan,</p>
<p>Lee Jung-Hoon, the former chairman of South Korea's Bithumb exchange, was declared not guilty of fraud over the failed acquisition of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Co-founder of crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co, Cameron Winklevoss, has accused the CEO of Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert, of negotiating in bad faith.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has launched a cryptocurrency academy aimed at educating those wanting to invest in digital assets free of charge.</p>
<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France, given the recent turmoil in the market.</p>
<p>Liquidators found a unique way to subpoena Three Arrows Capital co-founders Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, issuing them a copy of the subpoena via Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>New York Attorney General Letitia James has sued the founder and former CEO of collapsed crypto bank Celsius, Alex Mashinsk, for misrepresenting the financial condition of Celsius.</p>
<p>Fabio Panetta of the ECB has written that trading in cryptocurrencies is akin to gambling and should be treated as such by regulators.</p>
<p>Brian Armstrong-led cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has reached a $100 million settlement with New York&rsquo;s Department of Financial Services (DFS).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firms continue to struggle even in the first week of the new year, with businesses laying off workforces and announcing bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s find out how crypto has been faring in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>In the wake of the devastating winter storm in Texas in December 2022, Bitcoin miners returned up to 1,500 megawatts of energy to the grid, enough to power over 1.5 million small homes.</p>
<p>According to an Mt Gox announcement, base and intermediate payments will be moved back from July to September 2023.</p>
<p>Investor Michael Burry has said that the US will have a recession and more inflation in 2023. He thinks that inflation is currently very high, but it will not remain so.</p>
<p>Eric Voorhees, founder and CEO of crypto exchange Shapeshifter, says he cannot call the next bull market with any exactitude, but it would come in the next 6 months to 3 years.</p>
DeFi
<p>DeFi protocol Balancer has warned LPs on the protocol to withdraw their liquidity immediately due to an ongoing issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uniswap's newly implemented bug bounty program has uncovered and subsequently resolved an existing vulnerability in its Universal Router smart contract.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol SushiSwap has announced it would be shutting down its lending protocol, Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>South Korean tech giant LG Electronics has announced a partnership with the cloud-based technology platform Oorbit to bring the metaverse directly into the living room of TV viewers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A hack that exploited and drained GMX tokens from a whale enabled the perpetrator to exchange the assets for 2,627 Ether.</p>
<p>Crypto suffered its worst-ever year for hacks in 2022, with most of them affecting DeFi platforms which saw a third of all such activity in the last year.</p>
Business
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>Tron founder Justin Sun made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Customers of crypto-focused US bank Silvergate have withdrawn over $8 billion of their crypto-linked deposits, resulting in a drop in its share value.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the latest court ruling, Celsius Network has been rewarded the rights to interest-bearing accounts, pushing actual account holders to the end of the repayment queue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The US government has seized hundreds of millions of dollars worth of shares in Robinhood Markets Inc. as part of the fraud case against Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>With the crypto winter showing no signs of abating, crypto payment companies Wyre and EmpireDAO have become its latest casualties.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Core Scientific has come to an agreement with Celsius Network to shut down the 37,000 mining rigs that it was hosting for the latter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Indonesia is set to launch a cryptocurrency exchange in 2023 as part of a financial reform plan,</p>
<p>Lee Jung-Hoon, the former chairman of South Korea's Bithumb exchange, was declared not guilty of fraud over the failed acquisition of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Co-founder of crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co, Cameron Winklevoss, has accused the CEO of Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert, of negotiating in bad faith.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has launched a cryptocurrency academy aimed at educating those wanting to invest in digital assets free of charge.</p>
<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France, given the recent turmoil in the market.</p>
<p>Liquidators found a unique way to subpoena Three Arrows Capital co-founders Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, issuing them a copy of the subpoena via Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>New York Attorney General Letitia James has sued the founder and former CEO of collapsed crypto bank Celsius, Alex Mashinsk, for misrepresenting the financial condition of Celsius.</p>
<p>Fabio Panetta of the ECB has written that trading in cryptocurrencies is akin to gambling and should be treated as such by regulators.</p>
<p>Brian Armstrong-led cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has reached a $100 million settlement with New York&rsquo;s Department of Financial Services (DFS).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US still gunning for crypto exchange Binance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-still-gunning-for-crypto-exchange-binance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-crash.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-crash.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-crash.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 12:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-still-gunning-for-crypto-exchange-binance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange is still in the sights of US authorities as hedge funds are subpoenaed.</p>
<p>It was reported by Reuters last month that the long-running investigation into Binance could result in criminal charges being levied against senior executives at the crypto company, including founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the report also said that there could be a possible settlement in the case that sufficient evidence was not forthcoming. All this is taking place in the awful environment for crypto, which is potentially further fueling the flight of more investors from the sector.</p>
<p>An article in the Washington Post put forward the argument of Patrick Hillmann, Chief Strategy Officer for Binance. He said that Binance did have shortcomings in the past, but that the company had &ldquo;invested heavily in compliance programs&rdquo;, and that it was now working closely with law enforcement agencies around the globe. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Over the last two years, the company has completely changed its posture. Now that we have those resources, we are easily one of the most proactive parties to identify, freeze and get back funds&rdquo;</p>

<p>John Ghose, a former Justice Department prosecutor, was also featured in the Washington Post article. He stated that it was his belief that when&nbsp; he was a prosecutor Binance did not have a good reputation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In relation to whether Binance had allowed money laundering, tax evasion, or other crimes to take place on its platform, he said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The basis of those charges is whether there are U.S. customers. If there are U.S. customers, there are charges for avoiding the money laundering requirements.&rdquo;</p>

Could the Binance FUD topple crypto?
<p>Given that Binance is easily the biggest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, for it to fall would arguably have a simply huge knock-on for the rest of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>A collapse of the exchange could have dire consequences that could put the industry back years, making transacting in cryptocurrencies that much more difficult, as well as removing a very large investor in the space.</p>
<p>With all the furore surrounding the FTX debacle, the various bankruptcies of other crypto companies etc., now is a very bad time for crypto, and a very good time for authorities to turn the screw and attempt to subjugate, if not almost eliminate private digital asset transactions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange is still in the sights of US authorities as hedge funds are subpoenaed.</p>
<p>It was reported by Reuters last month that the long-running investigation into Binance could result in criminal charges being levied against senior executives at the crypto company, including founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the report also said that there could be a possible settlement in the case that sufficient evidence was not forthcoming. All this is taking place in the awful environment for crypto, which is potentially further fueling the flight of more investors from the sector.</p>
<p>An article in the Washington Post put forward the argument of Patrick Hillmann, Chief Strategy Officer for Binance. He said that Binance did have shortcomings in the past, but that the company had &ldquo;invested heavily in compliance programs&rdquo;, and that it was now working closely with law enforcement agencies around the globe. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Over the last two years, the company has completely changed its posture. Now that we have those resources, we are easily one of the most proactive parties to identify, freeze and get back funds&rdquo;</p>

<p>John Ghose, a former Justice Department prosecutor, was also featured in the Washington Post article. He stated that it was his belief that when&nbsp; he was a prosecutor Binance did not have a good reputation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In relation to whether Binance had allowed money laundering, tax evasion, or other crimes to take place on its platform, he said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The basis of those charges is whether there are U.S. customers. If there are U.S. customers, there are charges for avoiding the money laundering requirements.&rdquo;</p>

Could the Binance FUD topple crypto?
<p>Given that Binance is easily the biggest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, for it to fall would arguably have a simply huge knock-on for the rest of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>A collapse of the exchange could have dire consequences that could put the industry back years, making transacting in cryptocurrencies that much more difficult, as well as removing a very large investor in the space.</p>
<p>With all the furore surrounding the FTX debacle, the various bankruptcies of other crypto companies etc., now is a very bad time for crypto, and a very good time for authorities to turn the screw and attempt to subjugate, if not almost eliminate private digital asset transactions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Flares FLR Token Could Be This Years GMX]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/flares-flr-token-could-be-this-years-gmx</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-229.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-229.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-229.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/flares-flr-token-could-be-this-years-gmx</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>There weren&rsquo;t many standout tokens last year &ndash; holding anything other than stablecoins was likely to see you lose 80% in dollar value &ndash; but GMX was a notable exception. The native token of Arbitrum&rsquo;s derivatives exchange, GMX is up 35% in 12 months, no mean feat when most other assets were hemorrhaging hard through 2022.</p>
<p>2023 looks like another testing year for the crypto market, but observers have already zeroed in on one token that&rsquo;s being tipped as the next GMX. Its name? FLR. The native token of Flare&rsquo;s interoperable blockchain network is finally dropping on January 9, and anticipation is mounting that FLR could shake up a stagnant market.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
XRP Holders Get Their Day
<p>It&rsquo;s been over two years since a snapshot was taken of XRP balances with the goal of airdropping Flare&rsquo;s native token to them when the network launched. XRP was originally identified by Flare as being the community that would benefit the most from its interoperable EVM chain.</p>
<p>The XRP ledger, like other blockchains of that era, has no smart contract capacity, which severely limits the use cases for its eponymous asset. Step forward Flare, whose team believe they&rsquo;ve found a way to safely unlock assets on &ldquo;legacy chains&rdquo; such as Bitcoin, XRP, and Dogechain, freeing them to be used on Flare Network.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Airdrop It Like It&rsquo;s Hot
<p>So what can XRP holders and the crypto community at large expect on January 9 when FLR becomes tradable? Around 15% of FLR&rsquo;s total supply will be issued to airdrop recipients on this date, with the remainder of their share vesting monthly over 36 months. XRP holders whose tokens were held on a centralized exchange at the time of the original snapshot will be able to claim their FLR tokens there.</p>
<p>Flare has published the full list of exchanges supporting the airdrop and it includes most of the major players such as Binance, OKX, and Huobi. It&rsquo;s likely that many of these exchanges will also list the FLR token as opposed to simply letting users withdraw their balance.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Can Flare Reignite Crypto?
<p>There aren&rsquo;t many events to get the crypto community excited at the dawn of a new year; it&rsquo;s a time when nothing more dangerous than testnets is typically shipped. The launch of Flare&rsquo;s native token, then, should bring some cheer to airdrop recipients and give dormant traders a reason to awaken from their slumber and put their stablecoins to good use.</p>
<p>Hopes are high that Flare&rsquo;s interoperability solution will introduce a safer way to transfer value between chains. With $2 billion lost to bridge exploits last year alone, it can&rsquo;t come soon enough for DeFi users.</p>
<p>&ldquo;If information is revealed to be incorrect after transactions have been validated and assets have subsequently been reallocated to more established chains, the risk is introduced to the entire system,&rdquo; explains Flare CEO Hugo Philion. The industry will be watching closely to see whether Flare can improve on these shortcomings to deliver a secure system for cross-chain transfers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There weren&rsquo;t many standout tokens last year &ndash; holding anything other than stablecoins was likely to see you lose 80% in dollar value &ndash; but GMX was a notable exception. The native token of Arbitrum&rsquo;s derivatives exchange, GMX is up 35% in 12 months, no mean feat when most other assets were hemorrhaging hard through 2022.</p>
<p>2023 looks like another testing year for the crypto market, but observers have already zeroed in on one token that&rsquo;s being tipped as the next GMX. Its name? FLR. The native token of Flare&rsquo;s interoperable blockchain network is finally dropping on January 9, and anticipation is mounting that FLR could shake up a stagnant market.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
XRP Holders Get Their Day
<p>It&rsquo;s been over two years since a snapshot was taken of XRP balances with the goal of airdropping Flare&rsquo;s native token to them when the network launched. XRP was originally identified by Flare as being the community that would benefit the most from its interoperable EVM chain.</p>
<p>The XRP ledger, like other blockchains of that era, has no smart contract capacity, which severely limits the use cases for its eponymous asset. Step forward Flare, whose team believe they&rsquo;ve found a way to safely unlock assets on &ldquo;legacy chains&rdquo; such as Bitcoin, XRP, and Dogechain, freeing them to be used on Flare Network.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Airdrop It Like It&rsquo;s Hot
<p>So what can XRP holders and the crypto community at large expect on January 9 when FLR becomes tradable? Around 15% of FLR&rsquo;s total supply will be issued to airdrop recipients on this date, with the remainder of their share vesting monthly over 36 months. XRP holders whose tokens were held on a centralized exchange at the time of the original snapshot will be able to claim their FLR tokens there.</p>
<p>Flare has published the full list of exchanges supporting the airdrop and it includes most of the major players such as Binance, OKX, and Huobi. It&rsquo;s likely that many of these exchanges will also list the FLR token as opposed to simply letting users withdraw their balance.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Can Flare Reignite Crypto?
<p>There aren&rsquo;t many events to get the crypto community excited at the dawn of a new year; it&rsquo;s a time when nothing more dangerous than testnets is typically shipped. The launch of Flare&rsquo;s native token, then, should bring some cheer to airdrop recipients and give dormant traders a reason to awaken from their slumber and put their stablecoins to good use.</p>
<p>Hopes are high that Flare&rsquo;s interoperability solution will introduce a safer way to transfer value between chains. With $2 billion lost to bridge exploits last year alone, it can&rsquo;t come soon enough for DeFi users.</p>
<p>&ldquo;If information is revealed to be incorrect after transactions have been validated and assets have subsequently been reallocated to more established chains, the risk is introduced to the entire system,&rdquo; explains Flare CEO Hugo Philion. The industry will be watching closely to see whether Flare can improve on these shortcomings to deliver a secure system for cross-chain transfers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
