<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:18:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Here is How Much Curve Finance Has Recovered From Its $70M+ Hack </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-much-curve-finance-has-recovered-from-its-70m-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 01:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264808</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Curve_Hack.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Curve_Hack.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Since the deadline has passed, Curve has extended a 10% bounty for the remaining funds to the public as promised.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The hackers behind the recent exploit of several pools on the decentralized exchange Curve Finance have returned approximately 73% of the stolen crypto assets, accounting for about $52.3 million.</p>
<p>Blockchain security firm PeckShield <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1688404426825117697?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> Monday that Curve Finance lost $73.5 million in the hack. With the amount recovered so far, the exchange is looking to recoup the remaining $19.7 million.</p>
<h2>Curve Finance Recovers $52M of Stolen Assets</h2>
<p>Eight days ago, Curve Finance <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-finance-hacker-returns-5-4-million-but-crv-dumps-15/" data-wpel-link="internal">suffered</a> a reentrancy attack that affected four pools using a certain version of the Ethereum Virtual Machine smart contract programming language Vyper. The hack extended to several decentralized finance protocols, including Metronome, Alchemix, and Ellipsis.</p>
<p>On August 3, Curve, Metronome, and Alchemix contacted the attackers via an on-chain message, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-finance-offers-10-bug-bounty-to-attackers-behind-vyper-50m-exploit/" data-wpel-link="internal">offering</a> a 10% bug bounty in exchange for the return of 90% of the stolen assets. The platforms promised to cease pursuing the case with law enforcement if the assets were returned before 08:00 UTC on August 6.</p>
<p>Failure to comply with the proposal would force the protocols to offer a public and give the reward to whoever identifies the hackers in a way that leads to their conviction in court, per the message.</p>
<p>Less than 24 hours after the proposal, one of the exploiters <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xdce5d6b41c32f578f875efffc0d422c57a75d7d8#tokentxns" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">sent</a> 4,819 ether (ETH) worth $8.9 million to Alchemix after <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x0af1d34ec0bb67a99f0148863558e4c84804349415801874876a17f85e4290e1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">asking</a> the protocol team to confirm their wallet address to avoid making a wrong transfer.</p>
<h2>Curve Extends Bounty for Remaining Funds</h2>
<p>Over the weekend, the attackers returned most funds to the affected protocols. PeckShield explained that Alchemix received all of its lost assets, amounting to $22 million in ETH and alETH, while JPEG’d, another affected protocol, received $10.1 million in WETH.</p>
<p>In addition, white hat hackers returned the $13 million taken from Alchemix during the exploit, and Metronome received $1.4 million, adding to the $5.4 million returned by c0ffeebabe.eth on August 31. It is worth noting that JPEG’d and Metronome hackers returned 90% of the funds, keeping the remaining 10% as Curve offered.</p>
<p>Since the deadline has passed, Curve has <a href="https://twitter.com/CurveFinance/status/1688221472815284224?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">extended</a> a 10% bounty for the remaining funds to the public as promised. The exchange noted that the offer would end if the exploiter chose to return the funds in full.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-much-curve-finance-has-recovered-from-its-70m-hack/" rel="nofollow">Here is How Much Curve Finance Has Recovered From Its $70M+ Hack </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Short Bitcoin Outflows Halt for the First Time in 14 Weeks: CoinShares Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/short-bitcoin-outflows-halt-for-the-first-time-in-14-weeks-coinshares-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264879</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_cover-8.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_cover-8.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Solana saw the highest inflows among the altcoins, clocking its most bullish week in 16 months.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The summer period&#8217;s lackluster trading activity is evident as digital asset investment products recorded outflows of $107 million this week. The profit-taking has gathered tremendous pace lately, with weekly trading volumes in investment products 36% below the year-to-date average.</p>
<p>The wider on-exchange market has experienced a more significant decline, with volumes down 62% relative to the year-to-date average, according to the latest edition of CoinShares&#8217; weekly report on digital asset fund flows.</p>
<ul>
<li>Institutional investors have continued to focus on Bitcoin and <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-143-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-6d46f78754c" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">witnessed</a> outflows of $111 million. This marks the largest weekly outflows since March as regulatory tensions escalated in the US.</li>
<li>CoinShares also revealed that the outflows into short bitcoin have stopped for the first time in 14 weeks, indicating that institutional investors have stopped betting against crypto despite the summer doldrums.</li>
<li>Ethereum, too experienced outflows amounting to a total of $6 million, contributing to a combined outflow of $117 million for both Bitcoin and Ethereum in the past week.</li>
<li>There is an apparent improvement in sentiment towards altcoins, which has helped counterbalance the outflows in Bitcoin and Ethereum.</li>
<li>Solana witnessed its most significant influxes, reaching a total of $9.5 million, representing the highest amount of weekly inflows since March 2022.</li>
<li>Noteworthy highlights included XRP and Litecoin, which experienced inflows of $0.5 million and $0.46 million, respectively. While Ripple&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partial win</a> against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) can be attributed to renewed bullish sentiment for XRP, the recent<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-undergoes-3rd-halving-but-ltc-plunges-6-why/" data-wpel-link="internal"> halving event</a> can be deemed as a catalyst for Litecoin&#8217;s inflows.</li>
<li>On the other hand, Uniswap and Cardano encountered outflows of $0.8 million and $0.3 million, respectively.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/short-bitcoin-outflows-halt-for-the-first-time-in-14-weeks-coinshares-report/" rel="nofollow">Short Bitcoin Outflows Halt for the First Time in 14 Weeks: CoinShares Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Records Impressive 49% QoQ Growth in Dapp Transactions; 10% Rise in TVL: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-records-impressive-49-qoq-growth-in-dapp-transactions-10-rise-in-tvl-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264885</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/cardano_cover-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/cardano_cover-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cardano ecosystem has grown significantly despite ADA's inaction. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) has shown promising indications of growth in Q2 despite lackluster market activity. Emerging infrastructure such as stablecoins, programming languages, and wallets are helping Cardano developers to craft advanced applications enriched with enhanced user experiences, according to a new report by Messari.</p>
<p>The blockchain intelligence platform reported that the Cardano ecosystem has managed to diversify with newer protocols that have contributed significantly to various activity metrics even as ADA&#8217;s price and market cap suffered a drawdown during the period.</p>
<h2>Cardano Ecosystem Growth: Q2</h2>
<p>According to Messari&#8217;s <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-cardano-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> titled &#8216;State of Cardano&#8217; for the Q2 edition, the average transaction rose by 8.5% compared to the previous quarter, going from $0.117 to $0.126. Despite this consecutive quarterly rise, the average transaction fee in USD remains 50.8% lower year over year, primarily due to decreased ADA prices compared to the previous year.</p>
<p>Transaction activity also surged in the second quarter of the year. Average daily transactions increased by approximately 2% QoQ from 67,500 to 68,800. Messari highlighted that the growth is crucial as movement in transactions and active addresses are typically correlated, but have deviated slightly in recent quarters.</p>
<p>Over the last five quarters, there has been a consistent increase in the ratio of transactions to active addresses, indicating heightened user engagement compared to earlier periods. During Q2, the Transaction / Active Address ratio reached 1.19, marking a sequential rise of 6.1% and a year-over-year surge of 13.2%.</p>
<p>For the third successive quarter, Cardano has witnessed growth in its average daily dapp transactions. Dapp usage surged with a notable 49.0% increase from the previous quarter in Q2, maintaining an average of 57,900 daily transactions.</p>
<h2>Surging Blockchain Activity</h2>
<p>Cardano&#8217;s total value locked (TVL) saw a 9.7% quarter-over-quarter rise, reaching $151.7 million. This growth in TVL is particularly noteworthy given the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ada-at-critical-support-massive-move-expected-three-things-to-watch-cardano-price-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">decrease</a> in ADA&#8217;s price. Furthermore, the layer-1 smart contract platform&#8217;s year-to-date TVL has soared by 198.6% (in USD), propelling it from the 34th to the 21st position among all networks in 2023.</p>
<p>Minswap, which happens to be an automated market maker (AMM), continued to hold its position as the liquidity king of Cardano DeFi, concluding the second quarter of the year with a TVL of nearly $50 million and over 32% dominance.</p>
<p>The report also noted that the stablecoin infrastructure is yet another factor fueling this TVL run on the blockchain. Data also suggest that Cardano&#8217;s stablecoin market cap climbed up from 54th to 37th in 2023.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-records-impressive-49-qoq-growth-in-dapp-transactions-10-rise-in-tvl-report/" rel="nofollow">Cardano Records Impressive 49% QoQ Growth in Dapp Transactions; 10% Rise in TVL: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MakerDAO&#8217;s Spark Protocol Blocks VPN Use; Privacy Advocates Cry Foul</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/makerdaos-spark-protocol-blocks-vpn-use-privacy-advocates-cry-foul/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MakerDAO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264742</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/makerdao.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/makerdao.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Spark's stance on VPN usage courts criticism from the DeFi community. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MakerDAO&#8217;s recently launched lending platform, Spark Protocol, has courted significant backlash over its decision to ban VPN users on the front end. The initial motive was to prevent US-based users from accessing the platform. But it prohibits anyone from using a VPN regardless of whether or not they are situated within the US.</p>
<p>This has sparked strong reactions from privacy advocates.</p>
<h2>War on Privacy</h2>
<p>MakerDAO ramped up the yield on the DAI stablecoin from 3% to 8% as part of the <a href="https://twitter.com/RuneKek/status/1688235137178509312" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">implementation</a> of the Enhanced Dai Savings Rate (EDSR).</p>
<p>Following the modifications in yield, on-chain data identified a peculiar transaction from an individual wallet involving the transfer of over 14.3 million DAO stablecoin into MarkerDAO by a single crypto participant. The transfer was speculated to have been conducted to take advantage of the 8% yield, which is offered through MakerDAO&#8217;s lending platform, Spark.</p>
<p>While Maker restricted users in the United States from accessing the crypto lending platform, what caught many by surprise was an <a href="https://www.sparkprotocol.io/terms-of-use.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a> on Spark Protocol&#8217;s terms and conditions cautioning against employing VPNs to bypass the restriction.</p>
<p>The notification read,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Use of the credit protocol functions of the site by persons who are currently or ordinarily located or resident in the United States is strictly prohibited, regardless of the user&#8217;s IP address. Utilizing a virtual private network or other method to conceal a user&#8217;s United States residence is also strictly prohibited and may result in permanent blocking of the use of the site in connection with blockchain addresses suspected of being tied to a United States residence.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>For the uninitiated, Spark Protocol was launched in May this year, which offered users up to 8% in annual returns by lending DAI. It was created as a soft fork of Aave v3 by a blockchain company rolled out by the Maker Foundation called Phoenix Labs.</p>
<h2>Reactions</h2>
<p>Popular DeFi analyst Chris Blec <a href="https://twitter.com/ChrisBlec/status/1688236822399217666" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">expressed</a> his strong disapproval, emphasizing that it essentially functions as a comprehensive prohibition on VPNs worldwide, extending beyond the borders of the US.</p>
<p>Blec highlighted a clear distinction between blocking access for US residents and imposing a broader prohibition on individuals globally who utilize VPNs to safeguard their privacy. He characterized this broader move as a significant encroachment on the concept of privacy, likening it to an active campaign against the fundamental notion of personal privacy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/makerdaos-spark-protocol-blocks-vpn-use-privacy-advocates-cry-foul/" rel="nofollow">MakerDAO&#8217;s Spark Protocol Blocks VPN Use; Privacy Advocates Cry Foul</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>71-Year Old Israeli Lady Who Made 100X on Her BTC Investment Dismisses Lawsuit Against Uncooperating Local Bank</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/71-year-old-israeli-lady-who-made-100x-on-her-btc-investment-dismisses-lawsuit-against-uncooperating-local-bank/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Israel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264845</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2021-11-20_21-20-37.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2021-11-20_21-20-37.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["For various reasons, the procedure became irrelevant, and therefore the sides agreed to dismiss the claim," the pensioner's lawyer said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Esther Freeman &#8211; a 70-year-old Israeli resident who turned a $3,000 BTC investment into over $320,000 in 2021 &#8211; has terminated the legal battle with Bank Hapoalim. The latter was unwilling to accept her crypto profits, casting doubts on the source of the funds she used to hop on the Bitcoin bandwagon.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Her investment is currently worth approximately $160,000 due to the price decrease of the leading digital asset over the following years.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dismissal of the Case Less Than Two Years After its Start</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Israeli pensioner </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/israeli-bank-refuses-to-deposit-over-300000-earned-from-a-bitcoin-investment-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">made the headlines</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in November 2021 when her initial $3,240 investment in Bitcoin rose to an astonishing $324,000. She revealed that she entered BTC&#8217;s ecosystem in 2013, meaning it took her eight years to see her stash reach that level. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I listened to my son and nephews, to the young guys, and said that an attempt would be made. Without any knowledge on the subject, in the real innocence of an ordinary citizen,&#8221; she explained the reason behind her decision. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">And while it sounded like Freeman had won the lottery jackpot, she encountered unexpected issues with Bank Hapoalim, which refused to deposit the profit. The financial institution claimed that her initial investment in Bitcoin was made in cash, which could have originated from illicit procedures. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The characteristics of virtual (i.e., digital) currencies allow them to be transferred anonymously and unsupervised, often bypassing the need to use the financial factors that apply to the anti-money laundering and terrorist financing regime,&#8221; the bank added at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Freeman appointed an attorney and filed a lawsuit against the entity, insisting that she had been a loyal client over the years. She also asserted that the money would help one of her children to buy an apartment.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite her efforts, though, Freeman seems to have had little success in her legal battle against Bank Hapoalim and recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.calcalistech.com/ctechnews/article/hkskmbas2" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">dismissed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the case.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The lawsuit against the bank has been dismissed. The bank acted from the beginning in accordance with its obligations according to law, including the Anti-Money Laundering Law,&#8221; the monetary organization stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It also pointed out its policies, according to which it should not be forced to accept funds generated from crypto investments.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Freeman called the bank&#8217;s claims &#8220;unfounded.&#8221; Her lawyer &#8211; Shaul Zioni &#8211; confirmed the termination of the lawsuit, adding that the Israeli authorities are currently looking to establish a mechanism to regulate such transfer of funds. He did not disclose whether the pensioner was able to deposit the profits at some point.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Profit is not so Whopping any More</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is interesting to note that the USD representation of Freeman&#8217;s Bitcoin investment is now quite different from its peak in November 2021. Calculated by current prices, her stash is approximately worth $160,000, or a 50% decrease.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is hard to predict whether the investment could rise to such a level again in the future. However, there are many pending developments in the crypto industry that could propel another bull run for the primary digital asset should or when they see the light of day.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The possible approval of a spot BTC ETF in America, a probable adoption coming from a giant corporation (such as Tesla or Apple), or the highly-anticipated Halving in 2024 could be some of the contributing factors.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/71-year-old-israeli-lady-who-made-100x-on-her-btc-investment-dismisses-lawsuit-against-uncooperating-local-bank/" rel="nofollow">71-Year Old Israeli Lady Who Made 100X on Her BTC Investment Dismisses Lawsuit Against Uncooperating Local Bank</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $200 Million Worth of Major Tokens to be Unlocked This Week: What You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/over-200-million-worth-of-major-tokens-to-be-unlocked-this-week-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitMEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Sandbox (SAND)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264833</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unlock_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unlock_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DAO, GMT, ICP, BMEX, APT, and SAND token unlocks are lined up this week. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto tokens worth upwards of $212 million are set to unlock this week. According to the latest data, five projects &#8211; Dao Maker (DAO), STEPN (GMT), Internet Computer (ICP), BitMEX (BMEX), Aptos (APT), The Sandbox (SAND), according to data compiled by DropsTab.</p>
<p>The token unlocks could potentially create some significant sell pressure.</p>
<h2>Token Unlocks: Weekly Edition</h2>
<p>The DAO Maker Token is the governance token of the DAO Maker ecosystem built on top of the Ethereum blockchain. The token unlock of 20.82 million DAO, representing 7.41% of the total supply, is <a href="https://dropstab.com/insights/vesting" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">scheduled</a> for August 9th.</p>
<p>GMT is the native token of a WEB 3 lifestyle app called STEPN which has &#8220;Social-Fi and Game-Fi&#8221; elements. The token unlock of 87.92 million GMT, accounting for 1.47% of the total supply, is also set for August 9th.</p>
<p>ICP is the native utility token of layer-1 blockchain Internet Computer and is used to facilitate network governance and reward participants. It&#8217;s scheduled for an unlock of 3.31 million ICP, which is over 0.7% of the total supply, on August 11th.</p>
<p>BMEX is a functional utility token designed for use on the crypto exchange, BitMEX. More than 18.5 million of BMEX, representing 4.12% of the total supply, will be unlocked on August 11th.</p>
<p>APT, the native token of a layer 1 blockchain <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-apt-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Aptos</a>, that uses the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, is scheduled for another unlock event on August 12th involving the release of 4.54 million APT, which is around 0.45% of the total supply.</p>
<p>SAND, the ERC-20 utility token built on the Ethereum blockchain and used throughout The Sandbox ecosystem, is slated to witness an unlocking event on August 14th, during which 308.46 million SAND or 10.28% of the total supply will be released.</p>
<p>Collectively, this week will see the unlock tokens worth over $212 million.</p>
<h2>Pressure on Price?</h2>
<p>Token lockup, often called a vesting period, is essentially a specific timeframe during which tokens are restricted from being traded or liquidated. The length of this interval is determined by the team&#8217;s chosen approach and can extend for multiple years in certain instances.</p>
<p>Hence, the release of crypto tokens usually amplifies selling pressure on the assets, influenced by both the number of unlocked tokens and their influx into cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>Previous unlocks, too, have demonstrated more declines amidst new tokens entering the market. All five assets have already been experiencing significant bearish pressure.</p>
<p>APT was the biggest loser of the five tokens, seeing its value decline by more than 8% over the past month. DAO also recorded a decline of nearly 5% during the same period, followed by SAND with a little over 4%. Other tokens, such as GMT and BMEX, also noted an underwhelming price performance and were down by 3.7% and 2.4%, respectively in the last month. ICP was the highest gainer among all, with a minor decline of 1%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-200-million-worth-of-major-tokens-to-be-unlocked-this-week-what-you-need-to-know/" rel="nofollow">Over $200 Million Worth of Major Tokens to be Unlocked This Week: What You Need to Know</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kenyan Police Raided Worldcoin Warehouse in Nairobi: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kenyan-police-raided-worldcoin-warehouse-in-nairobi-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264861</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Kenya.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Kenya.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Data Commissioner Immaculate Kassait said Worldcoin’s parent company, Tools for Humanity, did not reveal its true intentions during registration.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kenyan police officers have reportedly raided a warehouse belonging to the recently launched crypto project Worldcoin, carting away documents and machines for investigative purposes.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://kahawatungu.com/police-raid-worldcoin-cryptocurrency-warehouse-in-nairobi-over-data/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> by local media KahawaTungu, police officers showed up at the Nairobi-based warehouse over the weekend with a search warrant and multi-agency officials. They left with equipment believed to store data collected by Worldcoin.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin Nairobi Warehouse Raided</h2>
<p>Recall that the Kenyan government <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kenya-authorities-suspend-worldcoin-activities-over-data-privacy-concerns/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> the suspension of all activities related to Worldcoin’s registration and the distribution of its native token WLD on August 2, less than two weeks after the project’s launch. Relevant agencies want to investigate the legality and authenticity of the project’s launch.</p>
<p>Worldcoin was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/openai-ceo-sam-altmans-crypto-project-worldcoin-launches-wld-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> in July as a decentralized identification project to differentiate humans from artificial intelligence bots. Using a proof-of-person concept, the project claims to preserve privacy while combating income inequality.</p>
<p>The most controversial part of the Worldcoin project is the requirement for users to prove their humanity online by scanning their irises through a biometric verification device called Orb and afterward receive free WLD tokens. While the project’s team, led by OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, stated that the Orb does not store users’ data, the method has sparked concerns about privacy violations.</p>
<p>The machines seized from Worldcoin’s Nairobi warehouse were taken to the Directorate of Criminal Investigations headquarters for analysis and investigations. Data Commissioner Immaculate Kassait said Worldcoin’s parent company, Tools for Humanity, did not reveal its true intentions during registration.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin Not Registered in Kenya: Government</h2>
<p>The Kenyan Capital Markets Authority has also expressed concerns about Worldcoin’s registration activities, alerting residents that the project is not regulated in the country. While Worldcoin claims its operations comply with Kenyan regulations, Interior Cabinet Secretary Kithure Kindiki has told Parliament that the project is not registered as a legal entity.</p>
<p>Worldcoin announced that it chose Kenya as the first African country to begin its operations because of the nation’s growing tech space and the significant number of Kenyans who trade crypto. The entity also operates in the UK, Germany, Spain, and Japan.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, data protection agencies in various regions, including France, Germany, and the UK, have begun examinations into the crypto project to ensure no data regulations are violated.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kenyan-police-raided-worldcoin-warehouse-in-nairobi-report/" rel="nofollow">Kenyan Police Raided Worldcoin Warehouse in Nairobi: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CryptoMinerBros Celebrates 5 Years of Building the Future in the Crypto Mining Community</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264881</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Crypto_miner_bros_5th_anniversary_1691144335FpO8KV6zJG.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Crypto_miner_bros_5th_anniversary_1691144335FpO8KV6zJG.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Kowloon city, HongKong, August 7th, 2023] Founded in August 2018 and headquartered in Hong Kong, Crypto Miner Bros has become one of the leading crypto mining hardware distributors within five years of its launch. With a dedicated team of blockchain experts, e-commerce specialists, and crypto mining professionals, Crypto Miner Bros has become [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Kowloon city, HongKong, August 7th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Founded in August 2018 and headquartered in Hong Kong, <a href="https://www.cryptominerbros.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Crypto Miner Bros</a> has become one of the leading crypto mining hardware distributors within five years of its launch. With a dedicated team of blockchain experts, e-commerce specialists, and crypto mining professionals, Crypto Miner Bros has become a reputable name in the crypto mining industry.</p>
<p>Crypto Miner Bros has built an incredible mining community that wholeheartedly believes in the company’s vision of making crypto mining accessible to everyone. The company’s progress and achievements would not have been possible without the invaluable support of the clients. Crypto Miner Bros is committed to giving back to the community by offering the world’s finest crypto mining tools and comprehensive end-to-end crypto mining solutions.</p>
<p>In August 2018, Crypto Miner Bros started as an E-commerce platform specializing in crypto mining hardware with a vision of providing miners with a positive crypto mining experience. Within one year of its launch, the company had already become one of the world’s most trusted platforms for crypto mining hardware. Crypto Miner Bros is endorsed by globally recognized brands such as Nicehash, Asic Miner Value, Crypto Compare, Whattomine, and CoinWarz. The company’s goal for the upcoming year is to continue making crypto mining accessible to everyone, spreading the benefits of this technology far and wide.</p>
<p>Buying crypto mining hardware from a reliable source has always been challenging for international buyers. Crypto Miner Bros provides an excellent platform for miners by joining hands with reputed mining hardware manufacturers in China and Hong Kong. Miners can find all the reputed mining hardware brands from Bitmain to Canaan Avalon Goldshell, Jasminer, MicroBT, Innosilicon, and more on the Crypto Miner Bros <a href="https://www.cryptominerbros.com/product-brands/innosilicon/?orderby=date" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">website</a>.</p>
<p>Entering its sixth year, Crypto Miner Bros focuses on bridging the gap between miners and manufacturers and getting quality crypto mining products to the global market. The company constantly strives to expand the mining community of Crypto Miner Bros in the coming year by introducing P2P (Peer-to-Peer) deals. Thus, miners can readily access advanced ASICs at better deals and enjoy hassle-free buying. The company also aids faster shipping to customers worldwide with its dedicated sales team. Though Crypto Miner Bros has an active international sales team, the organization plans to have dedicated technical support centers in every continent. Thus, the company can promptly ship the miners to any location and assist the customer with their queries. Besides, Crypto Miner Bros will continue to act as a reliable platform for all crypto miners with a rich source of information related to crypto mining, cryptocurrencies, blockchain, and other related topics. Moreover, the company’s dedicated customer support team will assist the customers 24/7 in setting up the ASIC or any hiccups customers may face with crypto mining.</p>
<h4><strong>About Crypto Miner Bros</strong></h4>
<p>Crypto Miner Bros, a leading Asic hardware provider, continues delivering high-quality products and services worldwide to all crypto mining enthusiasts. The company partners with reputed mining hardware manufacturers and deals with high-quality mining equipment to provide a positive mining experience to its customers. For more information visit Crypto Miner&#8217;s <a href="https://www.cryptominerbros.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">official website</a>.</p>
<p>Crypto Miner Bros extends its heartfelt gratitude to its customers, stakeholders, and employees. Crypto Miner Bros promises to continue delivering excellent products and services in the years to come. Miners can look forward to Crypto Miner Bros for advanced mining equipment, informative videos, educational content, and, of course, 24/7 assistance.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptominerbros-celebrates-5-years-of-building-the-future-in-the-crypto-mining-community/" rel="nofollow">CryptoMinerBros Celebrates 5 Years of Building the Future in the Crypto Mining Community</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Launches USD Stablecoin For Payments and Transfers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264864</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/paypal-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/paypal-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[For now, users can only use PYUSD for crypto and web3-related activities, such as in-game payments and exchanges with other crypto assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Global payments giant PayPal has deepened its footsteps into the crypto industry by launching a dollar-backed stablecoin dubbed PayPal USD (PYUSD). The move makes PayPal one of the first large U.S. financial companies to launch its own stablecoin despite regulatory uncertainty around crypto assets in the country. </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As a USD-pegged stablecoin, PayPal USD maintains a fixed value to the U.S. dollar, and it will be issued by the popular white-label stablecoin maker </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paxos Trust Co.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Like other USD-pegged stablecoins, PYUSD is backed by USD deposits, short-term treasuries, and other cash equivalents, according to a Fortune <a href="https://archive.is/mmyrG#selection-1307.7-1307.37" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> on Monday.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For now, users can only use PYUSD for crypto and web3-related activities, such as in-game payments and exchanges with other crypto assets. But in the long run, PayPal intends to use PYUSD to facilitate low-cost payments and transfers among users and merchants worldwide.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company said it would gradually roll out the new digital currency to customers in the U.S.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dan Schulman, president and CEO of PayPal, believes the move is part of the company&#8217;s efforts to cement its position in the digital payments industry, as there is a need for a stable asset to bridge the gap between the traditional and digital worlds. </span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The shift toward digital currencies requires a stable instrument that is both digitally native and easily connected to fiat currency like the U.S. dollar,&#8221; Schulman said in a statement.</span></li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company has already <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-enables-eligible-us-customers-to-buy-sell-and-store-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">added</a> support for other cryptocurrencies, such as bitcoin and ether, since 2020, and users can swap PYUSD for all supported digital assets on the platform. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" rel="nofollow">PayPal Launches USD Stablecoin For Payments and Transfers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Price Slips Over 6% as Major Coins Struggle, But These New Tokens Are Defying the Bear Market</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-price-slips-over-6-as-major-coins-struggle-but-these-new-tokens-are-defying-the-bear-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264886</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/wsm_shibie_shib_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/wsm_shibie_shib_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Several top meme coins have dropped significantly over the weekend, with Shiba Inu one of the worst affected, down 4.69% in 24 hours. Other high-value meme coins are also down in the last seven days, with Dogecoin and Pepe down 6% and 10%, respectively. However, newer low-cap meme coins have pushed ahead unfazed, with Shibie [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several top meme coins have dropped significantly over the weekend, with Shiba Inu one of the worst affected, down 4.69% in 24 hours. Other high-value meme coins are also down in the last seven days, with Dogecoin and Pepe down 6% and 10%, respectively.</p>
<p>However, newer low-cap meme coins have pushed ahead unfazed, with Shibie Coin and Wall Street Memes leading the way amongst the next generation of viral crypto assets.</p>
<h2><strong>Shiba Inu Loses Its Recent Gains Amid Bearish Market Sentiment</strong></h2>
<p>Shiba Inu is working towards the mainnet release of Shibarium, its Ethereum layer two scaling solution. This recently generated significant excitement in the community, causing the SHIB price to climb. However, the project stalled over the weekend, causing a subsequent dump, with SHIB falling from $0.00001035 on 5 August to $0.0000092 today.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264891" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-11.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="624" height="343" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-11.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-11-300x165.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-11-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>The recent selloff is likely a consequence of the broader meme coin market&#8217;s current bearish sentiment, with other top meme coins down significantly in the last seven days.</p>
<p>However, the recent Shiba Inu pump may have been a mere “bull trap” because if we zoom out to the one-year chart, we can see SHIB’s overarching direction is bearish.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264890" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-7.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="624" height="343" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-7.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-7-300x165.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-7-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>SHIB is down 23% over the past year and 89.64% from its ATH, continuing to make lower lowers and lower highs.</p>
<p>As a result, the recent pump may have been caused by fear of missing out (FOMO) due to the Shibarium development and market makers artificially pumping the price to trick retail into buying SHIB at a higher price.</p>
<p>Also, Dogecoin and Pepe have faced difficulty recently, with both projects massively down from their ATHs.</p>
<p>Dogecoin is down 89% from its ATH. Meanwhile, Pepe is down 73% from its ATH and down 25% in the past month alone.</p>
<p>One of the reasons for the downfall of the top meme coins is that they are driven by hype and FOMO. Investors want to capitalize on volatility but realize that lower-cap coins provide better alternatives to multi-billion dollar market cap projects.</p>
<p>As such, the hype around top meme coins is dying out, with much of the meme coin community shifting its focus to new lesser-known meme coins.</p>
<h2><strong>Barbie-Shiba Inu Crossbreed Shibie Coin Eyes Quick Presale After Raising $160K</strong></h2>
<p>What happens when a culturally revolutionary movie like Barbie crossbreeds with a top meme coin like <a href="https://bs_ff115a97.cleardayboat.care/?referrer=shiba-inu-price-slips-over-6-as-major-coins-struggle-but-these-new-tokens-are-defying-the-bear-market" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shiba Inu</a>? That remains to be seen, but a group of trend-savvy devs have dared to find out.</p>
<p>Shibie Coin is a new meme coin inspired by a blend of Barbie and Shiba Inu. The project was released following the blockbuster Barbie movie release, which took the world by storm recently.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264889" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-4.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="624" height="288" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-4.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-4-300x138.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-4-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>It is currently available at presale, with a hard cap of just $999,999, and has already raised over $160K. The presale looks to sell out quickly, with just seven days until it closes.</p>
<p>According to its <a href="https://shibie.io/whitepaper/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, 60% of tokens will be available at presale, with 20% allocated to liquidity, 10% towards CEX listings, 5% to marketing, and 5% to the team.</p>
<p>Shibie Coin has proven widely popular, with prominent analysts like <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txQR4Toe1JY&amp;pp=ygULc2hpYmllIGNvaW4%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Jacob Bury</a> praising the project.</p>
<p>One of its main draws is that it enables prudent investors to capitalize on the iconic cultural talking points raised in the new movie.</p>
<p>That said, the project also promises a fun “tail-wagging journey” and will launch an AI-powered Telegram bot for the community to “engage in playful banter” with.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_ff115a97.cleardayboat.care/?referrer=shiba-inu-price-slips-over-6-as-major-coins-struggle-but-these-new-tokens-are-defying-the-bear-market" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Shibie Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2><strong>Wall Street Memes Touted as Next Big Meme Coin Having Raised $22 Million at Presale</strong></h2>
<p>One of the most successful crypto presales of this year so far, <a href="https://bs_4b4d7160.cleardayboat.care/?referrer=shiba-inu-price-slips-over-6-as-major-coins-struggle-but-these-new-tokens-are-defying-the-bear-market" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a>, has recently surpassed $22 million in raised funds. Investors have been flocking to the project the past week to secure their $WSM tokens at a discounted presale price ahead of its exchange launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264888" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-2.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="624" height="291" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-2.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-2-300x140.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-2-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>Popular YouTuber <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ly8OH76mbTs&amp;pp=ygURd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXM%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Michael Wrubel</a>, who has over 300K subs, has been a big proponent of the project, backing it since early in its presale.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Memes project quickly rose to prominence as it launched with over one million social media followers. Founded in 2021, Wall Street Memes was inspired by the GameStop and Wall Street Bets saga.</p>
<p>It began posting memes to social media and then released an NFT collection, Wall St Bulls, which sold out in 32 minutes and raised $2.5 million. Since then, the project has built a massive community, with even <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1649784663924244482" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Elon Musk engaging with its tweets</a>.</p>
<p>The new meme coin aims to follow in the footsteps of Wall Street Bets and fight traditional finance malpractice through community, memes and humor. However, Wall Street Memes will “tokenize the movement” by bringing it to crypto.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes’ presale has a $30,577,000 hard cap, so time is running out to join with over $22 million already raised.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_4b4d7160.cleardayboat.care/?referrer=shiba-inu-price-slips-over-6-as-major-coins-struggle-but-these-new-tokens-are-defying-the-bear-market" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-price-slips-over-6-as-major-coins-struggle-but-these-new-tokens-are-defying-the-bear-market/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu Price Slips Over 6% as Major Coins Struggle, But These New Tokens Are Defying the Bear Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
