<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:18:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cirus Invited to Attend the Web3 Investor Day Conference Sponsored by Decasonic</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cirus-invited-to-attend-the-web3-investor-day-conference-sponsored-by-decasonic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258971</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Michael_Decasonic_1_1688570346FJzr0YV5Ub.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Michael_Decasonic_1_1688570346FJzr0YV5Ub.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Raratonga, Cook Islands, July 6th, 2023] Cirus, a prominent company in the Web3 industry, is pleased to be a select invitee and keynote speaker at the Web3 Investor Day Conference, an invite-only event powered by Decasonic. Decasonic is a Web3 venture and digital assets fund supporting the development of blockchain innovation. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Raratonga, Cook Islands, July 6th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.cirusfoundation.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Cirus</a>, a prominent company in the Web3 industry, is pleased to be a select invitee and keynote speaker at the Web3<a href="https://www.decasonic.com/2023-web3-investor-day" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> Investor Day Conference</a>, an invite-only event powered by Decasonic. Decasonic is a Web3 venture and digital assets fund supporting the development of blockchain innovation. The event is scheduled to take place on July 20th, 2023, in Chicago, IL.</p>
<p>The Web3 Investor Day Conference brings together an elite group of prominent capital allocators, family offices, endowments, and builders who are at the forefront of the Web3 industry. With over 300 influential stakeholders and Web3 investors expected, this event serves as a unique platform for startups and established projects to showcase their innovative ideas with leading funds.</p>
<p>Michael Luckhoo, a pioneer in the Web3 industry and Founder of Cirus, will be on panel discussions on topics covering the impact of Web3 in current industries, expressed his enthusiasm for the upcoming event, stating,</p>
<blockquote><p>“I’m excited to represent Cirus and speak about critical subjects that separate technology advantages over industry mishaps this year. I think smart investors need a renewed view on the inevitable future of Web3 and the removal of labels caused in-part by highly centralized figures.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Cirus, has established itself as a must-watch project in the Web3 industry. Recognized as the next generation of Web3 wallets, Cirus has gained traction in the market, captivating the attention of Web3 enthusiasts. With its focus on being the most seamless on-ramp into Web3, Cirus has been pushing to drive the adoption across various sectors, including finance, data, and most recently enterprise as they announced <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/23/06/33065204/cirus-launches-wallet-as-a-service-initiative-waas" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">the launch of their WaaS Innovation unit</a> last week.</p>
<p>The event organizers have carefully curated an exceptional lineup of speakers who will share their insights and expertise, making the Web3 Investor Day Conference an invaluable event for all participants.</p>
<h2>About Cirus Foundation</h2>
<p>Cirus Foundation is the development team behind the Cirus Ecosystem, an accessible onramp designed to accelerate the adoption of Web 3.0 and the Ownership Economy. This consists of the Cirus suite of tools, which work together to give users true ownership over their assets, and the data streams they generate</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cirus-invited-to-attend-the-web3-investor-day-conference-sponsored-by-decasonic/" rel="nofollow">Cirus Invited to Attend the Web3 Investor Day Conference Sponsored by Decasonic</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock&#8217;s BTC ETF Filing Could &#8216;Democratize Crypto,&#8217; CEO Larry Fink Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-btc-etf-filing-could-democratize-crypto-ceo-larry-fink-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258892</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/LarryFink.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/LarryFink.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Fink likened crypto to "digitizing gold" and outlined bitcoin as an "international asset" that could serve as a hedge against inflation.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Larry Fink &#8211; Chief Executive Officer of BlackRock &#8211; raised hopes that his company&#8217;s recent filing to launch a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the USA could make investing in the primary cryptocurrency less expensive and &#8220;democratize crypto.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American regulators have not approved such a product yet. However, BlackRock&#8217;s outstanding record with the SEC made some believe it could become the first company with such a green light.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Praising Crypto (Bitcoin)</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/video/6330640643112" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Fox Business, Fink noted that BTC transactions are still quite expensive. As such, one of BlackRock&#8217;s efforts in the field is to remove that burden for investors:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;What we&#8217;re trying to do with crypto is make it more democratized and make it much cheaper for investors. It costs a lot of money right now to transact Bitcoin. We hope our regulators look at these filings as a way to democratize crypto.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_258893" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258893" style="width: 712px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Larry-Fink.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-258893" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Larry-Fink.webp" alt="Larry Fink" width="712" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Larry-Fink.webp 931w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Larry-Fink-300x169.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Larry-Fink-768x431.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Larry-Fink-50x28.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 712px) 100vw, 712px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258893" class="wp-caption-text">Larry Fink, Source: Fox Business</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;" data-preserver-spaces="true">Recall that the world&#8217;s largest asset manager splashed the waters in mid-June when it </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" style="font-size: 16px;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;" data-preserver-spaces="true"> to introduce a spot BTC ETF in the US. The SEC has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" style="font-size: 16px;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">approved</span></a><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;" data-preserver-spaces="true"> 575 out of its 576 ETF attempts over the years, causing some to believe that such a BTC-related product could finally see the light of day in America. </span><br />
</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, the Commission initially considered the effort &#8220;inadequate,&#8221; forcing BlackRock to refile, naming Coinbase as a &#8220;surveillance partner.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fink also joined the list of prominent individuals who think the asset class is akin to digital gold. More specifically, he claimed that people could distribute some of their wealth in BTC instead of in the precious metal as a hedge against inflation and protection against the devaluation of many national currencies.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Bitcoin is an international asset. It&#8217;s not based on anyone&#8217;s currency, and so it can represent an asset that people can play as an alternative,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">From a Critic to a Proponent</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlike his current view on the crypto industry, Fink was nowhere near that supportive of it in the past, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2017/10/13/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-calls-bitcoin-an-index-of-money-laundering.html#close" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">calling</a> </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin an &#8220;index of money laundering&#8221; in 2017:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Bitcoin just shows you how much demand for money laundering there is in the world. That&#8217;s all it is.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He opined in 2020 that the development of the digital asset sector could undermine the dominance of the US dollar as the world&#8217;s reserve currency. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fink softened his stance last year, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-crypto-sceptic-larry-fink-says-blackrock-is-studying-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that BlackRock has started &#8220;studying digital currencies, stablecoins, and the underlying technologies to understand how they can help us serve our clients.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In his most recent interview for Fox Business, he explained that his initial backlash toward the industry was because &#8220;it was heavily used for, let&#8217;s say, illicit activities.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-btc-etf-filing-could-democratize-crypto-ceo-larry-fink-says/" rel="nofollow">BlackRock&#8217;s BTC ETF Filing Could &#8216;Democratize Crypto,&#8217; CEO Larry Fink Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX to Launch Signal Trading Platform, Empowering Traders with High-Quality Signals and Seamless Execution</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258961</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230703-115735_1200x633_1_1200x720_1688611728ANEleS4OOr.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/20230703-115735_1200x633_1_1200x720_1688611728ANEleS4OOr.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, July 6th, 2023] OKX&#8217;s Signal Trading is a trading bot and marketplace that bridges the gap between signal providers and traders Signal Trading will be integrated with TradingView, enabling signal providers and traders to create signals directly on the leading charting platform A pre-launch waitlist is available now for signal [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, July 6th, 2023]</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>OKX&#8217;s Signal Trading is a trading bot and marketplace that bridges the gap between signal providers and traders</li>
<li>Signal Trading will be integrated with TradingView, enabling signal providers and traders to create signals directly on the leading charting platform</li>
<li>A pre-launch <a href="https://www.okx.com/landingpage/signal-trading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">waitlist</a> is available now for signal providers and institutions</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><u>OKX</u></a>, the world&#8217;s second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, has announced the upcoming launch of Signal Trading, a marketplace where users can access automated trading strategies based on technical analysis, or &#8216;signals,&#8217; which indicate whether to buy or sell crypto.</p>
<p>The marketplace, set to launch in August-September 2023, will allow users to choose from a range of signal providers, including institutions and pro traders. Interested users and signal providers can sign up for the <a href="https://www.okx.com/landingpage/signal-trading" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">waitlist</a> to be the first to receive updates and access.</p>
<p>Signal Trading will be integrated with <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">TradingView</a>, enabling signal providers and traders to create signals directly on the charting platform, as well as specify the desired action, instrument, and other parameters associated with that particular trading signal. With Signal Trading, users can access, follow and copy signals without manual execution, saving time and effort.</p>
<p><strong>Advantages for signal providers include:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Expansion opportunities by listing signals on OKX&#8217;s Signal Trading, giving them access to a marketplace of over 50 million traders</li>
<li>Integrated with TradingView, a leading platform for generating signals</li>
<li>In many cases, a significant reduction in latency and costs typically associated with listing signals on third-party platforms</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Advantages for signal traders include:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Avoidance of subscription fees associated with third-party platforms</li>
<li>In many cases, a significant reduction in latency issues that are prevalent on third-party platforms</li>
<li>Trust and reliability of using one of the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchanges</li>
<li>A wide variety of signal providers to choose from and compare</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>OKX Global Chief Commercial Officer Lennix Lai said: </strong>&#8220;OKX Signal Trading will further improve users&#8217; trading experience on OKX by providing access to a diverse range of high-quality signals from top providers, reducing manual entry errors and unlocking a world of trading opportunities for traders. With advanced algorithms, real-time market data and a diverse range of signal providers available, Signal Trading will be the ultimate solution for those seeking to elevate their trading game and connect with a global community of traders.&#8221;</p>
<h2>About OKX</h2>
<p>OKX is the second-largest global crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 ecosystem. Trusted by more than 50 million global users, OKX is known for being the fastest and most reliable crypto trading app for traders everywhere.</p>
<p>As a top partner of English Premier League champions Manchester City FC, McLaren Formula 1, Olympian Scotty James and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo, OKX aims to supercharge the fan experience with new engagement opportunities. OKX is also the top partner of the Tribeca Festival as part of an initiative to bring more creators into web3.</p>
<p>Beyond OKX’s exchange, the OKX Wallet is the platform&#8217;s latest offering for people looking to explore the world of NFTs and the metaverse while trading GameFi and DeFi tokens.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=vkUWbL0o0JBxwWO1mi9Q5RYeTcfwfKctC8EsU6CmARry_6kT3HDi2KFTrNH2xhp7HOp5Y3x79UifjEn3MEa1dw==" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><u>okx.com</u></a></p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p><em>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, hold or offer any services relating to digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition and risk tolerance. OKX does not provide investment or asset recommendations. You are solely responsible for your investment decisions, and OKX is not responsible for any potential losses. Past performance is not indicative of future results. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-to-launch-signal-trading-platform-empowering-traders-with-high-quality-signals-and-seamless-execution/" rel="nofollow">OKX to Launch Signal Trading Platform, Empowering Traders with High-Quality Signals and Seamless Execution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Veloce Media Group Announces Major Investment Commitment of $50M from GEM Digital Limited</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50m-from-gem-digital-limited/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258951</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/04_1688551374RVJ1jwG7Fl.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/04_1688551374RVJ1jwG7Fl.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, July 6th, 2023] Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited Significant investment to fuel Veloce Media Group’s growth  Gem Digital Ltd &#8211; a global leading digital asset investment firm  Following the announcement of Veloce Media Group’s evolution to Web3, with the launch of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, July 6th, 2023]</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Veloce Media Group announces major investment commitment of $50 million from GEM Digital Limited Significant investment to fuel Veloce Media Group’s growth </strong></li>
<li><strong>Gem Digital Ltd &#8211; a global leading digital asset investment firm </strong></li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Following the announcement of Veloce Media Group’s evolution to Web3, with the launch of its new blockchain utility and governance token, <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/about" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">VEXT</a>, it was today announced that GEM Digital Ltd will invest up to $50 million through a structured token subscription agreement into the organization.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/f89kZB5qIBw?showinfo=0"></iframe></div></p>
<p>Veloce, comprising of industry-leading gaming and racing platform Veloce Esports and race-winning Extreme E outfit Veloce Racing, has attracted over 35 million subscribers, nearly one billion monthly views, across multiple digital platforms, including YouTube and Twitch, and millions of social media followers to become the <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/network" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">world’s largest racing gaming media network.</a></p>
<p>The London-based organization also operates esports and gaming teams and brands for some of the industry’s most influential names, including Mercedes AMG, Ferrari, McLaren, Yas Heat, whilst also establishing a successful joint venture sub-brand with Lando Norris – <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/brands" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Quadrant</a> – and continually competing and winning with Veloce Elites.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The introduction of <a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/vext" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">VEXT</a> in the coming weeks will position Veloce as a leading decentralised gaming and sports media organization, providing token holders with real utility through a variety of games integrating VEXT and tangible influence, benefits, and rewards across all of the Veloce Media Group assets.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1019520927-LAT-20230310-XP2301_084916XE_SAUDI23_CL_16885512239MXS4FBYG3.jpg" /></p>
<p>The partnership with GEM Digital has all the signs of being a perfect ‘meeting of minds’ as the investment firm moves to increase its stake in this fast-moving world of sourcing, structuring, and investing in utility tokens in relevant and growing industries.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This is a very exciting transaction ,” <strong>said Daniel Bailey, Chief Commercial Officer Veloce and CEO Veloce Racing</strong>, “It comes very soon after the announcement of VEXT and our plans to evolve our media and sports group into this truly innovative space; validating Veloce’s position as a pioneer in the industry.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>“The GEM commitment will allow us to focus on growth and expansion, through acquisition of more gaming and real-life racing properties, ultimately giving our vast community further VEXT utility and influence.”</p></blockquote>
<p>For GEM Digital, the investment has found a natural home that reflects its ambitions to work with a diverse set of organizations whilst promoting businesses in emerging markets, supporting sustainable and inclusive ambitions through business. The investment promises to herald mutual long-term opportunities.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Garage_Render_F1-min_1688551590uBDaQ64pvp.jpg" /></p>
<h2>About Veloce Media Group</h2>
<p>Founded in 2018, Veloce is a multi-pillared gaming and sports media group operating across some of the most innovative, fast-growing, and future-focused sectors in the UK.</p>
<p>Headquartered in London, the Veloce brand comprises the industry-leading gaming and racing platform Veloce Esports and race-winning outfit Veloce Racing, currently competing in the renowned Extreme E championship.</p>
<p>As the world’s largest digital racing media network, Veloce has so far attracted over 35 million subscribers and nearly one billion monthly views with a focus on esports, gaming, purpose-driven motorsport, and Web3.</p>
<p>Veloce is partnered with a number of high-profile teams from across the globe, running multiple gaming and esports team operations, including Mercedes AMG, Ferrari, and Yas Heat. Well-established JV sub-brands, including Lando Norris’ gaming and lifestyle brand Quadrant, make up another key aspect of Veloce’s vast global network.</p>
<h2>About GEM Digital Limited</h2>
<p>GEM Digital Limited is a digital asset investment firm. Based in The Bahamas, the firm actively sources, structures, and invests in utility tokens listed on over 30 CEXs and DEXs globally.</p>
<p>Global Emerging Markets (&#8220;GEM&#8221;) is a $3.4 billion alternative investment group with offices in Paris, New York, and Bahamas. GEM manages a diverse set of investment vehicles focused on emerging markets and has completed over 530 transactions in 72 countries. Each investment vehicle has a different degree of operational control, risk-adjusted return, and liquidity profile. The family of funds and investment vehicles provide GEM and its partners with exposure to: Small-Mid Cap Management Buyouts, Private Investments in Public Equities and select venture investments.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.velocemediagroup.com/sign-up" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/VEXT_SignUP_4x_1688552352gpwr9Zbzh8.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/veloce-media-group-announces-major-investment-commitment-of-50m-from-gem-digital-limited/" rel="nofollow">Veloce Media Group Announces Major Investment Commitment of $50M from GEM Digital Limited</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Jumps 8% Daily, Bitcoin Challenges $31K Again (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-jumps-8-daily-bitcoin-challenges-31k-again-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258940</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH_BTC_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH_BTC_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[XEC has surged the most from the top 100 digital assets, by adding 18% in a day. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After dipping to just over $30,000, bitcoin has reacted well and has spiked toward the coveted $31,000 line once more.</p>
<p>Most larger-cap altcoins are slightly in the red on a daily scale, aside from SOL and BCH, both of which have neared round-numbered milestones as well.</p>
<h2>BTC to Challenge $31K Again</h2>
<p>Last Friday turned out to be a highly unfavorable day for the BTC bulls as the asset slumped by $1,500 in minutes after the SEC issued a warning against the most recent filings for a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>However, the cryptocurrency reacted well and recovered almost all losses by the time Saturday arrived. As it happens frequently during the weekends, this one was relatively calm, with BTC standing mostly at around $30,500.</p>
<p>Monday didn&#8217;t bring any more price fluctuations either, but the landscape <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-taps-31k-on-blackrocks-etf-refiling-aptos-jumps-10-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">changed</a> on early Tuesday when BTC pushed to $31,400. However, it failed there, and the subsequent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/comp-mkr-aave-soar-triple-digits-weekly-btc-loses-31k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">rejection</a> drove it south to $30,200 on Wednesday.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the bulls seem to be back in charge now as they stopped bitcoin&#8217;s freefall and initiated another leg-up that has helped it touch $31,000 as of now.</p>
<p>As such, the asset&#8217;s market cap has reclaimed $600 billion once again, and its dominance over the alts has taken a breather and is close to 50%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258941" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258941" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-258941" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-5-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258941" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>BCH on a Roll</h2>
<p>While BTC is trying its hand at taking down $31,000, several of the larger-cap alts are sitting quietly, mostly in the red. These include Ethereum, Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Dogecoin, Litecoin, Polkadot, Polygon, and Shiba Inu, as all of them are down by up to 2% in a day.</p>
<p>Solana, on the other hand, has jumped by 3% and has neared $20. Bitcoin Cash has soared by 8% and sits close to $300. Recall that BCH <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-explodes-33-to-14-month-high-solana-and-litecoin-soar-15-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">tapped</a> a 14-month high last week at over $320.</p>
<p>eCash has also been on a roll lately, having surged 18% in a day and over 60% in the past week.</p>
<p>In total, the crypto market cap has added just over $10 billion in a day and has gone back above $1.210 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258942" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258942" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-258942" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="843" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3-1024x459.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3-768x345.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3-1536x689.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-3-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258942" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-jumps-8-daily-bitcoin-challenges-31k-again-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Cash Jumps 8% Daily, Bitcoin Challenges $31K Again (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Options Contracts Open Interest Surges Following ETF Filings</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-options-contracts-open-interest-surges-following-etf-filings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258904</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Institutional investors are showing much more interest in Bitcoin derivatives and options contracts since BlackRock and several other firms filed for exchange-traded funds.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Professional traders are flocking back to Bitcoin funds in the wake of multiple applications for exchange-traded funds by leading asset managers.</p>
<p>As a result, open interest (OI) for options contracts has soared to $13.8 billion, according to blockchain analytics firm Glassnode.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the increase in demand for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-posts-2-consecutive-green-quarters-for-the-first-time-since-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a> options has pushed OI close to its all-time high of $15.1 billion, the firm added before commenting:</p>
<blockquote><p>“This suggests market investors are increasing their exposure to risk-defined derivative instruments.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> Options Contracts have experienced an increase in demand as Open Interest recently soared to a value of $13.8B, just $1.3B shy of the ATH of $15.1B.</p>
<p>This suggests market investors are increasing their exposure to risk-defined derivative instruments. <a href="https://t.co/vZyQQJtVvw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/vZyQQJtVvw</a></p>
<p>— glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1676528202905268225?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Options Demand Surges</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/for-the-first-time-bitcoin-options-open-interest-higher-than-futures-what-does-it-mean/" data-wpel-link="internal">Open interest</a> refers to the total number of outstanding derivative contracts that have not been settled. For each buyer of a futures or options contract, there must be a seller.</p>
<p>Options are similar to futures but do not have a fixed settlement date and have the ‘option’ to be renewed or extended.</p>
<p><a href="https://metrics.deribit.com/options/BTC" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Deribit, around $116 million in Bitcoin options are set to expire on July 6. However, this is a very small amount of options contracts compared to previous expiries. Around $1.7 billion options contracts are set to expire on July 28, which may have a bigger impact on markets.</p>
<p>It also noted that the put/call ratio for these contracts was 0.81. This means that there are slightly more calls than puts which is neutral but leaning to bullish.</p>
<p>The ratio is calculated by dividing the number of put (short) contracts by the number of call (long) contracts. Values lower than 1 are often considered bullish as more speculators are trading in long options contracts.</p>
<p>Bitcoin futures trading has also seen an uptick last month. According to data provided to the U.S. Commodities Futures Trading Commission, the number of traders maintaining futures position of at least 25 BTC increased from a recent low of 94 at the end of May to 121 by the last week of June.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Bitcoin derivatives may be in high demand, but spot markets are continuing to decline from their recent rally. Total capitalization is down 1.2% on the day to $1.23 trillion at the time of writing.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC</a> has dropped 1.1% over the past 24 hours in a fall to $30,516 as it struggles to break heavy resistance. Meanwhile, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">ETH</a> has retreated a similar percentage to trade at $1,914 at the time of writing, according to CoinGecko.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-options-contracts-open-interest-surges-following-etf-filings/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Options Contracts Open Interest Surges Following ETF Filings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius and Former CEO Alex Mashinsky Violated US Law, Says CFTC Spokesman</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-and-former-ceo-alex-mashinsky-violated-us-law-says-cftc-spokesman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258912</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/celsius_legal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/celsius_legal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The investigation launched by the CFTC in the wake of Celsius’ collapse has concluded, and a lawsuit may be in the wings.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three days after Celsius imploded on the 13th of July 2022, the CFTC, swiftly followed by the SEC, launched separate investigations into the crypto platform’s business practices.</p>
<p>The company was also investigated – and in some cases sued – separately by local <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-engaged-in-an-unregistered-securities-offering-alleged-vermonts-financial-regulator/" data-wpel-link="internal">authorities</a> in Vermont, New York, and elsewhere.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I&#8217;m suing the former CEO of cryptocurrency platform <a href="https://twitter.com/CelsiusNetwork?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@CelsiusNetwork</a> for defrauding investors out of billions of dollars.</p>
<p>Alex Mashinsky lied to people about the risks of investing in Celsius, hid its deteriorating financial condition, and failed to register in New York.</p>
<p>— NY AG James (@NewYorkStateAG) <a href="https://twitter.com/NewYorkStateAG/status/1611023481285578752?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Charges brought against Celsius by the CFTC, however, would likely be federal.</p>
<h2>Celsius Misled Investors, Says Confidential CFTC Source</h2>
<p>The CFTC’s investigation has now concluded, and individuals within the organization have said that both Alex Mashinsky and his platform misled investors and ignored existing regulations, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-05/cftc-probe-concludes-crypto-lender-celsius-ex-ceo-mashinsky-broke-rules" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to Bloomberg.</p>
<p>These allegations are aligned with those posited by NYAG Letitia James, who accused Mashinsky of deliberately making false claims regarding his firm’s financial situation to woo investors.</p>
<blockquote><p>“As the former CEO of Celsius, Alex Mashinsky promised to lead investors to financial freedom but led them down a path of financial ruin. The law is clear that making false and unsubstantiated promises and misleading investors is illegal. […] My office will stay vigilant and ensure that bad actors trying to take advantage of New York investors are held accountable.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In turn, Mashinsky retorted that the New York Attorney General “fundamentally misunderstood” both Celsius’ business model and the role he played as CEO.</p>
<p>However, the organization itself has so far refused to officially comment on the matter. The sources from within the organization also refrained from specifying which regulations Celsius and Mashinsky broke specifically, outside of failing to register with the relevant authorities.</p>
<h2>Lawsuit Possible by the End of July</h2>
<p>Now that the investigation has concluded, the CFTC will reportedly host an internal vote on what to do with the information they’ve uncovered.</p>
<p>If a majority of CFTC commissioners agree with the interpretation of the research teams’ findings, a federal lawsuit may be filed against Celsius and, very likely, against Mashinsky himself. According to the confidential source, the gavel may drop no later than the end of July, assuming nobody decides to play devil’s advocate within the Commission.</p>
<p>Should the case be brought before a federal court, it would be the latest in a series of over 85 cases filed by the CFTC concerning digital assets. So far, the agency has been the reason for over $4 billion in penalties and restitutions sourced from fraudulent crypto markets, said CFTC director Rostin Benham.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-and-former-ceo-alex-mashinsky-violated-us-law-says-cftc-spokesman/" rel="nofollow">Celsius and Former CEO Alex Mashinsky Violated US Law, Says CFTC Spokesman</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aave Token Holders Vote on Proposal Seeking Conversion of 1.6K ETH From Protocol&#8217;s Treasury</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/aave-token-holders-vote-on-proposal-seeking-conversion-of-1-6k-eth-from-protocols-treasury/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258739</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/aave_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/aave_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A majority of Aave token holders have voed in favor of the governance proposal.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new Aave proposal took place to decide the fate of $3 million in the protocol&#8217;s treasury.</p>
<p>The holders of the Aave tokens will be voting on a governance proposal on whether 1,600 Ether, worth around $3 million, in the DeFi protocol treasury will be converted to wrapped staked ether (wstETH) and rocket pool ether (rETH).</p>
<ul>
<li>The <a href="https://app.aave.com/governance/proposal/?proposalId=261" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">proposal</a>, created on July 3rd, has received 252,152 affirmative votes out of a required 320,000 at the time of publication. Aave token holders have until July 7th to vote.</li>
<li>For the uninitiated, wrapped Staked Ether (WETH) and Rocket Pool Ether (rETH) are examples of staking derivatives that enable market participants to earn staking rewards.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Aave DAO currently holds 1,786.51 awETH (v2) and 104.548 units of ETH in the Collector Contract. The awETH deposit yield in Aave v2 earns 1.69%, relative to 3.8% with wstETH and 3.13% with rETH. This AIP converts all the unproductive ETH balance, along with aWETH (v2 and v3) into the same amounts of wstETH and rETH.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Aave&#8217;s native token, AAVE, has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aave-explodes-25-daily-eth-pushes-above-1-9k-market-watch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">recovered</a> significantly alongside the broader digital assets market over the past three weeks.</li>
<li>It was up by more than 22% over the past week alone and was currently trading at $74.95.</li>
<li>According to the latest <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/aave?tvl=true" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> compiled by DefiLlama, Aave&#8217;s TVL increased by nearly 60% from $3.74 billion in January to the press time value of $5.98 billion.</li>
<li>While the recovery has been notable, Aave&#8217;a TVL was down by nearly 70% from its ATH of nearly $20 billion in October 2021.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aave-token-holders-vote-on-proposal-seeking-conversion-of-1-6k-eth-from-protocols-treasury/" rel="nofollow">Aave Token Holders Vote on Proposal Seeking Conversion of 1.6K ETH From Protocol&#8217;s Treasury</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchanges in South Africa Must be Licensed By November 30, Says Regulator: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchanges-in-south-africa-must-be-licensed-by-november-30-says-regulator-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 23:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Africa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258631</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Africa.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Africa.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto exchanges in South Africa could face enforcement action they fail to obtain a license with the country's financial regulator by the end of the year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">South Africa&#8217;s financial regulator has asked exchanges operating in the country to obtain a license before the end of 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto firms who fail to adhere to the directive before the deadline could be fined or have their businesses closed down by authorities.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">New Licensing Regime in South Africa</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Financial Sector Conduct Authority (FSCA) has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-04/south-africa-to-require-crypto-exchanges-licensing-by-year-end?utm_medium=social&amp;utm_content=crypto&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic&amp;utm_source=twitter" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">required</a> crypto exchanges in South Africa to secure a license before the November 30 deadline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to FSCA Commissioner Unathi Kamlana, about 20 firms have applied since the watchdog first opened the licensing process a few weeks ago, while expecting more companies to file an application before the deadline.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In October 2022, the FSCA <a href="https://www.fsca.co.za/Regulatory%20Frameworks/Temp/Policy%20Document%20supporting%20the%20Declaration%20of%20crypto%20assets%20as%20a%20financial%20product.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">declared</a> crypto a financial product after a declaration proposal in November 2022 and a consultation on the draft regulation. Also, the publication of the final declaration mentioned that crypto exchanges in South Africa must be licensed by the end of 2023. Defaulters could be fined 10 million rands ($536,387), face 10 years in prison, or suffer both consequences.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the FSCA proposed a four-month window for crypto businesses to submit their license applications, some commentators believed the time frame was insufficient, with some comments suggesting six months and another two years. The financial watchdog, in response, extended the license application period to six months in the final declaration, stating that it was not necessary and unjustified.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">South Africa&#8217;s High-Profile Crypto Scams</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The South African regulator, meanwhile, maintains that the crypto asset industry is risky, with Kamlana stating that &#8220;it is an area where you can lose quite a bit of money, so you must think twice before exposing yourself to it.&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The African country, which has seen an increased interest in the asset class, has also experienced some high-profile cryptocurrency scams causing investors losses worth billions of dollars. In June 2021, the founders of South African crypto investment platform Africrypt, the Cajee brothers, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-major-crypto-scam-in-south-africa-two-brothers-and-69000-btc-have-vanished-together/" data-wpel-link="internal">allegedly made away</a> with nearly 70,000 BTC (worth over $2 billion).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, Johannes Steynberg, CEO of the international multi-level marketing scheme Mirror Trading International (MTI), reportedly disappeared with 29,000 bitcoin in customer funds. Following his <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/man-behind-29000-bitcoin-ponzi-scam-is-arrested-in-brazil/" data-wpel-link="internal">arrest</a> in Brazil, a US court recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-african-ceo-ordered-to-pay-a-record-3-4-billion-penalty-in-cftc-bitcoin-fraud-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> Steynberg to pay a penalty worth $3.4 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Kamlana further said the FSCA introduced consumer protection measures which include awareness about crypto products and financial education.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the FSCA Commissioner:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;There is potentially serious harm to financial customers when using crypto products, and therefore it makes sense for us to introduce the regulatory framework. Time will tell the effectiveness of our measures, and we will continue to work together with the industry to refine and make changes where and if necessary.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchanges-in-south-africa-must-be-licensed-by-november-30-says-regulator-report/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Exchanges in South Africa Must be Licensed By November 30, Says Regulator: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canadian Teens Busted for Stealing $4M in BTC and ETH Pretenting to Be Coinbase Support: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-teens-busted-for-stealing-4m-in-btc-and-eth-pretenting-to-be-coinbase-support-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258771</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The teens deceived the victim by pretending to be Coinbase's support team. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two teenage boys from Hamilton, Ontario, have been busted for allegedly stealing over $4 million worth of bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH) from an American man through what authorities described as a &#8220;spear phishing attack.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/hamilton/crypto-teens-charged-1.6896349" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">local reports</a>, Hamilton police started working with the United States Federal Bureau of Investigations (FBI) and the Secret Service Electronic Crimes Task Force to investigate the boys in June 2023.</p>
<h2>A Spear Phishing Attack</h2>
<p>Const. Krista-Lee Ernst of the Hamilton police noted that the boys, both 17 years old, used a spear phishing attack to deceive their victim into giving them $4.2 million in crypto.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-giveaway-twitter-scam-caused-by-a-phone-spear-phishing-attack/" data-wpel-link="internal">A spear phishing attack</a> is a targeted form of phishing used by scammers to trick individuals into revealing sensitive information such as passwords, credit card numbers, or other personal data. Unlike traditional phishing attacks that cast a wide net, spear phishing attacks are highly personalized and tailored to specific individuals or organizations.</p>
<p>In a spear phishing attack, the bad actor conducts thorough research to gather information about the target, such as their name, position, company, colleagues, or even personal details from social media platforms. With such information, the scammer can craft compelling and customized emails or messages that appear to be from a trusted source, such as a colleague, supervisor, or a reputable organization the target is associated with.</p>
<p>In the case of the Hamilton teens, the duo, known by their fake aliases &#8220;Felon&#8221; and &#8220;Gaze,&#8221; pretended to be members of the support team of the popular American crypto exchange Coinbase. They aimed to take over the man&#8217;s crypto account on the exchange.</p>
<h2>Over $13 Million Seized</h2>
<p>After successfully gaining control of the account, the boys were able to access the man&#8217;s digital assets stored on the platform.</p>
<p>According to the police, the teens spent some of the funds to purchase the Instagram username &#8220;@zombie,&#8221; a rare username in the gaming community. Police also seized at least $13.4 million worth of digital assets after they were caught.</p>
<p>Although authorities initially arrested both teens, only one was charged with theft of over $5,000 and possession of property or proceeds acquired through criminal means, while the other was released.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-teens-busted-for-stealing-4m-in-btc-and-eth-pretenting-to-be-coinbase-support-report/" rel="nofollow">Canadian Teens Busted for Stealing $4M in BTC and ETH Pretenting to Be Coinbase Support: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
