<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:52:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Amazon&#8217;s New Venture: A Digital Assets Company for NFTs and Crypto Games, Sources Say</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-new-venture-digital-assets-company-nfts-crypto-games-sources-say/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235096</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/amazon1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/amazon1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Sources said that Amazon's upcoming digital assets company and NFT marketplace could be set to launch this spring.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amazon is reportedly working on a digital assets company that will power an NFT marketplace this spring.</p>
<p>According to sources interviewed by the media outlet Blockworks, the retail giant has been buying digital collectibles companies from various players in the crypto ecosystem to power its new venture.</p>
<p>So far, Amazon has invested in layer-1 blockchains and crypto gaming companies and has hired developers from NFT companies and cryptocurrency exchanges for its own <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-job-post-digital-currency-blockchain-unit/" data-wpel-link="internal">blockchain unit</a>.</p>
<h2>Amazon Bets On Crypto Gaming Industry</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://blockworks.co/news/amazon-nft-marketplace-web3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">one source</a>, Amazon is preparing to launch a series of crypto games that would allow its customers to claim free NFTs. This move would be significant for the crypto gaming industry, which has seen a decline in players due to the multiple project scams that hit the market in late 2021. However, Amazon doesn&#8217;t seem concerned about that data, as the company witnessed the best of times for crypto gaming when many of those projects were forced to expand the storage services offered by Amazon Web Services due to the enormous player demand.</p>
<p>The entry of a giant like Amazon is significant for the crypto ecosystem, as it will surely attract many players just waiting for the right moment to return to the crypto gaming industry. Sources seemed to be quite positive about the positive outcome of Amazon&#8217;s entry into the Web3 space:</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We knew it was possible, [&#8230;] But now it seems like it’s really happening. That’s going to affect the existing players in the space — if they execute and do this right and are smart about it.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Amazon Could Become The Biggest Thing In The NFT Industry</h2>
<p>Several sources said that Amazon will be running the new NFT platform, rather than by subsidiaries, to have complete control of a platform that could become the largest in the NFT industry. It is currently unknown whether Amazon&#8217;s new platform will seek to compete directly against the big NFT marketplaces like OpenSea, Rarible, or the latest Samsung NFT Platform or whether it will be more focused on crypto gaming—especially considering that Amazon owns Twitch.</p>
<p>With the vast number of Amazon users, its entry into the crypto ecosystem will not go unnoticed. It will attract many investors who know the potential of an industry that is growing and has a lot of room for improvement and growth inside the broader gaming industry —the <a href="https://www.thedrum.com/opinion/2022/05/16/gaming-s-singularity-how-games-media-taking-over-the-world#:~:text=Gaming%20is%20now%20the%20largest,2021%20%E2%80%93%20that&#039;s%20bigger%20than%20Hollywood." target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">largest business</a> in the entertainment sector.</p>
<p>As reported by Cryptopotato, In April 2022, Amazon CEO Andy Jassy said the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-could-sell-nfts-in-the-future-claims-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">was open to selling non-fungible tokens</a> (NFTs) &#8220;in the distant future,&#8221; but that they were not planning to accept cryptocurrency payments. However, on January 11th, Ava Labs announced a partnership with Amazon to increase the adoption of blockchain technology in businesses, institutions, and at the government level by managing Avalanche&#8217;s decentralized infrastructure and applications through Amazon Web Services (AWS).</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We’re joining forces with <a href="https://twitter.com/amazon?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Amazon</a> to help enterprises and governments build compliant blockchain solutions. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AWS?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#AWS</a> makes it easier to launch and manage <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Avalanche?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Avalanche</a> nodes, giving the network more strength and flexibility for developers.<a href="https://t.co/vgabB5c6Ya" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/vgabB5c6Ya</a></p>
<p>— Ava Labs <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f53a.png" alt="🔺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@avalabsofficial) <a href="https://twitter.com/avalabsofficial/status/1613252634802294785?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Although the company still refuses to accept payments in cryptocurrencies, for now, it is gradually opening its doors to the crypto ecosystem. So who knows, we might see Amazon as a crypto-friendly company in a couple of years.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-new-venture-digital-assets-company-nfts-crypto-games-sources-say/" rel="nofollow">Amazon&#8217;s New Venture: A Digital Assets Company for NFTs and Crypto Games, Sources Say</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deribit Eyes Dubai Amidst Global Expansion Plans: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/deribit-eyes-dubai-amidst-global-expansion-plans-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deribit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234944</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Deribit_Dubai.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Deribit_Dubai.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto options exchange is also looking to obtain broker licenses in UK, Brazil, and Singapore. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Deribit is planning to move its main headquarters to Dubai as soon as the third quarter of this year. The Bloomberg report suggests that the new office will be staffed by a team of 10 people comprising both domestic hires alongside the exchange&#8217;s core employees.</p>
<p>Roles in management, compliance, and support will be housed in the Dubai office.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitcoin-options-exchange-deribit-looks-to-relocate-to-dubai-1.1874911" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Deribit Chief Legal, Compliance, and Regulatory Officer David Dohmen, some employees will continue to be based in Panama.</li>
<li>Dohmen was quoted saying that the regulatory regime in Dubai is more tailored to crypto than other jurisdictions.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’ve had a number of clients who basically intimated to us that they would like to trade on a crypto exchange that’s actually regulated. In Panama, we are not regulated. Also, we also saw where the regulatory winds were blowing, and there was a drive toward regulation across the globe.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The exec also said Deribit seeks to submit an application and supporting documents for a Full Market Product license to Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority once it receives regulatory clarity from the agency.</li>
<li>Deribit has operations in Amsterdam as well, while its Netherlands-based parent company and related subsidiaries currently have 95 employees across the world.</li>
<li>The news comes after the United Arab Emirates (UAE) <a href="https://www.arabianbusiness.com/industries/technology/uaes-new-law-for-virtual-assets-sector-to-trigger-mass-entry-of-global-companies" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">introduced</a> a new regulation that governs digital assets, a move that established the country&#8217;s initial regulatory regime for the cryptocurrency space at the federal level.</li>
<li>Dubai also established its own crypto regulator &#8211; the Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA) &#8211; which the industry insiders believe would act as a major catalyst for both global and regional Web3 companies to enter or expand their operations in the next few months.</li>
<li>The city has become home to multiple crypto exchanges, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-secures-another-crypto-license-in-dubai/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance</a>, Crypto.com, OKX, and others.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/deribit-eyes-dubai-amidst-global-expansion-plans-report/" rel="nofollow">Deribit Eyes Dubai Amidst Global Expansion Plans: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Roger Ver Breaks Silence on Genesis Lawsuit, Claims He Has Sufficient Funds to Pay</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/roger-ver-breaks-silence-on-genesis-lawsuit-claims-he-has-sufficient-funds-to-pay/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 23:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roger Ver]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234954</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/roger_ver-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/roger_ver-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ver slammed the crypto broker and said that it "can’t ask its clients to play a 'Heads clients lose, tails Genesis wins' game."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Early Bitcoin adopter and executive chair of Bitcoin.com, Roger Ver, said he has &#8220;sufficient funds&#8221; to pay Genesis Global after being hit by a lawsuit by the now-bankrupt crypto broker&#8217;s unit &#8211; GGC International.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin Cash proponent noted that he is happy to pay the amount he owes but pointed out that the agreement requires Genesis to remain solvent. In a new Reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/btc/comments/10ki2ll/did_roger_ver_get_rekt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a>, Ver claimed that Genesis failed to provide him assurances about its finances.</p>
<p>The Digital Currency Group broker and lending desk slid into bankruptcy after weeks of fresh fundraising attempts. The court documents reveal that it has over $150 million to fund its restructuring efforts.</p>
<p>Ver allegedly owes around $21 million to Genesis.</p>
<h2>Genesis Vs. Roger Ver</h2>
<p>Ver, who was once known as &#8220;Bitcoin Jesus,&#8221; claimed that the financial information provided by Genesis has been called into question by recent events. He even said that the crypto broker refused to clarify the information it had provided him and instead chose to file suit.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin evangelist accused Genesis of causing &#8220;discrepancies between the valuation of customer collateral and their own digital assets.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Genesis can’t ask its clients to play a “heads clients lose, tails Genesis wins” game. It appears that at points since at least last June Genesis dipped under the solvency line.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>GCC filed the suit against Ver in the New York State Supreme Court earlier this week, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-sues-roger-ver-for-20-million-for-failing-to-settle-crypto-options/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">accusing</a> the blockchain-industry veteran of failing to settle crypto options transactions that expired back on December 30. A total of 20 days was given to Ver to answer the summons, a failure of which will require him to pay the total amount by default.</p>
<h2>Spat With CoinFLEX</h2>
<p>This isn&#8217;t the first time Ver has been embroiled in a controversy surrounding the failure of payment. He made headlines last summer for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/roger-vers-debt-part-of-the-reason-for-coinflexs-collapse-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">allegations</a> of defaulting on a debt. The company&#8217;s CEO, Mark Lamb, claimed that Ver owes the firm $47 million in USDC stablecoin and was bound by a written contract and added that he had been issued a default notice for the same.</p>
<p>Ver, on the other hand, vehemently refuted the allegations and instead claimed that the company owed him money.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/roger-ver-breaks-silence-on-genesis-lawsuit-claims-he-has-sufficient-funds-to-pay/" rel="nofollow">Roger Ver Breaks Silence on Genesis Lawsuit, Claims He Has Sufficient Funds to Pay</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Bitcoin Mining Facility Slapped With $10,000 Per Day Fine</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-bitcoin-mining-facility-slapped-with-10000-per-day-fine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235074</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_mining_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_mining_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[US Bitcoin could be forced to pay a $540,000 fine if it doesn’t shut down its operations before the end of January. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">US Bitcoin Corp – a North American Bitcoin mining firm – has been ordered to cease operations by a State Supreme Court Justice, or face penalties of $10,000 per day. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">If the miner continues to operate through the end of January, the fine will increase to $25,000 per day. </span></p>
<p><b>US Bitcoin Under Fire</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://www.lockportjournal.com/news/local_news/judges-finds-bitcoin-facility-in-falls-is-operating-in-violation-of-court-order-sets-fine/article_1170797d-9994-5836-9289-8f3bca1d51a1.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Lockport Journal on Thursday, the order from Justice Edward Pace is a follow-up to Supreme Court Justice Frank Sedita III’s temporary restraining order issued against the firm on December 1. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The latter justice sought to stop the firm from operating as the Falls sought a preliminary injunction to force the company’s facility to comply with zoning laws governing energy-intensive industries. The city charged the mining facility, based on Buffalo avenue, with violating these laws, and creating “a public nuisance.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Pace, the $10,000 fine will be in place until January 31. Speaking to John P. Bartolomei, an attorney for US Bitcoin, she added that the fine will increase to $25,000 per day after that deadline until the case is fully settled. Bartolomei protested this ruling and said he would appeal the decision to the State Supreme Court Appellate Division Fourth Department.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“If by January 31, (the cryptocurrency mining operation) has not shut down, then a check should be delivered to the city of Niagara Falls on February 1 for $540,000,” Pace said. The $540,000 in payments accounts for a $10,000 penalty every day from December 9 until January 31.</span></p>
<h2>New York’s Mining Crackdown</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Despite its historical popularity as a geography for Bitcoin mining, regulation against the industry in New York state hasn’t been the most welcoming. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In November, state governor Kathy Hochul </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-becomes-first-us-state-to-restrict-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">signed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a moratorium ending the use of fossil fuels to mine Bitcoin in the region. The measure was taken primarily to meet the state’s economic development and climate goals. Per the company’s </span><a href="https://usbitcoin.com/our-campuses/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, US Bitcoin’s Niagra Falls facility is 90% powered by zero-emissions electricity – but even hasn’t satisfied the lawyers at the Falls. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">New York City mayor Eric Adams, a crypto bull, has previously said he is opposed to Bitcoin mining. However, he later </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nyc-mayor-adams-will-urge-gov-hochul-to-veto-anti-bitcoin-mining-bill-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">promised</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to urge governor Hochul to veto the bill banning fossil-fuel-based mining activity, out of concern for the industry’s future growth. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-bitcoin-mining-facility-slapped-with-10000-per-day-fine/" rel="nofollow">New York Bitcoin Mining Facility Slapped With $10,000 Per Day Fine</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mango Markets Sues Exploiter Avraham Eisenberg for $47M in Damages</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mango-markets-sues-exploiter-avraham-eisenberg-for-47m-in-damages/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 21:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234990</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Eisenberg is also in legal battles with several US federal and regulatory agencies.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mango Markets&#8217; exploiter Avraham Eisenberg was hit with a lawsuit by Mango Labs, the company behind the DeFi protocol, for $47 million in damages.</p>
<p>The Wednesday <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66760250/1/mango-labs-llc-v-eisenberg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> with the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York alleges that Eisenberg executed a malicious attack on Mango Markets by manipulating the native token, MNGO, through &#8220;fraud, deception,&#8221; and converted nearly $114 million from the depositors of the protocol into his own accounts.</p>
<h2>Eisenberg in Trouble</h2>
<p>A Mango Markets&#8217; related decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) and Eisenberg entered into an agreement that enabled the exploiter to keep $47 million from the exploit while protecting him against any potential criminal investigation. While he returned $67 million and retained the rest, Mango Labs now wants the remaining funds in damages in addition to interest starting from the time of the exploit in October last year.</p>
<p>The filing read,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;He forced Mango DAO to enter into an unenforceable settlement agreement—under duress—purporting to release depositors’ claims against him and precluding them from pursuing a criminal investigation. Following the Mango DAO vote regarding Defendant’s ultimatum, he returned approximately $67 million of the money he unlawfully recovered.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The protocol&#8217;s developer also called Eisenberg to be a &#8220;notorious cryptocurrency market manipulator&#8221; and accused him of having a history of attacking multiple platforms as well as manipulating digital asset markets.</p>
<p>Mango Labs also highlighted that the exploiter was involved in allegedly abusing a DeFi project called Fortress DAO&#8217;s treasury redemption mechanism as well as embezzling $14 million from it where he was serving as its developer.</p>
<h2>Pressure From SEC and CFTC</h2>
<p>Eisenberg, who happens to be a software coder and crypto trader, outed himself after carrying out a self-funded economic attack by manipulating the oracle price of MNGO. The attack drained around $117 million from Mango Markets&#8217; treasury. He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mango-markets-exploiter-says-profitable-traders-like-him-attract-jealousy-and-hate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">described</a> the incident previously as &#8220;legal open market actions,&#8221; but the regulatory agencies are not on board with the stunt.</p>
<p>In December 2022, the US Department of Justice (DOJ) arrested Eisenberg in Puerto Rico for fraud and manipulation. He was denied bail as the judge deemed him to be &#8220;a flight risk.&#8221; The Commodities Future Trading Commission (CFTC) also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-charges-mango-markets-exploiter-with-market-manipulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">charged</a> him with violating the country&#8217;s commodities federal commodities laws. Similar charges were slapped by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI).</p>
<p>More recently, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-13" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">sued</a> Eisenberg for allegedly violating anti-fraud and market manipulation provisions of the securities laws</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mango-markets-sues-exploiter-avraham-eisenberg-for-47m-in-damages/" rel="nofollow">Mango Markets Sues Exploiter Avraham Eisenberg for $47M in Damages</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Infamous &#8216;Blockchain Bandit&#8217; Begins Moving His Stash 6 Years Later</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/infamous-blockchain-bandit-begins-moving-his-stash-6-years-later/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234988</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hacker_steal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hacker_steal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The unidentified hacker emptied multiple Ethereum wallets by guessing their keys years ago.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we’ve seen over the years, blockchains aren’t quite as secure as some pretend they are.</p>
<p>Rather, although the technology is one of the most secure ways of storing data available to the public, poor coding, social engineering, and the like can still allow bad actors to take advantage of unwary victims.</p>
<h2>Guessing Games</h2>
<p>In the case of the “Blockchain Bandit,” however, the tech worked as intended. The unknown attacker managed to steal crypto assets from up to 732 wallets by a process known as ethercombing – essentially educated guesswork.</p>
<p>A private key to an Ethereum wallet is a 78-digit string of random numbers. Theoretically, this should be impossible to guess without quantum computing or other resources that, as far as we know, do not exist yet.</p>
<p>However, the sheer number of strings will eventually allow for a private key to be guessed by having a low value. Statistically, this would be due to an error or an inexperienced user choosing the key himself.</p>
<blockquote><p>“If a private key is chosen at random, then the chances of someone else generating that same key are approximately 1 in 2256, which is, for all practical purposes, a 0% chance. Since a private key of 0x01 has approximately zero percent chance of occurring randomly, we must assume this value was either chosen on purpose or due to an error. “</p></blockquote>
<p>A detailed rundown of the math involved can be found in this academic <a href="https://www.ise.io/casestudies/ethercombing/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">article</a>. To sum it up, the chance of guessing a private key has roughly the same probability as <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/blockchain-bandit-ethereum-weak-private-keys/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">identifying</a> one particular atom in our universe.<br />
That didn’t stop the Blockchain Bandit.</p>
<h2>Methodical Work</h2>
<p>Over the past few years, the unidentified bad actor scoured the blockchain looking for wallets with private keys whose values added up to numbers 1 through 732. By doing this for a couple of years, they had amassed a fortune. Their wallet is currently being emptied of 51k Ether and 470 Bitcoin, now worth around $90 million – a sum smaller than many of the hacks we’ve seen over the course of 2022 but no less impressive.</p>
<p>The news was broken by Chinalysis, who suspect the recent bullish movements of the crypto market gave the attacker the impulse to cash out.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />$90M stolen funds on the move: After 6 years of hodling, the “Blockchain Bandit” has awoken. In this <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> we cover how the Blockchain Bandit amassed this treasure trove and where the funds are currently held.</p>
<p>— Chainalysis (@chainalysis) <a href="https://twitter.com/chainalysis/status/1618282974973427712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 25, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Given the tremendous amount of time needed to pull off such an operation, it is possible that the attacker was indeed a state actor – although an organized crime ring or a regular individual could also be the culprits.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/infamous-blockchain-bandit-begins-moving-his-stash-6-years-later/" rel="nofollow">Infamous &#8216;Blockchain Bandit&#8217; Begins Moving His Stash 6 Years Later</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Creditors List Include Apple, Google, Amazon, WSJ, and Even Australia&#8217;s Govt</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-creditors-list-include-apple-google-amazon-wsj-and-even-australias-govt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234955</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/FTX_Australia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/FTX_Australia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A filing dislosed that 9,693,985 people and companies, including Google, Apple, Amazon, and Meta, were affected by the FTX crash.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent document filed with the United States Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware revealed that FTX&#8217;s creditors consist of over 9.7 million companies and individuals.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some of the most famous entities include the likes of Apple, Amazon, Google, Meta, Netflix, Microsoft, and more.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Who Got Burned?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the darkest moments in crypto&#8217;s recent history &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the collapse of FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8211; triggered massive financial losses for people and organizations. The lawyers of the bankrupt exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DocketInfo" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in a 115-page document that the number of affected investors is 9,693,985.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prominent cryptocurrency-related firms with funds stuck on the platform are Coinbase, Circle, Genesis, BlockFi, Galaxy Digital, Paradigm, and many others. </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcgs-subsidiary-genesis-global-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Genesis</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-files-for-bankruptcy-following-ftx-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BlockFi</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> could not resume their regular course of business after the crash and filed for bankruptcy protection.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tech behemoths, such as Apple, Meta, Samsung, Amazon, and Microsoft, are also part of the nearly 10 million creditors. The attorneys further mentioned some media outlets, including The Wall Street Journal, The New York Times, and CoinDesk.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that even the government entities of the United Arab Emirates (UAE), Australia, Japan, Hong Kong, Guam, and The Virgin Islands are listed as FTX creditors. Central banks like the Bank of Cyprus and the Bank of the Bahamas are affected, too.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from the aforementioned giants, the exchange owes money to a range of other companies. Some interesting names include the largest airline in the world measured by fleet size &#8211; American Airlines, the German banking institution &#8211; Deutsche Bank, the biggest hotel chain &#8211; Marriott International, The Miami Heat Charitable Fund, and many more.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The filing did not disclose the amount owed to each creditor, while an inclusion explained that not every organization had a trading account with FTX.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celebrities who Parted With Their Investment</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato</em> recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-amount-of-ftx-shares-tom-brady-and-gisele-bundchen-will-probably-lose/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the exchange&#8217;s demise harmed many famous people, such as Tom Brady and his ex-spouse Gisele Bundchen.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The NFL athlete owns more than 1.1 million shares of FTX, while the Brazilian fashion model has 686,761 stocks. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert Kraft &#8211; an American billionaire and owner of The New England Patriots &#8211; bought 110,000 Series B Preferred shares of FTX Trading and 479,000 common shares. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kevin O&#8217;Leary is among the most controversial individuals on that list. He served as an ambassador of FTX, for which he received $15 million. He also had a close relationship with the platform&#8217;s former CEO &#8211; Sam Bankman- Fried (SBF) &#8211; and purchased 139,000 Class A Common shares and 12,631 Series A Preferred shares of West Realm Shires (the firm that controls FTX US).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He even </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/FredRadford/status/1590843252437299201" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">declared</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in October last year (a few weeks before the infamous fallout) that FTX is one of the safest places for investors.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-creditors-list-include-apple-google-amazon-wsj-and-even-australias-govt/" rel="nofollow">FTX Creditors List Include Apple, Google, Amazon, WSJ, and Even Australia&#8217;s Govt</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana is Up 6% Daily, Here&#8217;s the Key Resistance (SOL Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/solana-is-up-6-daily-heres-the-key-resistance-sol-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235007</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Solana continues to perform despite a decline in the buying volume, booking a 6% increase in the past 24h. Key Support levels: $20 Key Resistance levels: $27 The resistance at $27 is keeping bulls in check. They have been rejected at that level on Saturday. In the process, SOL has formed an ascending triangle, and [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">Solana continues to perform despite a decline in the buying volume, booking a 6% increase in the past 24h.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $20</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $27</strong></p>
<p>The resistance at $27 is keeping bulls in check. They have been rejected at that level on Saturday. In the process, SOL has formed an ascending triangle, and a major breakout is expected over the coming days. Should bulls fail, then the price can quickly fall to the $20 support.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235029" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235029" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235029" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-34-43-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235029" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume:</strong> The considerable buying volume has allowed Solana to remain on the offensive, but the momentum is fading.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The daily RSI is just under 80 points and is making lower highs. This is bearish.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The daily MACD is still bullish but may do a bearish cross at any moment based on the histogram, which is also making lower highs.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235028" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235028" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235028" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-26_17-35-07-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235028" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for SOL is neutral at this time.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for SOL Price</h2>
<p>There are some clear signs that Solana may not be able to overtake the key resistance at $27. Buyers would really need to step up to achieve that, and the current volume and indicators don&#8217;t show it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-is-up-6-daily-heres-the-key-resistance-sol-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Solana is Up 6% Daily, Here&#8217;s the Key Resistance (SOL Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Reasons Why Aptos Exploded by 400% in 30 Days</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/three-reasons-why-aptos-exploded-by-400-in-30-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos Blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234993</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/aptos_moon_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/aptos_moon_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aptos exploded by over 400% in the past 30 days, becoming one of the market's best performers. Here are three possible reasons why. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aptos is undoubtedly the hottest story of the past month, being amongst the absolute best-performing cryptocurrencies in the past 30 days. APT, its native token, skyrocketed by a mind-blowing 400% during that period.</p>
<p>This put the project at the forefront and also gave way to a renewed layer-1 trade narrative, with other names also popping off.</p>
<p>You can check our complete guide on Aptos in the following video:</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="Aptos (APT) In Depth: Is It Really the Solana Killer?" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Md_99cqkj68" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p>
<p>That said, there are a few reasons which explain the increase in APT&#8217;s price, so let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<h2>The Entire Market Rallied</h2>
<p>Undoubtedly the biggest reason for APT&#8217;s increase is the fact that the entire cryptocurrency market saw tremendously renewed interest since the beginning of 2023.</p>
<p>The total market capitalization is up by about $250 billion in that period, showcasing the renewed investors&#8217; appetite for risk-on assets such as cryptocurrencies.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235000" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235000" style="width: 1294px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235000" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123.jpg" alt="img1_mcap_coingecko_260123" width="1294" height="518" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123.jpg 1294w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123-300x120.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123-1024x410.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123-768x307.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_mcap_congecko_260123-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1294px) 100vw, 1294px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235000" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>The main reason for that, according to many, is that inflation in the US seems to be slowing down. The consumer price index numbers for December were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/enhanced-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-cpi-numbers-clock-in-at-6-5/" data-wpel-link="internal">released</a> earlier this month. They were in line with the expectations, propelling the market even further.</p>
<p>As it&#8217;s almost always the case, when Bitcoin runs, so does the rest of the market, albeit at a different velocity. Some altcoins outperform others, and in this case, APT was the clear winner.</p>
<h2>PancakeSwap and Aptos</h2>
<p>Another reason why the price increased so much is furthering its efforts to build within the Aptos ecosystem.</p>
<p>Just recently, a new proposal called <em>Confirmation Proposal for Aptos Multichain Farm Emission </em>was put forward that, if approved, would cement the team&#8217;s intentions to &#8220;build upon the initial deployment.&#8221;</p>
<p>Per the document itself:</p>
<blockquote><p>PancakeSwap will aim to get further visibility within the Aptos ecosystem to attract additional Aptos-based projects to deploy on PancakeSwap.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap will look to bring more our existing and build on future products to Aptos so that we can attract more projects with a competitive offering.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap will be looking to leverage its strength on BNB Chain to attract Aptos-based projects to BNB Chain and vice-versa, so as to improve CAKE burn.</p></blockquote>
<p>It&#8217;s also worth noting that most of the value locked on Aptos is currently in PancakeSwap, as per <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Aptos" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from DefiLlama.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235008" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235008" style="width: 1398px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235008" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231.jpg" alt="img1_tvl_defillama_2601231" width="1398" height="571" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231.jpg 1398w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231-300x123.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231-1024x418.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231-768x314.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_tvl_defillama_2601231-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1398px) 100vw, 1398px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235008" class="wp-caption-text">Source: DeFiLlama</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Aptos NFT Sales Through the Roof</h2>
<p>The appetite for non-fungible tokens built on Aptos is also through the roof. One of the more popular marketplaces &#8211; Topaz &#8211; displays triple and even quadruple increases in the volumes of multiple NFT collections as of late.</p>
<p>On the other hand, this NFT list compiled by <em>Tracemove </em>also <a href="https://tracemove.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shows</a> the considerable transaction count on a lot of the leading projects built on Aptos.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235013" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235013" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235013" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-scaled.jpg" alt="img_nft_list_aptos_2601231" width="2560" height="409" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-300x48.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-1024x164.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-768x123.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-1536x246.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-2048x327.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img_nft_list_aptos_2601231-50x8.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235013" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Tracemove</figcaption></figure>
<p>It is, however, worth noting that on-chain data is somewhat unclear in terms of justifying the explosive movement of APT&#8217;s price. For instance, the total value locked in the protocol remains relatively little and only increased by 10% during the same period when APT gained 400%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-reasons-why-aptos-exploded-by-400-in-30-days/" rel="nofollow">3 Reasons Why Aptos Exploded by 400% in 30 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stable at $23K as Q4 2022 US GDP Beats Expectations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stable-at-23k-as-q4-2022-us-gdp-beats-expectations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234995</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/UnitedStates.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/UnitedStates.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin reacted with minor fluctuations but remains above $23,000 for now. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&#8217;s largest economy just announced the GDP figures for the latest quarter of 2022, showing moderate but declining growth compared to Q3.</p>
<p>Unlike most previous statements coming from the US, this one brought little-to-no immediate volatility to the crypto market, with BTC still standing above $23,000.</p>
<ul>
<li>The overall <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/25/4q-2022-gdp-estimates.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">expectations</a> ahead of the Q4 2022 GDP numbers claimed that the economic growth in the country slowed down during the last three months of last year. Q3 saw an increase of 3.2%, while the estimations now suggested 2.6% for Q4.</li>
<li>Despite the Halloween and Christmas Holidays, retail sales had declined, showing reduced confidence among consumers.</li>
<li>However, the actual numbers were slightly higher &#8211; at 2.9%, instead of the estimated 2.6%. Thus, growth indeed slowed down in Q4 but not as much as expected.</li>
<li>The jobless claims were <a href="https://twitter.com/TrendSpider/status/1618602675863715844" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lower</a> than the estimated &#8211; 186,000 versus 205,000.</li>
<li>Being the largest economy in the world, almost any data typically results in immediate volatility for the stock and crypto markets. While the former is yet to open in the States, the latter reacted with minor price movements, at least for now.</li>
<li>Bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-apt-soars-another-36-bitcoin-rejected-at-24k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">stood</a> at $23,200 after yesterday&#8217;s enhanced fluctuations, and it slipped by a few hundred dollars after the numbers came out. However, it recovered almost all losses rather quickly, and trades above $23,000 as of writing these lines.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stable-at-23k-as-q4-2022-us-gdp-beats-expectations/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Stable at $23K as Q4 2022 US GDP Beats Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
