<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>SEC: Coinbase Knew About Potential Securities Law Breaches</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-coinbase-knew-about-potential-securities-law-breaches.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission has claimed that Coinbase was aware of a potential securities breach when it listed some cryptocurrencies.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent filing, lawyers for the SEC slammed Coinbase's argument that it was not aware of violating securities laws, noting that the largest US-based cryptocurrency exchange had a sophisticated legal counsel. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-coinbase-knew-about-potential-securities-law-breaches.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC: Coinbase Knew About Potential Securities Law Breaches&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-coinbase-knew-about-potential-securities-law-breaches.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119068/316859/coinbase-logo-media-libra.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="176727"/></item><item><title>Elon Musk Crypto ($MUSK) is Uniswap's Biggest Gainer Today - But Has a Blacklist Function</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-crypto-is-uniswaps-biggest-gainer-today-but-has-a-blacklist-function.htm</link><description>The biggest crypto gainer today on Uniswap is Elon Musk (MUSK), but it has some red flags - according to DEXTools the new meme token has a blacklist function in its smart contracts. &lt;br /&gt;
At the time of writing $MUSK is up approximately 30,000% - large percentage gains within the space of just a few hours are often due to low liquidity, rather than real buying volume and demand....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-crypto-is-uniswaps-biggest-gainer-today-but-has-a-blacklist-function.htm"&gt;Read More: Elon Musk Crypto ($MUSK) is Uniswap's Biggest Gainer Today - But Has a Blacklist Function&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-crypto-is-uniswaps-biggest-gainer-today-but-has-a-blacklist-function.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119066/316853/elon-musk-crypto-token-scam.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="504737"/></item><item><title>Bill Token Rises 50,000% In 24 Hours But Experts Say It Is a Scam - These Lesser Known Cryptos Are Better Alternatives</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bill-token-rises-50000-in-24-hours-but-experts-say-it-is-a-scam-these-lesser-known-cryptos-are-better-alternatives.htm</link><description>A new meme crypto asset, $BILL, has captured the interest of the crypto community.  &lt;br /&gt;
This token has experienced an astounding surge of over 50,000% within a single day, attracting the attention of numerous investors. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite the influx of eager participants, crypto experts are raising concerns that $BILL could be a honeypot scam looking to rip off investors. &lt;br /&gt;
These experts strongly urge investors to exercise utmost caution when considering involvement with the project. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bill-token-rises-50000-in-24-hours-but-experts-say-it-is-a-scam-these-lesser-known-cryptos-are-better-alternatives.htm"&gt;Read More: Bill Token Rises 50,000% In 24 Hours But Experts Say It Is a Scam - These Lesser Known Cryptos Are Better Alternatives&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bill-token-rises-50000-in-24-hours-but-experts-say-it-is-a-scam-these-lesser-known-cryptos-are-better-alternatives.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119063/316848/bill.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="786463"/></item><item><title>DCG Dismisses Gemini Lawsuit As “Publicity Stunt” By Winklevoss</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-dismisses-gemini-lawsuit-as-publicity-stunt-by-winklevoss.htm</link><description>Digital Currency Group responded to the lawsuit filed by Gemini alleging it defrauded its creditors by calling it a “publicity stunt” by Cameron Winklevoss.  &lt;br /&gt;
Gemini revealed yesterday that it has filed a lawsuit against DCG and its CEO Barry Silbert for orchestrating and directly perpetrating a fraud against creditors. &lt;br /&gt;
Gemini claimed that the DCG CEO pushed to continue the Earn program despite being fully aware of Genesis’ insolvency. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-dismisses-gemini-lawsuit-as-publicity-stunt-by-winklevoss.htm"&gt;Read More: DCG Dismisses Gemini Lawsuit As “Publicity Stunt” By Winklevoss&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Winklevoss twins</category><category>DCG</category><category>Gemini</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-dismisses-gemini-lawsuit-as-publicity-stunt-by-winklevoss.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119059/316842/digital-currency-group-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96990"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin is Top Target, Exchange Heads are Summoned, Ban is Enforced and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/bitcoin-is-top-target-exchange-heads-are-summoned-ban-is-enforced-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/bitcoin-is-top-target-exchange-heads-are-summoned-ban-is-enforced-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin is Top Target, Exchange Heads are Summoned, Ban is Enforced and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/bitcoin-is-top-target-exchange-heads-are-summoned-ban-is-enforced-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118743/316417/koinbasket-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="332862"/></item><item><title>Multichain Breach Forces Circle to Freeze $63 Million in USDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/multichain-breach-forces-circle-freeze-63-million-usdc.htm</link><description>USD Coin (USDC) issuer Circle has frozen $63 million belonging to three wallet addresses associated with the hack of the cross-chain bridge platform Multichain. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Friday tweet, security firm PeckShield revealed that Circle has frozen $27.65 million, $30.1 million, and $5.5 million in three wallet addresses that received a significant outflow of funds from Multichain after the security breach....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/multichain-breach-forces-circle-freeze-63-million-usdc.htm"&gt;Read More: Multichain Breach Forces Circle to Freeze $63 Million in USDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/multichain-breach-forces-circle-freeze-63-million-usdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119053/316833/adobestock-tomasz-biderma.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="155469"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Builds Strong Support at $30,000 Level – Where is BTC Going Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-builds-strong-support-at-30000-level-where-btc-going-next.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, has been gaining momentum as it establishes a strong support level at $30,000. The recent insights from industry experts add an interesting perspective to Bitcoin's future.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of BitMEX, Bitcoin has the potential to become the predominant currency for artificial intelligence (AI), highlighting its unique attributes and resemblance to pure energy. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-builds-strong-support-at-30000-level-where-btc-going-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Builds Strong Support at $30,000 Level – Where is BTC Going Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-builds-strong-support-at-30000-level-where-btc-going-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119052/316837/8.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="524943"/></item><item><title>South Korean Regulator Will Force Staff to Declare Crypto – Will Other Countries Follow Suit?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-regulator-will-force-staff-declare-crypto-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm</link><description>The top South Korean financial regulator will force its employees to declare their crypto holdings in the aftermath of the “Coin Gate” scandal. &lt;br /&gt;
Lawmakers in the nation have come under fire for suspected insider trading, with one MP accused of selling his tokens in advance of the rollout of a new piece of crypto regulation. &lt;br /&gt;
It has since emerged the MP was serving on a crypto-related parliamentary subcommittee at the time....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-regulator-will-force-staff-declare-crypto-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Regulator Will Force Staff to Declare Crypto – Will Other Countries Follow Suit?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-regulator-will-force-staff-declare-crypto-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118976/316671/skorea-0707.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="853191"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Tumbles Down to $30,000 Level – Will it Fall Lower?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tumbles-down-30000-level-will-it-fall-lower.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC), the dominant cryptocurrency, experienced a downturn as it encountered selling pressure near the $30,202 threshold.  &lt;br /&gt;
The release of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) minutes played a role in this downward trend.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, amidst the market turbulence, renewed optimism has emerged regarding Bitcoin's ability to revolutionize the financial landscape, largely due to the positive remarks of Larry Fink, BlackRock's CEO. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tumbles-down-30000-level-will-it-fall-lower.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Tumbles Down to $30,000 Level – Will it Fall Lower?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tumbles-down-30000-level-will-it-fall-lower.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119042/316818/7.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="479683"/></item><item><title>Top Crypto Gainers on DEXTools – Moon, Pepe 3.0, Azuki 2.0</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-moon-pepe-30-azuki-20.htm</link><description>Crypto markets are generally flat or trading with a slight positive bias on Friday, with the latest US jobs numbers for June not having rocked the boat too much. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last around $30,000, ether (ETH) around $1,870, while the overall market’s capitalization was half a percent up around $1.18 trillion. &lt;br /&gt;
In the meantime, there is plenty of action in small-cap meme coin markets, with crypto degens on the hunt as ever for the next 100x meme coin like Pepe or Shiba Inu....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-moon-pepe-30-azuki-20.htm"&gt;Read More: Top Crypto Gainers on DEXTools – Moon, Pepe 3.0, Azuki 2.0&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Shit Coin</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>Thug Life Token</category><category>THUG</category><category>DEXTools</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-moon-pepe-30-azuki-20.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119038/316805/wsm.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="697841"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 July – eCash, Filecoin, Polygon</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-july-ecash-filecoin-polygon.htm</link><description>Crypto markets are generally flat or trading with a slight positive bias on Friday, with the latest US jobs numbers for June not having rocked the boat too much. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last around $30,000, ether (ETH) around $1,870, while the overall market’s capitalization was half a percent up around $1.18 trillion. &lt;br /&gt;
For crypto investors keen to diversify their holdings away from blue-chip names like bitcoin and ether, here are some of the best coins to consider buying on Friday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-july-ecash-filecoin-polygon.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 July – eCash, Filecoin, Polygon&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Polygon</category><category>MATIC</category><category>eCash</category><category>XEC</category><category>Filecoin</category><category>FIL</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-july-ecash-filecoin-polygon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119036/316800/bestcrypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as $700 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Selling?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-700-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-selling.htm</link><description>XRP (XRP), the cryptocurrency that powers the decentralized payments-focused XRP Ledger that was created by US fintech company Ripple, has recovered back into the green after slipping to fresh monthly lows earlier in the day. &lt;br /&gt;
XRP was last changing hands around $0.4650, up a little under 1% for the day, but still lower by about 6% versus last Sunday’s monthly highs near $0.50....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-700-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-selling.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as $700 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Selling?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Ripple</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-700-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-selling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119033/316796/xrp-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="558468"/></item><item><title>Crypto Executives Stay Positive Amidst VC Funding Slump</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-executives-stay-positive-amidst-vc-funding-slump.htm</link><description>Executives in the crypto industry are still positive about the sector’s long-term prospects despite a slump in venture capital funding. &lt;br /&gt;
Based on numbers from the crypto data provider RootData, the second quarter of last year saw the lowest amount of funds raised by crypto firms since tracking of the data started in Q3 2021, with $2.17 billion raised. &lt;br /&gt;
The amount compared to $2.47 billion in the prior quarter, and $3.36 billion in the fourth quarter of 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-executives-stay-positive-amidst-vc-funding-slump.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Executives Stay Positive Amidst VC Funding Slump&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-executives-stay-positive-amidst-vc-funding-slump.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119019/316768/positive.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="201122"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Credits Ordinals NFTs for Reviving a "Builder Culture" on Bitcoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-credits-ordinals-nfts-for-reviving-builder-culture-bitcoin.htm</link><description>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has shared insights regarding new developments on the Bitcoin blockchain.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a July 7 Twitter Spaces session, Buterin spoke with Bitcoin proponents Eric Wall and Udi Wertheimer, suggesting a thing or two Bitcoin could learn from Ethereum developers. &lt;br /&gt;
The co-founder said the advent of Bitcoin Ordinals, the Bitcoin layer for NFTs, revived the “builder culture” on the network....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-credits-ordinals-nfts-for-reviving-builder-culture-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Credits Ordinals NFTs for Reviving a "Builder Culture" on Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-credits-ordinals-nfts-for-reviving-builder-culture-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119031/316790/vitalik.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="524546"/></item><item><title>Winklevoss’ Gemini Sues DCG and Barry Silbert For Fraud</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/winklevoss-gemini-sues-dcg-barry-silbert-for-fraud.htm</link><description>Winklevoss twins led crypto exchange Gemini has filed a lawsuit against the conglomerate Digital Currency Group (DCG) and its CEO Barry Silbert for allegedly defrauding creditors.  &lt;br /&gt;
As per the lawsuit, Gemini claims the DCG CEO committed fraud as Genesis attempted to continue the Earn Program despite being “massively insolvent.” &lt;br /&gt;
US-based crypto exchange Gemini is the largest creditor of bankrupt crypto lending firm Genesis, the subsidiary of DCG. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/winklevoss-gemini-sues-dcg-barry-silbert-for-fraud.htm"&gt;Read More: Winklevoss’ Gemini Sues DCG and Barry Silbert For Fraud&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Winklevoss twins</category><category>Barry Silbert</category><category>DCG</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/winklevoss-gemini-sues-dcg-barry-silbert-for-fraud.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119024/316786/gemini-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115093"/></item><item><title>Bakkt Targets Hong Kong, UK, and EU for International Crypto Expansion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-targets-hong-kong-uk-eu-for-international-crypto-expansion.htm</link><description>Regulatory uncertainty in the US is driving digital assets platform Bakkt to expand internationally to Hong Kong, the United Kingdom, and the European Union, CEO Gavin Michael noted. &lt;br /&gt;
“We’re particularly focused on Hong Kong, the UK and parts of the EU because we see partners wanting to move into those spaces and we want to be able to support them,” Michael said during the Piper Sandler Global Exchange &amp; FinTech Conference held in New York last month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-targets-hong-kong-uk-eu-for-international-crypto-expansion.htm"&gt;Read More: Bakkt Targets Hong Kong, UK, and EU for International Crypto Expansion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-targets-hong-kong-uk-eu-for-international-crypto-expansion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119001/316708/businessman-2682712-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="185585"/></item><item><title>New Report: FTX Abandoned the Deal with Taylor Swift, Not the Other Way Around</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-ftx-abandoned-deal-with-taylor-swift-not-other-way-around.htm</link><description>Now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX pulled out of the planned deal with Taylor Swift, not the other way around.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to sources cited by The New York Times, Swift signed a proposed tour sponsorship agreement with FTX in the spring of 2022, following six months of negotiations.  &lt;br /&gt;
The deal was reportedly worth up to $100 million, and discussions had taken place about other partnership approaches before settling on the tour sponsorship opportunity....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-ftx-abandoned-deal-with-taylor-swift-not-other-way-around.htm"&gt;Read More: New Report: FTX Abandoned the Deal with Taylor Swift, Not the Other Way Around&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Taylor Swift</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-ftx-abandoned-deal-with-taylor-swift-not-other-way-around.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118993/316701/taylor-swift-at-2000x1270.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="48149"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Prediction: ADA Falls 7% as Crypto Markets Retrace – Time to Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-ada-falls-3-as-crypto-markets-retrace-time-buy-dip.htm</link><description>Cardano (ADA) is experiencing a bounce at key support in the $0.28 area in the form of its 21-Day Moving Average and an uptrend from the June lows. &lt;br /&gt;
The bounce, which comes as crypto markets breathe a sign of relief in wake of not-as-hot-as-feared US jobs numbers, keeps alive hopes that ADA has formed a bullish ascending triangle structure. &lt;br /&gt;
These technical patterns tend to form ahead of a bullish breakout....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-ada-falls-3-as-crypto-markets-retrace-time-buy-dip.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Prediction: ADA Falls 7% as Crypto Markets Retrace – Time to Buy the Dip?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cardano</category><category>ADA</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-ada-falls-3-as-crypto-markets-retrace-time-buy-dip.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119015/316748/ada.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="516240"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Price Shoots Up 13% and AI Crypto Predictions Platform yPredict Just Hit 2.8 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-shoots-up-13-ai-crypto-predictions-platform-ypredict-just-hit-28-million.htm</link><description>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is a little higher on Friday at current levels just above $280, having managed to recover more than 13% from earlier weekly lows around $250. &lt;br /&gt;
However, in the grand scheme of things, the recovery isn’t much to get excited about as BCH remains well within its $250-$330ish ranges of the last week. &lt;br /&gt;
Indeed, the BCH bulls have been taking a breather over the past seven days after a huge 3x pump in the second half of June from lows under $100 per token....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-shoots-up-13-ai-crypto-predictions-platform-ypredict-just-hit-28-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Price Shoots Up 13% and AI Crypto Predictions Platform yPredict Just Hit 2.8 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin Cash</category><category>BCH</category><category>Is It Too Late</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-shoots-up-13-ai-crypto-predictions-platform-ypredict-just-hit-28-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119013/316739/bch-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="388325"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Saga Pulls Back From Blockchain Gaming, Bitfinex Recovers More Stolen Assets, BarnBridge DAO Members Told to Stop 'All Work' Amidst Investigation, Lightning Labs Releases Tools for Bitcoin Lightning &amp; AI Devs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-saga-pulls-back-from-blockchain-gaming-bitfinex-recovers-more-stolen-assets-barnbridge-dao-members-told-to-stop-all-work-amidst-investigation-lightning-labs-releases-tools-for-bitcoin-lightning-ai-devs.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-saga-pulls-back-from-blockchain-gaming-bitfinex-recovers-more-stolen-assets-barnbridge-dao-members-told-to-stop-all-work-amidst-investigation-lightning-labs-releases-tools-for-bitcoin-lightning-ai-devs.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Saga Pulls Back From Blockchain Gaming, Bitfinex Recovers More Stolen Assets, BarnBridge DAO Members Told to Stop 'All Work' Amidst Investigation, Lightning Labs Releases Tools for Bitcoin Lightning &amp; AI Devs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Gaming</category><category>Sega</category><category>GameFi</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Bitfinex</category><category>Hack</category><category>DAO</category><category>Regulation</category><category>SEC</category><category>AI</category><category>Lightning Network</category><category>Lightning Labs</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Europe</category><category>DeFi</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Canada</category><category>ETF</category><category>NFT</category><category>Cardano</category><category>Cronos</category><category>Protocol Labs</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-saga-pulls-back-from-blockchain-gaming-bitfinex-recovers-more-stolen-assets-barnbridge-dao-members-told-to-stop-all-work-amidst-investigation-lightning-labs-releases-tools-for-bitcoin-lightning-ai-devs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118994/316711/adobestock-savvapanf-photo-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="293239"/></item></channel></rss>
