<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 03:29:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[FTX's Extensive Creditor List Finally Published]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/ftxs-extensive-creditor-list-finally-published</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1920-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1920-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1920-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/ftxs-extensive-creditor-list-finally-published</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Financial advisors for bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX published an extensive list of the company's creditors, excluding the names of 9.7 million customers. Creditors include companies like Netflix, Apple, and the Wall Street Journal.</p>
<p>The extensive list of FTX's creditors was finally revealed after being sealed for three months. The 116-page index, which excludes the names of 9.7 million customers, indicates Netflix and Apple as creditors. The list certainly paints a comprehensive picture of how far FTX's reach extended. It is important to note that a company's inclusion on the list does not necessarily mean it had a trading account with FTX. The document was filed by FTX's lawyers as part of its bankruptcy proceedings in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court in Delaware after Judge John Dorsey, who oversees the proceedings, requested a list of the names of institutions that invested in FTX. Judge Dorsey first allowed individual creditors' names to be sealed for three months.</p>
<p>The filing indicated that FTX owes money to universities, media companies, airlines, charities, and many others. The list names explicitly the Wall Street Journal, American Airlines Group, and Stanford University, where the parents of Sam Bankman-Fried work, as entities to which FTX owes money. Included in the list is Giselle Bundchen Charitable Giving &ndash; Bundchen and her former husband, Tom Brady, famously invested in the FTX and even appeared in the company's Super Bowl ad.</p>
<p>The filing has also been redacted to exclude the amount each creditor is owed, but the company previously revealed that it owed $3.1 billion to its top 50 creditors. The bankruptcy proceeding and unwinding of FTX have proven to be long and arduous. The company appointed John J Ray as its new chief to oversee its restructuring. Ray is famous for liquidating and supervising the restructuring of Enron. In a recent interview with the Wall Street Journal, Mr. Ray said despite the difficulties, he is exploring the possibility of restarting FTX.com &ndash; FTX's main international exchange.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Financial advisors for bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX published an extensive list of the company's creditors, excluding the names of 9.7 million customers. Creditors include companies like Netflix, Apple, and the Wall Street Journal.</p>
<p>The extensive list of FTX's creditors was finally revealed after being sealed for three months. The 116-page index, which excludes the names of 9.7 million customers, indicates Netflix and Apple as creditors. The list certainly paints a comprehensive picture of how far FTX's reach extended. It is important to note that a company's inclusion on the list does not necessarily mean it had a trading account with FTX. The document was filed by FTX's lawyers as part of its bankruptcy proceedings in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court in Delaware after Judge John Dorsey, who oversees the proceedings, requested a list of the names of institutions that invested in FTX. Judge Dorsey first allowed individual creditors' names to be sealed for three months.</p>
<p>The filing indicated that FTX owes money to universities, media companies, airlines, charities, and many others. The list names explicitly the Wall Street Journal, American Airlines Group, and Stanford University, where the parents of Sam Bankman-Fried work, as entities to which FTX owes money. Included in the list is Giselle Bundchen Charitable Giving &ndash; Bundchen and her former husband, Tom Brady, famously invested in the FTX and even appeared in the company's Super Bowl ad.</p>
<p>The filing has also been redacted to exclude the amount each creditor is owed, but the company previously revealed that it owed $3.1 billion to its top 50 creditors. The bankruptcy proceeding and unwinding of FTX have proven to be long and arduous. The company appointed John J Ray as its new chief to oversee its restructuring. Ray is famous for liquidating and supervising the restructuring of Enron. In a recent interview with the Wall Street Journal, Mr. Ray said despite the difficulties, he is exploring the possibility of restarting FTX.com &ndash; FTX's main international exchange.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cardano To Launch Stablecoin Next Week, Crypto Daily TV 26/1/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/cardano-to-launch-stablecoin-next-week-crypto-daily-tv-26-1-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-cardano-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-cardano-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-cardano-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/cardano-to-launch-stablecoin-next-week-crypto-daily-tv-26-1-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Binance introduces function for API users to prevent self trading.</p>
<p>"Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has introduced a new function to help its API users prevent self-trading on their platform. The service will be available to Binance's API users starting January 26th. Users of the exchange's website and app will not be affected."</p>
<p>Gemini becomes the latest victim of crypto winter.</p>
<p>The Winklevoss twins&rsquo; brainchild, Gemini, is bleeding employees left and right due to its exposure to the now-bankrupt crypto lending platform Genesis. The exchange is laying off 10% of its workforce, citing reasons of &lsquo;bad actors&rsquo; in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Cardano-based overcollateralized stablecoin Djed to launch next week</p>
<p>Cardano-based decentralized stablecoin Djed is on track for a launch next week, one of the developers behind the token said. The highly-anticipated Djed stablecoin has been jointly developed by Cardano code maintainer IOG and Coti, a layer 1 blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
BTC/USD exploded 4.8% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained 4.8% in the last session after rising as much as 5.2% during the session. The Ultimate Oscillator indicates an overbought market. Support is at 22078.3333 and resistance at 23428.3333.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD skyrocketed 5.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair skyrocketed 5.4% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1477.3233 and resistance at 1680.5233.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is currently in negative territory.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD exploded 3.8% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 3.8% in the last session. The MACD is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 0.3857 and resistance at 0.4421.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 5.0% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair gained 5.0% in the last session after rising as much as 5.4% during the session. According to the Williams indicator, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 84.71 and resistance at 93.3833.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP Coincident Index</p>
<p>The Coincident Index released by the Cabinet Office is a single summary statistic that tracks the current state of the Japanese economy.&nbsp; The US Durable Goods Orders will be released at 13:30 GMT, the US Gross Domestic Product Annualized at 13:30 GMT, the Irish Consumer Confidence at 00:01 GMT.</p>
<p>DE IFO &ndash; Business Climate</p>
<p>The IFO Business Climate index is regarded as an early indicator of current conditions and business expectations. The Institute surveys enterprises on their assessment of the economic situation.</p>
<p>UK PPI Core Output</p>
<p>The Producer Prices Index (PPI) Core Output is a price index of producer prices and excludes volatile items such as food and energy.</p>
<p>US MBA Mortgage Applications</p>
<p>The MBA Mortgage Applications released by the Mortgage Bankers Association presents various mortgage applications. It is considered as a leading indicator of the U.S Housing Market. Spain's Unemployment Survey will be released at 07:00 GMT, Japan's Tokyo Consumer Price Index at 23:30 GMT, and Japan's Tokyo CPI at 23:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Producer Price Index</p>
<p>The Producer Price Index measures the average changes in prices in primary markets by producers of commodities in all states of processing.</p>
<p>AU Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Binance introduces function for API users to prevent self trading.</p>
<p>"Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has introduced a new function to help its API users prevent self-trading on their platform. The service will be available to Binance's API users starting January 26th. Users of the exchange's website and app will not be affected."</p>
<p>Gemini becomes the latest victim of crypto winter.</p>
<p>The Winklevoss twins&rsquo; brainchild, Gemini, is bleeding employees left and right due to its exposure to the now-bankrupt crypto lending platform Genesis. The exchange is laying off 10% of its workforce, citing reasons of &lsquo;bad actors&rsquo; in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Cardano-based overcollateralized stablecoin Djed to launch next week</p>
<p>Cardano-based decentralized stablecoin Djed is on track for a launch next week, one of the developers behind the token said. The highly-anticipated Djed stablecoin has been jointly developed by Cardano code maintainer IOG and Coti, a layer 1 blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
BTC/USD exploded 4.8% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained 4.8% in the last session after rising as much as 5.2% during the session. The Ultimate Oscillator indicates an overbought market. Support is at 22078.3333 and resistance at 23428.3333.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD skyrocketed 5.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair skyrocketed 5.4% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1477.3233 and resistance at 1680.5233.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is currently in negative territory.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD exploded 3.8% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 3.8% in the last session. The MACD is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 0.3857 and resistance at 0.4421.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 5.0% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair gained 5.0% in the last session after rising as much as 5.4% during the session. According to the Williams indicator, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 84.71 and resistance at 93.3833.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP Coincident Index</p>
<p>The Coincident Index released by the Cabinet Office is a single summary statistic that tracks the current state of the Japanese economy.&nbsp; The US Durable Goods Orders will be released at 13:30 GMT, the US Gross Domestic Product Annualized at 13:30 GMT, the Irish Consumer Confidence at 00:01 GMT.</p>
<p>DE IFO &ndash; Business Climate</p>
<p>The IFO Business Climate index is regarded as an early indicator of current conditions and business expectations. The Institute surveys enterprises on their assessment of the economic situation.</p>
<p>UK PPI Core Output</p>
<p>The Producer Prices Index (PPI) Core Output is a price index of producer prices and excludes volatile items such as food and energy.</p>
<p>US MBA Mortgage Applications</p>
<p>The MBA Mortgage Applications released by the Mortgage Bankers Association presents various mortgage applications. It is considered as a leading indicator of the U.S Housing Market. Spain's Unemployment Survey will be released at 07:00 GMT, Japan's Tokyo Consumer Price Index at 23:30 GMT, and Japan's Tokyo CPI at 23:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Producer Price Index</p>
<p>The Producer Price Index measures the average changes in prices in primary markets by producers of commodities in all states of processing.</p>
<p>AU Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) And Polygon (MATIC) Drop Prices As Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Aims At The Sky]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-btc-and-polygon-matic-drop-prices-as-orbeon-protocol-orbn-aims-at-the-sky</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-26-at-161448.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-26-at-161448.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-26-at-161448.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-btc-and-polygon-matic-drop-prices-as-orbeon-protocol-orbn-aims-at-the-sky</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) and Bitcoin (BTC) have recently experienced strong runs. But a new entry has surprised investors with its high presale numbers.</p>
<p class="s3">The presale for Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) just passed out of the first three phases, showing no signs of slowing down. Currently on the fourth presale stage, with the price at $0.06, analysts predict a rise to $0.24. Investors are looking further into each project and discussing how Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) transformed the low-cap market.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s3">Bitcoin (BTC) is likely to move upward after FTX's bankruptcy caused a decline in price</p>
<p class="s3">Bitcoin (BTC) is still the most valuable cryptocurrency, but this last week it gained significant value. Bitcoin (BTC) hit its all-time high of $68,789 in November 2021. Bitcoin (BTC) is now worth about $20,000.</p>
<p class="s3">Even though Bitcoin's (BTC) price had gone up, several different things exacerbated the bear market. There is an ongoing discussion about whether Bitcoin (BTC) is a real way to save money. It was thought it would do well in an environment with high inflation, but so far, it hasn't lived up to that hope.</p>
<p class="s3">One of the biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, FTX, went bankrupt because $8 billion was missing from their financial statements. This caused the most recent drop. In addition, it also triggered people to sell in a panic and sent Bitcoin (BTC) down. Nevertheless, as more people use Bitcoin (BTC) as a currency and a way to save money, Bitcoin&rsquo;s (BTC) value will likely increase over time.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) is recovering from its massive drop in price</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) is a protocol and a framework that helps build and connect blockchain platforms that work with Ethereum. This protocol works by putting scalable Ethereum solutions into groups to help the ecosystem of Ethereum with more than one chain.</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) is the Ethereum token that runs the Polygon (MATIC) Network. MATIC is also the native token of Polygon (MATIC). Polygon (MATIC) uses a Layer-2 sidechain, which is a blockchain that runs along with the main Ethereum chain, to make transactions on Ethereum faster and cheaper.</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon's (MATIC) collective security model is entirely optional. Sovereign platforms can keep their self-governance and flexibility if they don't need extra security. Polygon (MATIC) also says that it is flexible enough to work with any scaling solution, not just the optimistic rollups, ZK-rollups, and Plasma chains that are already planned.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s3">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN): a crypto investment platform for Web3 startups</p>
<p class="s3">The first people to put money into a business almost always get the best returns. Nevertheless, the sad reality is that these chances usually go to people who are rich and have good connections. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) wants to make early-stage investments easier for everyone to participate in by making the process easier.</p>
<p class="s3">The Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) team uses blockchain technology and diversifies non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to make this possible. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) tokenizes investments so that anyone can invest as little as $1 in early-stage companies.</p>
<p class="s3">For new businesses, this is a chance to change the game. They can now reach out to a much larger group of possible investors and raise money more quickly. In addition, regular investors can now enter the venture capital market, which used to be closed to them.</p>
<p class="s3">The Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) platform is built around smart contracts. For example, if a startup doesn't meet its goals, the money will be returned to the people who pledged it.</p>
<p class="s3">The Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) ecosystem is run by the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) token, which gives its owners the right to vote and access unique benefits, such as early entry to investment options and staking rewards. The price of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) tokens has increased by almost 1400% within a few weeks from their initial sale price of $0.004 to $0.06 per token.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p class="s9">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s9">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s9">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s9">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s9">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) and Bitcoin (BTC) have recently experienced strong runs. But a new entry has surprised investors with its high presale numbers.</p>
<p class="s3">The presale for Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) just passed out of the first three phases, showing no signs of slowing down. Currently on the fourth presale stage, with the price at $0.06, analysts predict a rise to $0.24. Investors are looking further into each project and discussing how Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) transformed the low-cap market.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s3">Bitcoin (BTC) is likely to move upward after FTX's bankruptcy caused a decline in price</p>
<p class="s3">Bitcoin (BTC) is still the most valuable cryptocurrency, but this last week it gained significant value. Bitcoin (BTC) hit its all-time high of $68,789 in November 2021. Bitcoin (BTC) is now worth about $20,000.</p>
<p class="s3">Even though Bitcoin's (BTC) price had gone up, several different things exacerbated the bear market. There is an ongoing discussion about whether Bitcoin (BTC) is a real way to save money. It was thought it would do well in an environment with high inflation, but so far, it hasn't lived up to that hope.</p>
<p class="s3">One of the biggest cryptocurrency exchanges, FTX, went bankrupt because $8 billion was missing from their financial statements. This caused the most recent drop. In addition, it also triggered people to sell in a panic and sent Bitcoin (BTC) down. Nevertheless, as more people use Bitcoin (BTC) as a currency and a way to save money, Bitcoin&rsquo;s (BTC) value will likely increase over time.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) is recovering from its massive drop in price</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) is a protocol and a framework that helps build and connect blockchain platforms that work with Ethereum. This protocol works by putting scalable Ethereum solutions into groups to help the ecosystem of Ethereum with more than one chain.</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon (MATIC) is the Ethereum token that runs the Polygon (MATIC) Network. MATIC is also the native token of Polygon (MATIC). Polygon (MATIC) uses a Layer-2 sidechain, which is a blockchain that runs along with the main Ethereum chain, to make transactions on Ethereum faster and cheaper.</p>
<p class="s3">Polygon's (MATIC) collective security model is entirely optional. Sovereign platforms can keep their self-governance and flexibility if they don't need extra security. Polygon (MATIC) also says that it is flexible enough to work with any scaling solution, not just the optimistic rollups, ZK-rollups, and Plasma chains that are already planned.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s3">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN): a crypto investment platform for Web3 startups</p>
<p class="s3">The first people to put money into a business almost always get the best returns. Nevertheless, the sad reality is that these chances usually go to people who are rich and have good connections. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) wants to make early-stage investments easier for everyone to participate in by making the process easier.</p>
<p class="s3">The Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) team uses blockchain technology and diversifies non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to make this possible. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) tokenizes investments so that anyone can invest as little as $1 in early-stage companies.</p>
<p class="s3">For new businesses, this is a chance to change the game. They can now reach out to a much larger group of possible investors and raise money more quickly. In addition, regular investors can now enter the venture capital market, which used to be closed to them.</p>
<p class="s3">The Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) platform is built around smart contracts. For example, if a startup doesn't meet its goals, the money will be returned to the people who pledged it.</p>
<p class="s3">The Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) ecosystem is run by the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) token, which gives its owners the right to vote and access unique benefits, such as early entry to investment options and staking rewards. The price of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) tokens has increased by almost 1400% within a few weeks from their initial sale price of $0.004 to $0.06 per token.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p class="s9">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s9">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s9">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s9">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s9">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Softer After 23824 - 27 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-softer-after-23824-27-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-26-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-26-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-26-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-softer-after-23824-27-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Takes Out 23194:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 27 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to trade around a significant technical level early in the Asian session as the pair orbited the 23194.61 area, a level that represents the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; Significant Stops were elected above this area during the rapid appreciation and BTC/USD rocketed to the 23824.66 area, its strongest print since August 2022.&nbsp; Notably, this new relative high represented a test of an upside price objective around the 23808 area that became technically significant when buying pressure strengthened around the 17927 area.&nbsp; Additional Stops were recently triggered above the 23375 and 23544 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 area include the 25455, 25774, 27609, and 28004 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 15460 area include the 23980, 24224, 26612, 26931, 29244, and 29639 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the recent move higher to multi-month highs, technical support levels and areas of potential buying pressure are around the 22055, 20960, 20075, 19190, 18095, and 17930 levels.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 21437, 20874, 20724, 20370, 20233, 20026, 19153, 18448, and 18253 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, technically significant areas include the 15900, 15512, 15313, 14500, 14364, 13369, 10727, 10432, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 22230.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 22869.19.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18390.99/ 16714.46/ 14500.15 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;23544.62/ 24224.60/ 25455.06 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Takes Out 23194:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 27 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to trade around a significant technical level early in the Asian session as the pair orbited the 23194.61 area, a level that represents the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; Significant Stops were elected above this area during the rapid appreciation and BTC/USD rocketed to the 23824.66 area, its strongest print since August 2022.&nbsp; Notably, this new relative high represented a test of an upside price objective around the 23808 area that became technically significant when buying pressure strengthened around the 17927 area.&nbsp; Additional Stops were recently triggered above the 23375 and 23544 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 area include the 25455, 25774, 27609, and 28004 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 15460 area include the 23980, 24224, 26612, 26931, 29244, and 29639 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the recent move higher to multi-month highs, technical support levels and areas of potential buying pressure are around the 22055, 20960, 20075, 19190, 18095, and 17930 levels.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 21437, 20874, 20724, 20370, 20233, 20026, 19153, 18448, and 18253 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, technically significant areas include the 15900, 15512, 15313, 14500, 14364, 13369, 10727, 10432, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 22230.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 22869.19.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18390.99/ 16714.46/ 14500.15 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;23544.62/ 24224.60/ 25455.06 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Visa CEO: Stablecoins and CBDCs will be Integral for Payments]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/visa-ceo-stablecoins-and-cbdcs-will-be-integral-for-payments</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/visa-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/visa-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/visa-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/visa-ceo-stablecoins-and-cbdcs-will-be-integral-for-payments</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The outgoing chief executive officer of the credit card behemoth Visa, Alfred Kelly, believes that the company can integrate stablecoins and central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) into its services to improve the future of payments. </p>
<p>In a call at Visa&rsquo;s annual stockholder meeting earlier in the week, Kelly, who will officially step down as CEO on February 1, shared Visa&rsquo;s plans regarding CBDCs and private stablecoins. Kelly said:</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s very early days, but we continue to believe that stablecoins and central bank digital currencies have the potential to play a meaningful role in the payments space, and we have several initiatives underway.</p>

<p>Adding,</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ve had an immaterial amount of investments in crypto funds and companies as we seek to invest in the payments ecosystem.</p>

<p>Ryan Mclnerney, the President of Visa, will officially replace Kelly as CEO on February 1, but Kelly will remain on board and serve as executive chairman, Cointelegraph reports. Mclnerney appears to be bullish on blockchain-powered payment solutions and said in an interview with Fortune that Visa still has &ldquo;$14 trillion of cash out there being spent by customers that can be digitized.&rdquo; He added that Visa continues to identify opportunities where best to use cryptocurrency payments.</p>
Visa Involved in a Number of Crypto-Related Initiatives
<p>During the stockholder meeting, Kelly assured that the firm&rsquo;s balance sheet had not been affected by some of the massive failures that severely impacted the sector:</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ve had no credit losses related to these failures [...] In everything we do, please know that we&rsquo;re extremely focused on maintaining the integrity of Visa&rsquo;s payment system and the payment system in totality and, of course, the reputation of our brand standing for trust.</p>

<p>Visa has not suffered much due to the failures in the crypto space in 2022, and as such, the firm is involved in several crypto-related projects. Most recently, Visa announced that it is collaborating with Ethereum to devise a solution to allow automated bills to be paid directly from an Ethereum-based wallet. The payments giant also announced that Blockchain.com would launch a pre-paid crypto-centric Visa card in which each card links to a verifiable Blockchain.com Wallet account.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The outgoing chief executive officer of the credit card behemoth Visa, Alfred Kelly, believes that the company can integrate stablecoins and central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) into its services to improve the future of payments. </p>
<p>In a call at Visa&rsquo;s annual stockholder meeting earlier in the week, Kelly, who will officially step down as CEO on February 1, shared Visa&rsquo;s plans regarding CBDCs and private stablecoins. Kelly said:</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s very early days, but we continue to believe that stablecoins and central bank digital currencies have the potential to play a meaningful role in the payments space, and we have several initiatives underway.</p>

<p>Adding,</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ve had an immaterial amount of investments in crypto funds and companies as we seek to invest in the payments ecosystem.</p>

<p>Ryan Mclnerney, the President of Visa, will officially replace Kelly as CEO on February 1, but Kelly will remain on board and serve as executive chairman, Cointelegraph reports. Mclnerney appears to be bullish on blockchain-powered payment solutions and said in an interview with Fortune that Visa still has &ldquo;$14 trillion of cash out there being spent by customers that can be digitized.&rdquo; He added that Visa continues to identify opportunities where best to use cryptocurrency payments.</p>
Visa Involved in a Number of Crypto-Related Initiatives
<p>During the stockholder meeting, Kelly assured that the firm&rsquo;s balance sheet had not been affected by some of the massive failures that severely impacted the sector:</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ve had no credit losses related to these failures [...] In everything we do, please know that we&rsquo;re extremely focused on maintaining the integrity of Visa&rsquo;s payment system and the payment system in totality and, of course, the reputation of our brand standing for trust.</p>

<p>Visa has not suffered much due to the failures in the crypto space in 2022, and as such, the firm is involved in several crypto-related projects. Most recently, Visa announced that it is collaborating with Ethereum to devise a solution to allow automated bills to be paid directly from an Ethereum-based wallet. The payments giant also announced that Blockchain.com would launch a pre-paid crypto-centric Visa card in which each card links to a verifiable Blockchain.com Wallet account.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Flare Partners With Blockchain Security Specialist FYEO For Ongoing Audits]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/flare-partners-with-blockchain-security-specialist-fyeo-for-ongoing-audits</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/FYEO_1674728842fKW03EzfyY.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/FYEO_1674728842fKW03EzfyY.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/FYEO_1674728842fKW03EzfyY.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/flare-partners-with-blockchain-security-specialist-fyeo-for-ongoing-audits</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, 26th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Flare is pleased to announce an official partnership with blockchain security specialist, FYEO. The firm will perform ongoing security audits of Flare&rsquo;s codebases, providing actionable feedback to support safer smart contract development and help to minimize risk for all users of the network.</p>
<p>Rigorous professional auditing and testing are an important part of Flare&rsquo;s blockchain security strategy. Alongside stringent internal testing measures, ongoing code audits help to establish a level of security assurance to application developers and users on the network. </p>
<p>Flare Co-Founder &amp; CEO Hugo Philion said, &ldquo;We are building our protocols with auditor reviews initiated from close to day one. We believe this guarantees a safer outcome than an auditor reviewing an entire code base at the end of development.&rdquo;</p>
<p>In addition to continuous auditing from partners including FYEO, Flare also employs rigorous testing with testnets and a Canary network called Songbird. The Canary network is a live but more experimental version of Flare (similar to Kusama&rsquo;s relationship to Polkadot) where Flare can test their protocols. The network advises application developers and builders to do the same. Flare recognizes that risk minimization from both an auditing and testnet perspective is crucial to building reputational trust amongst users. </p>
<p>In the words of Flare Co-Founder, Hugo Philion, "Our game as an organization within the industry is to mitigate the risk in blockchain such that people feel comfortable to use it. As a result of that, the usage can increase substantially&rdquo;. </p>
<p>Tammy Kahn, Co-CEO of FYEO, said, &ldquo;FYEO could not be more aligned with this vision for supporting adoption through user risk minimization, and look forward to our continuous work with Flare as it expands its presence as a leader of decentralized innovation.&rdquo;</p>
<p>About Flare</p>
<p>Flare is an EVM-based Layer 1 blockchain designed to allow developers to build applications that can use data from other chains and the internet. By providing decentralized access to high-integrity data, Flare enables new use cases and monetisation models.</p>
<p>Flare&rsquo;s State Connector protocols enable information, both from other blockchains and the internet to be used securely, scalably and trustlessly with smart contracts on Flare.</p>
<p>The Flare Time Series Oracle delivers highly-decentralized price and data feeds to dapps on Flare, without relying on centralized providers.</p>
<p>Build on Flare with more data than ever before or build with Flare to serve multiple ecosystems.</p>
<p>Twitter &nbsp;&nbsp;| &nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram &nbsp;&nbsp;| &nbsp;&nbsp;Discord
</p>
<p>About FYEO</p>
<p>FYEO is focused on solving the growing problem of cyber crime in Web3. FYEO&rsquo;s code audit team is composed of some of the best DeFi logic experts in the world having worked on 100s of projects and protocols such as Solana, Ethereum, Cardano, ICON, Hyperlane, Sommelier Finance, and more. Its flagship product, FYEO Domain Intelligence, which provides real-time threat monitoring and intelligence for organizations, was developed to provide unparalleled security and address present-day security issues impacting both organizations and individuals. Today, the FYEO team continues its work to identify and evolve its products to solve the biggest security problems facing Web3 ecosystems.</p>ContactDan HorowitzPR@Marketacross.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, 26th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Flare is pleased to announce an official partnership with blockchain security specialist, FYEO. The firm will perform ongoing security audits of Flare&rsquo;s codebases, providing actionable feedback to support safer smart contract development and help to minimize risk for all users of the network.</p>
<p>Rigorous professional auditing and testing are an important part of Flare&rsquo;s blockchain security strategy. Alongside stringent internal testing measures, ongoing code audits help to establish a level of security assurance to application developers and users on the network. </p>
<p>Flare Co-Founder &amp; CEO Hugo Philion said, &ldquo;We are building our protocols with auditor reviews initiated from close to day one. We believe this guarantees a safer outcome than an auditor reviewing an entire code base at the end of development.&rdquo;</p>
<p>In addition to continuous auditing from partners including FYEO, Flare also employs rigorous testing with testnets and a Canary network called Songbird. The Canary network is a live but more experimental version of Flare (similar to Kusama&rsquo;s relationship to Polkadot) where Flare can test their protocols. The network advises application developers and builders to do the same. Flare recognizes that risk minimization from both an auditing and testnet perspective is crucial to building reputational trust amongst users. </p>
<p>In the words of Flare Co-Founder, Hugo Philion, "Our game as an organization within the industry is to mitigate the risk in blockchain such that people feel comfortable to use it. As a result of that, the usage can increase substantially&rdquo;. </p>
<p>Tammy Kahn, Co-CEO of FYEO, said, &ldquo;FYEO could not be more aligned with this vision for supporting adoption through user risk minimization, and look forward to our continuous work with Flare as it expands its presence as a leader of decentralized innovation.&rdquo;</p>
<p>About Flare</p>
<p>Flare is an EVM-based Layer 1 blockchain designed to allow developers to build applications that can use data from other chains and the internet. By providing decentralized access to high-integrity data, Flare enables new use cases and monetisation models.</p>
<p>Flare&rsquo;s State Connector protocols enable information, both from other blockchains and the internet to be used securely, scalably and trustlessly with smart contracts on Flare.</p>
<p>The Flare Time Series Oracle delivers highly-decentralized price and data feeds to dapps on Flare, without relying on centralized providers.</p>
<p>Build on Flare with more data than ever before or build with Flare to serve multiple ecosystems.</p>
<p>Twitter &nbsp;&nbsp;| &nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram &nbsp;&nbsp;| &nbsp;&nbsp;Discord
</p>
<p>About FYEO</p>
<p>FYEO is focused on solving the growing problem of cyber crime in Web3. FYEO&rsquo;s code audit team is composed of some of the best DeFi logic experts in the world having worked on 100s of projects and protocols such as Solana, Ethereum, Cardano, ICON, Hyperlane, Sommelier Finance, and more. Its flagship product, FYEO Domain Intelligence, which provides real-time threat monitoring and intelligence for organizations, was developed to provide unparalleled security and address present-day security issues impacting both organizations and individuals. Today, the FYEO team continues its work to identify and evolve its products to solve the biggest security problems facing Web3 ecosystems.</p>ContactDan HorowitzPR@Marketacross.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cryptoâ€™s Options Market Expands With Toncoin on BIT Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/cryptos-options-market-expands-with-toncoin-on-bit-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ton.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ton.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ton.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/cryptos-options-market-expands-with-toncoin-on-bit-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Fans of the TON cryptocurrency now have a new way to trade their favorite altcoin following its addition to the options trading markets on the popular exchange platforms BIT and Paradigm.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BIT said that TON options trading is available on its platform now, while Paradigm is planning to go live with the token in the coming weeks, thanks to a close collaboration with technology partners Darley Technologies and DWF Labs, which are providing market making services. It&rsquo;s a big boost overall to the nascent options trading market in crypto, which, until now, has only supported the most well-known tokens - Bitcoin and Ethereum.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move is actually a fairly big deal because options trading is almost completely unknown in the crypto world. The vast majority of crypto exchanges support what&rsquo;s known as &ldquo;spot trading&rdquo;, which is where users simply exchange token pairs, such as BTC/ETH, BTC/USDC, ETH/USDT etc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Options trading is a completely different ballgame and many traders believe it&rsquo;s a much safer way of hedging against the price movements of different assets. Rather than just swapping tokens directly, options trading allows traders to purchase a contract that gives them the right to buy or sell a token at a specific price, either before or when the contract expires. But there&rsquo;s no obligation to execute the contract, so traders only have to do so when the price is advantageous to them. Alternatively they can let the contract expire without exercising their &ldquo;option&rdquo; and they&rsquo;ll only lose the fee paid to take out the contract in the first place.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s a very different way of trading than most crypto traders are used to. Last year, options trading accounted for just 2% of the overall crypto trading market. Spot trading is far more dominant, but BIT and Paradigm believe it has the potential to one day surpass that of spot trading, and say that&rsquo;s why they're adding support for TON. Their belief stems from the fact that in other markets, options is actually far more lucrative. The stock options and FOREX options markets for example, are said to be around 35-times larger than the spot markets. So it&rsquo;s logical to assume that if crypto options supports a greater number of assets, the market can grow considerably.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BIT and Paradigm selected TON as the third supported cryptocurrency for their options markets due to its incredible potential. It&rsquo;s one of the fastest-growing cryptocurrencies, currently ranked 23rd overall by market cap, with its value rising almost 200% in the last six months. TON is the native token of The Open Network, a layer-1 blockchain platform that supports a growing and extensive ecosystem of decentralized applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TON was originally developed by the creators of the Telegram messaging app, only to be abandoned after it had problems with the U.S. SEC. Since then, the project has been picked up by the open-source community and is now led by the TON Foundation. It&rsquo;s claimed to be one of the fastest and most scalable blockchain networks around, with the ability to support millions of transactions per second. DWF Labs is one of its main backers, providing services around market creation and token development. It also supports TON with significant funding, having already donated $10 million that will be used to fund the development of projects within its ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Darley Technologies played an instrumental role in bringing TON options trading to BIT and Paradigm. As the exchanges noted in a press release, the addition of any altcoin to the options trading market is a big challenge that comes with unique market risk management requirements. With its supporting infrastructure, Darley intends to democratize access to altcoin options trading, beginning with TON.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled to be working with Darley Technologies and DWF to offer TON options,&rdquo; BIT co-founder and COO Lan said. &ldquo;With the advent of dollar-margined products and the addition of various altcoin options, the options market has enormous growth potential. BIT and our trusted partners are devoted to increasing the accessibility of crypto options for both institutional and retail traders.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fans of the TON cryptocurrency now have a new way to trade their favorite altcoin following its addition to the options trading markets on the popular exchange platforms BIT and Paradigm.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BIT said that TON options trading is available on its platform now, while Paradigm is planning to go live with the token in the coming weeks, thanks to a close collaboration with technology partners Darley Technologies and DWF Labs, which are providing market making services. It&rsquo;s a big boost overall to the nascent options trading market in crypto, which, until now, has only supported the most well-known tokens - Bitcoin and Ethereum.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move is actually a fairly big deal because options trading is almost completely unknown in the crypto world. The vast majority of crypto exchanges support what&rsquo;s known as &ldquo;spot trading&rdquo;, which is where users simply exchange token pairs, such as BTC/ETH, BTC/USDC, ETH/USDT etc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Options trading is a completely different ballgame and many traders believe it&rsquo;s a much safer way of hedging against the price movements of different assets. Rather than just swapping tokens directly, options trading allows traders to purchase a contract that gives them the right to buy or sell a token at a specific price, either before or when the contract expires. But there&rsquo;s no obligation to execute the contract, so traders only have to do so when the price is advantageous to them. Alternatively they can let the contract expire without exercising their &ldquo;option&rdquo; and they&rsquo;ll only lose the fee paid to take out the contract in the first place.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s a very different way of trading than most crypto traders are used to. Last year, options trading accounted for just 2% of the overall crypto trading market. Spot trading is far more dominant, but BIT and Paradigm believe it has the potential to one day surpass that of spot trading, and say that&rsquo;s why they're adding support for TON. Their belief stems from the fact that in other markets, options is actually far more lucrative. The stock options and FOREX options markets for example, are said to be around 35-times larger than the spot markets. So it&rsquo;s logical to assume that if crypto options supports a greater number of assets, the market can grow considerably.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BIT and Paradigm selected TON as the third supported cryptocurrency for their options markets due to its incredible potential. It&rsquo;s one of the fastest-growing cryptocurrencies, currently ranked 23rd overall by market cap, with its value rising almost 200% in the last six months. TON is the native token of The Open Network, a layer-1 blockchain platform that supports a growing and extensive ecosystem of decentralized applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TON was originally developed by the creators of the Telegram messaging app, only to be abandoned after it had problems with the U.S. SEC. Since then, the project has been picked up by the open-source community and is now led by the TON Foundation. It&rsquo;s claimed to be one of the fastest and most scalable blockchain networks around, with the ability to support millions of transactions per second. DWF Labs is one of its main backers, providing services around market creation and token development. It also supports TON with significant funding, having already donated $10 million that will be used to fund the development of projects within its ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Darley Technologies played an instrumental role in bringing TON options trading to BIT and Paradigm. As the exchanges noted in a press release, the addition of any altcoin to the options trading market is a big challenge that comes with unique market risk management requirements. With its supporting infrastructure, Darley intends to democratize access to altcoin options trading, beginning with TON.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled to be working with Darley Technologies and DWF to offer TON options,&rdquo; BIT co-founder and COO Lan said. &ldquo;With the advent of dollar-margined products and the addition of various altcoin options, the options market has enormous growth potential. BIT and our trusted partners are devoted to increasing the accessibility of crypto options for both institutional and retail traders.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ex-Chancellor advocates that UK take â€œaccepted riskâ€ on crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/ex-chancellor-advocates-that-uk-take-accepted-risk-on-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hub.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hub.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hub.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/ex-chancellor-advocates-that-uk-take-accepted-risk-on-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to Philip Hammond, the ex-Chancellor of the Exchequer, the UK is in danger of falling behind other countries in its bid to become a global hub for crypto.</p>
<p>In an interview for the UK-based Financial Times, Philip Hammond warned that the UK is falling behind in its bid to become a financial centre for digital assets, and said that other countries were &ldquo;racing ahead&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The UK needs to be leading in this area post-Brexit,&rdquo; he told the Financial Times, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s allowed itself to slip behind,&rdquo; he added. &ldquo;Switzerland is further ahead. The EU is also moving faster. There has to be appetite to take some measured risk.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The ex-Chancellor voiced his frustration (and not for the first time) at what he perceived as the slow speed that the UK was moving, and that it needed to come up with a regulatory framework that could compete with other countries and allow the UK to lead the digital asset sector.</p>
<p>The Treasury is looking into a reform of regulations for the cryptocurrency industry, which it hopes will encourage and attract businesses to the UK that wish to &ldquo;invest and innovate&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Hammond was speaking with the Financial Times after taking on his new role as chairman of crypto exchange Copper. He revealed that the exchange had closed a new funding round, which was expected to lead to a valuation of $2 billion.</p>
<p>Hammond&rsquo;s company Copper was forced to register in Switzerland last year when it withdrew its application in the UK. He blamed the move on the FCA&rsquo;s temporary registration which could have led to Copper losing customers.</p>
<p>However, despite this, and also the huge bear market that crypto has endured for more than a year, Hammond said that Copper had managed to attract new customers and that there was a &ldquo;tremendous surge in interest&rdquo; in Copper. He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have managed to grow in a market that has shrunk 70 per cent,&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to Philip Hammond, the ex-Chancellor of the Exchequer, the UK is in danger of falling behind other countries in its bid to become a global hub for crypto.</p>
<p>In an interview for the UK-based Financial Times, Philip Hammond warned that the UK is falling behind in its bid to become a financial centre for digital assets, and said that other countries were &ldquo;racing ahead&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The UK needs to be leading in this area post-Brexit,&rdquo; he told the Financial Times, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s allowed itself to slip behind,&rdquo; he added. &ldquo;Switzerland is further ahead. The EU is also moving faster. There has to be appetite to take some measured risk.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The ex-Chancellor voiced his frustration (and not for the first time) at what he perceived as the slow speed that the UK was moving, and that it needed to come up with a regulatory framework that could compete with other countries and allow the UK to lead the digital asset sector.</p>
<p>The Treasury is looking into a reform of regulations for the cryptocurrency industry, which it hopes will encourage and attract businesses to the UK that wish to &ldquo;invest and innovate&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Hammond was speaking with the Financial Times after taking on his new role as chairman of crypto exchange Copper. He revealed that the exchange had closed a new funding round, which was expected to lead to a valuation of $2 billion.</p>
<p>Hammond&rsquo;s company Copper was forced to register in Switzerland last year when it withdrew its application in the UK. He blamed the move on the FCA&rsquo;s temporary registration which could have led to Copper losing customers.</p>
<p>However, despite this, and also the huge bear market that crypto has endured for more than a year, Hammond said that Copper had managed to attract new customers and that there was a &ldquo;tremendous surge in interest&rdquo; in Copper. He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have managed to grow in a market that has shrunk 70 per cent,&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Passive Income Opportunities For Crypto Investors In 2023, An interview session with Joseph Emmett, the CEO of Mosdex.com]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/passive-income-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-in-2023-an-interview-session-with-joseph-emmett-the-ceo-of-mosdexcom</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/passive-income-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-in-2023-an-interview.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/passive-income-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-in-2023-an-interview.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/passive-income-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-in-2023-an-interview.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/passive-income-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-in-2023-an-interview-session-with-joseph-emmett-the-ceo-of-mosdexcom</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>t&rsquo;s no secret that 2022 wasn&rsquo;t necessarily the best for anyone in the fledgling crypto space. After multiple platform collapses and with pressure mounting from the traditional economy, cryptocurrency prices cratered, with investors suffering losses. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Nevertheless, crypto is far from dead. In fact, the bear market of 2022 is giving more investors renewed hope of a coming bull cycle, and many are looking to prepare themselves for what is coming. Just as well, investors were still able to optimize returns in the market via arbitrage, a smart yet unrealized way to earn passive income using cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We conducted a session with Mr. Joseph Emmett, the CEO of Mosdex.com who discussed the current crypto market scenario and how Mosdex stands out as a potential arbitrage staking platform for offering recurring passive income.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrage - Beneficial for Everyone</p>
<p>The concept of arbitrage is simple: you look for the difference in the price of a certain asset, e.g., Bitcoin on different exchanges and capitalize on that to your advantage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For example, the price of BTC on a certain exchange can be $20,850, while the same asset could trade at $20,790 on a separate exchange. As seen, there is a difference of $60, which can be capitalized if trades are performed quickly. This activity of buying low on one exchange and selling high on the other is called arbitrage.</p>
<p>Of course, it is worth noting that the price of cryptocurrencies on exchanges fluctuates based on their levels of demand and supply. So, while exchanges do their bets to track market prices across other platforms, their demand and supply levels will be the ones to essentially determine where coins trade at the end of the day.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Over the years, there have been many traders who have mastered the act of moving assets on exchanges quickly, thus taking advantage of the arbitrage opportunities on these platforms. And as the crypto market has evolved, so have the arbitrage opportunities available to investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Then, there is cryptocurrency staking - the act of locking up coins on a specific exchange in order to support it. Staking was made popular thanks to the evolution of blockchains, which used to validate transactions using the mining consensus algorithm. With staking, investors can simply lock their coins up, and network validators continue to verify transactions on the network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Combine these two concepts together, and you have arbitrage staking - a way for cryptocurrency investors to lock their assets on a platform, and these tokens get used for trading by a bot or a trading engine.&nbsp; In return, investors earn returns that are paid out periodically to crypto stakers - and still get returns from their trading activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrage Staking, an innovative way to stake and earn</p>
<p>Arbitrage-based staking is great because it allows community members to participate without actively doing anything while also providing a launchpad for them to enjoy significant gains.</p>
<p>With investors looking for new passive income opportunities, MOSDEX, a highly efficient arbitrage platform, presents its automated arbitrage staking that combines AI and Defi to bring the best for its users. Joseph Emmet, the chief executive at MOSDEX, recently sat down for an interview where he spoke about his company and the objective they are trying to reach.</p>
<p>What is the issue that you hope to resolve?</p>
<p>Trading, be it in securities, currencies, or digital assets, has always been a time-consuming and effort-driven process as the user is not only required to be aware of the trading complexities and risks but also has to keep themselves updated on a multitude of information that can affect the value of the underlying asset. With so much volatility across markets and new forms of assets introduced every odd day, it becomes difficult, even for experienced traders, to cope and leverage it to their benefit. Arbitration is a method used for decades, where a trader purchases an asset on one exchange and simultaneously sells the same on another, using the difference to their advantage in ideally a low-risk environment. Although this trading method has almost entirely diminished, mainly due to the advanced synchronization of data among various exchanges, it still offers a significant opportunity within the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We believe that MOSDEX is in a good position to help with these challenges going forward, allowing investors to optimize their profitability.&rdquo; Said Mr. Emmet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With trust in seemingly centralized platforms at an all-time low, how have you been able to navigate the market?</p>

<p>&ldquo;We do understand that the market has uncertainties around centralized platforms, especially exchanges. However, MOSDEX isn&rsquo;t an exchange or a marketplace. Its parent company is a Finnish-based tech firm that deals in finance, fintech, and trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Essentially MOSDEX is a platform that runs by an algorithm. There is no centralized authority that dictates what funds are used for, so investors can trust that their money is safe.&rdquo; Continued Mr. Emmett.&nbsp;</p>

<p>What are the pitfalls you see in the crypto trading market, and how do you think they can be resolved?</p>
<p>Crypto is still very much in its infancy. And as we all know, this has led to challenges on the regulatory front and a lack of information transfer between crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We believe that the key to solving these challenges will be to introduce a stronger regulatory regime into the market that will help to lay down laws guiding the operation of cryptocurrencies and players within the space. And as the market continues to mature, the prospects of this happening continue to grow. &nbsp;</p>
<p>In traditional crypto trading, traders are wary of volatility as it can often affect their trades in diverse ways. How does Mosdex tackle volatility?</p>
<p>The crypto market is growing rapidly, with different innovations coming in and projects looking to take the industry to the next level. All of this has led to massive volatility, as investors themselves have different opportunities to profit.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Of course, volatility is still a part of the crypto market entirely. At MOSDEX, we simply want to provide an avenue for investors to embrace and harness this volatility for their own good.&rdquo; Said the CEO, Mr. Emmett.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Visit the official Twitter and Telegram for more information and regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>t&rsquo;s no secret that 2022 wasn&rsquo;t necessarily the best for anyone in the fledgling crypto space. After multiple platform collapses and with pressure mounting from the traditional economy, cryptocurrency prices cratered, with investors suffering losses. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Nevertheless, crypto is far from dead. In fact, the bear market of 2022 is giving more investors renewed hope of a coming bull cycle, and many are looking to prepare themselves for what is coming. Just as well, investors were still able to optimize returns in the market via arbitrage, a smart yet unrealized way to earn passive income using cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We conducted a session with Mr. Joseph Emmett, the CEO of Mosdex.com who discussed the current crypto market scenario and how Mosdex stands out as a potential arbitrage staking platform for offering recurring passive income.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrage - Beneficial for Everyone</p>
<p>The concept of arbitrage is simple: you look for the difference in the price of a certain asset, e.g., Bitcoin on different exchanges and capitalize on that to your advantage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For example, the price of BTC on a certain exchange can be $20,850, while the same asset could trade at $20,790 on a separate exchange. As seen, there is a difference of $60, which can be capitalized if trades are performed quickly. This activity of buying low on one exchange and selling high on the other is called arbitrage.</p>
<p>Of course, it is worth noting that the price of cryptocurrencies on exchanges fluctuates based on their levels of demand and supply. So, while exchanges do their bets to track market prices across other platforms, their demand and supply levels will be the ones to essentially determine where coins trade at the end of the day.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Over the years, there have been many traders who have mastered the act of moving assets on exchanges quickly, thus taking advantage of the arbitrage opportunities on these platforms. And as the crypto market has evolved, so have the arbitrage opportunities available to investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Then, there is cryptocurrency staking - the act of locking up coins on a specific exchange in order to support it. Staking was made popular thanks to the evolution of blockchains, which used to validate transactions using the mining consensus algorithm. With staking, investors can simply lock their coins up, and network validators continue to verify transactions on the network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Combine these two concepts together, and you have arbitrage staking - a way for cryptocurrency investors to lock their assets on a platform, and these tokens get used for trading by a bot or a trading engine.&nbsp; In return, investors earn returns that are paid out periodically to crypto stakers - and still get returns from their trading activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrage Staking, an innovative way to stake and earn</p>
<p>Arbitrage-based staking is great because it allows community members to participate without actively doing anything while also providing a launchpad for them to enjoy significant gains.</p>
<p>With investors looking for new passive income opportunities, MOSDEX, a highly efficient arbitrage platform, presents its automated arbitrage staking that combines AI and Defi to bring the best for its users. Joseph Emmet, the chief executive at MOSDEX, recently sat down for an interview where he spoke about his company and the objective they are trying to reach.</p>
<p>What is the issue that you hope to resolve?</p>
<p>Trading, be it in securities, currencies, or digital assets, has always been a time-consuming and effort-driven process as the user is not only required to be aware of the trading complexities and risks but also has to keep themselves updated on a multitude of information that can affect the value of the underlying asset. With so much volatility across markets and new forms of assets introduced every odd day, it becomes difficult, even for experienced traders, to cope and leverage it to their benefit. Arbitration is a method used for decades, where a trader purchases an asset on one exchange and simultaneously sells the same on another, using the difference to their advantage in ideally a low-risk environment. Although this trading method has almost entirely diminished, mainly due to the advanced synchronization of data among various exchanges, it still offers a significant opportunity within the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We believe that MOSDEX is in a good position to help with these challenges going forward, allowing investors to optimize their profitability.&rdquo; Said Mr. Emmet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With trust in seemingly centralized platforms at an all-time low, how have you been able to navigate the market?</p>

<p>&ldquo;We do understand that the market has uncertainties around centralized platforms, especially exchanges. However, MOSDEX isn&rsquo;t an exchange or a marketplace. Its parent company is a Finnish-based tech firm that deals in finance, fintech, and trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Essentially MOSDEX is a platform that runs by an algorithm. There is no centralized authority that dictates what funds are used for, so investors can trust that their money is safe.&rdquo; Continued Mr. Emmett.&nbsp;</p>

<p>What are the pitfalls you see in the crypto trading market, and how do you think they can be resolved?</p>
<p>Crypto is still very much in its infancy. And as we all know, this has led to challenges on the regulatory front and a lack of information transfer between crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We believe that the key to solving these challenges will be to introduce a stronger regulatory regime into the market that will help to lay down laws guiding the operation of cryptocurrencies and players within the space. And as the market continues to mature, the prospects of this happening continue to grow. &nbsp;</p>
<p>In traditional crypto trading, traders are wary of volatility as it can often affect their trades in diverse ways. How does Mosdex tackle volatility?</p>
<p>The crypto market is growing rapidly, with different innovations coming in and projects looking to take the industry to the next level. All of this has led to massive volatility, as investors themselves have different opportunities to profit.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Of course, volatility is still a part of the crypto market entirely. At MOSDEX, we simply want to provide an avenue for investors to embrace and harness this volatility for their own good.&rdquo; Said the CEO, Mr. Emmett.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Visit the official Twitter and Telegram for more information and regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[El Salvador Bitcoin City design wins prestigious prize]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/el-salvador-bitcoin-city-design-wins-prestigious-prize</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bc.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bc.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bc.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/el-salvador-bitcoin-city-design-wins-prestigious-prize</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>When and if El Salvador builds its Bitcoin City, it has the potential&nbsp; to be truly stunning. Design wins top architectural prize.</p>
<p>The doom mongers for El Salvador and its pro-Bitcoin President Nayib Bukele are basing their gloomy predictions on the king of the cryptocurrencies going to zero.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, should Bitcoin do what it has been doing for the last 14 years of its existence and now begin a new bull market surge upwards, then El Salvador stands to benefit greatly.</p>
<p>In anticipation of exactly this, President Bukele is fully committed to his grandiose plan to build a Bitcoin City that will attract investment wealth from across the globe, and enrich his country and citizens.</p>
<p></p>
<p>source: LOOP Design Awards</p>
<p>The design of the proposed Bitcoin City has been undertaken by Mexican Fernando Romero and his company Enterprise Free, and the design they have come up with has already triumphed in the prestigious LOOP Design Awards in the category of Landscape/Urban Design.</p>
<p>According to the description of the project on the LOOP Design Awards website, the city will be built in the east of the country, and it will benefit from having connections to a new airport and seaport.</p>
<p></p>
<p>source: LOOP Design Awards</p>
<p>Sustainability will be achieved by the city generating its own energy from the volcano at its perimeter. Foreign investment will be welcomed, and it is imagined that cryptocurrency miners and technology companies will be among the businesses that will come to the city.</p>
<p>The citizen will be the centre of focus for the city and will have everything he or she needs to have a comfortable place to live and work.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The new public space will be the culmination of decades of research on what humans need to live well in an anti-inflationary economy.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Should Bukele&rsquo;s dream live on and Bitcoin City become a reality, then the tiny Central American country of El Salvador could become wealthy beyond measure. Obviously Bitcoin would need to fulfil its potential as well, but that outcome is still hidden in the future.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When and if El Salvador builds its Bitcoin City, it has the potential&nbsp; to be truly stunning. Design wins top architectural prize.</p>
<p>The doom mongers for El Salvador and its pro-Bitcoin President Nayib Bukele are basing their gloomy predictions on the king of the cryptocurrencies going to zero.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, should Bitcoin do what it has been doing for the last 14 years of its existence and now begin a new bull market surge upwards, then El Salvador stands to benefit greatly.</p>
<p>In anticipation of exactly this, President Bukele is fully committed to his grandiose plan to build a Bitcoin City that will attract investment wealth from across the globe, and enrich his country and citizens.</p>
<p></p>
<p>source: LOOP Design Awards</p>
<p>The design of the proposed Bitcoin City has been undertaken by Mexican Fernando Romero and his company Enterprise Free, and the design they have come up with has already triumphed in the prestigious LOOP Design Awards in the category of Landscape/Urban Design.</p>
<p>According to the description of the project on the LOOP Design Awards website, the city will be built in the east of the country, and it will benefit from having connections to a new airport and seaport.</p>
<p></p>
<p>source: LOOP Design Awards</p>
<p>Sustainability will be achieved by the city generating its own energy from the volcano at its perimeter. Foreign investment will be welcomed, and it is imagined that cryptocurrency miners and technology companies will be among the businesses that will come to the city.</p>
<p>The citizen will be the centre of focus for the city and will have everything he or she needs to have a comfortable place to live and work.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The new public space will be the culmination of decades of research on what humans need to live well in an anti-inflationary economy.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Should Bukele&rsquo;s dream live on and Bitcoin City become a reality, then the tiny Central American country of El Salvador could become wealthy beyond measure. Obviously Bitcoin would need to fulfil its potential as well, but that outcome is still hidden in the future.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Arizona Senator Introduces Bill to Make Bitcoin Legal Tender]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/arizona-senator-introduces-bill-to-make-bitcoin-legal-tender</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/arizona-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/arizona-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/arizona-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/arizona-senator-introduces-bill-to-make-bitcoin-legal-tender</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>State Senator Wendy Rogers of Arizona introduced two bills to make Bitcoin legal tender in the state and allow state agencies to accept Bitcoin. </p>
<p>Sen. Wendy Rogers (R-AZ) introduced a set of bills to make bitcoin legal tender in Arizona and one that would allow state agencies in Arizona to accept Bitcoin. The bill to make Bitcoin legal tender in the state aims to have Bitcoin recognized as a legal form of currency in Arizona, meaning that individuals and entities may use it to pay debts, taxes, and further financial obligations. Essentially, this means that all transactions currently conducted in U.S. dollars could be done in Bitcoin and would afford businesses and individuals the option to use the currency as they see fit.</p>
Rogers Introduces Two Bills That Would Allow the Use of Bitcoin in Arizona
<p>The bill regarding Bitcoin as legal tender specifically mentions Bitcoin alone and defines it as:</p>

<p>The decentralized, peer-to-peer digital currency in which a record of transactions is maintained on the Bitcoin blockchain and new units of currency are generated by the computational solution of mathematical problems, and that operates independently of a central bank.</p>

<p>The second bill, which involves state acceptance, appears to be broader and does not mention only Bitcoin as a currency that state agencies could accept but refers to &ldquo;cryptocurrencies.&rdquo; The bill states:</p>

<p>A state agency may enter into an agreement with a cryptocurrency issuer to provide a method to accept cryptocurrency as a payment method for fines, civil penalties or other penalties, rent, rates, taxes, fees, charges, revenue, financial obligations, and special assessments to pay any amount due to that agency or this state.</p>

Rogers Continues to Push for the Acceptance of Bitcoin
<p>Senator Rogers previously introduced a bill proposing making Bitcoin legal tender in Arizona. The bill, introduced in January 2022, did not come to fruition. Rogers, fellow senators Sonny Borelli, and Justine Wadsack recently introduced new legislation that allows voters to decide in 2024 if virtual currencies should be classed as tax-exempt property. As it stands in Arizona, all public debts, certain household goods, and all federal, state, county, and municipal property are tax-exempt.</p>
<p>According to reports by Market Watch, Roger&rsquo;s tax bill defines virtual currencies as tokens that do not represent the U.S. dollar or a foreign currency and is not Arizona&rsquo;s first bill that pertains to crypto taxes. In 2018, a bill was proposed that would give Arizona residents the option to pay taxes using cryptocurrencies, but it was ultimately vetoed in May 2018.</p>
<p>&nbsp;Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>State Senator Wendy Rogers of Arizona introduced two bills to make Bitcoin legal tender in the state and allow state agencies to accept Bitcoin. </p>
<p>Sen. Wendy Rogers (R-AZ) introduced a set of bills to make bitcoin legal tender in Arizona and one that would allow state agencies in Arizona to accept Bitcoin. The bill to make Bitcoin legal tender in the state aims to have Bitcoin recognized as a legal form of currency in Arizona, meaning that individuals and entities may use it to pay debts, taxes, and further financial obligations. Essentially, this means that all transactions currently conducted in U.S. dollars could be done in Bitcoin and would afford businesses and individuals the option to use the currency as they see fit.</p>
Rogers Introduces Two Bills That Would Allow the Use of Bitcoin in Arizona
<p>The bill regarding Bitcoin as legal tender specifically mentions Bitcoin alone and defines it as:</p>

<p>The decentralized, peer-to-peer digital currency in which a record of transactions is maintained on the Bitcoin blockchain and new units of currency are generated by the computational solution of mathematical problems, and that operates independently of a central bank.</p>

<p>The second bill, which involves state acceptance, appears to be broader and does not mention only Bitcoin as a currency that state agencies could accept but refers to &ldquo;cryptocurrencies.&rdquo; The bill states:</p>

<p>A state agency may enter into an agreement with a cryptocurrency issuer to provide a method to accept cryptocurrency as a payment method for fines, civil penalties or other penalties, rent, rates, taxes, fees, charges, revenue, financial obligations, and special assessments to pay any amount due to that agency or this state.</p>

Rogers Continues to Push for the Acceptance of Bitcoin
<p>Senator Rogers previously introduced a bill proposing making Bitcoin legal tender in Arizona. The bill, introduced in January 2022, did not come to fruition. Rogers, fellow senators Sonny Borelli, and Justine Wadsack recently introduced new legislation that allows voters to decide in 2024 if virtual currencies should be classed as tax-exempt property. As it stands in Arizona, all public debts, certain household goods, and all federal, state, county, and municipal property are tax-exempt.</p>
<p>According to reports by Market Watch, Roger&rsquo;s tax bill defines virtual currencies as tokens that do not represent the U.S. dollar or a foreign currency and is not Arizona&rsquo;s first bill that pertains to crypto taxes. In 2018, a bill was proposed that would give Arizona residents the option to pay taxes using cryptocurrencies, but it was ultimately vetoed in May 2018.</p>
<p>&nbsp;Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tesla Hodling Its Bitcoin Despite Market Upheaval]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/tesla-hodling-its-bitcoin-despite-the-market-upheaval</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tesla-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tesla-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tesla-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/tesla-hodling-its-bitcoin-despite-the-market-upheaval</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to the company&rsquo;s latest earning report, electric carmaker Tesla has continued to hold on to its estimated 9720 BTC for a second straight quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The company has steadfastly refused to sell its remaining Bitcoin during the latter half of 2022, despite selling off 75% of its holdings during the second quarter.&nbsp;</p>
No Plans To Sell&nbsp;
<p>Electric vehicle manufacturer Tesla has reportedly refused to offload any Bitcoin during the latter half of 2022. This means that the company has not bought or sold any BTC for the second straight quarter, the company reported in its earnings report. This was despite the recent crypto market upheaval following the collapse of the FTX exchange. The move comes after the company had sold 75% of its holdings during the second quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the report, the company held $184 million in Bitcoin as of 31st December 2022, which was down from $218 million in holdings from the previous quarter. However, this was not due to a selloff but rather due to impairment charges, thanks to a decline in the price of Bitcoin. At the end of the third quarter, the price of Bitcoin was hovering at around $20,000, while at the end of the fourth quarter, the price had dropped to around $16,500.&nbsp;</p>
Massive Selloff In Second Quarter&nbsp;
<p>Tesla also revealed that it had made no changes to its Bitcoin holdings during the third quarter. However, the company surprised many investors during the second quarter when it sold around $936 million worth of BTC, which accounted for nearly 75% of its Bitcoin holdings. At the time, the company stated that the move was to raise cash due to the uncertainty created by the Covid-19 lockdown in China.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, CEO Elon Musk also stated that the company was open to increasing its Bitcoin exposure in the future, and the sale should not be looked at as a judgment on the viability of Bitcoin as an asset. He further explained that the sale also proved the liquidity of Bitcoin as an alternative to holding cash on the company&rsquo;s balance sheet. The move allowed Tesla to realize a profit of around $64 million.&nbsp;</p>
A Profitable Quarter&nbsp;
<p>The company&rsquo;s most recent earnings call did not feature any discussion of its Bitcoin holdings or its position on Bitcoin. The quarter proved quite profitable for Tesla, with the company recording $5.7 billion in profits and generating a revenue of around $24.3 billion for Q4, with the company&rsquo;s gross margins at their lowest levels in the past five quarters. The company posted an annual profit of $12.6 billion in 2022. While the figure missed analyst estimates, its profit margin was better than expected.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;In 2022, we produced &amp; delivered 1.3M+ vehicles in Q4. We achieved our highest-ever quarterly revenue, operating income &amp; net income.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The company&rsquo;s share price pushed up slightly following the report and has continued to trade in the green, up nearly 5%.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to the company&rsquo;s latest earning report, electric carmaker Tesla has continued to hold on to its estimated 9720 BTC for a second straight quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The company has steadfastly refused to sell its remaining Bitcoin during the latter half of 2022, despite selling off 75% of its holdings during the second quarter.&nbsp;</p>
No Plans To Sell&nbsp;
<p>Electric vehicle manufacturer Tesla has reportedly refused to offload any Bitcoin during the latter half of 2022. This means that the company has not bought or sold any BTC for the second straight quarter, the company reported in its earnings report. This was despite the recent crypto market upheaval following the collapse of the FTX exchange. The move comes after the company had sold 75% of its holdings during the second quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the report, the company held $184 million in Bitcoin as of 31st December 2022, which was down from $218 million in holdings from the previous quarter. However, this was not due to a selloff but rather due to impairment charges, thanks to a decline in the price of Bitcoin. At the end of the third quarter, the price of Bitcoin was hovering at around $20,000, while at the end of the fourth quarter, the price had dropped to around $16,500.&nbsp;</p>
Massive Selloff In Second Quarter&nbsp;
<p>Tesla also revealed that it had made no changes to its Bitcoin holdings during the third quarter. However, the company surprised many investors during the second quarter when it sold around $936 million worth of BTC, which accounted for nearly 75% of its Bitcoin holdings. At the time, the company stated that the move was to raise cash due to the uncertainty created by the Covid-19 lockdown in China.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, CEO Elon Musk also stated that the company was open to increasing its Bitcoin exposure in the future, and the sale should not be looked at as a judgment on the viability of Bitcoin as an asset. He further explained that the sale also proved the liquidity of Bitcoin as an alternative to holding cash on the company&rsquo;s balance sheet. The move allowed Tesla to realize a profit of around $64 million.&nbsp;</p>
A Profitable Quarter&nbsp;
<p>The company&rsquo;s most recent earnings call did not feature any discussion of its Bitcoin holdings or its position on Bitcoin. The quarter proved quite profitable for Tesla, with the company recording $5.7 billion in profits and generating a revenue of around $24.3 billion for Q4, with the company&rsquo;s gross margins at their lowest levels in the past five quarters. The company posted an annual profit of $12.6 billion in 2022. While the figure missed analyst estimates, its profit margin was better than expected.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;In 2022, we produced &amp; delivered 1.3M+ vehicles in Q4. We achieved our highest-ever quarterly revenue, operating income &amp; net income.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The company&rsquo;s share price pushed up slightly following the report and has continued to trade in the green, up nearly 5%.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Moonbirds Creator Loses $1 Million In NFTs After Wallet Exploit]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/moonbirds-creator-loses-1-million-in-nfts-after-wallet-exploit</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/moonbirds-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/moonbirds-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/moonbirds-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/moonbirds-creator-loses-1-million-in-nfts-after-wallet-exploit</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The creator of the Moonbirds NFT collection, Kevin Rose, has lost around $1 million in NFTs after falling victim to a wallet exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Rose lost a number of NFTs, including 25 Chronie Squiggles and an Autoglyph NFT. The hack was confirmed by Rose himself on his Twitter account.&nbsp;</p>
A Million Dollar Loss&nbsp;
<p>Kevin Rose, the co-founder of the Moonbirds NFT collection, has fallen victim to a phishing scam, losing over $1.1 million worth of NFTs from his personal collection. Rose confirmed the hack on his Twitter handle, and a glance at the transaction history for Rose&rsquo;s wallet on OpenSea reveals the extent of the hack. Rose lost several NFTs, such as OnChainMonkeys, Squiggles, and Cool Cats. Rose stated on Twitter,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I was just hacked; stay tuned for details - please avoid buying any squiggles until we get them flagged (just lost 25) + a few other NFTs (an autoglyph).&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, Rose was able to save his most valuable NFTs by keeping them in a separate vault. These NFTs include a Zombie CryptoPunk (CryptoPunk #5066), of which there are only 87 other NFTs. Users speculated that the wallet in question was compromised because Rose signed a malicious seaport bundle. A seaport bundle allows users to trade multiple assets for other items of the same value. Rose, on his part, urged users to avoid purchasing Squiggle NFTs while his team worked on getting them flagged as stolen.&nbsp;</p>
Details Of The Hack&nbsp;
<p>Details about how the hack took place soon emerged. It was revealed that the hack most likely took place after he approved a malicious signature, enabling the attacker to transfer a significant number of Rose&rsquo;s NFTs out of the wallet. An analysis of the hack revealed that the attacker managed to siphon off at least one Autoglyph, which has a floor price of 345 ETH, Chromie Squiggles, which were worth around 332.5 ETH, and nine OnChainMonkey items, worth around 7.2 ETH.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The vice president of PROOF, the entity behind the Moonbirds collection, Arran Schlosberg, elaborated on the hack on Twitter, revealing that Rose was the victim of a phishing exploit that tricked him into signing a malicious signature and allowed the attacker to steal the NFTs in question.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Earlier this evening, @kevinrose was phished into signing a malicious signature that allowed the hacker to transfer a large number of high-value tokens. Here is a breakdown of what happened, our immediate response, and our ongoing efforts. This was a classic piece of social engineering, tricking KRO into a false sense of security. The technical aspect of the hack was limited to crafting signatures accepted by OpenSea&rsquo;s marketplace contract.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Crypto analyst foobar explained that Rose had approved an OpenSea marketplace contract to move all of his NFTs whenever he signed transactions, stating that Rose was always one malicious signature away from disaster. The analyst added that Rose should have siloed his assets in a separate wallet.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Moving assets from your vault to a separate &lsquo;selling&rsquo; wallet before listing on NFT marketplaces will prevent this.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The malicious signature was enabled by the seaport marketplace contract, which, while a powerful tool, is also dangerous if users are not aware of how it works.&nbsp;</p>
Stolen Assets On The Move
<p>Foobar also revealed that the stolen assets were valued well above their floor price, which means that the loss could be considerably greater. On-chain crypto analyst ZachXBT tracked the stolen assets, revealing that the exploiter sent the assets to FixedFloat, an exchange on the Bitcoin Lightning Network. The funds were then swapped into BTC and deposited into a Bitcoin mixer.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Three hours ago, Kevin was phished for $1.4m+ worth of NFTs. Earlier today, the same scammer stole 75 ETH from another victim. Mapping this out, we can see a clear trend of sending the stolen funds to FixedFloat and swapping for BTC before depositing to a bitcoin mixer.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Bankless Founder Ryan Sean Adams pointed out the ease with which Rose was exploited and urged front-end engineers to improve user experience.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The creator of the Moonbirds NFT collection, Kevin Rose, has lost around $1 million in NFTs after falling victim to a wallet exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Rose lost a number of NFTs, including 25 Chronie Squiggles and an Autoglyph NFT. The hack was confirmed by Rose himself on his Twitter account.&nbsp;</p>
A Million Dollar Loss&nbsp;
<p>Kevin Rose, the co-founder of the Moonbirds NFT collection, has fallen victim to a phishing scam, losing over $1.1 million worth of NFTs from his personal collection. Rose confirmed the hack on his Twitter handle, and a glance at the transaction history for Rose&rsquo;s wallet on OpenSea reveals the extent of the hack. Rose lost several NFTs, such as OnChainMonkeys, Squiggles, and Cool Cats. Rose stated on Twitter,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I was just hacked; stay tuned for details - please avoid buying any squiggles until we get them flagged (just lost 25) + a few other NFTs (an autoglyph).&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, Rose was able to save his most valuable NFTs by keeping them in a separate vault. These NFTs include a Zombie CryptoPunk (CryptoPunk #5066), of which there are only 87 other NFTs. Users speculated that the wallet in question was compromised because Rose signed a malicious seaport bundle. A seaport bundle allows users to trade multiple assets for other items of the same value. Rose, on his part, urged users to avoid purchasing Squiggle NFTs while his team worked on getting them flagged as stolen.&nbsp;</p>
Details Of The Hack&nbsp;
<p>Details about how the hack took place soon emerged. It was revealed that the hack most likely took place after he approved a malicious signature, enabling the attacker to transfer a significant number of Rose&rsquo;s NFTs out of the wallet. An analysis of the hack revealed that the attacker managed to siphon off at least one Autoglyph, which has a floor price of 345 ETH, Chromie Squiggles, which were worth around 332.5 ETH, and nine OnChainMonkey items, worth around 7.2 ETH.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The vice president of PROOF, the entity behind the Moonbirds collection, Arran Schlosberg, elaborated on the hack on Twitter, revealing that Rose was the victim of a phishing exploit that tricked him into signing a malicious signature and allowed the attacker to steal the NFTs in question.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Earlier this evening, @kevinrose was phished into signing a malicious signature that allowed the hacker to transfer a large number of high-value tokens. Here is a breakdown of what happened, our immediate response, and our ongoing efforts. This was a classic piece of social engineering, tricking KRO into a false sense of security. The technical aspect of the hack was limited to crafting signatures accepted by OpenSea&rsquo;s marketplace contract.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Crypto analyst foobar explained that Rose had approved an OpenSea marketplace contract to move all of his NFTs whenever he signed transactions, stating that Rose was always one malicious signature away from disaster. The analyst added that Rose should have siloed his assets in a separate wallet.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Moving assets from your vault to a separate &lsquo;selling&rsquo; wallet before listing on NFT marketplaces will prevent this.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The malicious signature was enabled by the seaport marketplace contract, which, while a powerful tool, is also dangerous if users are not aware of how it works.&nbsp;</p>
Stolen Assets On The Move
<p>Foobar also revealed that the stolen assets were valued well above their floor price, which means that the loss could be considerably greater. On-chain crypto analyst ZachXBT tracked the stolen assets, revealing that the exploiter sent the assets to FixedFloat, an exchange on the Bitcoin Lightning Network. The funds were then swapped into BTC and deposited into a Bitcoin mixer.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Three hours ago, Kevin was phished for $1.4m+ worth of NFTs. Earlier today, the same scammer stole 75 ETH from another victim. Mapping this out, we can see a clear trend of sending the stolen funds to FixedFloat and swapping for BTC before depositing to a bitcoin mixer.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Bankless Founder Ryan Sean Adams pointed out the ease with which Rose was exploited and urged front-end engineers to improve user experience.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Secret BlockFi Financials Reveal $1.2 Billion Exposure to FTX]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/secret-blockfi-financials-reveal-12-billion-exposure-to-ftx</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/secret-blockfi-financials-reveal-12-billion-exposure-to-ftx</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency lender BlockFi accidentally revealed a previously redacted copy of its balance sheet indicating that it had over $1.2 billion in assets tied to FTX and Alameda Research. </p>
<p>BlockFi, which filed for bankruptcy in November citing massive exposure to FTX, accidentally revealed secret financial documents relating to its association with FTX and Alameda Research, according to reports by CNBC. According to one of the filings, the redacted sections include &ldquo;trade secret[s] or confidential research, development, or commercial information.&rdquo; The previously redacted financials show that BlockFi has a relationship with Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s crypto empire worth $1.2 billion, far more significant than previous disclosures indicated.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The unredacted filings show that as of January 14, BlockFi has assets linked to FTX worth $415.9 million and loans to Alameda worth $831.3 million. BlockFi&rsquo;s legal representatives previously disclosed that the firm had $355 million in digital assets tied to FTX and loans worth $671 million to Alameda.</p>
<p>The former censored version of the financials leaked during a presentation by M3 Partners &ndash; an advisor to the creditor committee who admitted that uploading the unredacted filings was done erroneously. The redacted financial declarations released on November 24 relate to the creditor committee&rsquo;s objection against BlockFi&rsquo;s wishes to pay its key employees $12.3 million in retention incentives despite the firm&rsquo;s limited operations and assets.</p>
BlockFi&rsquo;s Entanglement with FTX
<p>When the details surrounding FTX came to light, and the firm declared bankruptcy, BlockFi attempted to separate itself from FTX and Alameda Research. A separation has proven difficult as the financial entanglement between BlockFi and FTX is complicated.</p>
<p>BlockFi became financially involved with FTX in June 2022 when FTX agreed to extend BlockFi a credit line of $400 million. The credit line, however, gave FTX the option to purchase BlockFi. BlockFi had to extend its credit line about a week after the firm cut its staff by around 20% due to &ldquo;the dramatic shift in macroeconomic conditions worldwide.&rdquo; After only a few days of FTX&rsquo;s collapse, BlockFi suspended withdrawals, admitting it had &ldquo;significant exposure&rdquo; to FTX, including undrawn amounts from the credit line and assets held on the FTX platform.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency lender BlockFi accidentally revealed a previously redacted copy of its balance sheet indicating that it had over $1.2 billion in assets tied to FTX and Alameda Research. </p>
<p>BlockFi, which filed for bankruptcy in November citing massive exposure to FTX, accidentally revealed secret financial documents relating to its association with FTX and Alameda Research, according to reports by CNBC. According to one of the filings, the redacted sections include &ldquo;trade secret[s] or confidential research, development, or commercial information.&rdquo; The previously redacted financials show that BlockFi has a relationship with Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s crypto empire worth $1.2 billion, far more significant than previous disclosures indicated.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The unredacted filings show that as of January 14, BlockFi has assets linked to FTX worth $415.9 million and loans to Alameda worth $831.3 million. BlockFi&rsquo;s legal representatives previously disclosed that the firm had $355 million in digital assets tied to FTX and loans worth $671 million to Alameda.</p>
<p>The former censored version of the financials leaked during a presentation by M3 Partners &ndash; an advisor to the creditor committee who admitted that uploading the unredacted filings was done erroneously. The redacted financial declarations released on November 24 relate to the creditor committee&rsquo;s objection against BlockFi&rsquo;s wishes to pay its key employees $12.3 million in retention incentives despite the firm&rsquo;s limited operations and assets.</p>
BlockFi&rsquo;s Entanglement with FTX
<p>When the details surrounding FTX came to light, and the firm declared bankruptcy, BlockFi attempted to separate itself from FTX and Alameda Research. A separation has proven difficult as the financial entanglement between BlockFi and FTX is complicated.</p>
<p>BlockFi became financially involved with FTX in June 2022 when FTX agreed to extend BlockFi a credit line of $400 million. The credit line, however, gave FTX the option to purchase BlockFi. BlockFi had to extend its credit line about a week after the firm cut its staff by around 20% due to &ldquo;the dramatic shift in macroeconomic conditions worldwide.&rdquo; After only a few days of FTX&rsquo;s collapse, BlockFi suspended withdrawals, admitting it had &ldquo;significant exposure&rdquo; to FTX, including undrawn amounts from the credit line and assets held on the FTX platform.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[MakerDAO Community Plans To Deposit $100 Million In Yearn Finance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/makerdao-community-plans-to-deposit-100-million-in-yearn-finance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/maker-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/maker-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/maker-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/makerdao-community-plans-to-deposit-100-million-in-yearn-finance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The MakerDAO community has approved a proposal to deploy around $100 million worth of USDC into Yearn Finance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The decision to deposit the funds on Yearn Finance will allow MakerDAO to earn an annual yield of around 2% on the stablecoin deposits.&nbsp;</p>
MakerDAO To Deposit $100 Million On Yearn&nbsp;
<p>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol MakerDAO&rsquo;s community has approved a proposal to deploy $100 million in USD Coin (USDC) on the DeFi protocol Yearn Finance. The funds will be deposited in a special investment account called a &ldquo;vault,&rdquo; which is managed by Yearn Finance. The vault&rsquo;s ceiling will be set at $100 million and will allow MakerDAO to earn a yield of around 2% per year, totaling around $2 million on an annual basis.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Maker Governance voted to deploy 100 million USDC from the PSM into a bespoke @iearnfinance on-chain vault.&rdquo;</p>

Strong Support For Proposal&nbsp;
<p>The proposal to deposit the funds on Yearn was submitted in November 2022 and has found strong support within the Maker community. Around 72% of members voted in favor of the plan. The final implementation and the transfer of funds will require a further &ldquo;executive vote,&rdquo; according to the information shared by MakerDAO.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Talk of a partnership between MakerDAO and Yearn Finance was first suggested by Yearn Finance in November 2022. However, the partnership still requires a final approval through an executive vote. The executive vote is the final step in the MakerDAO governance process and is primarily used when implementing a technical change to the Maker Protocol.&nbsp;</p>
In Line With Long Term Vision&nbsp;
<p>MakerDAO&rsquo;s move to deposit funds on Yearn Finance is in line with the protocol&rsquo;s vision of earning a steady revenue stream by the allocation of a part of its reserve assets to several yield-generating strategies such as investing in US government bonds and partnering with cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase. Under the partnership with Coinbase, Coinbase proposed that MakerDAO deposit around $1.6 billion worth of USD Coin (USDC) on the platform, allowing the latter to earn an annual yield of 1.5% per year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>MakerDAO has also allocated USDC on a number of other decentralized finance platforms, including Idle Finance, Aave, and Compound. Additionally, DAI stablecoin holders have also received an annual reward of 1% since last month. MakerDAO is a platform managed by a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), with holders of the MKR token being able to vote on governance proposals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move to deposit USDC on Yearn could also improve the protocol&rsquo;s dwindling user activity. Yearn Finance&rsquo;s total value locked (TVL) is currently at around $442 million. This is a small fraction compared to the protocol&rsquo;s all-time high TVL of $6.9 billion, which was reached in December 2021, according to data sourced from DeFiLlama. The total value locked is an indicator of the worth of the assets deployed on a protocol.&nbsp;</p>
An Active Community&nbsp;
<p>The MakerDAO community has been quite active when it comes to governance proposals and recently voted on two important proposals related to Alameda Research and Gemini&rsquo;s GUSD stablecoin. In November 2022, the protocol announced that the community had voted on and passed a governance vote to remove the Alameda Research-linked RenBTC from its collateral vaults. The move was made to reduce the exposure to what the DAO deemed a risky asset following the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The MakerDAO community is also debating about keeping Gemini&rsquo;s GUSD stablecoin as part of the reserves. The vote comes amidst growing concerns about a liquidity crisis that has impacted Gemini&rsquo;s Earn program. Maker and Gemini had announced a partnership in September 2022, which allows Maker to earn 1.5% whenever the GUSD in Makers Peg Stability Module (PSM) goes above $100 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The MakerDAO community has approved a proposal to deploy around $100 million worth of USDC into Yearn Finance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The decision to deposit the funds on Yearn Finance will allow MakerDAO to earn an annual yield of around 2% on the stablecoin deposits.&nbsp;</p>
MakerDAO To Deposit $100 Million On Yearn&nbsp;
<p>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol MakerDAO&rsquo;s community has approved a proposal to deploy $100 million in USD Coin (USDC) on the DeFi protocol Yearn Finance. The funds will be deposited in a special investment account called a &ldquo;vault,&rdquo; which is managed by Yearn Finance. The vault&rsquo;s ceiling will be set at $100 million and will allow MakerDAO to earn a yield of around 2% per year, totaling around $2 million on an annual basis.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Maker Governance voted to deploy 100 million USDC from the PSM into a bespoke @iearnfinance on-chain vault.&rdquo;</p>

Strong Support For Proposal&nbsp;
<p>The proposal to deposit the funds on Yearn was submitted in November 2022 and has found strong support within the Maker community. Around 72% of members voted in favor of the plan. The final implementation and the transfer of funds will require a further &ldquo;executive vote,&rdquo; according to the information shared by MakerDAO.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Talk of a partnership between MakerDAO and Yearn Finance was first suggested by Yearn Finance in November 2022. However, the partnership still requires a final approval through an executive vote. The executive vote is the final step in the MakerDAO governance process and is primarily used when implementing a technical change to the Maker Protocol.&nbsp;</p>
In Line With Long Term Vision&nbsp;
<p>MakerDAO&rsquo;s move to deposit funds on Yearn Finance is in line with the protocol&rsquo;s vision of earning a steady revenue stream by the allocation of a part of its reserve assets to several yield-generating strategies such as investing in US government bonds and partnering with cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase. Under the partnership with Coinbase, Coinbase proposed that MakerDAO deposit around $1.6 billion worth of USD Coin (USDC) on the platform, allowing the latter to earn an annual yield of 1.5% per year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>MakerDAO has also allocated USDC on a number of other decentralized finance platforms, including Idle Finance, Aave, and Compound. Additionally, DAI stablecoin holders have also received an annual reward of 1% since last month. MakerDAO is a platform managed by a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO), with holders of the MKR token being able to vote on governance proposals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move to deposit USDC on Yearn could also improve the protocol&rsquo;s dwindling user activity. Yearn Finance&rsquo;s total value locked (TVL) is currently at around $442 million. This is a small fraction compared to the protocol&rsquo;s all-time high TVL of $6.9 billion, which was reached in December 2021, according to data sourced from DeFiLlama. The total value locked is an indicator of the worth of the assets deployed on a protocol.&nbsp;</p>
An Active Community&nbsp;
<p>The MakerDAO community has been quite active when it comes to governance proposals and recently voted on two important proposals related to Alameda Research and Gemini&rsquo;s GUSD stablecoin. In November 2022, the protocol announced that the community had voted on and passed a governance vote to remove the Alameda Research-linked RenBTC from its collateral vaults. The move was made to reduce the exposure to what the DAO deemed a risky asset following the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The MakerDAO community is also debating about keeping Gemini&rsquo;s GUSD stablecoin as part of the reserves. The vote comes amidst growing concerns about a liquidity crisis that has impacted Gemini&rsquo;s Earn program. Maker and Gemini had announced a partnership in September 2022, which allows Maker to earn 1.5% whenever the GUSD in Makers Peg Stability Module (PSM) goes above $100 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[DeFi platform Injective reveals $150 million ecosystem initiative]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/defi-platform-injective-reveals-150-million-ecosystem-initiative</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cos.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cos.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cos.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/defi-platform-injective-reveals-150-million-ecosystem-initiative</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>DeFi smart contracts blockchain platform Injective announces a $150 million ecosystem fund to promote building of interoperable infrastructure and DeFi on Cosmos.</p>
<p>The ecosystem fund announced by Injective a short time ago is designed to support developers who are building on the Cosmos Network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The fund is backed by a consortium of VC and Web3 companies, including Pantera Capital, Kraken Ventures, Jump Crypto, Kucoin Ventures, Delphi Labs, Flow Traders, Gate Labs and IDG Capital.</p>
<p>The members of the consortium will support projects that are building in some key areas of the Cosmos ecosystem, which include, interoperability, DeFi, trading, PoS infrastructure and scalability solutions.</p>
<p>Injective has been drawing eyes over time as it has become one of the most interoperable networks with access to Cosmos IBC enabled chains, as well as Ethereum.</p>
<p>It is a fully decentralised smart contracts platform with a focus on finance applications. Its plug and play modules can be used by developers to build protocols for exchanges, options, derivatives, and lending.</p>
<p>Eric Chen, co-founder and CEO of Injective Labs said:</p>

<p>"We're thrilled to see some of the largest names in the industry joining Injective's mission to create a more democratized financial system through decentralization. Developer activity on Injective is rapidly increasing with major projects and this new ecosystem fund will provide unmatched opportunities for new builders entering Web3 and the Cosmos ecosystem overall."</p>

<p>One of the first uses of the new ecosystem fund is the launch of an &ldquo;Injective Global Virtual Hackathon&rdquo;, which aims to encourage developers from across the world to learn how to build on Injective, but also to submit new proposals for funding.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi smart contracts blockchain platform Injective announces a $150 million ecosystem fund to promote building of interoperable infrastructure and DeFi on Cosmos.</p>
<p>The ecosystem fund announced by Injective a short time ago is designed to support developers who are building on the Cosmos Network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The fund is backed by a consortium of VC and Web3 companies, including Pantera Capital, Kraken Ventures, Jump Crypto, Kucoin Ventures, Delphi Labs, Flow Traders, Gate Labs and IDG Capital.</p>
<p>The members of the consortium will support projects that are building in some key areas of the Cosmos ecosystem, which include, interoperability, DeFi, trading, PoS infrastructure and scalability solutions.</p>
<p>Injective has been drawing eyes over time as it has become one of the most interoperable networks with access to Cosmos IBC enabled chains, as well as Ethereum.</p>
<p>It is a fully decentralised smart contracts platform with a focus on finance applications. Its plug and play modules can be used by developers to build protocols for exchanges, options, derivatives, and lending.</p>
<p>Eric Chen, co-founder and CEO of Injective Labs said:</p>

<p>"We're thrilled to see some of the largest names in the industry joining Injective's mission to create a more democratized financial system through decentralization. Developer activity on Injective is rapidly increasing with major projects and this new ecosystem fund will provide unmatched opportunities for new builders entering Web3 and the Cosmos ecosystem overall."</p>

<p>One of the first uses of the new ecosystem fund is the launch of an &ldquo;Injective Global Virtual Hackathon&rdquo;, which aims to encourage developers from across the world to learn how to build on Injective, but also to submit new proposals for funding.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Given at 23165 - 26 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-at-23165-26-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-25-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-25-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-25-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-at-23165-26-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Awaits Fresh Technical Sentiment:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 26 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair came off to the 22326.24 area after encountering fresh selling pressure around the 23165.36 area, representing a test of the 78.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 23375.60 to 22298.15.&nbsp; The fresh 5-month high also represented a test of the 23300.64 area, an upside price objective related to buying pressure that strengthened around the 20333.33 area.&nbsp; BTC/USD recently appreciated to the 23375.60 area, its strongest print since August 2022.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were elected above the 22042.59 area during the recent appreciation, an upside price objective related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 and 17927.36 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 area include the 23544, 23808, 25455, 25774, 27609, and 28004 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 15460 area include the 23980, 24224, 26612, 26931, 29244, and 29639 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the recent move higher to multi-month highs, technical support levels and areas of potential buying pressure are around the 21711, 20682, 19850, 19019, 17989, and 17834 levels.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 21437, 20874, 20724, 20370, 20233, 20026, 19153, 18448, and 18253 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, technically significant areas include the 15900, 15512, 15313, 14500, 14364, 13369, 10727, 10432, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 22001.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 22819.97.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18390.99/ 16714.46/ 14500.15 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;23544.62/ 24224.60/ 25455.06 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Awaits Fresh Technical Sentiment:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 26 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair came off to the 22326.24 area after encountering fresh selling pressure around the 23165.36 area, representing a test of the 78.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 23375.60 to 22298.15.&nbsp; The fresh 5-month high also represented a test of the 23300.64 area, an upside price objective related to buying pressure that strengthened around the 20333.33 area.&nbsp; BTC/USD recently appreciated to the 23375.60 area, its strongest print since August 2022.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were elected above the 22042.59 area during the recent appreciation, an upside price objective related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 and 17927.36 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 area include the 23544, 23808, 25455, 25774, 27609, and 28004 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 15460 area include the 23980, 24224, 26612, 26931, 29244, and 29639 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the recent move higher to multi-month highs, technical support levels and areas of potential buying pressure are around the 21711, 20682, 19850, 19019, 17989, and 17834 levels.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 21437, 20874, 20724, 20370, 20233, 20026, 19153, 18448, and 18253 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, technically significant areas include the 15900, 15512, 15313, 14500, 14364, 13369, 10727, 10432, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 22001.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 22819.97.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18390.99/ 16714.46/ 14500.15 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;23544.62/ 24224.60/ 25455.06 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Saudi Central Bank Continues Testing on its CBDC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/saudi-central-bank-continues-testing-on-its-cbdc</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/saudi-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/saudi-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/saudi-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/saudi-central-bank-continues-testing-on-its-cbdc</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Saudi Arabia Central Bank (SAMA) announced that it is continuing its experiment with a central bank digital currency (CBDC). </p>
<p>SAMA announced in a press release earlier in the week that it is stepping up its research into a CBDC but has not said anything regarding its deployment. The bank&rsquo;s press release stated that it was working on a project that &ldquo;focuses on domestic wholesale CBDC use cases in collaboration with local banks and fintechs.&rdquo; The bank, however, reiterated that no conclusive decision had been reached to launch a CBDC:</p>

<p>SAMA stresses that although no decision has been made regarding the introduction of CBDC in the Kingdom, it continues to focus on exploring the benefits and potential risks of implementing CBDC, which will contribute to informed decision-making within SAMA and to CBDC explorations within the central banking community.</p>

<p>The Central Bank further stated that it tests the economic impact of implementing a CBDC and its market readiness and fast applications of CBDC-based payment solutions. SAMA said that it will continue testing the viability of a CBDC to achieve its Saudi Vision 2030 objectives but will consider &ldquo;policy, legal and regulatory considerations&rdquo; before it continues with the project.</p>
<p>The governor of SAMA, H.E. Fahad Almubarak, further stated that local banks and payment companies would be the foundation of the project and its implementation. He added that SAMA had approached local banks and fintechs, along with other market players and third-party consulting and technology providers, to comprehensively understand such a currency&rsquo;s functionality and test different design options.</p>
<p>The press release also added:</p>

<p>SAMA is set to continue with its research on CBDC while consulting with relative international bodies, local government entities, and the public. Additionally, SAMA will continue to experiment with CBDC solutions as an infrastructure enabler of innovation in financial services that has the potential to contribute to a more resilient payment ecosystem and accelerate digital transformation in the local financial sector.</p>

<p>SAMA successfully undertook a CBDC experiment in 2019 in collaboration with the Central Bank of the UAE to explore if distributed ledger technology, or blockchain, &ldquo;could contribute to seamless cross-border payments.&rdquo; The experiment was dubbed &ldquo;Projects Aber.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Saudi Arabia Central Bank (SAMA) announced that it is continuing its experiment with a central bank digital currency (CBDC). </p>
<p>SAMA announced in a press release earlier in the week that it is stepping up its research into a CBDC but has not said anything regarding its deployment. The bank&rsquo;s press release stated that it was working on a project that &ldquo;focuses on domestic wholesale CBDC use cases in collaboration with local banks and fintechs.&rdquo; The bank, however, reiterated that no conclusive decision had been reached to launch a CBDC:</p>

<p>SAMA stresses that although no decision has been made regarding the introduction of CBDC in the Kingdom, it continues to focus on exploring the benefits and potential risks of implementing CBDC, which will contribute to informed decision-making within SAMA and to CBDC explorations within the central banking community.</p>

<p>The Central Bank further stated that it tests the economic impact of implementing a CBDC and its market readiness and fast applications of CBDC-based payment solutions. SAMA said that it will continue testing the viability of a CBDC to achieve its Saudi Vision 2030 objectives but will consider &ldquo;policy, legal and regulatory considerations&rdquo; before it continues with the project.</p>
<p>The governor of SAMA, H.E. Fahad Almubarak, further stated that local banks and payment companies would be the foundation of the project and its implementation. He added that SAMA had approached local banks and fintechs, along with other market players and third-party consulting and technology providers, to comprehensively understand such a currency&rsquo;s functionality and test different design options.</p>
<p>The press release also added:</p>

<p>SAMA is set to continue with its research on CBDC while consulting with relative international bodies, local government entities, and the public. Additionally, SAMA will continue to experiment with CBDC solutions as an infrastructure enabler of innovation in financial services that has the potential to contribute to a more resilient payment ecosystem and accelerate digital transformation in the local financial sector.</p>

<p>SAMA successfully undertook a CBDC experiment in 2019 in collaboration with the Central Bank of the UAE to explore if distributed ledger technology, or blockchain, &ldquo;could contribute to seamless cross-border payments.&rdquo; The experiment was dubbed &ldquo;Projects Aber.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Miner US Limited provide a reliable hash  USDT cloud mining]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/miner-us-limited-provide-a-reliable-hash-usdt-cloud-mining</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-161210.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-161210.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-161210.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/miner-us-limited-provide-a-reliable-hash-usdt-cloud-mining</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Mining bitcoin was one of the most lucrative business opportunities available in the blockchain industry up until a few years ago. Currently, this is not the case. However, as more people entered the mining sector, the level of competition increased, which resulted in a decrease in profitability. Because the amount of computing power required to solve challenging cryptographic mathematical equations increases with the number of competitors, which results in a smaller profit margin for the business. </p>
<p>In addition, mining requires an initial investment of a significant amount of money, the installation of loud mining equipment in an area that has adequate ventilation, and a significant monthly investment in the cost of energy. Customers also have the option to adopt a mining service that is hosted in the cloud, which eliminates the complications and obstacles that were previously mentioned.</p>
<p>The first option that comes to mind is Miner US, which is widely regarded as one of the cloud mining industry's most effective and forward-thinking services while also preserving a reputation for exceptional ease of use. Customers can rent mining rigs from a service provider using cloud mining. After making the appropriate plan selection, paying the required fees, and getting started mining cryptocurrency, customers can start earning cryptocurrency. Take a look at this video to get a better understanding of Miner US Limited.</p>
<p>What is Miner US?</p>
<p>Miner US Limited has been successful in launching the Miner US platform, which enables investors to increase the transparency of the global financial, consumer, and internet infrastructure by leveraging digital assets and blockchains. This was accomplished through the use of blockchain technology. Miner US is a trustworthy platform that is well-known in the industry and regularly audited. Miner US possesses the legal authorization necessary to commence business operations, as well as the approval of the New York State Government. As a consequence of this, Miner US has been successful in convincing all of its users that it is a genuine and reliable platform, which has led to a significant increase in the size of its user base.</p>
<p>It is essential to pick a plan that satisfies the requirements of a high hash rate while remaining within a reasonable price range. The best part is that Miner US offers a variety of memberships, so potential miners from all walks of life are able to begin their path to success in the mining industry. This is the best thing that Miner US has to offer. Every plan, regardless of whether it lasts for 150 days or a lifetime, comes with a certain amount of mining power already included.</p>
<p>Why is Miner US the best option for you?</p>
<p>In case you were curious about the matter, the answer is "yes,&rdquo; moving your business to Miner US does come with a number of benefits, and here are a few of them:</p>
â— Customers are required to spend several thousand dollars on an expensive setup that includes a miner, a cooling system, and a high-performance central processing unit when they construct a mining rig. This setup consists of the three components listed above. This configuration is made up of the following parts and pieces: Using Miner US is one way to avoid all of this, and getting started is simple and won't take too much time.
â— Because everything can be done on a computer, there is no need to set aside space in the home or garage for a mining setup when using Miner US. This is because everything can be done on the computer. The procedure can be carried out in its entirety using a computer.
â— Dashboard with simple navigation: The cloud dashboard provided by Miner US is uncluttered and straightforward, enabling customers to quickly validate the total income, offered hash rate, and monthly fee. This is made possible as a result of the accessibility of the dashboard.
â— The mining of cryptocurrencies requires a significant amount of electricity, which leads to an increase in the amount of power that is consumed. This has a detrimental effect on the natural world if recyclable energy sources are not utilized instead. The mining of Bitcoin does not have a negative impact on the environment. Miner US has responded to the challenge by putting in place the mining rigs that are the most powerful and effective ones that are currently available. These systems have the ability to produce the highest output with the lowest possible amount of energy consumption.
â— The platform is dedicated to providing a staff of conscientious specialists who are available to assist customers with their challenges and requirements twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week. One more advantage of using a cloud mining service is that the mining process with Miner US is the quickest.
<p>In the event that you have not already done so, sign up for Miner US right away so that you can witness firsthand the significant advances that it will bring to the field of cloud mining. The process is straightforward, and it shouldn't take too much time to get everything up and running properly.</p>
<p>How does Miner US referral rebate work?</p>
<p>When someone who is already a part of Miner US wants to invite a friend to join, they can do so by giving them an invitation code or a link to the site. In the "My Team" section of your account, you will be able to see your friend's profile once they have finished signing. Then they'll need to allocate more resources to acquire the necessary hash rate power. Only if the funds are spent on offline computer power are you eligible to take part in the commission dividend, which can be anywhere from 5% to 12% of the purchase price.</p>
<p>You can get more information about Miner US by going to the official website of the company and looking at the various pricing options that are listed on the website. Please visit the registration page if you are interested in becoming a member of Miner US. You should also make sure that you are following Miner US on all of its social groups and channels so that you can stay up to date with the most recent changes.</p>
<p class="s9">Registration Link | Official Website | Telegram Channel | Telegram Group | Facebook Page | Twitter</p>
<p class="s9">Youtube Channel | White Paper | License &amp; Certificate</p>
<p class="s10">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mining bitcoin was one of the most lucrative business opportunities available in the blockchain industry up until a few years ago. Currently, this is not the case. However, as more people entered the mining sector, the level of competition increased, which resulted in a decrease in profitability. Because the amount of computing power required to solve challenging cryptographic mathematical equations increases with the number of competitors, which results in a smaller profit margin for the business. </p>
<p>In addition, mining requires an initial investment of a significant amount of money, the installation of loud mining equipment in an area that has adequate ventilation, and a significant monthly investment in the cost of energy. Customers also have the option to adopt a mining service that is hosted in the cloud, which eliminates the complications and obstacles that were previously mentioned.</p>
<p>The first option that comes to mind is Miner US, which is widely regarded as one of the cloud mining industry's most effective and forward-thinking services while also preserving a reputation for exceptional ease of use. Customers can rent mining rigs from a service provider using cloud mining. After making the appropriate plan selection, paying the required fees, and getting started mining cryptocurrency, customers can start earning cryptocurrency. Take a look at this video to get a better understanding of Miner US Limited.</p>
<p>What is Miner US?</p>
<p>Miner US Limited has been successful in launching the Miner US platform, which enables investors to increase the transparency of the global financial, consumer, and internet infrastructure by leveraging digital assets and blockchains. This was accomplished through the use of blockchain technology. Miner US is a trustworthy platform that is well-known in the industry and regularly audited. Miner US possesses the legal authorization necessary to commence business operations, as well as the approval of the New York State Government. As a consequence of this, Miner US has been successful in convincing all of its users that it is a genuine and reliable platform, which has led to a significant increase in the size of its user base.</p>
<p>It is essential to pick a plan that satisfies the requirements of a high hash rate while remaining within a reasonable price range. The best part is that Miner US offers a variety of memberships, so potential miners from all walks of life are able to begin their path to success in the mining industry. This is the best thing that Miner US has to offer. Every plan, regardless of whether it lasts for 150 days or a lifetime, comes with a certain amount of mining power already included.</p>
<p>Why is Miner US the best option for you?</p>
<p>In case you were curious about the matter, the answer is "yes,&rdquo; moving your business to Miner US does come with a number of benefits, and here are a few of them:</p>
â— Customers are required to spend several thousand dollars on an expensive setup that includes a miner, a cooling system, and a high-performance central processing unit when they construct a mining rig. This setup consists of the three components listed above. This configuration is made up of the following parts and pieces: Using Miner US is one way to avoid all of this, and getting started is simple and won't take too much time.
â— Because everything can be done on a computer, there is no need to set aside space in the home or garage for a mining setup when using Miner US. This is because everything can be done on the computer. The procedure can be carried out in its entirety using a computer.
â— Dashboard with simple navigation: The cloud dashboard provided by Miner US is uncluttered and straightforward, enabling customers to quickly validate the total income, offered hash rate, and monthly fee. This is made possible as a result of the accessibility of the dashboard.
â— The mining of cryptocurrencies requires a significant amount of electricity, which leads to an increase in the amount of power that is consumed. This has a detrimental effect on the natural world if recyclable energy sources are not utilized instead. The mining of Bitcoin does not have a negative impact on the environment. Miner US has responded to the challenge by putting in place the mining rigs that are the most powerful and effective ones that are currently available. These systems have the ability to produce the highest output with the lowest possible amount of energy consumption.
â— The platform is dedicated to providing a staff of conscientious specialists who are available to assist customers with their challenges and requirements twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week. One more advantage of using a cloud mining service is that the mining process with Miner US is the quickest.
<p>In the event that you have not already done so, sign up for Miner US right away so that you can witness firsthand the significant advances that it will bring to the field of cloud mining. The process is straightforward, and it shouldn't take too much time to get everything up and running properly.</p>
<p>How does Miner US referral rebate work?</p>
<p>When someone who is already a part of Miner US wants to invite a friend to join, they can do so by giving them an invitation code or a link to the site. In the "My Team" section of your account, you will be able to see your friend's profile once they have finished signing. Then they'll need to allocate more resources to acquire the necessary hash rate power. Only if the funds are spent on offline computer power are you eligible to take part in the commission dividend, which can be anywhere from 5% to 12% of the purchase price.</p>
<p>You can get more information about Miner US by going to the official website of the company and looking at the various pricing options that are listed on the website. Please visit the registration page if you are interested in becoming a member of Miner US. You should also make sure that you are following Miner US on all of its social groups and channels so that you can stay up to date with the most recent changes.</p>
<p class="s9">Registration Link | Official Website | Telegram Channel | Telegram Group | Facebook Page | Twitter</p>
<p class="s9">Youtube Channel | White Paper | License &amp; Certificate</p>
<p class="s10">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ZenGo Becomes The First Seedless Wallet on Polygon]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/zengo-becomes-the-first-seedless-wallet-on-polygon</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-231.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-231.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-231.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/zengo-becomes-the-first-seedless-wallet-on-polygon</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency wallets are the most straightforward option for users to engage in self-custody. However, the traditional approach of seed phrases and recovery seeds warrants improvements. ZenGo, a non-custodial Polygon wallet, offers a glimpse of what that future may look like.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seed Phrases May Be Phased Out
<p>Anyone who interfaced with a crypto wallet will have encountered a seed phrase or recovery seed. The string of words - often 12 or 24 words long - lets users restore their crypto wallet on a new device or within another software client. It is a big improvement over remembering the private key, a string of random letters and numbers. However, users still bear responsibility for handling their seed phrases correctly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, that is often where the issue begins. Writing down the seed phrase on a piece of paper isn't a good idea. Users often leave that paper out in the open, exposing their seed phrases to anyone who passes by it. It is a terrible security practice, although a very common one. Storing the data digitally - in a text document on an internet-connected device - is an even worse idea.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, it seems evident a new solution will be introduced eventually. Industry experts, like Udi Wertheimer, have publicly talked about how seed phrases need to go. He even deems it a "cop-out by wallet developers" and remains convinced builders can develop more secure solutions. More importantly, those new solutions should not result in less convenience.</p>
<p>The debate regarding seed phrases is pivotal for the crypto industry. Since the collapse of FTX, more people have moved funds off centralized exchanges. It is plausible to assume the funds moved to non-custodial wallets secured by recovery seeds. Unfortunately, most people will not conduct the correct security precautions to keep that sensitive data safe. As such, wallets without seed phrases may be the next frontier.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seedless Without Compromising Security
<p>On paper, it sounds straightforward to come up with a replacement for a seed phrase. However, it requires a security-oriented mindset to pull this off successfully. One wallet exploring the opportunity is ZenGo, a wallet for the Polygon ecosystem. It also supports ETH, BTC, and other assets. Rather than using a seed phrase, the wallet protects user funds through advanced biometrics and MPC cryptography.</p>
<p>Rather than using a private key, wallet users receive mathematical shares. One share resides on the user's phone or tablet, while the other is on ZenGo's servers. That ensures there is always a recovery option without having to worry about a single point of failure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The primary benefit of this approach is the ease of use when setting up the wallet while removing a single point of failure. Its non-seed phrase approach has proven successful, as no ZenGo wallet was breached since the company's launch in 2018.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition to biometrics, there is also a native Web3 firewall dubbed ClearSign. It is designed to provide more insight into what users sign off on when engaging with decentralized applications and smart contracts. That should also help prevent the signing of dangerous and malicious transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency wallets are the most straightforward option for users to engage in self-custody. However, the traditional approach of seed phrases and recovery seeds warrants improvements. ZenGo, a non-custodial Polygon wallet, offers a glimpse of what that future may look like.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seed Phrases May Be Phased Out
<p>Anyone who interfaced with a crypto wallet will have encountered a seed phrase or recovery seed. The string of words - often 12 or 24 words long - lets users restore their crypto wallet on a new device or within another software client. It is a big improvement over remembering the private key, a string of random letters and numbers. However, users still bear responsibility for handling their seed phrases correctly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, that is often where the issue begins. Writing down the seed phrase on a piece of paper isn't a good idea. Users often leave that paper out in the open, exposing their seed phrases to anyone who passes by it. It is a terrible security practice, although a very common one. Storing the data digitally - in a text document on an internet-connected device - is an even worse idea.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, it seems evident a new solution will be introduced eventually. Industry experts, like Udi Wertheimer, have publicly talked about how seed phrases need to go. He even deems it a "cop-out by wallet developers" and remains convinced builders can develop more secure solutions. More importantly, those new solutions should not result in less convenience.</p>
<p>The debate regarding seed phrases is pivotal for the crypto industry. Since the collapse of FTX, more people have moved funds off centralized exchanges. It is plausible to assume the funds moved to non-custodial wallets secured by recovery seeds. Unfortunately, most people will not conduct the correct security precautions to keep that sensitive data safe. As such, wallets without seed phrases may be the next frontier.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seedless Without Compromising Security
<p>On paper, it sounds straightforward to come up with a replacement for a seed phrase. However, it requires a security-oriented mindset to pull this off successfully. One wallet exploring the opportunity is ZenGo, a wallet for the Polygon ecosystem. It also supports ETH, BTC, and other assets. Rather than using a seed phrase, the wallet protects user funds through advanced biometrics and MPC cryptography.</p>
<p>Rather than using a private key, wallet users receive mathematical shares. One share resides on the user's phone or tablet, while the other is on ZenGo's servers. That ensures there is always a recovery option without having to worry about a single point of failure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The primary benefit of this approach is the ease of use when setting up the wallet while removing a single point of failure. Its non-seed phrase approach has proven successful, as no ZenGo wallet was breached since the company's launch in 2018.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition to biometrics, there is also a native Web3 firewall dubbed ClearSign. It is designed to provide more insight into what users sign off on when engaging with decentralized applications and smart contracts. That should also help prevent the signing of dangerous and malicious transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
