<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 16:07:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hotbit Closes Operations as Centralized Exchanges &#8216;Becoming Increasingly Cumbersome&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/hotbit-closes-operations-as-centralized-exchanges-becoming-increasingly-cumbersome/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251723</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/kraken_halt_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/kraken_halt_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hotbit notified its users to withdraw their remaining assets before June 21st.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shanghai-based cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Hotbit &#8211; announced its decision to stop all its operations starting May 22.</p>
<p>The team behind the platform believes centralized exchanges are &#8220;becoming increasingly cumbersome.&#8221; It further added that the highly complex and interconnected businesses are difficult to comply with, whether for compliance or decentralization and are &#8220;unlikely to meet long-term trends.&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>The crypto exchange explained that successive collapses of large centralized institutions have led the industry to either embrace the regulation or become more decentralized. This change in trend in the crypto industry is an important factor that has prompted it to shut shops.</li>
<li>In the blog <a href="https://hotbit.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/14750194236823-It-s-time-to-take-a-bow" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a>, Hotbit notified its users to withdraw their remaining assets before June 21st this year and cited that its decision is based on other reasons as well.</li>
<li>The platform also blamed the deterioration of the operating conditions as a result of a series of crises that followed, including the collapse of FTX and bank crises causing USDC off-peg incidents.</li>
<li>The events led to continuous outflows of funds from CEX users, including Hotbit.</li>
<li>The announcement comes almost a year after the platform halted its trading, withdrawal, and deposits as law-enforcement authorities <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hotbit-freezes-withdrawals-following-subpoena-of-senior-managers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">froze</a> some of its assets in connection to the alleged criminal misconduct of a former employee.</li>
<li>Hotbit suffered repeated cyber attacks and the exploitation of project defects by malicious users that fetched significant losses. Due to this, the team said its current operating model of supporting a diverse range of assets is unsustainable from a risk management standpoint.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hotbit-closes-operations-as-centralized-exchanges-becoming-increasingly-cumbersome/" rel="nofollow">Hotbit Closes Operations as Centralized Exchanges &#8216;Becoming Increasingly Cumbersome&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DCG Missed Promised $630 Million Loan Repayment, Says Gemini</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-missed-promised-630-million-loan-repayment-says-gemini/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251749</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Gemini_DCG.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Gemini_DCG.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DCG is currently at risk of defaulting should the company be held to an earlier agreement with creditors.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Digital Currency Group (DCG) has been dealing with financial turmoil for several months now. Mostly, its financial issues are due to the liquidity crisis that one of its owned companies, Genesis, is facing.</p>
<h2>Internal and External Disputes</h2>
<p>Although the financial problems of the DCG Group primarily boil down to the predicament Genesis is in, some creditors – Gemini chief among them – believe the main culprit is the CEO of the DCG Group, Barry Silbert.</p>
<p>According to the Winklevoss twins, DCG currently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-ready-to-take-legal-action-against-dcgs-barry-silbert/" data-wpel-link="internal">owes</a> Gemini north of $1.6 billion, a problem which has cascaded onto the exchange&#8217;s users due to Gemini’s Earn partnership with Genesis.</p>
<p>Silbert previously refuted the claim, stating that DCG had fulfilled all outstanding payments, with the next loan maturity being in May.</p>
<blockquote><p>“DCG did not borrow $1.675 billion from Genesis. DCG has never missed an interest payment to Genesis and is current on all loans outstanding; the next loan maturity is May 2023. DCG delivered to Genesis and your advisors a proposal on December 29th and has not received any response.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, the loan maturity has now been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-and-dcg-agree-on-mediation-process-to-create-final-resolution-for-creditors/" data-wpel-link="internal">reached</a>. According to Gemini, no payment has been made to Genesis.</p>
<h2>Creditors Looking for a Solution</h2>
<p>Late last week, the loan of about $630 million from Genesis to DCG was not repaid. In order to avert a default – which could send DCG into bankruptcy – Gemini, Genesis, and the committee of DCG creditors are <a href="https://www.gemini.com/earn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">considering</a> a loan forbearance to prevent the issue from spiraling out of control.</p>
<p>Any deal with DCG would be wholly dependent on whether the debtor intends to engage in good faith, according to the statement published by Gemini.</p>
<p>Should a deal be impossible to reach, Genesis will plead for an amended plan of reorganization that would afford it a greater chance of paying back creditors. Gemini would be consulted on any proposal, although their approval is not guaranteed.</p>
<p>In the meantime, Gemini will file the Gemini Master Claim, formally requesting the immediate return of $1.1 billion worth of digital assets belonging to its users that Genesis had custody over as part of the Earn partnership between the two companies.</p>
<p>This claim would be a separate proceeding from the case against DCG and its CEO, in particular, whom the Winklevoss twins have repeatedly accused of wrongdoing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-missed-promised-630-million-loan-repayment-says-gemini/" rel="nofollow">DCG Missed Promised $630 Million Loan Repayment, Says Gemini</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Promotes Preservation of Ethereum Blockchain&#8217;s &#8216;Minimalism&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-promotes-preservation-of-ethereum-blockchains-minimalism/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251746</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Vitalik_Buterin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Vitalik_Buterin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Extending the Ethereum blockchain's core with more and more functionality comes with a heavy price.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has warned against ‘&#8221;overloading&#8221; Ethereum&#8217;s social consensus &#8211; which, if discouraged or resisted &#8211; could bring &#8220;high systemic risks to the ecosystem.&#8221;</p>
<p>While admitting the &#8220;natural urge&#8221; to try to extend the Ethereum blockchain&#8217;s core functionality, Buterin added that such actions could end up making the consensus layer more fragile.</p>
<h2>Risks of Overloading Consensus Layer</h2>
<p>Over the years, several proposals have emerged suggesting the use of Ethereum social consensus for other purposes, including price and data oracles, re-staking initiatives, and using layer-1 soft forks to recover layer-2 projects. The Ethereum co-founder, however, warned against such a notion and explained,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It is natural for application-layer projects to attempt such a strategy, and indeed such ideas are often simply conceived without an appreciation of the risks, but its result can easily become very misaligned with the goals of the community as a whole.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In the latest blog <a href="https://vitalik.ca/general/2023/05/21/dont_overload.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a> titled, &#8216;Don&#8217;t overload Ethereum&#8217;s consensus,&#8217; Buterin offered some potential solutions to address risks such as price oracles, either &#8220;not-quite-cryptoeconomic decentralized oracles&#8221; or validator-voting-based oracles that explicitly commit to their emergency recovery strategies being something other than appealing to L1 consensus.</p>
<p>Buterin also pointed out that more complex truth oracles could be counted as a solution as the focus would be on reporting facts more subjective than price. He added that it would be &#8220;some kind of decentralized court system&#8221; built on a not-quite-cryptoeconomic DAO.</p>
<p>Minimizing reliance on cross-chain bridges is also important since these protocols have become an attractive target for malicious entities.</p>
<h2>Minimalism</h2>
<p>Buterin said that any expansion of the &#8220;duties&#8221; of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-weaknesses-of-ethereum-vs-modern-blockchains-interview-with-radix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum&#8217;s</a> consensus triggers an increase in costs, complexities as well as risks of running a validator. He argued that preserving the chain&#8217;s minimalism should be the focus which can be achieved by supporting uses of re-staking that do not look like slippery slopes to extending the role of Ethereum consensus.</p>
<p>He also highlighted the importance of helping developers find alternate strategies to achieve their security goals.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-promotes-preservation-of-ethereum-blockchains-minimalism/" rel="nofollow">Vitalik Buterin Promotes Preservation of Ethereum Blockchain&#8217;s &#8216;Minimalism&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 8 Events That Shocked the Crypto World</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-8-events-that-shocked-the-crypto-world/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt. Gox]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251793</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Crypto_Shocks.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Crypto_Shocks.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite its rather short history, the cryptocurrency industry has gone through some real shockers. Here are some examples.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the dynamic world of cryptocurrencies, where innovation and volatility often go hand in hand, certain events have the power to send shockwaves through the entire industry. From groundbreaking partnerships to catastrophic crashes, the crypto realm has witnessed its fair share of astonishing moments that have left investors, enthusiasts, and skeptics alike in awe.</p>
<p>In this article, we&#8217;ll take a walk through memory lane, reviewing eight extraordinary events that have not only reshaped the landscape of digital currencies but have also left an unforgettable mark on the collective consciousness of the crypto world.</p>
<h2>February 2014: The Mt. Gox Hack</h2>
<p>It was a moment that sent shockwaves through the fledgling cryptocurrency world &#8211; a sudden halt to all activities, an offline website, and a vanishing Twitter account. This grim reality unfolded in February 2014 when Mt. Gox, once the largest crypto exchange in the early days of Bitcoin, closed its doors. The tale of Mt. Gox remains a legendary chapter in the history of cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>Launched in 2007 as &#8220;Magic: The Gathering Online Exchange&#8221; by U.S. programmer Jed McCaleb, Mt. Gox initially served as a card exchange for the popular fantasy game. However, in 2010, it transitioned into a Bitcoin exchange, quickly becoming a significant player in the market.</p>
<p>During those early days, trading Bitcoin was a cumbersome process, with traders resorting to bartering their digital assets for basic items such as pizzas and t-shirts. Mt. Gox changed the game, offering a simplified platform for buying and selling BTC. Though it came at the cost of relinquishing control over assets to the exchange, investors saw it as a necessary trade-off. The success of Mt. Gox was immediate. As the largest crypto exchange at the time, it handled a significant portion of all Bitcoin transactions.</p>
<p>Along the line, Mt. Gox&#8217;s ownership changed. In 2011, McCaleb sold the platform to the French developer Mark Karpelès who became the exchange&#8217;s CEO. That same year, the platform hit a bump when it experienced its first hack.</p>
<p>The attackers managed to gain access to Mt. Gox auditor&#8217;s computer and altered the price of Bitcoin to 1 cent. They quickly bought an estimated 2,000 BTC at this artificial price using customers&#8217; accounts on the platform. Additionally, about 650 bitcoins were purchased by Mt. Gox customers at the artificial price, none of which was ever returned.</p>
<p>After the hack, Mt. Gox moved to tighten its security, including taking most of its bitcoins offline and keeping them in cold storage. If only the management team knew that this measure would not be enough to protect the exchange in the long run.</p>
<p>Mt. Gox continued waxing stronger, and by 2013, the company had established its position as the largest crypto trading platform, handling more than 70% of all bitcoin transactions. With this large volume, Mt. Gox became synonymous with the crypto market. However, while it appeared to be thriving on the surface, trouble lurked behind the scenes.</p>
<p>In May 2013, Mt. Gox faced a lawsuit from former business partner Coinlab, claiming a breach of contract and seeking $75 million in damages. At the same time, the exchange came under investigation by the U.S. Department of Homeland Security for operating without a license in the country.</p>
<p>These challenges proved to be the cracks that would eventually break the dam. In February 2014, the exchange suspended bitcoin withdrawals, citing the need for a technical assessment. Weeks of uncertainty followed, leading to the suspension of all trading activities and the disappearance of the website and official Twitter account.</p>
<p>Subsequent revelations unveiled the staggering truth &#8211; Mt. Gox had fallen victim to the largest crypto hack in history. Hackers had stolen 744,408 BTC from customers&#8217; wallets, along with 100,000 BTC owned by the exchange, amounting to approximately $473 million at the time.</p>
<p>The aftermath was devastating. Bitcoin&#8217;s price plummeted, and confidence in the industry was shattered. Mt. Gox then filed for bankruptcy protection in Japan and the United States, marking the end of an era. Investigations later revealed that the exchange had been insolvent for years, with the stolen BTC serving as a final blow to its already precarious financial situation.</p>
<p>Years of legal battles and investigations followed as complex bankruptcy proceedings unfolded. Creditors and investors sought restitution, while key figures like Karpelès faced criminal charges. It&#8217;s been nearly a decade since the exchange collapsed, but the recovery and distribution of assets are still ongoing, with creditors still <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mt-gox-extends-repayment-registration-deadline-to-march-30/" data-wpel-link="internal">awaiting</a> resolution.</p>
<p>The story of Mt. Gox serves as a valuable lesson, a reminder of the challenges and vulnerabilities that accompanied the early years of the crypto market. It highlights the importance of security, regulation, and transparent operations in building trust within the crypto ecosystem. While the crypto world has matured since then, the legacy of Mt. Gox continues to resonate, shaping the industry&#8217;s present and future.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-146897" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox.jpg" alt="BitcoinMtGox" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>August 2017: Bitcoin Cash Hard Fork</h2>
<p>Bitcoin gained immense popularity for its promise to tackle the limitations of traditional finance. However, the protocol was not without its own set of challenges.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin gained traction, scalability issues arose, manifesting as prolonged transaction times and costly fees. These issues stemmed from the size restriction of Bitcoin blocks, which were limited to 1 megabyte (MB). The increasing number of transactions overwhelmed the network&#8217;s capacity. In response, the concept of Bitcoin Cash emerged.</p>
<p>In August 2017, a divergence of opinions among Bitcoin developers led to a hard fork of the Bitcoin blockchain. A hard fork is a significant software upgrade that splits a blockchain network into two separate chains. One group maintains the existing rules, while the other diverges to forge its own path with updated software.</p>
<p>Although most Bitcoin developers and miners opted for the inclusion of Segregated Witness (SegWit), a consensus layer designed to enhance scalability, not everyone favored this update. SegWit employs a scaling solution that separates transactions into two segments, reducing their weight on the block and enabling more transactions to be included in a single block.</p>
<p>At block 478,558, the Bitcoin blockchain split, giving birth to Bitcoin Cash. The new fork aimed to address scalability concerns by increasing the block size from Bitcoin&#8217;s 1 MB to a range between 8 MB and 32 MB. This increase facilitated the validation of more transactions per block, with the network capable of processing over 100 transactions per second.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin Cash operates under similar rules as Bitcoin, sharing a 21 million supply cap and utilizing the same consensus mechanism, it has not achieved the same level of prominence in the crypto market. Nonetheless, it currently stands as one of the top 30 cryptocurrencies worldwide.</p>
<h2>March 2020: Covid Crash</h2>
<p>For years, Bitcoin was described as a safe-haven asset and a hedge against inflation, earning the nickname &#8220;digital gold&#8221; from its enthusiasts. However, in 2020, the perception of the asset as a secure refuge was severely diminished when it fell short of expectations.</p>
<p>The year commenced on an optimistic trajectory, with Bitcoin trading at $7,000. Within a mere six weeks, the digital asset skyrocketed to $10,000. Then, the COVID-19 pandemic struck, catching crypto investors off guard and profoundly impacting the crypto market and the global financial landscape.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price swiftly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coronavirus-madness-continues-bitcoin-price-crashes-below-4300-over-40-daily-loss/" data-wpel-link="internal">plummeted</a>, sinking below $4,000 within hours. Market analysts attributed this volatile price movement primarily to the influence of the COVID-19 outbreak on global markets, which compelled investors to seek the safety of cash. The sharp decline raised doubts regarding Bitcoin&#8217;s potential as a reliable safe-haven asset.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-241542" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover.jpg" alt="bitcoin_crash_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_crash_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>March 2021: Beeple $69M NFT</h2>
<p>In 2021, the NFT market emerged as a prominent sector within the digital asset industry, capturing widespread attention. Although non-fungible tokens came into existence in 2014, their popularity soared in 2021, coinciding with the bull market. NFTs quickly transitioned from a relatively unknown niche to a mainstream phenomenon, significantly increasing awareness of digital asset ownership.</p>
<p>However, nobody could have anticipated that a digital artwork would fetch a staggering $69 million. But that is exactly what happened with Beeple&#8217;s record-breaking $69 million NFT auction.</p>
<p>Before Q4 2020, the highest sum Mike Winkleman, also known as Beeple, had ever received for his artwork was a mere $100. Beeple introduced his first NFT series to the market in October 2020, with each pair selling for over $66,000. Through a series of subsequent NFT auctions, Beeple established a notable presence in the NFT market, leading up to the largest such sale to date.</p>
<p>The auction took place at Christie&#8217;s, a renowned auction house with a 257-year history of selling some of the world&#8217;s most famous artworks, including the only known portrait of Shakespeare and the last-discovered painting by Leonardo da Vinci. The event garnered immense attention from crypto and non-crypto investors, particularly as it marked Christie&#8217;s inaugural digital-only art auction.</p>
<p>Beeple&#8217;s NFT, titled &#8220;Everydays: The First 5000 Days,&#8221; encompasses a collection of his work spanning 13 years, capturing the evolution of his artistic career. Following a two-week-long auction, Beeple&#8217;s NFT <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/record-breaking-beeples-first-5000-days-nft-sold-for-69-million/" data-wpel-link="internal">fetched</a> an astonishing $69.3 million, firmly establishing him as one of the top three most valuable living artists.</p>
<figure id="attachment_108250" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-108250" style="width: 742px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-108250" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple.jpg" alt="beeple" width="742" height="742" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple.jpg 742w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple-300x300.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple-239x239.jpg 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/beeple-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 742px) 100vw, 742px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-108250" class="wp-caption-text">Everydays: The First 5000 Days by Beeple. Source: Christie&#8217;s</figcaption></figure>
<h2>June 2021: El Salvador BTC Legal Tender</h2>
<p>On June 9, 2021, El Salvador, a small Central American nation, made a historic decision as President Nayib Bukele <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/its-official-bitcoin-a-legal-tender-in-el-salvador-following-a-supermajority-decision/" data-wpel-link="internal">declared</a> the adoption of Bitcoin as legal tender. The groundbreaking decision marked the first time Bitcoin gained recognition as an official currency.</p>
<p>At a time when many countries were tightening their regulations on the industry, including China&#8217;s complete ban on crypto operations, El Salvador&#8217;s move garnered significant attention. Enacting the Bitcoin Law provided various advantages for crypto businesses and investors, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-wont-tax-foreign-investors-on-bitcoin-profits/" data-wpel-link="internal">exemption</a> from capital gains tax on BTC due to its legal tender status.</p>
<p>But the decision faced opposition from global financial organizations and economic experts. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/president-bukele-bites-back-as-el-salvador-snubs-imfs-advice-to-stop-using-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">urged</a> El Salvador to remove Bitcoin as a legal tender. At the same time, the World Bank <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/world-bank-shuns-el-salvador-bitcoin-adoption-plan/" data-wpel-link="internal">expressed</a> concerns over environmental impact and transparency issues and declined to assist with the implementation.</p>
<p>Undeterred, President Bukele announced plans to utilize the country&#8217;s renewable geothermal energy for Bitcoin mining and encouraged local companies to adopt BTC for salary payments.</p>
<p>In September 2021, El Salvador <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-officially-becomes-first-country-to-buy-bitcoin-with-initial-200-btc-purchase/" data-wpel-link="internal">made</a> history again by becoming the first country to purchase Bitcoin, acquiring an initial 200 BTC. This marked the beginning of the nation&#8217;s entry into the crypto market, with more purchases following suit. El Salvador currently holds over 2,380 BTC, maintaining unwavering confidence in the asset&#8217;s future despite its significant price fluctuations.</p>
<figure id="attachment_125650" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-125650" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-125650" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador.jpg" alt="PresidentSalvador" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-125650" class="wp-caption-text">President Nayib Bukele</figcaption></figure>
<h2>October 2021: Shiba Inu Parabolic Rally</h2>
<p>The crypto industry is no stranger to impressive short-term gains, but the extraordinary surge delivered by the memecoin Shiba Inu in 2021 caught everyone by surprise. This parabolic rally remains one of the most remarkable financial achievements in history.</p>
<p>Following in the footsteps of Dogecoin&#8217;s success, the crypto market witnessed the emergence of various memecoins, including Shiba Inu (SHIB). Founded in 2020 as an experiment in decentralized community building, Shiba Inu had a modest start in January 2021, with minimal trading activity. The coin was so cheap that for as little as $1, one could acquire over 13.6 billion SHIB, with each unit priced at $0.000000000073.</p>
<p>However, as the memecoin&#8217;s popularity grew in the subsequent months, so did its value. The SHIB trend attracted thousands of investors looking to make quick profits, propelling the coin into the mainstream spotlight.</p>
<p>With increased visibility, SHIB quickly climbed the ranks in market capitalization and popularity, prompting more crypto exchanges to list it on their platforms. As the number of exchanges offering the coin multiplied, the fear of missing out (FOMO) drove an influx of Shiba Inu holders, enhancing liquidity.</p>
<p>By October 2021, SHIB had shed six zeroes, smashing one all-time high after another, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-shiba-inu-shib-up-over-100000000-this-year-a-closer-look/" data-wpel-link="internal">achieving</a> a staggering 100,000,000% growth in just one year! Another significant factor contributing to the rally was the launch of ShibaSwap, the memecoin&#8217;s decentralized exchange, in July 2021. The platform improved liquidity and enabled SHIB holders to stake their assets and earn passive income, incentivizing long-term coin holdings.</p>
<p>Although Shiba Inu&#8217;s price has since declined from its 2021 all-time high, investors remain hopeful of a potential revival of this historic rally. While it may be challenging to envision such a resurgence in the near future, one can never truly predict what lies ahead, especially in the ever-changing crypto market.</p>
<h2>May 2022: DoKwon/Terra Collapse</h2>
<p>Stablecoins have often been considered a safer choice in the digital asset space due to their relatively stable prices. However, that notion was shattered in the Terra ecosystem, exposing the risks involved.</p>
<p>Terra is a blockchain protocol that leverages algorithmic stablecoins to create a payment network. At its peak, Terra provided investors with fully stable prices through the relationship between its native token, LUNA, and the popular dollar-pegged stablecoin within its ecosystem, UST.</p>
<p>Instead of relying on reserve assets, LUNA maintained price stability for UST through a smart contract-based algorithm. The algorithm utilized arbitrage trading to uphold prices, allowing users to seamlessly exchange LUNA for UST at a 1:1 ratio, regardless of the tokens&#8217; market prices.</p>
<p>When demand for UST surged, driving its price above $1, LUNA holders could swiftly swap their tokens to mint one UST and profit from the price difference. During the token swap, a portion of LUNA was burned, reducing UST demand and increasing its supply. This mechanism restored UST&#8217;s market price to $1. In contrast, when UST demand waned and prices dropped below $1, holders could exchange UST for LUNA, which held a higher value.</p>
<p>Trouble began for the Terra ecosystem when an anonymous wallet dumped over $500 million worth of UST. Whether this action stemmed from market volatility or a malicious attack on Terra&#8217;s system remains unknown. In an attempt to rescue UST, the Luna Foundation Guard (LFG), an organization responsible for building reserves, emptied its Bitcoin reserve to support the stablecoin&#8217;s peg during volatile market conditions.</p>
<p>However, these efforts failed to prevent the collapse of the stablecoin. As UST lost its peg, investors rushed to sell, causing LUNA to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-700-million-liquidated-as-terra-luna-crashes-below-1/" data-wpel-link="internal">shed</a> 99.9% of its value.</p>
<p>The damage inflicted by the crash extended beyond the Terra ecosystem, as the event exacerbated the prevailing bearish market sentiment, dragging down the entire crypto market. The Terra UST collapse wiped out over $26 billion from the stablecoin market and more than $700 billion from the broader crypto sector.</p>
<p>Even before the UST crash, numerous analysts cautioned investors about the risks of Terra&#8217;s mechanism, and they were quick to assert their earlier concerns when the Terra ecosystem crumbled.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s founders became targets of industry scrutiny. In the aftermath of Terra&#8217;s catastrophic failure, Korean investors initiated legal actions against the co-founders, filing criminal and civil lawsuits while seeking to seize the assets of Terra&#8217;s Do Kwon.</p>
<p>The South Korean government summoned Kwon to give accounts of the collapse of both LUNA and UST. The authorities also called upon executives from local crypto exchanges to explain their actions during UST&#8217;s depegging.</p>
<p>Kwon is currently facing document forgery charges in Montenegro, where he was arrested while on the run.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-220166" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon.png" alt="Do_Kwon" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon.png 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon-300x180.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon-1024x614.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon-768x460.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon-50x30.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>November 2022: SBF/FTX Failure</h2>
<p>November 2022 marked the downfall of Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) and his bankrupt crypto exchange, FTX. SBF had been hailed as a key figure in driving mainstream adoption and a crypto champion within and beyond the industry. As FTX grew, the 31-year-old entrepreneur became synonymous with the company, gaining prominence in the crypto world.</p>
<p>Founded in 2019, FTX rapidly gained international recognition through aggressive marketing tactics and attractive trading fees, luring crypto and non-crypto users. The exchange promised substantial returns on digital asset holdings, surpassing traditional banking offerings. FTX&#8217;s Super Bowl ads, celebrity endorsements, and arena naming rights with the Miami Heat made them hard to ignore.</p>
<p>FTX and SBF aimed to solidify their dominance by acquiring high-profile companies like Blockfolio, LedgerX, and Liquid Global. With almost $2 billion in investments from venture capital firms, FTX&#8217;s valuation <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-valuation-hits-32-billion-following-a-400-million-funding-round-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">reached</a> $32 billion by January 2022, and the company was ranked as the third largest crypto exchange in the industry.</p>
<p>To further strengthen his company&#8217;s dominance in the space, SBF became Crypto&#8217;s White Knight by rescuing numerous firms impacted by the first wave of the bear market, which stemmed from the Terra-Luna crash.</p>
<p>As the CEO of FTX, SBF played a pivotal role in supporting and revitalizing struggling companies within the crypto industry. His intervention provided a lifeline to these firms during a challenging period characterized by plummeting prices and market uncertainty. SBF&#8217;s efforts were widely recognized and celebrated, positioning him as a prominent figure in driving the industry forward.</p>
<p>However, in the first two weeks of November, FTX and its founder lost their shine as the third-largest crypto exchange collapsed. Trouble started when a CoinDesk report <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/11/02/divisions-in-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-blur-on-his-trading-titan-alamedas-balance-sheet/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that FTX&#8217;s sister trading house Alameda Research was in a dire financial condition. The publication also unveiled a major fraud that caused the loss of billions of dollars in investors&#8217; assets.</p>
<p>Alameda&#8217;s balance sheet, composed mainly of FTX&#8217;s FTT token and Solana&#8217;s SOL token, disclosed $9 billion in liabilities, $900 million in assets, and poorly labeled records revealing an $8 billion negative balance. Investigations uncovered FTX&#8217;s diversion of investors&#8217; funds to other investments using FTT as collateral through Alameda.</p>
<p>FTX and its affiliated companies lacked transparency, neglecting standard financial reporting practices that disclose assets and liabilities. This made it difficult to ascertain the company&#8217;s funds and their allocation.</p>
<p>Upon learning the news, Binance&#8217;s CEO, Changpeng Zhao, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-stablecoin-reserves-dwindle-after-binance-promises-to-sell-ftt/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to sell his company&#8217;s FTT holdings worth over $500 million. The announcement triggered panic selling, rendering the FTT token practically worthless. FTX then <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/market-in-shambles-as-ftx-withdrawal-uncertainty-runs-rampant/" data-wpel-link="internal">suspended</a> all withdrawals on its platform, causing shockwaves throughout the market.</p>
<p>Initially, CZ offered to assist FTX and prevent a broader market crash. However, the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-will-not-acquire-ftx-exchange-confirms/" data-wpel-link="internal">deal</a> fell through due to a closer examination of FTX&#8217;s balance sheet and further reports of mishandled customer funds.</p>
<p>The collapse of FTX had a cascading effect on the entire industry, particularly affecting crypto firms associated with it. Numerous companies, such as BlockFi, with significant exposure to FTX, had to halt withdrawals following the overwhelming number of users&#8217; requests. Most of these firms eventually filed for bankruptcy protection.</p>
<p>Major FTX investors, including CoinShares, Galaxy Digital, BlackRock, and others, wrote off millions of dollars in losses. Several projects that FTX had invested in also suffered significant treasury shortfalls.</p>
<p>Unable to secure a lifeline, FTX <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-investors-sue-bankman-fried-over-yield-bearing-crypto-accounts-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">initiated</a> bankruptcy proceedings, leading to SBF stepping down as CEO. John J. Ray III, FTX&#8217;s new CEO, described the collapse as a &#8220;complete failure of corporate control&#8221; unprecedented in his experience managing the aftermath of major corporate failures.</p>
<p>Criminal charges and lawsuits flooded in, including a class-action lawsuit filed by FTX investors on November 15 against FTX and its celebrity endorsers, including Naomi Osaka and Tom Brady. The lawsuit alleged &#8220;false representation and deceptive conduct.&#8221;</p>
<p>SBF was arrested in the Bahamas on December 12, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-deported-and-released-on-bail-ftx-fiasco-rageson-bitcoin-stuck-below-17k-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">extradited</a> to the United States, and released on a $250 million bond. He faces multiple criminal charges, including money laundering, wire fraud, campaign finance violations, and securities fraud.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229133" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229133" style="width: 768px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_arrest.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-229133" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_arrest.jpg" alt="sbf_arrest" width="768" height="432" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_arrest.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_arrest-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/sbf_arrest-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229133" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Sky News</figcaption></figure>
<p>Due to the numerous lawsuits against FTX, several partners, including the Miami Heat, terminated their agreements with the exchange.</p>
<p>The FTX saga also prompted increased scrutiny of the crypto industry by global financial regulators. The UK government <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-uk-to-enforce-robust-standards-in-the-crypto-industry-after-ftx-crash/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to implement stringent regulations for the industry in response to the collapse of FTX.</p>
<p>As of April 2023, FTX had managed to recover more than $7 billion in lost customer assets. The funds are now set to be distributed among the affected clients, numbering over 150,000.</p>
<p>Despite the significant losses and the tarnished reputation of SBF and FTX, efforts are underway to restore stability and trust within the crypto industry, aiming to prevent similar incidents in the future.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>While most of these events harmed the broader crypto market, it is worth noting that the industry has always found a way to bounce back, better than before, with great lessons to learn.</p>
<p>Furthermore, most of these events serve as a cautionary tale, highlighting the need for transparency, responsible financial practices, and regulatory compliance as the crypto market matures.</p>
<p>As we enter a new phase of growth in preparation for the next bull run, the market will be better prepared to navigate similar situations. Which of these events did you personally witness?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-8-events-that-shocked-the-crypto-world/" rel="nofollow">The 8 Events That Shocked the Crypto World</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traders Are Backing These Two AI Cryptos to Explode</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/traders-are-backing-these-two-ai-cryptos-to-explode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251832</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/aidoge_ypredict_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/aidoge_ypredict_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency token’s real-world utility could be the difference between sustainable 10x growth and a temporary fad. A few high-quality tokens are utilizing artificial intelligence to provide cutting-edge solutions to difficult problems. Blockchain and artificial intelligence are two complementary futuristic technologies that offer significant advantages over traditional computing systems. Blockchain’s transparent and decentralized data storage, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A cryptocurrency token’s real-world utility could be the difference between sustainable 10x growth and a temporary fad. A few high-quality tokens are utilizing artificial intelligence to provide cutting-edge solutions to difficult problems.</p>
<p>Blockchain and artificial intelligence are two complementary futuristic technologies that offer significant advantages over traditional computing systems. Blockchain’s transparent and decentralized data storage, along with AI’s analytical decision-making capability, can provide a variety of revolutionary tools in the field of finance, healthcare, freelancing, etc.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AiDoge</a> and <a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict</a> are two AI crypto tokens that are being backed by traders to show an explosive price movement in the near future.</p>
<h2><strong>AiDoge Hits $11m in Presale, Could it Be the Next 100x Meme Coin?</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AiDoge</a> is receiving enormous interest due to its innovative approach to meme generation using artificial intelligence. The platform recognizes the importance of memes as a method of communication for crypto companies. AiDoge uses advanced artificial intelligence algorithms that are trained on millions of memes and crypto news to produce high-quality and relevant content.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251835" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="1379" height="786" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1-300x171.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1-1024x584.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1-768x438.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a></p>
<p>AI is the native token of the AiDoge platform and is absolutely dominating its presale. The token has already raised over $10.2 million and is quickly approaching its goal of $10.8 million. AI will comfortably surpass this goal as the presale still has multiple stages left. The token is currently priced at $0.0000316 and will surge to $0.0000336 at the launch.</p>
<p>Apart from being used to create memes on AiDoge, the AI token also offers other exciting rewards to users. For example, traders can earn significant returns by staking the token or voting on the AiDoge platform.</p>
<p>The token is receiving backing from several traders and crypto influencers. The <a href="https://youtu.be/eyhBV-z625s" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CryptoTV youtube channel</a> praises the token for its strong presale, adding that heavy investment adds a certain level of legitimacy. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-vCt5WUTrVM&amp;t=270s" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Bleeves Crypto</a> is also bullish on the project.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251836" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="128" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1-300x64.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1-50x11.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Similarly, <a href="https://youtu.be/5U_dytHc0kc" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">2BitCrypto</a> praises the project for its extensive and well-planned development roadmap. AiDoge expects that the token will be available on various centralized and decentralized exchanges by the end of the 3rd quarter of 2023. The meme generation platform is expected to go live in Q4 2023. Users will be able to create memes based on the credits they have accumulated by staking the token.</p>
<p>The project is making conscious efforts to expand its user adoption. It has announced a 50 billion token airdrop for users who purchased AI during the presale. Such users will only need to share the unique referral link they receive at the time of purchase. Based on the amount raised through the link, users will receive a share of the 50 billion tokens.</p>
<p>AiDoge is also receiving praise for its adherence to security standards. The AI token will be audited by Certik to assure the investors regarding any potential threats. Furthermore, over 25% of the token will be staked with the company for 10 years to show its commitment to long-term excellence and offer security against rug pulls.</p>
<p>Users can purchase AI tokens by swapping ETH or BNB after connecting their crypto wallets. Support and incorporation of BNB in the presale make it likely that AI will be listed on the Binance platform, which can result in a 10x price boost. Alternatively, users can also purchase the tokens by credit card.</p>
<p><strong>                                               </strong><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge ($AI) Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2><strong>Revolutionary AI Crypto Analytics Platform yPredict Set for Explosive Growth</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict</a> is a cutting-edge trading platform that provides an unbeatable edge to market participants. It is another project that utilizes blockchain technology, artificial intelligence, and crypto tokenomics to provide significant upgrades over existing companies. The AI-powered ecosystem is built for developers, traders, quants, and analysts and provides meaningful insights in the field of technology, finance, healthcare, and human resources.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251837" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="1379" height="896" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1-300x195.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1-1024x665.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1-768x499.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a></p>
<p>Primarily, yPredict is an all-in-one trading platform that offers a wide variety of tools. yPredict Predictions platform provides price predictions for thousands of crypto assets and securities. This platform is free of cost for every YPRED holder. yPredict Analytics uses advanced techniques such as pattern and chart recognition, sentiment analysis, and on-chain data analysis to provide real-time insights to traders.</p>
<p>yPredict’s flagship product Marketplace matches traders and investors with data scientists and ML experts. Experts publish their cutting-edge data models on the marketplace, which traders can then subscribe to as signals. These signals can be used to make informed decisions while trading. Finally, the yPredict Terminal is a sophisticated trading engine that enables pro traders to execute their trades instantaneously.</p>
<p>yPredict provides tools for traders and investors of all levels, from beginners to experts. For example, beginners can access the predictions platform free of cost. Similarly, the Analytics platform uses a freemium structure and offers three levels of membership: free, active, and pro trader.</p>
<p>YPRED, the native token of the platform, is receiving enormous interest due to its utility and sound tokenomics. The Polygon-based token has already raised over $1.3 million and is extremely close to achieving its goal of $1.6 million. YPRED is currently priced at $0.07 and will list at $0.12. The token already has over 20,000 traders on the waiting list and will have a $6.5 million market cap at launch. Users staking the token can receive up to 45% APY and huge discounts on yPredict services.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251838" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-1.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="143" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-1-300x71.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-1-50x12.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The platform claims that YPRED has 10 &#8211; 100x potential and many traders fully agree. <a href="https://youtu.be/QL4EmqPUyFE" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Jacob Bury</a>, a popular crypto YouTuber, believes that the token has 100x potential and claims that he is incredibly bullish on it. Similarly, <a href="https://youtu.be/KwoCQl5h4qE" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Michael Wrubel</a>, another popular influencer, claims that he is bullish on YPRED. He highlights that there is no other platform that provides a similar level of market analytics. Moreover, the token’s foundation in Polygon makes the project incredibly attractive.</p>
<p>Users can purchase the token by swapping ETH or MATIC tokens and allocating YPRED to their crypto wallets. Alternatively, they can also acquire the tokens by credit or debit cards.</p>
<p><strong>                                        </strong><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict ($YPRED) Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/traders-are-backing-these-two-ai-cryptos-to-explode/" rel="nofollow">Traders Are Backing These Two AI Cryptos to Explode</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s 13th Pizza Day: Reflecting on the Transaction that Changed Crypto History</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-13th-pizza-day-reflecting-on-the-transaction-that-changed-crypto-history/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251757</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/BitcoinPizza.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/BitcoinPizza.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hanyecz's decision to purchase pizza with Bitcoin was a deliberate attempt to test the usability of the currency in a real-world setting.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today- May 22 &#8211; is the 13th anniversary of Bitcoin Pizza Day, a historic event that marked the first time BTC was publicly used as a medium of exchange. On 22 May 2010, Laszlo Hanyecz, a programmer and early Bitcoin adopter, forever etched his name in history by purchasing two Papa John&#8217;s pizzas for 10,000 BTC.</p>
<p>As the world celebrates the 13th Bitcoin Pizza Day, let&#8217;s reflect on the astronomical growth that Bitcoin has achieved, both in value and as a viable payment method for goods and services, since that fateful day.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Pizza Day</h2>
<p>Although the 10,000 BTC Hanyecz spent to purchase the two pizzas was worth $40 at the time of the transaction, the present value is worth an astonishing $270 million, with the asset&#8217;s current price standing at $27,000. This illustrates just how much the value of Bitcoin has grown in the past decade, as well as the profit margin for early adopters who held to date.</p>
<p>Many in the crypto community look back on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/12-years-since-a-florida-based-programmer-bought-2-papa-johns-pizzas-with-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin Pizza Day</a> with nostalgia and disbelief as they try to put themselves in Hanyecz&#8217;s shoes and imagine what it must have been like to spend what would eventually become a fortune on a couple of pizzas. Others see it as an important reminder of the potential of cryptocurrencies and the power that early adopters can have in shaping the future.</p>
<h2>The Significance of Bitcoin Pizza Day</h2>
<p>It is worth noting that purchasing those pizzas was not just a random act of food-loving frivolity. Hanyecz&#8217;s decision to use BTC to make a purchase was a deliberate attempt to test the usability of the currency in a real-world setting. At the time, Bitcoin was still a relatively unknown and untested currency, and Hanyecz&#8217;s experiment was one of the first real-world applications of the technology.</p>
<p>Today, hundreds of mainstream companies, including entertainment giant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amc-theatres-to-accept-bitcoin-payments-by-the-end-of-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">AMC</a>, coffee maker Starbucks, and retail platform <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/overstock-to-become-the-first-major-us-corporation-to-pay-taxes-with-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Overstock.com</a>, accept Bitcoin and other crypto assets as payment options.</p>
<h2>Hanyecz&#8217;s Contributions to the Bitcoin Network</h2>
<p>Beyond his infamous pizza purchase, Laszlo Hanyecz was a significant contributor to the early development of Bitcoin. He played a crucial role in fixing many vulnerabilities in the network during its early stages, helping to make the protocol more secure and stable.</p>
<p>Hanyecz&#8217;s pioneering work also extended to software development. He was the first person to release the Bitcoin code for Mac OS, which helped pave the way for the wide adoption of Bitcoin as a digital currency. Additionally, he played a vital role in transforming the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/surging-bitcoin-mining-stocks-outperform-tech-heavy-shares-in-2023-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin mining</a> landscape, laying the groundwork for today&#8217;s industry&#8217;s growth.</p>
<p>Looking back on this day 13 years ago, it is clear that Hanyecz&#8217;s decision to buy those pizzas for 10,000 BTC was a defining moment in the history of cryptocurrencies. It demonstrated the potential and utility of Bitcoin, paving the way for many more use cases and innovations to come.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-13th-pizza-day-reflecting-on-the-transaction-that-changed-crypto-history/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin&#8217;s 13th Pizza Day: Reflecting on the Transaction that Changed Crypto History</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Due for a Price Explosion? Consolidation at $0.36 Tightens (ADA Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-due-for-a-price-explosion-consolidation-at-0-36-tightens-ada-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251729</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With the price consolidating under the key resistance, ADA may attempt a breakout. Key Support levels: $0.36, $0.34 Key Resistance levels: $0.38, $0.40 The price has formed a double bottom with good support at 36 cents. As long as this key level holds, bulls have a good chance to take ADA&#8217;s price to the resistance [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">With the price consolidating under the key resistance, ADA may attempt a breakout.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.36, $0.34</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.38, $0.40</strong></p>
<p>The price has formed a double bottom with good support at 36 cents. As long as this key level holds, bulls have a good chance to take ADA&#8217;s price to the resistance at 38 cents. A breakout above it would confirm the end of this correction that started in April.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251732" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251732" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251732" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36" width="1813" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36-768x365.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-36-36-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251732" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume: </strong>The volume continues to be low, and momentum has yet to return for bulls.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The daily RSI is making higher lows which gives hopes of a reversal soon.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The daily MACD did a bullish cross today, and if buyers return, it could signal the start of an uptrend.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251731" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251731" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251731" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23" width="1813" height="860" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23-768x364.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-22_15-37-23-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251731" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for ADA is neutral.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for ADA Price</h2>
<p>Cardano is found at a critical moment which will be decisive for the remainder of the month. If buyers manage to return and break the key resistance at 38 cents, then ADA will turn bullish and could visit 40 cents next.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-due-for-a-price-explosion-consolidation-at-0-36-tightens-ada-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Cardano Due for a Price Explosion? Consolidation at $0.36 Tightens (ADA Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Web3 Builders Back RedStone’s Cross-Chain Expansion with $350K Angel Round</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/top-web3-builders-back-redstones-cross-chain-expansion-with-350k-angel-round/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251802</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] BAAR, Switzerland – May 22, 2023 – RedStone, originator of the next-generation decentralized finance oracle platform, has announced an exclusive $350,000 angel investment round led by recognized Web3 leaders including Stani Kulechov, Sandeep Naiwal, Alex Gluchovski, and Emin Gün Sirer. The support from a host of Web3 pioneers demonstrates [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>BAAR, Switzerland – May 22, 2023 – <a href="https://redstone.finance/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">RedStone</a>, originator of the next-generation decentralized finance oracle platform, has announced an exclusive $350,000 angel investment round led by recognized Web3 leaders including Stani Kulechov, Sandeep Naiwal, Alex Gluchovski, and Emin Gün Sirer.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251805" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone.jpeg" alt="RedStone" width="1280" height="673" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone.jpeg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone-300x158.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone-1024x538.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone-768x404.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/RedStone-50x26.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a></p>
<p>The support from a host of Web3 pioneers demonstrates the pronounced need for diverse and efficient oracle options across the industry. With presence on all EVM L1 and L2 networks, modular design and customizable data feeds, RedStone is disrupting the status quo oracle space, providing Web3 and DeFi protocols with actionable real-time data at lower latency.</p>
<p>The high-profile list of angel round participants includes Stani Kulechov, Aave Companies Founder and CEO; Sandeep Nailwal, Polygon Co-Founder; Alex Gluchovski, Matter Labs (zkSync) CEO &amp; Co-Founder; Emin Gün Sirer, AvaLabs CEO &amp; Co-Founder; Coinflipcanada, GMX Core Contributor; Jacob Blish, Lido Head of BD and Partnerships; Richard Ma, Quantstamp CEO; Marco Cora, Matter Labs (zkSync) SVP Business and Operations; Justin Reyes, Lido Head of DeFi BD; and Patrick Dai, Qtum Founder.</p>
<p>Having recently raised $7 million in seed funding – supported by some of the most renowned Web3-focused VCs such as Lemniscap, Blockchain Capital, Maven11 and Coinbase Ventures – RedStone is spearheading the development of cost-efficient, cross-chain oracles that provide high-performance DeFi protocols with rich, actionable real-time data at lower latency. RedStone provides affordable and reliable data feeds delivered to over 40 chains, including Ethereum, Avalanche, Polygon, Celo, Optimism, Arbitrum, Fantom, Stacks and EVMOS – all with testnets.</p>
<p>Founded in 2021 with first production deployment in January 2023, RedStone leverages a proprietary ‘EVM-connector’ method for putting data on-chain, in which data is automatically attached to a transaction and subsequently erased, reducing gas fees. By keeping signed data packages in the RedStone Data Access Layer and delivering them according to conditions set by dApps, gas costs can be reduced by up to 90% while achieving sub-second price feed latency on high-performance ecosystems. Moreover, RedStone offers data feeds that are unique and otherwise unavailable in the industry.</p>
<p>Jakub Wojciechowski, CEO and Founder of RedStone, said: “Receiving buy-in from these renowned Web3 visionaries is major validation for our platform. The oracle market has been monopolized for years, placing a glass ceiling on innovation and the ability of dApps’ to negotiate. By embracing modular flow, we are delivering a customizable data scalability layer that inherits the security of the destination chain. Sincere thanks to the participating angels for supporting our vision!”</p>
<p>Stani Kulechov, Aave Companies Founder and CEO said: “RedStone has created a unique, modular oracle that supports both new and established dApps on L1 and L2 networks. Combined with strong security measures and their ability to deliver non-standard data, RedStone is poised to provide choice and flexibility for the industry.”</p>
<blockquote><p>Sandeep Nailwal, Polygon Co-Founder said: “To create innovative protocols, we can’t keep on using the same concepts from the 2020 DeFi summer. The way oracles work has not evolved much in the past years, which stifles growth. We need quick responses to market trends, an architecture compatible with zk-powered L2s and optimization in gas costs &#8211; that’s what RedStone Oracles brings to the table.”</p>
<p>Alex Gluchovski, Matter Labs (zkSync) CEO &amp; Founder said: “Creative startups who come and challenge incumbents are very important as they boost growth and ecosystem vibrancy. In the coming months, we will see innovative DeFi protocols powered by RedStone models launching on major networks such as zkSync era.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>About RedStone</h2>
<p>RedStone is a next-generation cross-chain data oracle providing pricing data for financial protocols. It leverages the Arweave blockchain to create affordable storage with a permanent audit trail and provides an automatic dispute mechanism, backed with insurance through locked collateral from Data Providers. Follow the official RedStone and <a href="https://twitter.com/warp_contracts" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Warp</a> Twitter accounts to stay up to date on all key developments.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/top-web3-builders-back-redstones-cross-chain-expansion-with-350k-angel-round/" rel="nofollow">Top Web3 Builders Back RedStone’s Cross-Chain Expansion with $350K Angel Round</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>LOVESNOOPY Announces 85.0246% of Tokens Burned</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lovesnoopy-announces-85-0246-of-tokens-burned/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251810</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ILOVESNOOPY_1684767634Dob5uo0MIt.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ILOVESNOOPY_1684767634Dob5uo0MIt.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Seattle, USA / Washington, May 22nd, 2023] LOVESNOOPY, a meme coin inspired by the beloved original dog character Snoopy, has announced the burning of 65% of its total supply on May 21st, which, when combined with previous burns, amounts to 85.0246% tokens burned. The current price of $0.00000005928, the market capitalization of LOVESNOOPY [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Seattle, USA / Washington, May 22nd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>LOVESNOOPY, a meme coin inspired by the beloved original dog character Snoopy, has announced the burning of 65% of its total supply on May 21st, which, when combined with previous burns, amounts to 85.0246% tokens burned. The current price of $0.00000005928, the market capitalization of LOVESNOOPY stands at approximately $8.26 million USD.</p>
<p>I LOVE SNOOPY, a project that boldly launched with the vision of becoming the global number one memecoin, started by supporting its website in multiple languages from the beginning. I LOVE SNOOPY issues the Ethereum-based meme token, $LOVESNOOPY, while diligently executing its roadmap, including four burns, listings on MEXC, Bitrue, BitMart, and a <a href="https://skynet.certik.com/projects/i-love-snoopy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">recent successful security audit by CERTIK</a>. In addition, ILOVESNOOPY&#8217;s extensive fan base of nearly 200,000 Twitter followers boasts considerable fandom compared to other memecoins in its stage.</p>
<p>Internet detective ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1651238822963826694?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">highlighted</a> the abundance of memecoins, stating that a single individual created 114 scam memecoins over the past month, redirecting funds to the same address. The memecoin market is indeed saturated, with CoinMarketCap listing 706 memecoins in the &#8220;Memes&#8221; category.</p>
<p><strong>Evaluation and Risk Factors</strong></p>
<p>Although memecoins often lack clear issuers and tangible utility, their speculative nature makes them well-suited for the &#8220;high risk, high return&#8221; investment strategy. ILOVESNOOPY has addressed some previous concerns about centralization and has implemented the CERTICK audit to minimize risks.</p>
<h2>About LOVESNOOPY</h2>
<p>The main utility of <a href="https://www.snoopy.land/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">$LOVESNOOPY</a> is to establish a vibrant and impassioned meme community that we can embrace with all our hearts. LOVESNOOPY’s path to global domination is simple! Just enjoy and ‘LOVE SNOOPY’! The more people enjoy, and LOVE SNOOPY, the more indelible his legacy as a beloved meme will become.</p>
<p>LOVESNOOPY is the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lovesnoopy-announces-85-0246-of-tokens-burned/" rel="nofollow">LOVESNOOPY Announces 85.0246% of Tokens Burned</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Headed for Massive Price Moves Soon, According to This Metric</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-headed-for-massive-price-moves-soon-according-to-this-metric/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251785</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_price_prediction_2023.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_price_prediction_2023.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's 7-day price range is down to just 3.4%.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although typically regarded as a volatile asset with major price fluctuations, bitcoin has been stuck in a tight range for the past several days.</p>
<p>However, all that could change in the following days, at least according to similar historical developments.</p>
<ul>
<li>Aside from a price dive on May 12 to a two-month low, BTC&#8217;s recent performance has been rather <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-trx-soars-7-daily-bitcoin-btc-below-27k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">uneventful</a>.</li>
<li>The asset went to a high of $27,600 last week and then dipped by a grand, which was the most substantial price move of the past ten days or so.</li>
<li>Somewhat expectedly, the 7-day price range of the cryptocurrency has gone into rarely-seen territory. Glassnode informed that this metric is at 3.4% now, which is &#8220;one of the tightest of the last 3 years.&#8221;</li>
<li>Although rare, this development is not without previous examples. The analytics company provided a few of those, including one in July 2020 and another early this year (January 2023), both of which were followed by substantial price moves.</li>
<li>After the July 2020 stagnation, bitcoin went on a massive run that resulted in smashing the previous all-time high and charting a new one several months down the road. Following the January 2023 example, BTC shot up once again, albeit in a more modest fashion.</li>
<li>Another similar situation transpired in late 2021 and early 2022. That one, though, was followed by a significant price retracement that drove BTC from its ATH of $69,000 to under $30,000 in a few months.</li>
<li>Given the historical developments, Glassnode suggested that more volatility is in the cards for BTC but failed to make a prediction of whether it will be up or down.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The 7-day price range (3.4%) <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> has consolidated within is one of the tightest over the last 3yrs.</p>
<p>It is comparable to Jan 2023, and July 2020, both of which preceded large market moves.</p>
<p>This suggests high volatility is likely on the horizon.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4ca.png" alt="📊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/VHIhAlOSWL" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/VHIhAlOSWL</a> <a href="https://t.co/JZjvZe3yJa" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/JZjvZe3yJa</a></p>
<p>— glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1660513624593674240?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-headed-for-massive-price-moves-soon-according-to-this-metric/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin (BTC) Headed for Massive Price Moves Soon, According to This Metric</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
