<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:09:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>World of Dypians: A Virtual World That Allows Users To Play In and Build Out A Thriving Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/world-of-dypians-a-virtual-world-that-allows-users-to-play-in-and-build-out-a-thriving-metaverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257438</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-27_13-09-21.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-27_13-09-21.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Singapore, June 27th Since the metaverse gained mainstream popularity in the Fall of 2021, the world has been captivated by its potential. With over 400 million monthly active users and a projected market value of $900 billion by 2030, the metaverse has become a significant focus for game developers [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</p>
<p>Singapore, June 27th</p>
<p>Since the metaverse gained mainstream popularity in the Fall of 2021, the world has been captivated by its potential. With over 400 million monthly active users and a projected market value of $900 billion by 2030, the metaverse has become a significant focus for game developers and Web3 projects.</p>
<p>World of Dypians, the largest metaverse gaming platform ever built, is set to capture a substantial share of this burgeoning market. With its stunning metropolis landscapes and thrilling gameplay, WoD offers a unique and immersive experience.</p>
<p>One of the key aspects that set World of Dypians apart is its multiple blockchain support. Currently live on Ethereum and BNB Chain mainnets, the WoD metaverse has attracted thousands of users, including 2,800 beta testers actively enjoying the platform, and an additional 7,000 applicants eagerly awaiting access.</p>
<p>World of Dypians has set a bold goal to introduce new users to the world of cryptocurrencies through engaging content, educational campaigns, and exciting gameplay. To achieve this vision, the platform has already secured partnerships with prominent players in the Web3 and blockchain ecosystem, including Chainlink, KuCoin, Coin98, Avalanche, Gate.io, MEXC Global, and Easy2Stake.</p>
<p>Mihai Busica, the CEO of Dypius, expressed his excitement about the future of World of Dypians, saying, &#8220;Our incredible community of passionate players, combined with groundbreaking technologies and innovative storytelling, paves the way for a bright and extraordinary future. Together, we’ll continue to push boundaries, unlock new dimensions of imagination, and create a truly immersive experience that transcends the boundaries of gaming.&#8221;</p>
<p>With a vision to introduce new users to crypto through engaging content and exciting gameplay, WoD is on the path to shaping the future of the virtual universe. Join the adventure today and be a part of this extraordinary journey.</p>
<h2>About World of Dypians</h2>
<p>World of Dypians is a metaverse and virtual game that was created by Dypius. In the World of Dypians metaverse, players explore endless maps and participate in various activities such as hunting for rewards or purchasing items with digital currency. The game features a primary customizable character, which is chosen by the player. It is accompanied by NFTs and AI to help users on their journey exploring the different World of Dypians lands.</p>
<p>For more information, visit <a href="https://www.worldofdypians.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/worldofdypians" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/worldofdypians" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://t.co/qonk6rBbPy" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Discord</a> | <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCnRXdsNpnb2kMiNb7Cu4bDA" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Youtube</a> |</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/world-of-dypians-a-virtual-world-that-allows-users-to-play-in-and-build-out-a-thriving-metaverse/" rel="nofollow">World of Dypians: A Virtual World That Allows Users To Play In and Build Out A Thriving Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Arms in Partnership With Barrett Firearms to Launch Historic Barrett M82A1 NFT Drop</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/digital-arms-in-partnership-with-barrett-firearms-to-launch-historic-barrett-m82a1-nft-drop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257423</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/pasted_image_0_1687876942C9HRcutpjz.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/pasted_image_0_1687876942C9HRcutpjz.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Sydney, Australia, June 28th, 2023] In a first-of-its-kind collaboration, Digital Arms and Barrett Firearms are thrilled to announce the launch of the Barrett M82A1 Non-Fungible Token (NFT) collection on 28th June. This innovative partnership brings the legendary Barrett M82A1, renowned for its performance and reliability, to the digital world, offering collectors a [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Sydney, Australia, June 28th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>In a first-of-its-kind collaboration, <a href="https://www.hunter-token.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Digital Arms</a> and Barrett Firearms are thrilled to announce the launch of the Barrett M82A1 Non-Fungible Token (NFT) collection on 28th June. This innovative partnership brings the legendary Barrett M82A1, renowned for its performance and reliability, to the digital world, offering collectors a unique opportunity to own a piece of digital histoNon-fungible tokens, or NFTs, are unique digital assets stored on the blockchain, providing verifiable digital ownership rights. Unlike other digital assets, each NFT is unique, making them the perfect vehicle for digital collectibles. The Barrett M82A1 NFT collection, crafted from original 3D CAD files used in the actual manufacturing of Barrett firearms, embodies this uniqueness, making it a desirable collector&#8217;s item.</p>
<p>The Barrett M82A1 NFT is not just a digital asset, it&#8217;s a part of digital history and a testament to the convergence of technology, art, and history. Owning a Barrett M82A1 NFT is akin to holding a digital first-edition book or a unique piece of art. As the world&#8217;s first IP-licensed firearm NFT, it offers exclusivity and desirability unprecedented in the digital collectibles market.</p>
<p><strong>The Barrett M82A1 NFT brings a variety of benefits to its owners:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>In-Game Utility Across Partner Games: The Barrett NFT is a functional piece of gaming gear, enhancing your gaming experience across various partner platforms.</li>
<li>Exclusive Access Within the Digital Arms Ecosystem: As a Barrett NFT holder, you gain access to exclusive events, boosted APY in our HNTR Token staking platform, and unique content.</li>
<li>Join a Visionary Community: By acquiring a Barrett NFT, you join a forward-thinking community of gamers and investors.</li>
<li>Investment in the Future: The Barrett M82A1 NFT represents a strategic investment in the rapidly expanding market of blockchain technology.</li>
</ol>
<p>The NFT drop includes a total of 2222 Barrett M82A1 NFTs, comprising five distinct skins of varying rarity. The public sale begins on 28th June at 5 PM AEST (07:00 UTC). However, early birds with whitelist access can start claiming their NFTs 24 hours ahead, at 5 PM AEST (07:00 UTC) on 27th June.</p>
<p>The Barrett M82A1 NFT drop is an opportunity to be part of a historical digital revolution. More than just a digital asset, each NFT is a ticket to an exclusive community and a stake in the rapidly expanding world of blockchain technology. Secure your stake, enhance your gaming experience, and join us in this thrilling journey on the 28th June.</p>
<p>For more information, visit the <a href="https://www.hunter-token.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Digital Arms Marketplace</a>.</p>
<p><strong>About Digital Arms</strong></p>
<p>Digital Arms is an NFT creator and marketplace leveraging blockchain technology&#8217;s interoperability to bring real firearms and greater authenticity to Web3 gaming. As an NFT creator, Digital Arms builds scarce blockchain-based in-game items for first-person shooters, hunting and sports shooting titles. The platform is already partnered with some of the biggest names in the weapon manufacturing industry, including Blackwater, Primary Arms, Head Down Firearms and Barrett Firearms.</p>
<p class="ql-align-center"><a href="https://www.hunter-token.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/DigitalArmsNFT" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://www.facebook.com/digitalarmsnft" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Facebook</a> | <a href="https://t.me/huntertokenofficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://discord.com/invite/digital-arms" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a> | <a href="https://digital-arms.medium.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Medium</a> | <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC9GiplXdtSChL9D_iMNKt6A" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Youtube</a></p>
<p><strong>About Barrett</strong></p>
<p>Headquartered in Murfreesboro, Tennessee, Barrett is the world leader in large-caliber riﬂe design and manufacturing. In 2023, the company became part of the NIOA Group – a family-owned global munitions company based in Australia.</p>
<p>Barrett products are used by civilian sport shooters, law enforcement agencies, the United States military and more than 75 State Department approved countries across the world. The Barrett Quality Management System (QMS) has received the prestigious ISO 9001:2015 certiﬁcation for the design and manufacture of ﬁrearms, ammunition, and accessories, and to provide training for those systems.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimers and Legal Information</strong></p>
<p>Please note that participation in the Barrett M82A1 NFT drop involves certain risks and potential financial loss. The value of NFTs can be highly volatile, and there is no guarantee of future performance or value. This document does not constitute investment advice, and you should always do your own research before participating in any NFT sale.</p>
<p>All transactions will be subject to the terms and conditions of the Digital Arms Marketplace, and you must agree to these terms before you can participate in the NFT drop. Please read these terms carefully. They govern your use of the marketplace, your rights and obligations as a buyer, and our respective legal rights and responsibilities.</p>
<p>The Barrett M82A1 NFTs are digital assets that use blockchain technology. They are subject to various legal and regulatory requirements, which may vary significantly between jurisdictions. You are solely responsible for understanding and complying with any applicable laws, regulations, and duties in your jurisdiction.</p>
<p>Finally, please note that owning a Barrett M82A1 NFT does not confer any legal or ownership rights in the physical Barrett M82A1 firearm, the Barrett brand, or any other intellectual property owned by Barrett Firearms Manufacturing. The NFTs are purely digital assets, and their ownership is limited to the blockchain.</p>
<p>By participating in the Barrett M82A1 NFT drop, you acknowledge and agree to these terms, and you understand the risks associated with NFTs and cryptocurrency transactions. If you have any questions or concerns, we encourage you to seek independent legal advice.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/digital-arms-in-partnership-with-barrett-firearms-to-launch-historic-barrett-m82a1-nft-drop/" rel="nofollow">Digital Arms in Partnership With Barrett Firearms to Launch Historic Barrett M82A1 NFT Drop</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257415</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DWFxConflux_1687874589BaxFluxIJq.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DWFxConflux_1687874589BaxFluxIJq.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Hong Kong, China, June 28th, 2023] DWF Labs, the global digital asset market maker, and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, has further strengthened its commitment to support the growth of Conflux, the tree-graph consensus algorithm Layer-1 blockchain. Conflux has been gaining significant traction since February 2023 on the back of some key partnerships, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Hong Kong, China, June 28th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>DWF Labs, the global digital asset market maker, and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, has further strengthened its commitment to support the growth of Conflux, the tree-graph consensus algorithm Layer-1 blockchain. Conflux has been gaining significant traction since February 2023 on the back of some key partnerships, including the signature collaboration with China Telecom announced on February 15th, with the goal of developing a blockchain SIM (BSIM) card that was first unveiled in May.</p>
<p>DWF Labs recently purchased $18M in CFX token, cementing the long-term relationship between the investment firm and Conflux. This follows DFW Labs buying $10M worth of CFX tokens in March 2023.</p>
<p>More recently, Conflux joined Hong Kong’s Web3 Institute, participated in the Singapore Digital Economy Roundtable organized by the Singaporean Government, and led the drafting of IEEE P3217, an international blockchain standard by the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers. In addition, Conflux announced key partnerships including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Supremacy &#8211; Web3 security platform</li>
<li>dappOS &#8211; an operating protocol that manages crypto infrastructures for users</li>
<li>NuLink &#8211; a privacy-preserving technology that provides APIs for decentralized applications</li>
<li>Smooth Labs &#8211; developing the Layer 2 solution that supports parallel execution</li>
<li>Opside &#8211; a decentralized ZK-RaaS network featuring PoW of ZKP mining</li>
</ul>
<p>DWF Labs has made significant contributions to placing Conflux on the global stage. Since then, Conflux has established ecosystem partnerships with Floki, Worldcoin, Blockbank, Luganodes, AirDAO, Mask, and OpenEden, with a growing list of ongoing partnerships being discussed. Conflux and DWF Labs have also co-hosted multiple events, including those organized in Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Paris.</p>
<p>Fan Long, Conflux Network’s Co-Founder, stated: “Conflux Network has experienced exponential growth since the start of 2023, pioneering advances in the Chinese NFT market and establishing fresh Web3 access through the BSIM card project with China Telecom. DWF Lab is one of the key supporters of Conflux. This infusion of capital not only strengthens our bond, but also acts as a catalyst for our shared ambition to expand the Conflux ecosystem. Conflux plans to leverage the raised funds to further fuel its ecosystem growth in Asia and Hong Kong, empower burgeoning developer communities, and bring an increasing number of real-world assets onto the Conflux chain.”</p>
<blockquote><p>The Managing Partner of DWF Labs, Andrei Grachev stated: &#8220;We take great pride in our role as supporters of Conflux throughout its remarkable growth trajectory. It exemplifies our commitment to backing projects with immense potential and providing the necessary support to fill in the missing pieces of the Web3 puzzle. Our deep understanding of the crypto market has served as a compass for Conflux, allowing it to fully express its potential on the global stage. We are delighted to have played a part in Conflux&#8217;s journey towards success.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>About Conflux</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://confluxnetwork.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Conflux</a> is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols.</p>
<p>Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p>
<p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities in the region on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald’s China, and Oreo.</p>
<p><strong>About DWF Labs</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.dwf-labs.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DWF Labs</a> is the global digital asset market maker and multi-stage Web3 investment firm, supporting portfolio companies from token listing to market making to OTC trading solutions.</p>
<p>With offices in Singapore, Switzerland, the UAE, Hong Kong, South Korea and BVI, the investment company DWF Labs is an affiliate of Digital Wave Finance (DWF), which consistently ranks among the top 5 trading entities by volume in the cryptocurrency world through its proprietary technology for high-frequency trading.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dwf-labs-doubles-down-on-conflux-with-28-million-invested/" rel="nofollow">DWF Labs Doubles Down on Conflux with $28 Million Invested</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New PEPE Memecoin to Launch on BNB Chain</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-pepe-memecoin-to-launch-on-bnb-chain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257393</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-27_08-32-34_1687828796iAmg9VdEZf.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-27_08-32-34_1687828796iAmg9VdEZf.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Eden Island, Republic of Seychelles, June 27th, 2023] A new PEPE memecoin is launching, following hot on the heels of its Ethereum namesake. Issued as a BEP20 on BNB Chain, PEPE is a novel memecoin with a number of unique mechanisms programmed into its tokenomics. Like the original PEPE token, which has [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Eden Island, Republic of Seychelles, June 27th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>A new PEPE memecoin is launching, following hot on the heels of its Ethereum namesake. Issued as a BEP20 on BNB Chain, PEPE is a novel memecoin with a number of unique mechanisms programmed into its tokenomics.</p>
<p>Like the original PEPE token, which has proven a runaway success in 2023, the BEP20 PEPE draws its cues from the mischievous frog of the same name, whose design was derived from the webcomic &#8220;Boy&#8217;s Club.&#8221;</p>
<p>The market capitalization of the original PEPE token, which debuted on Ethereum in April, exceeded $1 billion on May 5th, prompting a new wave of memecoins, including a number of frog-themed efforts. Unlike subsequent memecoins, the PEPE (BEP20) has several unusual features programmed in including a syndication system designed to support price stabilization.</p>
<p>The team behind the BNB Chain PEPE aren’t settling for just one memecoin either: they plan to launch multiple PEPE projects, all based on the loveable frog. 13 such launches have been cued up for 2023 alone.</p>
<p>Although each PEPE project will operate independently, the introduction of a &#8220;Burn &amp; Drop&#8221; system will govern the consortium. Burn &amp; Drop is a first-of-its-kind system in which burning one token leads to the airdrop of another.</p>
<p>To initiate a Burn &amp; Drop, two types of tokens are required. For example, this could involve a scenario in which Token A is priced at $1 and PEPE (BEP20) is also priced at $1. However, if the price of Token A were to drop to $0.8, Token A holders would have the option to burn their tokens on the Burn &amp; Drop platform, automatically receiving PEPE (BEP20) through an airdrop, and with Token A having been burned, its total supply would decrease.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/2_1687895654gGffTWpnZh.jpg" /></p>
<p>By initiating the Burn &amp; Drop process between tokens, excess volatility can be reduced while possibly providing trading opportunities for arbitrage and intra-token trading. This logic is a fundamental component of PEPE (BEP20), and one which users can engage with directly within the platform.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/3_1687895715ru06UoZ1YN.jpg" /></p>
<p>In addition, PEPE (BEP20) has plans to introduce numerous services that will further extend the token’s utility. To further increase interest in the project, PEPE (BEP20) is currently running an airdrop campaign on Twitter that’s open to everyone.</p>
<p><strong>About PEPEBEP20</strong></p>
<p>PEPE is a project launched on the Binance Smart Chain, taking the form of a BEP20 token. The Pepe Syndicate and the unique &#8220;Burn&amp;Drop&#8221; mechanism of Pepe are designed to manage the token&#8217;s price volatility. This is not a guarantee of price stability, but a mechanism to potentially mitigate price fluctuations. Furthermore, various projects that participate in the &#8220;Burn&amp;Drop&#8221; system collaborate with each other, fostering a robust Pepe Syndicate network.</p>
<p>For more information regarding the campaign, please visit PEPE BEP20&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/pepecoinbep20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> (@pepecoinbep20) or Join PEPE BEP20&#8217;s <a href="https://t.me/pepe_bep20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram.</a></p>
<p><a href="https://pepe.markets/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>https://pepe.markets/</strong></a></p>
<p>PEPEBEP20 is the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><strong>PEPE BEP 20 FOUNDATION</strong><br />
<strong>pepebep20@gmail.com</strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-pepe-memecoin-to-launch-on-bnb-chain/" rel="nofollow">New PEPE Memecoin to Launch on BNB Chain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Firm Riot Secures 33,280 Mining Rigs Ahead of Halving</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-firm-riot-secures-33280-mining-rigs-ahead-of-halving/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257310</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Riot also has the option to potentially purchase an additional 66,000 machines.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the world&#8217;s largest Bitcoin mining firms &#8211; Riot Blockchain &#8211; has announced securing an initial order of 33,280 next-generation Bitcoin miners after entering into a long-term purchase agreement with China-based Bitcoin miner manufacturer MicroBT.</p>
<p>Riot said that the deal will boost the Colorado-based company&#8217;s self-mining capacity to 20.1 EH/s once the machines are installed in the first quarter of 2024.</p>
<h2>Riot&#8217;s Boost its Hashrate Capacity</h2>
<p>Announcing Riot&#8217;s first order of Bitcoin miners for its Corsicana Facility, the company&#8217;s CEO Jason Les <a href="https://www.riotplatforms.com/news-media/press-releases/detail/155/riot-purchases-7-6-ehs-of-next-generation-miners-from" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">explained</a> that the new additions are among the most powerful and efficient miners ever made for Bitcoin mining. The exec further added that these new models are designed and produced specifically for immersion cooling systems, such as those that will be used at Riot&#8217;s Texas facility.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;These new miners will contribute an additional 7.6 EH/s to Riot’s self-mining capacity when fully deployed and will further enhance our already strong fleet efficiency in advance of the upcoming Bitcoin halving.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As per the official statement, the initial order for the agreement clocks in at 33,280 machines costing approximately $163 million, or $21.50 per terahash (TH). Riot has the option to purchase an additional 66,560 machines before the end of 2024 at the same terms.</p>
<p>The new partnership between the two companies is expected to secure a &#8220;robust&#8221; domestic supply chain in the United States. Besides, MicroBT will be tasked with manufacturing these miners at a Pittsburgh facility resulting in the creation of new jobs in the region.</p>
<p>MicroBT&#8217;s COO Jordan Chen also said all machines that will be manufactured will help in expanding the former&#8217;s operations in the country, thereby enabling them to boost their market share in the US. The M56S+ and M56S++ models bought by Riot are reportedly the most powerful machines developed by MicroBT.</p>
<h2>Riot Mined 740 BTC in January</h2>
<p>The recent winter storms in Texas damaged the Rockdale Facility, which slashed the hash rate capacity of Riot. Despite this, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/riot-mined-an-all-time-high-of-740-btc-in-january/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">generated</a> a 740 BTC in January a 62% increase compared to January 2022 and a new monthly all-time high.</p>
<p>During the same period, Riot also announced plans to onboard with new members even as it rival Core Scientific laid off a chunk of their employees.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-firm-riot-secures-33280-mining-rigs-ahead-of-halving/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Mining Firm Riot Secures 33,280 Mining Rigs Ahead of Halving</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey Calls Out Tim Cook: Why Doesn&#8217;t Apple Pay Support Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-calls-out-tim-cook-why-doesnt-apple-pay-support-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 23:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257401</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/jackdorsey_cnbc.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/jackdorsey_cnbc.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin-based social app Damus has been banned from Apple’s app store – and Jack Dorsey is not pleased.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Block CEO Jack Dorsey is putting Apple CEO Tim Cook on blast for seemingly not supporting Bitcoin payments, per the app store’s policies.</p>
<p>His comments follow Apple’s recent confirmation that it would be pulling the Bitcoin-based social app, Damus, from its marketplace.</p>
<h2>Apple’s Crackdown On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Damus is a decentralized social media app for interacting with Nostr – a Bitcoin-based protocol for exchanging information and messages in a censorship-resistant manner.</p>
<p>The app includes a tipping feature called “zaps” which let users tip one another in Bitcoin over the lightning network. The value exchange is totally peer-to-peer, and Damus takes no cut from such transactions.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the feature <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-backed-damus-faces-explusion-from-apples-app-store-over-bitcoin-tipping-feature/" data-wpel-link="internal">ran afoul</a> of Apple’s terms of service two weeks ago. The company said that it could allow for optional tips and donations, but not for payments that were required in exchange for digital content. “They must use in-app purchase in accordance with guideline 3.1.1,” said the company.</p>
<p>Damus refused to remove this functionality from its app, and tried to explain that zaps did not “unlock” any digital content for users. However, it <a href="https://twitter.com/damusapp/status/1673326463297392640" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">received</a> the same message from Apple again on Monday, and accepted that its removal from the app store was imminent.</p>
<p>“Their suggested fix is to use apple pay,” tweeted Damus on Tuesday. “Sure, I&#8217;ll use apple pay when it supports censorship-resistant, peer-to-peer payments to anyone in the world. Maybe start with peer-to-peer first?”</p>
<h2>Jack Dorsey Responds</h2>
<p>Jack Dorsey was quick to defend Damus on Monday upon hearing the news. “Tips aren’t unlocking content,” he <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1673364469068578822" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>, rehashing the company’s own arguments.</p>
<p>He followed up on Tuesday by calling out Apple’s CEO specifically:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Why doesn’t Apple Pay support bitcoin <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@tim_cook</a>? <a href="https://t.co/2TfqzgXUP1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/2TfqzgXUP1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; jack (@jack) <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1673634767403712514?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“Removed from the App Store for enabling tipping to everyone in the world without the need for a bank, payment card, or government permission,” he added.</p>
<p>Dorsey has previously praised Nostr for being one of two “truly censorship resistant technologies at scale” – alongside Bitcoin itself. While still the CEO of Twitter, Dorsey helped enable a tipping feature on the platform that incorporated Bitcoin lightning tips similar to those used by Nostr.</p>
<p>Tim Cook hasn’t shown interest in putting Bitcoin on Apple’s balance sheet but has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/apple-ceo-tim-cook-confirms-owning-bitcoin-or-ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> that he personally owns some coins.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-calls-out-tim-cook-why-doesnt-apple-pay-support-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Jack Dorsey Calls Out Tim Cook: Why Doesn&#8217;t Apple Pay Support Bitcoin?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Has 70% Odds Of Winning SEC Lawsuit: Bloomberg Analyst</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-has-70-odds-of-winning-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257388</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/grayscale_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/grayscale_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Grayscale’s oral arguments and BlackRock’s ETF filing create a strong likelihood that a Bitcoin spot ETF is approved this year, analysts claim.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The company behind the world’s largest Bitcoin fund has a 70% chance of overcoming the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a major crypto industry lawsuit, according to Bloomberg Intelligence Senior Legal Analyst Elliot Z. Stein.</p>
<p>Given the circumstances, the firm’s analysts assign a 50% likelihood to a Bitcoin spot ETF being approved in the United States this year.</p>
<h2>Grayscale, BlackRock, and the SEC</h2>
<p>According to Stein, the optimistic outlook for Grayscale’s lawsuit may actually serve to benefit BlackRock – which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for a spot ETF product last week – rather than Grayscale’s own filing.</p>
<p>“The SEC and Chair Gary Gensler may be bracing for a loss and looking to preemptively soften it or make it meaningless by approving spot Bitcoin ETF application before or around the same time as a court decision,” <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1673685658538323968" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wrote</a> the analyst in a Tuesday note.</p>
<p>Grayscale’s lawsuit <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-rejects-grayscale-spot-bitcoin-etf-sparking-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> the SEC of violating the Administrative Procedure Act and Securities Exchange Act by arbitrarily denying its Bitcoin spot ETF application last year, despite choosing to approve many similar futures ETF products.</p>
<p>The SEC has rejected every spot ETF application to date, citing failures from their prospective issuers to provide sufficient protections and oversight against market manipulation.</p>
<p>During the first round of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judges-scrutinize-sec-during-oral-arguments-in-grayscale-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">oral arguments</a> in March, all three judges overseeing the case expressed skepticism of the SEC’s case, stating that the agency “has not offered any explanation that the petitioners are wrong.” For Stein, this skepticism boosted Grayscale’s odds of victory from 40% to 70%.</p>
<h2>BlackRock’s Approval Odds</h2>
<p>Bitcoin rallied above $31,000 this week on optimism that a Bitcoin spot ETF could be approved after BlackRock’s filing. Prior submissions from the $10 trillion asset manager have a historical <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" data-wpel-link="internal">approval rate</a> of 575:1.</p>
<p>The SEC even <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/27/the-first-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-is-hitting-the-market-as-crypto-gains-new-momentum.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">approved</a> a leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF last week. Bloomberg’s ETF analyst James Seyffart interpreted this as a sign that the SEC’s attitude toward Bitcoin products could be “lightening up,” per a <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1672275688458539009" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> on Friday.</p>
<p>That said, there’s one aspect of BlackRock’s ETF filing that Seyffart thinks could undermine its application: its partnership with Coinbase for custody – an exchange that the SEC just filed a major lawsuit against.</p>
<p>“You have to take that as a risk,” he said during an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ILy-74GVxV8&amp;ab_channel=UnchainedPodcast" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> on the Unchained podcast on Friday. “We don’t think the odds of this thing getting approved are like 70% like we think the Grayscale lawsuit. The odds are still stacked against BlackRock.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-has-70-odds-of-winning-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-analyst/" rel="nofollow">Grayscale Has 70% Odds Of Winning SEC Lawsuit: Bloomberg Analyst</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swiss National Bank Will Do a Test Run of CBDCs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-national-bank-will-do-a-test-run-of-cbdcs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Switzerland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257316</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Switzerland.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Switzerland.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Swiss CBDC will be sold on the SIX platform and counted as a test run for a possible wider release.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the Point Zero Forum banking conference held in Zurich yesterday, the upcoming launch of a Swiss CHF-based CBDC was announced by Thomas Jordan, the chairman of the Swiss Nation Bank (SNB).</p>
<p>Although no exact date has been put forth by the bank, the chairman of the SNB announced that the CBDC would be released sooner rather than later. This seems in line with earlier <a href="https://www.bis.org/about/bisih/topics/cbdc/tourbillon.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statements</a> from the BIS – who often work closely with the SNB – who planned to have a working prototype ready by mid-2023 as part of Switzerland’s research into cryptocurrencies, codenamed Project Tourbillon.</p>
<h2>Launching On SIX</h2>
<p>According to Jordan, the CBDC will be available – for a limited time only – on SIX Digital Exchange. SIX Digital Exchange is a subsidiary of the SIX Group, which also controls the official stock exchange of Switzerland and the 3<sup>rd</sup> largest stock exchange in Europe.</p>
<p>Although the institution he represents will view the endeavor as a simple test run to ascertain whether a larger scale approach to eCHF is warranted or not, the chairman of the SNB has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/snb-launch-digital-currency-pilot-chairman-2023-06-26/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">confirmed</a> that the CBDC will be “real money”, backed by his institution.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This is not just an experiment, it will be real money equivalent to bank reserves and the objective is to test real transactions with market participants. We do not exclude that we will never introduce retail [CBDCs] but nevertheless we are a little bit prudent at the moment.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Cash Will Remain A Fixture</h2>
<p>At a separate panel held at the same conference, Andrea Maechler – the governor of the SNB – clarified that even if CBDCs are introduced at a larger scale within Switzerland, cash will not be going anywhere.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;[Cash] is the one way that retail households can hold central bank money. That feature needs to be maintained irrespective of the technology&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>The introduction of a CBDC – even if only as a test run – is indicative of the constant research performed by Swiss authorities on the subject, considering their prior outright <a href="https://www.handelszeitung.ch/unternehmen/nationalbank-blockchain-ist-ungeeignet-fur-digitales-zentralbankengeld-342522" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">refusal</a> to consider blockchain-based reserves.</p>
<p>Known worldwide as a banking sector leader, Switzerland has always ensured that its citizens have easy and equitable access to a share of the country’s vast resources and reserves.</p>
<p>Although Switzerland has always been open to exploring new technical solutions – regarding financial products or otherwise – the financial stability of its citizens has remained a steadfast priority of the small yet powerful nation nestled within the Alps.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-national-bank-will-do-a-test-run-of-cbdcs/" rel="nofollow">Swiss National Bank Will Do a Test Run of CBDCs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Pays Close Attention to Hong Kong&#8217;s Crypto Policies, CEO Allaire Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circle-pays-close-attention-to-hong-kongs-crypto-policies-ceo-allaire-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257266</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Jeremy_Allaire.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Jeremy_Allaire.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to Circle's CEO, Asia is a huge area of focus.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jeremy Allaire &#8211; co-founder and CEO of the stablecoin-issuer Circle &#8211; said his company has been closely observing the regulatory developments in Hong Kong. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of the former British colony have recently allowed investors to trade cryptocurrency under a new regime as they carry &#8220;fundamental value.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Asia is a &#8216;Huge Area of Focus&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-firm-circle-eyeing-hong-kong-policies-with-asia-in-focus-1.1938301" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Bloomberg, Allaire noted Hong Kong&#8217;s efforts to establish itself as a &#8220;very significant center for digital markets and for stablecoins.&#8221; As such, Circle is paying &#8220;very close attention to that,&#8221; he added.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The executive sees Asia as an important region for the industry. Recall that Circle </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-and-paxos-secure-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> regulatory approval from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) in November last year. The license enabled the firm to offer digital payment token products and conduct cross-border and local transactions in the city-state.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ruling body of Hong Kong has shown a pro-crypto stance lately, introducing a regulatory framework for the sector at the beginning of the month. According to the new rules, digital asset providers can offer services to retail clients, assuming disclaimers of the possible investment risks are in place.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some suggested that Hong Kong&#8217;s positive approach could signal that China might start warming up to the industry. The government of the world&#8217;s most populated country </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/trading-and-mining-crackdown-in-china-escalates-bitcoin-plunges-3k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">banned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> all crypto-related activities on its territory in 2021.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Moreover, the subsidiaries of some of the largest Chinese banking institutions, including the Bank of Communications, the Bank of China, and Shanghai Pudong Development Bank, have supposedly </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/leading-chinese-banks-support-hong-kong-based-crypto-firms-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">supported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> crypto companies based in Hong Kong.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;What&#8217;s happening in Hong Kong may be a proxy for ultimately how do these markets grow in Greater China,&#8221; Allaire concluded.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_173640" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-173640" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-173640" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" alt="Jeremy Allaire" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-173640" class="wp-caption-text">Jeremy Allaire, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hong Kong Said &#8216;Yes&#8217; to Crypto ETFs</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides implementing cryptocurrency rules, Hong Kong </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/hsbc-hong-kong-lets-clients-trade-btc-and-eth-etfs-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">recently jumped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on the cryptocurrency ETF bandwagon. Earlier this week, Hong Kong and Shanghai Banking Corporation (HSBC) – the largest domestic bank &#8211; enabled clients to buy and sell Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The approved products include CSOP Bitcoin Futures ETF, CSOP Ethereum Futures, and Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, the bank launched an educational program called the Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre, whose goal is to tutor investors for the risks they might encounter when joining the ecosystem.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-pays-close-attention-to-hong-kongs-crypto-policies-ceo-allaire-says/" rel="nofollow">Circle Pays Close Attention to Hong Kong&#8217;s Crypto Policies, CEO Allaire Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Reason Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Surged Over 100% in 7 Days</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-reason-bitcoin-cash-bch-surged-over-100-in-7-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257357</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/bitcoin_cash-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/bitcoin_cash-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash is seriously outperforming the rest of the crypto market. Where’s the hype coming from?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) – the most popular hardfork of Bitcoin (BTC)&#8217;s blockchain – is up over 117% this week, outperforming Bitcoin’s still sizable 15% rise. As of this writing, its the only coin to see anything close to 2X gains within that time frame.</p>
<p>What’s attracting traders and investors to the large-blocker network? Let’s dive in.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash’s EDX Listing</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Cash’s seismic gains began on June 21, precisely when the Wall Street-backed crypto exchange EDX Markets (EDXM) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-backed-cryptocurrency-exchange-edx-goes-live/" data-wpel-link="internal">went live</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/citadel-charles-schwab-fidelity-launched-crypto-exchange-edx-markets/" data-wpel-link="internal">Announced</a> in September 2022, the exchange – backed by Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, and Charles Schwab – promised: “a platform that can meet the needs of both retail traders and institutional investors with high compliance and security standards.”</p>
<p>Upon launch, the high-profile exchange kept its listing count to a conservative four digital assets. One of them, however, was BCH – which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-explodes-100-weekly-as-btc-looks-for-direction-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">rose</a> to $231 on Tuesday, from just $111 on June 21.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257361" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257361" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257361 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-1024x564.png" alt="" width="1024" height="564" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-1024x564.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-300x165.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-768x423.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-1536x846.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-50x28.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20.png 1574w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257361" class="wp-caption-text">BCH / USD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>According to crypto market intelligence platform Santiment, BCH was the biggest beneficiary of the EDXM listing compared to the platform’s other coins, including BTC, Ether (ETH), and Litecoin (LTC). “Notably, $BCH has seen a 3-year high in social discussion rates, &amp; volume has easily eclipsed 2023 highs,” the company <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1672443431602491392" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweeted</a> on Friday.</p>
<p>Data from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/currencies/BCH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Coinglass</a> shows that liquidations for trades involving the coin have also moonshot this week and have mostly impacted short traders, indicating that something of a short squeeze is underway.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash’s Regulatory Status</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Cash’s approval by an exchange backed by Wall Street incumbents may be viewed as tacit approval of the coin’s safe regulatory status compared to other altcoins.</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued crypto exchange giants Binance and Coinbase earlier this month for listing many alleged “securities” including large caps coins like Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC).</p>
<p>The four coins listed have already been granted regulatory safeguards in certain segments of the global crypto market. Canada, for example, <a href="https://help.newton.co/hc/en-us/articles/4413904757651" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">imposes</a> a net buy limit on exchange users of $30,000 per year for most cryptocurrencies, but excludes BTC, ETH, LTC, and BCH from that rule.</p>
<p>SEC Chair Gary Gensler has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-reasserts-every-crypto-is-a-security-aside-from-bitcoin-lawyers-disagree/" data-wpel-link="internal">explained</a> that he considers Bitcoin a unique commodity because of its “unique history and creation story.” Bitcoin Cash, however, is a mere fork of Bitcoin’s blockchain code, sharing Bitcoin’s history in terms of how it is issued.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-reason-bitcoin-cash-bch-surged-over-100-in-7-days/" rel="nofollow">The Reason Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Surged Over 100% in 7 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
