<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 09:17:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pomerium Secures $20 Million Angel Investment and Gets Listed on Bitget</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pomerium-secures-20-million-angel-investment-and-gets-listed-on-bitget/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252496</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pomerium_1685006333jrrt1gZMMe.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pomerium_1685006333jrrt1gZMMe.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, May 25th, 2023] Pomerium Pte. Ltd., a leading Web3 gaming studio, is proud to announce that it has secured a $20 million angel investment from an undisclosed investor. The funding will allow the company to expand its portfolio of blockchain-based games and drive innovation in the rapidly growing Web3 gaming [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, May 25th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://pomerium.space/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Pomerium Pte. Ltd</strong></a><strong>.</strong>, a leading Web3 gaming studio, is proud to announce that it has secured a $20 million angel investment from an undisclosed investor. The funding will allow the company to expand its portfolio of blockchain-based games and drive innovation in the rapidly growing Web3 gaming industry.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to have secured this significant investment from an undisclosed investor,&#8221; said Kim CEO of <strong>Pomerium Pte. Ltd.</strong> &#8220;It demonstrates a strong belief in our team, our vision, and the potential of blockchain-based gaming to revolutionise the gaming industry. With this investment, we can accelerate our development, attract top talent, and bring new and exciting games to our users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Pomerium Pte. Ltd.</strong>, founded in February 2022, has established itself as a leading innovator in the Web3 gaming space, with a portfolio of casual P2E games that leverage the security and transparency of blockchain technology. The company&#8217;s games provide users with a unique and immersive experience, with ownership and control over their in-game assets, including NFTs and utility tokens.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are proud of the progress we have made so far, and we are excited about the opportunities ahead. Our mission is to create the best Web3 gaming experiences for our users, and this investment will help us achieve that.&#8221; said <strong>Kim</strong>.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Pomerium</strong> is committed to advancing the Web3 gaming industry by delivering high-quality, innovative, and fun casual games that engage and delight users.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, <strong>Pomerium</strong> has listed $PMG (Pomerium Ecosystem Token) on Bitget, a leading global cryptocurrency exchange. The listing, which occurred on May 4, 2023, marks a significant milestone for Pomerium as it seeks to expand its influence in the fast-growing blockchain gaming industry.</p>
<p>Bitget, an exchange that adopted Proof of Reserve (PoR), has recently launched a $100 million Web3 fund to support promising Web3 projects in Asia. Pomerium&#8217;s selection for listing on Bitget underscores the platform&#8217;s strong reputation and potential for growth.</p>
<h2>About Pomerium</h2>
<p><a href="https://pomerium.space/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Pomerium</a> is a Web3 multi-game platform that focuses on mobile games. Its unique token economy is designed to create a sustainable mobile gaming ecosystem, and its platform enables gamers to play games on mobile devices instead of being limited to PC or web browsers. Pomerium plans to expand its services and influence in the GameFi market in the coming years.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pomerium-secures-20-million-angel-investment-and-gets-listed-on-bitget/" rel="nofollow">Pomerium Secures $20 Million Angel Investment and Gets Listed on Bitget</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 09:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252499</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CerusMarkets-400-1Leverage_1200x720_1_16850053681RTEn4cVLP.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CerusMarkets-400-1Leverage_1200x720_1_16850053681RTEn4cVLP.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Labuan, Malaysia, May 26th, 2023] Cerus Markets is thrilled to announce an exciting update to its leverage options for non-crypto instruments. Effective immediately, Cerus Markets clients can enjoy leverage of up to 400:1 for Forex, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks trading. This increase in leverage options allows traders to make the most [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Labuan, Malaysia, May 26th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Cerus Markets is thrilled to announce an exciting update to its leverage options for non-crypto instruments. Effective immediately, Cerus Markets clients can enjoy <strong>leverage of up to 400:1</strong> for Forex, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks trading.</p>
<p>This increase in leverage options allows traders to make the most of their investments, providing greater market exposure and the potential for higher returns. By offering increased leverage options for non-crypto instruments, Cerus Markets aims to provide clients with even more opportunities to capitalize on market movements.</p>
<p>At Cerus Markets, the company prides itself on its commitment to providing clients with the best possible trading experience. This update is just one example of the company&#8217;s dedication to ensuring that clients have access to the best tools and trading conditions.</p>
<h2>About Cerus Markets</h2>
<p>Established in 2022, Cerus Markets Limited is a multi-asset broker authorized and regulated by the Labuan Financial Service Authority, Malaysia. With a focus on innovation, Cerus offers unique crypto derivative products that allow clients to trade over 200 instruments paired with cryptocurrencies. Alongside crypto derivatives, Cerus provides trading opportunities in FX, Commodities, Indices, and Single Stocks.</p>
<p>Cerus Markets believes in empowering traders of all levels with easy and affordable access to the market. The trading platform stands out from traditional brokers by not charging entry fees and allowing trading of a wide range of digital assets starting from just $50, with leverage up to 400:1.</p>
<p>Moreover, traders can benefit from a <strong>100% deposit matching bonus</strong>, doubling the amount of their first deposit and further enhancing their trading experience.</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://cerusmarkets.com/?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">cerusmarkets.com</a> to learn more about Cerus Markets and its offerings.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/cerusmarkets/?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Instagram</a> l <a href="https://twitter.com/CerusMarkets?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> l <a href="https://t.me/cerusmarkets_official?&amp;PARTNER_ID=81328&amp;clientSource=PR_distribution&amp;referral=leverage_update&amp;utm_source=Chainwire_com&amp;utm_medium=PR_distribution" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cerus-markets-announces-4001-leverage-update/" rel="nofollow">Cerus Markets Announces 400:1 Leverage Update</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Stable Above $26K as XRP, LTC, ARB Jump 3% (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-stable-above-26k-as-xrp-ltc-arb-jump-3-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 08:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252488</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple, Litecoin, and Arbitrum have added the most value from the top 50 alts today. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After dipping to a 13-day low yesterday, bitcoin reacted well and regained almost $600 in the following hours.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also slightly in the green on a daily scale, including ETH, MATIC, XRP, and LTC. LDO, on the other hand, has dropped below $2.</p>
<h2>BTC Remains Above $26K</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency stood in a tight range, as confirmed by Glassnode recently, that had it trading mostly around $27,000. It tried its hand to break out of it a few times but was stopped at $27,500.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-rejected-at-27-5k-while-ldo-ltc-dumped-by-6-daily-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">latest rejection</a> came on Wednesday and brought the asset south hard. Firstly, BTC dropped under $27,000, but the bears took it a step further yesterday. This culminated in a drop to $25,900, which became bitcoin&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumped-to-2-week-low-apecoin-nosedives-8-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">lowest price position</a> in almost two weeks.</p>
<p>The bulls finally reminded of their presence at this point and started helping bitcoin recover some of its lost value. At first, they pushed it to over $26,000 and later propelled another minor leg up that resulted in BTC jumping to its current value of $26,500.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency is up by 1% in a day, and its market cap has increased above $510 billion. Its dominance over the alts sits stagnant, though, at 46.2%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252497" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252497" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252497" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-25-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252497" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LTC, XRP, ARB Up 3-4%</h2>
<p>The altcoins also suffered yesterday, but most have produced minor gains now. ETH went below $1,800 for the first time in a few weeks, but a 2% increase since then has pushed it above that level as of now.</p>
<p>Cardano, Dogecoin, Solana, and Shiba Inu are also slightly in the green. Ripple, MATIC, and Litecoin have jumped by somewhere between 2.5% and 4% in the past 24 hours. Arbitrum has increased by a similar percentage as well.</p>
<p>Lido DAO&#8217;s native token, though, has slipped for a second consecutive day and currently trades below $2.</p>
<p>In total, the crypto market cap has managed to defend the $1.1 trillion level and has added $15 billion daily.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252501" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252501" style="width: 1880px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252501" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5.png" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1880" height="825" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5.png 1880w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5-300x132.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5-1024x449.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5-768x337.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5-1536x674.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-5-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1880px) 100vw, 1880px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252501" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-stable-above-26k-as-xrp-ltc-arb-jump-3-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">BTC Stable Above $26K as XRP, LTC, ARB Jump 3% (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dip Buying Sentiment Slides as Bitcoin Drops to Long-Term Support</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dip-buying-sentiment-slides-as-bitcoin-drops-to-long-term-support/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 07:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252441</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_red_background_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_red_background_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders and short-term speculators have traditionally “bought the dips” but that sentiment appears to be waning at the moment.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On May 26, on-chain analytics provider Santiment observed that Bitcoin traders often buy short-term, small crypto price dips but have been scared to buy the longer-term bigger ones.</p>
<p>It added that mentions of buying the dip are dormant at the moment, suggesting very weak market sentiment.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Historically, this kind of #FUD has been good to capitalize on,” it said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Bitcoin prices have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumped-to-2-week-low-apecoin-nosedives-8-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">retreated</a> almost 15% since its rally to just under $31,000 in mid-April. The lack of volume at the moment also suggests that this dip isn’t low enough yet to entice more buying pressure.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Drops to Support</h2>
<p>Santiment also reported that there has been an increase in selling at a loss among crypto holders. It used the MVRV (market-value-to-realized-value) metric, which indicates the vast majority of crypto assets are flashing under-bought signals across the sector.</p>
<blockquote><p>“With markets seeming dull to traders, we&#8217;re continuing to see restless addresses emptying their wallets and selling at a loss.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Glassnode noted that using the previous bull market peak as an anchor, Bitcoin price has fallen to the golden Fibonacci ratio of -61.8%. This is at $26,200, where prices had fallen to a few hours ago.</p>
<p>Since then, BTC has nudged up slightly to just below $26,500 at the time of writing but remains bearish in the short term.</p>
<p>Following weeks of consolidation and slow depreciation, the Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index has remained at neutral status. It is currently showing a value of 49 where it has been for the past fortnight.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Crypto markets fell to a ten-week low in late trading on May 25, with total capitalization falling to $1.14 trillion. They have only recovered marginally during the Friday morning Asian trading session suggesting more consolidation could be ahead over the weekend.</p>
<p>Following a dip to $26,000, BTC prices have added half a percent on the day but remain sideways, hovering just above long-term support levels. A breakdown from here would find further support at around $25,000.</p>
<p>Ethereum prices fell to $1,770 yesterday but have since recovered to trade at $1,807 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>The only altcoins posting a measurable gain at the moment are XRP, MATIC, and LTC, each having gained 3% on the day.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dip-buying-sentiment-slides-as-bitcoin-drops-to-long-term-support/" rel="nofollow">Dip Buying Sentiment Slides as Bitcoin Drops to Long-Term Support</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Currency Group Shuts Down TradeBlock Unit, Trade Execution Service</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/digital-currency-group-shuts-down-tradeblock-unit-trade-execution-service/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252454</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DCG_Stop.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/DCG_Stop.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[TradeBlock - the trade execution and prime brokerage arm of DCG - will shut down effective as of May 31st.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital Currency Group &#8211; the cryptocurrency firm founded and spearheaded by Barry Silber, announced today that it will be shutting down its trade execution and prime brokerage unit &#8211; TradeBlock.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-25/digital-currency-group-closes-tradeblock-institutional-platform?leadSource=uverify%20wall" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, the shutdown of the unit will be effective starting from May 31st.</li>
<li>CoinDesk, the news media owned by DCG, also revealed a statement by the latter:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>Due to the state of the braoder economy and prolonged crypto winter, along wiht the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the US, we made the deision to susnet the institutional traading platform side of the business, known as TradeBlock, effective May 31, 2023.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Interestingly enough, TradeBlock was acquired back in 2020 by the media company itself but was later spun out as a standalone business. The details of the acquisition were not revealed.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/digital-currency-group-shuts-down-tradeblock-unit-trade-execution-service/" rel="nofollow">Digital Currency Group Shuts Down TradeBlock Unit, Trade Execution Service</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gateway to Cosmos 2023 Announces Speakers for Europe’s Largest Internet of Blockchains Ecosystem Gathering</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gateway-to-cosmos-2023-announces-speakers-for-europes-largest-internet-of-blockchains-ecosystem-gathering/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252381</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Gateway_to_cosmos_1685023107n5qmO8aawz.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Gateway_to_cosmos_1685023107n5qmO8aawz.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Prague, Czech Republic, May 25th, 2023] Conference and Hackathon set for June 3-5 to start Prague Blockchain Week  Gateway to Cosmos 2023 announced today the speakers and sponsors for the three-day in-person conference and hackathon in Prague June 3-5 that will bring together top Web3 minds to shape the future of Cosmos, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Prague, Czech Republic, May 25th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><em><strong>Conference and Hackathon set for June 3-5 to start Prague Blockchain Week </strong></em></p>
<p><a href="https://gateway.events/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Gateway to Cosmos</a> 2023 announced today the speakers and sponsors for the three-day in-person conference and hackathon in Prague June 3-5 that will bring together top Web3 minds to shape the future of Cosmos, the Internet of blockchains.</p>
<p>The event, which will kick off <a href="https://explore.prgblockweek.com/23" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Prague Blockchain Week</a>, where Vitalik Buterin is a confirmed attendee, and will be the largest Cosmos community gathering in Europe, with 40+ exceptional speakers, 30+ presentations, 10 panel discussions, and 15 workshops.</p>
<p>In addition to attending scheduled addresses, an anticipated 600 attendees will have a chance to browse the booths in the Cosmos Gateway Expo, talk to project and vendor teams, network with fellow Cosmonauts – as community members refer to one another – or visit the oasis of the Neutron Hackers Lounge for a chance to code, chat and chill.</p>
<p>Cosmos and its Inter-Blockchain Communication (IBC) protocol solves what was previously a key challenge for builders in Web3 &#8211; the need to select a blockchain, like Ethereum, Avalanche, Solana, or Aptos, to build their applications upon. Projects benefit if that chain’s adoption grows, because a vibrant application ecosystem means more users, and better user journeys. With Cosmos / IBC technology, builders now launch applications that are operational across chains from Day 1, and can focus only on developing great products and businesses.</p>
<p>The conference will showcase the ecosystem’s leading projects and startups, technical roadmap developments, investment trends, and offer a window on adjacent technologies, like privacy and scaling solutions, with the potential to advance today’s most exciting blockchain use cases.</p>
<p>“While other blockchain technologies that were once the darlings of builders, users, and investors have struggled in this more bearish environment, Cosmos is uniquely on the rise. It has attracted more developers than almost any other blockchain ecosystem &#8211; a testament to the now-clear benefits of “app-chains,” and the limitations of public blockchains. Cosmos has emerged as a main rival to Ethereum to house the future of decentralized finance (DeFi),” said Samantha Bohbot of RockawayX, the global venture capital firm and an organizer of the conference.</p>
<p>Speakers will include leaders of prominent projects that use Cosmos and Inter-Blockchain Communication (IBC) technology, including Osmosis Co-Founder Sunny Aggarwal, Sommelier Co-Founder Zaki Manian, Agoric Co-Founder Dean Tribble, and Juno Co-Founder Jake Hartwell, just to name a few. Others, like Node Capital’s Amos Meiri, The Block’s Frank Chapparro, and Binance’s Kiril Khomiakov will offer fresh perspectives from outside Cosmos’ borders.</p>
<p>Gateway to Cosmos 2023 builds on the success of last year’s Rockaway-hosted<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jiyfbQ91bm8" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> inaugural conference</a>, a buzzy, packed event that drew 300+ attendees and was rated a success by guests and speakers alike.</p>
<p>Day One, Launching The Rocket into Cosmos, will feature the best use cases already in production as well as those hitting the launchpad in the near future. Keynote addresses will come from key representatives of Cosmos, Interchain, Informal, Agoric, Celestia, Sommelier, and NYM, among others.</p>
<p>Day Two will focus on steering the Cosmos rocket in the right direction. Speakers will lift the hood and offer deep insight into topics such as governance, interoperability, and decentralization at large.</p>
<p>Day Three will be all about welcoming new Cosmonauts on board–milestones ahead for leading projects and what’s required to develop and scale the next generation of “killer decentralized applications.”</p>
<p>The event’s partners span the top companies using Cosmos and IBC technology today and leaders across the digital asset space, including Halborn, Flow Traders, Fraction, SubQuery, and more.</p>
<h2>About Cosmos</h2>
<p>Cosmos Hub is the gateway to a rapidly expanding ecosystem of independent interconnected blockchains built using developer-friendly application components and connected with ground-breaking IBC (Inter-Blockchain Communication) protocol.</p>
<h2>About RockawayX</h2>
<p>RockawayX has been investing in early-stage crypto companies and token projects since 2017. In addition to running VC strategies and a credit fund, the firm operates businesses that provide critical services to the digital asset space. Its infrastructure arm runs nodes on leading decentralized networks, and it operates a crypto security business that offers smart contract audits and code diligence services to crypto protocols. Rockaway&#8217;s web3 venture studio incubates and spins out products that address gaps in web3 infrastructure and its commercial ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gateway-to-cosmos-2023-announces-speakers-for-europes-largest-internet-of-blockchains-ecosystem-gathering/" rel="nofollow">Gateway to Cosmos 2023 Announces Speakers for Europe’s Largest Internet of Blockchains Ecosystem Gathering</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Concordex Launches Testnet of its Institutional-Focused DEX Built on Concordium</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/concordex-launches-testnet-of-its-institutional-focused-dex-built-on-concordium/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252373</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Announcement_-_concordex_-_Twitter7_3_1685015780UoxOb9ZKyx.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Announcement_-_concordex_-_Twitter7_3_1685015780UoxOb9ZKyx.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Schwarzenbach, Switzerland, May 25th, 2023] Concordex, the first dedicated decentralized exchange (DEX) built on the Concordium blockchain, has officially launched its testnet. The project raised $1.7 million in seed funding from Tacans Labs, Skynet Trading, Seier Capital, Amdax and Concordium blockchain in December 2022 to bring institutional-grade DeFi trading tools to the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Schwarzenbach, Switzerland, May 25th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.concordex.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Concordex</a>, the first dedicated decentralized exchange (DEX) built on the <a href="https://concordium.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Concordium</a> blockchain, has officially launched its testnet. The project <a href="https://tacans.com/press-releases/concordex-raises-1-7-million-in-seed-funding-for-institutional-grade-dex" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">raised $1.7 million in seed funding</a> from Tacans Labs, Skynet Trading, Seier Capital, Amdax and Concordium blockchain in December 2022 to bring institutional-grade DeFi trading tools to the Concordium blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>Concordium is the permissionless green Layer 1 science-backed blockchain creating a safer digital world with an embedded identity verification layer. It provides a secure way for users and enterprises across the world to trade and remain compliant while ensuring the privacy crypto users have grown accustomed to. Concordex will utilize the regulatory-ready Concordium ecosystem to offer one of the first regulation-friendly DeFi platforms, a radical step forward in the evolution of DeFi.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The launch of our testnet today will offer a glimpse into the robust set of DeFi tools we are developing for the Concordium blockchain. By leveraging their regulatory-ready blockchain ecosystem, Concordex is set to be one of the first regulation-friendly DeFi platforms in the market, taking a significant step forward in the evolution of DeFi, while offering a unique trading experience for users,&#8221; said James Davies, Chief Product Officer at Concordex Labs.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Concordium meets the growing demands from institutional investors for enterprise-grade DeFi. Together with Concordex we will provide the highest standards of security, compliance and scalability. Unlocking liquidity, diversification, and yield generation beyond traditional investments. &#8221; Torben Kaaber, Head of Commercial at Concordium</p></blockquote>
<p>Concordex will bring a variety of features to the Concordium ecosystem, including simple trading, as well as concentrated liquidity and flexible fee levels for liquidity providers allowing them to optimize capital deployment and maximize returns over time. With a team of highly capable TradFi and DeFi veterans, the platform is set to bridge the gap between TradFi and DeFi with true on-chain derivatives and other tools dedicated to institutional investors.</p>
<p>To celebrate the launch of its public testnet, Concordex has also launched a <a href="https://medium.com/@concordexlabs/introducing-the-100-000-usd-concordex-testnet-rewards-program-a573f6d4bc92" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Concordex Testnet Rewards Program</a>, allocating a total of USD 100,000 in its upcoming $CCDX token as rewards for participants in the program, which is set to continue for the duration of the testnet phase with rewards distributed after the token’s token generation event (TGE) later this year.</p>
<h2>About Concordex</h2>
<p>Concordex is an advanced institutional-grade liquidity management DEX built on the Concordium blockchain. The project was developed by DeFi venture studio Tacans Labs, with core team members including award-winning entrepreneur Mathias Lundoe, and industry veterans James Davies, Ivan Ivaschenko, and Marie Tatibouet. The platform aims to launch on Mainnet in Q3 2023.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Concordium</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Concordium is a permissionless green layer 1, a science-backed blockchain that balances privacy with accountability through its ID layer and Zero-knowledge proofs. Creating trust with ID is key to scaling businesses. Concordium provides a fast, secure, and high-scale blockchain platform that makes building use cases and using dApps easy. Concordium differs by having verified ID and instant finality with high throughput and low transaction fees, pegged to FIAT. With leadership from Fortune 500 companies, Volvo, IKEA, Credit Suisse, Uber, and successful Fintech platforms, the team is scaling the chain to its extensive network of the world&#8217;s biggest enterprises.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/concordex-launches-testnet-of-its-institutional-focused-dex-built-on-concordium/" rel="nofollow">Concordex Launches Testnet of its Institutional-Focused DEX Built on Concordium</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stably Launches #USD as the First BRC20 Stablecoin on the Bitcoin Network</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252361</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/USD_On_Bitcoin__-_Graphic_2_16849862576x4964vfYh.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/USD_On_Bitcoin__-_Graphic_2_16849862576x4964vfYh.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Renton, United States, May 25th, 2023] Stably, a leading Stablecoin-as-a-Service (SCaaS) and fiat on/off-ramp infrastructure provider for Web3 projects, is aiming to revolutionize the nascent Bitcoin ordinals market by launching its US Dollar (USD)-backed stablecoin, Stably USD, as a natively-issued BRC20 token under the symbol #USD. This groundbreaking development marks a critical [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Renton, United States, May 25th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://stably.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Stably</a>, a leading Stablecoin-as-a-Service (SCaaS) and fiat on/off-ramp infrastructure provider for Web3 projects, is aiming to revolutionize the nascent Bitcoin ordinals market by launching its US Dollar (USD)-backed stablecoin, <a href="https://stably.io/brc20-usd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Stably USD</a>, as a natively-issued BRC20 token under the symbol <strong>#USD</strong>. This groundbreaking development marks a critical milestone in the exponentially growing Bitcoin ordinals ecosystem that is now reaching half a billion dollars in total market capitalization in less than six months.</p>
<p>#USD is a BRC20 standard stablecoin created via the Bitcoin <a href="https://docs.ordinals.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ordinals protocol</a> which was introduced in January 2023 after the recent <a href="https://bitcoin.org/en/releases/0.21.1/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Taproot</a> upgrade. BRC20 tokens use a technique called ordinal inscriptions to attach data to individual &#8220;satoshis,&#8221; the smallest unit of a Bitcoin. These satoshis can then represent anything from digital art ownership to “meme coins” and even stablecoins.</p>
<p>According to Stably, every #USD token is backed 1-to-1 with USD in a collateral account managed by a US-regulated custodian for the benefit of KYC/AML-verified token holders. Monthly reports for the account are also conducted by a third-party stablecoin attestor to ensure #USD tokens are always fully collateralized with USD.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;<strong>When I met Domo, the creator of the BRC20 standard, at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami, I told him about our upcoming plans for #USD</strong>,&#8221; said Kory Hoang, Stably’s CEO and Co-Founder. “<strong>He thought it was great and funny how we are creating a stablecoin on Bitcoin to enable Bitcoin trading on-chain… With a stablecoin built on Bitcoin. I’m still chuckling about it to this day, actually</strong>. <strong>In just one week after that, however, we made it happen!</strong>”</p></blockquote>
<p>The integration of BRC20 #USD into the Bitcoin network is part of Stably’s mission to power the next billion Web3 users with a seamless fiat-to-crypto and stablecoin onramp to all popular and emerging blockchain networks. The company’s upcoming collaborations with prominent ordinals and BRC20 projects, including UniSat–the world’s largest decentralized wallet/marketplace for ordinals–and Ordzaar–Asia’s first decentralized ordinals marketplace project, reflect Stably&#8217;s aspiration to drive global innovation and adoption toward decentralized finance on the Bitcoin network, or “BitFi.” Additionally, Stably’s engineers are now exploring the new ORC20 standard for Bitcoin ordinals, which could significantly enhance the token properties of #USD once implemented.</p>
<p>#USD can be issued/redeemed with Fedwire, SWIFT, USDC, and USDT by KYC-verified users across 200+ countries/regions currently, including up to 44 US states. Stably states that it is employing a <a href="https://support.stably.io/en/articles/7933928-how-to-buy-and-sell-brc20-usd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">manual process</a> of issuance/redemption for #USD’s initial launch but plans to release support for automatic issuance/redemption through Stably Ramp, the company&#8217;s plug-and-play fiat gateway widget, during Q3 2023. By then, users of #USD will be able to on/off-ramp via more traditional payment methods like ACH, instant ACH, and credit/debit cards, in addition to bank wires.</p>
<p>Founded in 2018, the 20+ team member Seattle FinTech is backed by leading institutional and angel investors in the crypto space, such as Morgan Creek Capital, BEENEXT, 500 Startups, Hard Yaka, CREAM Labs, Sunny Lu of VeChain, and Paul Stahura of Donuts, Inc. The company has raised over $7.5-million in total funding to-date, $5-million of which was collected during its last Pre-Series A round in December 2021. Stably has also expanded its fiat on/off-ramp and stablecoin natively to more than ten emerging networks, including Arbitrum, XRP Ledger, Stellar, Tezos, VeChainThor, Harmony, Polymesh, Coreum, ICON, and Chia Network.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Stably</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Stably is a Web3 payment infrastructure provider and FinCEN-registered MSB from Seattle. The company specializes in providing stablecoins and fiat &lt;&gt; crypto on and off-ramps to users of Web3 applications. Stably’s mission is to power this decade’s next billion Web3 users with regulatory-compliant payment infrastructure across both developed and emerging blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p><em><strong>Risk Disclaimer:</strong> Digital assets involve significant risks, including (but not limited to) market volatility, cybercrime, regulatory changes, and technological challenges. Past performance is not indicative of future results. Digital assets are not insured by any government agency and holding digital assets could result in loss of value and even principal. Bridged or wrapped digital assets (e.g. WBTC) involve additional risks, such as technical challenges, higher fees, security vulnerabilities, and reliance on third-party custodians. Please conduct your own thorough research and understand potential risks before purchasing/holding digital assets. Nothing herein shall be considered legal or financial advice. For more information about the risks and considerations when using our services, please visit: <a href="https://stably.io/terms-of-service/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stably.io/terms-of-service</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stably-launches-usd-as-the-first-brc20-stablecoin-on-the-bitcoin-network/" rel="nofollow">Stably Launches #USD as the First BRC20 Stablecoin on the Bitcoin Network</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Politicians Must Report Their Bitcoin Holdings Under New Law</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-politicians-must-report-their-bitcoin-holdings-under-new-law/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 22:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252436</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[South Korean politicians now must report their crypto holdings as they do cash, stocks, bonds, or gold. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">South Korea’s National Assembly has officially passed a bill into law requiring lawmakers and high-ranking government officials to disclose their crypto asset holdings. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The new law is a response to a recent scandal involving a politician allegedly violating campaign finance laws using cryptocurrency. </span></p>
<h2>The “Kim Nam-guk Prevention Law”</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to a </span><a href="https://www.news1.kr/articles/5058538" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from local news agency News1, the relevant amendments to the National Assembly Act and Public Service Ethics Act passed unanimously on May 22 among all lawmakers present for each, with 269 votes and 268 votes respectively. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The National Assembly Act amendment puts cryptocurrency on the list of lawmakers’ registered properties and “private interests.” Meanwhile, the amendment to the Public Officials Ethics Act passed the Public Administration and Security Committee on the same day, making both high-ranking officials and National Assembly members need to register their holdings. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The bill was originally scheduled for implementation in December but was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-koreas-ppp-seeks-to-speed-up-bill-requiring-lawmakers-crypto-holdings-disclosure/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">fast-tracked</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to this month after the conservative People Power Party’s newly elected leader, Rep. Yun Jae-ok, said the previous date was “too late.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Given the current high level of public interest, especially regarding lawmakers, it’s not appropriate to enforce the law six months later after the promulgation,” said the party leader last week, while proposing a fast-tracked version of the bill last week. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The “public interest” refers to a high-profile scandal surrounding Kim Nam-guk – who was alleged to have cashed out $4.5 million in cryptocurrency at Wemix exchange early last year. The same lawmaker backed legislation in 2022 to defer a law implementing a 20% capital gains tax on cryptocurrencies from 2023 to 2025, though he’s denied there being any conflicts of interest. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, the revelations invited investigations into the former Democratic Party lawmaker for suspected campaign finance violations, tax portals, and criminal possession of crypto. </span></p>
<h2>Which Politicians Hold Crypto in America?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Lawmakers in the United States are already required to disclose their crypto and Bitcoin holdings, among whom only a small number hold any digital assets. Senator Cynthia Lummis </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/i-only-have-5-bitcoin-senator-lummis-encourages-people-to-buy-and-hold-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">revealed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in 2021 that she owns 5 BTC – three of which she bought for just $300. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Senator Ted Cruz has also confessed to owning a little more than 2 BTC, respecting the asset as a long-term inflation hedge and decentralized governance. Last month, he </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-senator-ted-cruz-likes-and-owns-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that he has a standing order to buy more Bitcoin every Monday morning. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I like bitcoin for the same reason that the Chinese communist government doesn’t like bitcoin,” he said. “They don’t like bitcoin, and they banned it because they can’t control it.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-politicians-must-report-their-bitcoin-holdings-under-new-law/" rel="nofollow">South Korean Politicians Must Report Their Bitcoin Holdings Under New Law</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin? 5 Best Altcoins That Could Explode Instead</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-it-too-late-to-buy-bitcoin-5-best-altcoins-that-could-explode-instead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252377</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CryptoPotato-1200x780-1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CryptoPotato-1200x780-1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is around 60% since the turn of the year, and while that doesn’t necessarily signal the end of the crypto winter, it’s a sign that investors who have been holding off on the world’s largest cryptocurrency may have missed their chance to buy in while it was undervalued. However, there are still plenty of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is around 60% since the turn of the year, and while that doesn’t necessarily signal the end of the crypto winter, it’s a sign that investors who have been holding off on the world’s largest cryptocurrency may have missed their chance to buy in while it was undervalued.</p>
<p>However, there are still plenty of explosive opportunities in the crypto market for investors who are willing to look beyond Bitcoin. We’ll take a closer look at Bitcoin’s price and highlight 5 emerging altcoins that could generate massive returns in the weeks and months ahead.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Momentum Stalls, Some Analysts See Bearish Move Ahead</h2>
<p>After a year of crypto winter, Bitcoin had an impressive start to 2023. The token gained more than 80% in the first four months of the year and briefly broke through the key $30,000 price level in mid-April.</p>
<p>However, bullish momentum in BTC has stalled in the past month. Bitcoin has been unable to remain above $30,000. Instead, the token has remained in a range between $27,000 and $30,000, with the price <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumped-to-2-week-low-apecoin-nosedives-8-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently sliding</a> to $26,250.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252408" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252408" style="width: 1379px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252408" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="1379" height="886" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2-300x193.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2-1024x658.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2-768x493.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-2-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252408" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>Some crypto analysts see this as a worrying trend for Bitcoin. If the token can’t firmly break through resistance at $30,000, it is likely to fall to its next support level around $23,000 &#8211; that would represent a 12% loss from today’s price.</p>
<p>The macroeconomic picture for Bitcoin is equally uncertain. Although a pause in interest rate hikes by the US Federal Reserve is widely expected to be positive for BTC, continued high rates and fears of a recession have turned investors away from cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>At the same time, BTC faces increasing scrutiny in the US and abroad for the energy required to mine it. New restrictions on mining could make BTC less accessible and decrease demand for the token, thus holding down the price for the foreseeable future.</p>
<p>All of these trends suggest that while Bitcoin may still be well below its all-time high, it’s more likely to go through another round of bearish price action before it surges, with a true crypto bull run not expected until 2024 with the next halving approaching.</p>
<p>So, investors in search of speedy profits in the crypto market may be better served by exploring altcoins that are gaining traction right now.</p>
<h2>AiDoge Raises $13.5 Million for AI-powered Meme Generation</h2>
<p>AiDoge is a meme coin that’s leveraging generative AI to make meme creation easier than ever.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252409" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="1379" height="745" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3-1024x553.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a></p>
<p>AiDoge users just need to describe the meme they want to create, and the AI will take care of the rest. Within seconds, it will provide a custom image and text that users can customize.</p>
<p>AiDoge enables users to mint their creations as NFTs before sharing them. That way, if a meme goes viral, users can verifiably claim ownership over the latest trend.</p>
<p>In order to create memes with AiDoge, users will need the project’s native AI token. Users who stake AI earn daily credits to use the meme generation algorithm. This incentivizes long-term investing while encouraging users to create new memes.</p>
<p>The AiDoge presale is going on now and has already raised more than $13.5 million in just four weeks. Investors need to hurry if they want to join the presale—less than 10% of AI tokens allocated to the presale remain available and the project could hold an ICO in the next few weeks.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Launchpad XYZ to Drive Mainstream Web3 Adoption with Gateway Portal</h2>
<p>Launchpad XYZ is another crypto presale project that is quickly grabbing the attention of investors.</p>
<p>The new protocol will act as a gateway platform for new Web3 users and crypto natives by providing a broad range of tools and access to help drive mass adoption.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252410" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-3.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="312" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-3-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-3-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The project, which has its own Web3 wallet, will simplify Web3 navigation by providing an easy portal to various different marketplaces, experiences, and protocols.</p>
<p>That includes a decentralized exchange, NFT marketplace, play-to-earn gaming hub and metaverse library, a trading terminal, fractionalized assets, and whitelist spots to the best new crypto presales.</p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ, which has been developed by a doxxed and experienced group, is powered by LPX, a utility token that is needed to earn access to all the different features on offer.</p>
<p>The Launchpad XYZ presale has already raised more than $600k, with LPX tokens currently on sale for $0.0445 during stage 2 of 10, with the price to increase to $0.0565 in the final stage.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_596f215c.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>yPredict Builds AI-powered Crypto Trading Platform with 20,000+ Backers</h2>
<p>yPredict is a new crypto project that’s using AI to help traders achieve greater profits in the market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252411" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="1379" height="833" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2-300x181.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2-1024x619.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2-768x464.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-2-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a></p>
<p>The project is building a suite of AI-powered predictive modeling tools. Analysts, quants, and developers can use these tools to create custom models that predict where the price of a crypto asset will be in hours, days, or weeks.</p>
<p>Model builders can share their models with traders on a subscription basis through yPredict’s marketplace. yPredict gets a cut of each subscription, and it shares 10% of that revenue back to traders who stake its native YPRED token.</p>
<p>In addition to the predictive models, yPredict is building a custom trading terminal that’s loaded with other AI features. The platform will support automated chart pattern recognition, social sentiment analysis, trading from charts, and more.</p>
<p>YPRED, which is built on the Polygon Matic network, is available to buy now through the yPredict presale. It’s currently priced at $0.07, a more than 40% discount from the planned list price of $0.12.</p>
<p>The yPredict presale has raised almost $1.7 million and the project has more than 20,000 users on its wait list. The next price increase is just days away.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Ecoterra Pioneers Recycle-to-earn Ecosystem, Raises Over $4 Million</h2>
<p>Ecoterra is a green crypto project that’s promoting sustainability with a unique recycle-to-earn rewards system.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252412" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="1379" height="771" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2-300x168.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2-1024x573.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2-768x429.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-2-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a></p>
<p>The recycle-to-earn system revolves around Ecoterra’s Web3 app. Users scan the barcode of the packaging they want to recycle, and Ecoterra matches it to material in its database.</p>
<p>Once users deposit their recyclables at a reverse vending machine, Ecoterra releases ECOTERRA tokens as a reward.</p>
<p>Users can hold onto their ECOTERRA or exchange them, but they can also use ECOTERRA to buy carbon credits. Ecoterra has partnered with solar and wind energy projects to offer certified carbon credits that can offset users’ own emissions.</p>
<p>There’s a lot more to Ecoterra, including a marketplace and sustainability report cards for businesses. The platform has the potential to become one of the key players in an eco-friendly revolution.</p>
<p>Ecoterra is currently offering ECOTERRA on presale at only $0.0085, a discount of 15% from the expected listing price. The presale has raised more than $4.25 million so far, indicating that investors have a lot of confidence in this project’s future.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Deelance Raises Over $1 Million to Change the Future of Work</h2>
<p>Deelance is reimagining the future of work and taking on established companies like Upwork, Freelancer, and Fiverr.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252413" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="1379" height="787" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1.jpg 1379w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1-300x171.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1-1024x584.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1-768x438.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-1-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1379px) 100vw, 1379px" /></a></p>
<p>This crypto project is building a decentralized, Web3 freelance marketplace that offers lower fees and more powerful features than existing marketplaces. Deelance plans to charge just 2% for businesses, the lowest fee in the industry.</p>
<p>One of Deelance’s innovations is to enable freelancers to be paid in crypto, thus eliminating costly foreign transaction fees. The platform is also creating a way to turn intellectual property into NFTs, thus resolving questions over who owns what aspects of a piece of contract work.</p>
<p>Deelance is also creating a metaverse where freelancers and businesses can meet. The metaverse will enable users to advertise their services, rent virtual office space, host meetings, and much more.</p>
<p>In order to rent space or ads in Deelance’s virtual world, freelancers and businesses will need DLANCE. This ERC-20 token is on presale now at a price of $0.033. The presale has already raised more than $1 million.</p>
<p>Deelance expects to launch DLANCE at a price of $0.057, so early investors have a chance to lock in paper returns of 72%.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_3bcb6414.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Deelance Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-it-too-late-to-buy-bitcoin-5-best-altcoins-that-could-explode-instead/" rel="nofollow">Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin? 5 Best Altcoins That Could Explode Instead</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
