<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 16:43:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Could Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Meme Coin As It Hits $10M in Presale?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/could-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin-as-it-hits-10m-in-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 22:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256880</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Amid the recent meme coin surge that saw the likes of Pepe gain more than 7,000%, new meme crypto Wall Street Memes (WSM) has stepped into the limelight. Over the past month, when most cryptos tanked amid market uncertainty, Wall Street Memes has raised over $10 million during its presale. This highlighted the project&#8217;s potential [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the recent meme coin surge that saw the likes of Pepe gain more than 7,000%, new meme crypto Wall Street Memes (WSM) has stepped into the limelight.</p>
<p>Over the past month, when most cryptos tanked amid market uncertainty, <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> has raised over $10 million during its presale.</p>
<p>This highlighted the project&#8217;s potential and the strong support it enjoys from its community, which has a million followers across various social media platforms.</p>
<p>The token has been developed from the same creators of the Wall St Bulls NFT collection, which quickly <a href="https://thedalesreport.com/crypto-nfts/wall-street-bulls-nft-collection-sells-out-in-half-an-hour/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">sold out within 32 minutes after its launch</a> on Ethereum.</p>
<p>The team&#8217;s understanding of crypto trends has only improved since then, leading to the successful launch of the Bitcoin Ordinals NFTs and, now, the <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a> meme coin. This aligns quite well with the market&#8217;s current inclination toward meme coins.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Memes whitepaper highlights that the token aims to merge memes with blockchain to disrupt the modern financial landscape through the power of community.</p>
<p>The project believes memes can connect people, inspire new ideas, and question established norms. Leveraging the power of decentralization, Wall Street Memes aims to create a movement designed to return control to its rightful owners &#8211; the people.</p>
<h2><strong>Wall Street Memes: Community-Backed Meme Token That Has Already Raised $10 Million</strong></h2>
<p>In the initial day following the commencement of the project, the WSM token raised more than $300k, and just four weeks since launch it has now attracted over $10 million, showing significant interest from investors.</p>
<p>Given its current expansion rate and strong financial backing, the WSM token could become an attractive option for large crypto exchanges, including leading platforms.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256881" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="695" height="349" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24.jpg 695w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></a></p>
<p>WSM token is presently in the presale stage, priced at $0.0301 during stage 18 of 30. While inherently risky, presales yield substantial returns, particularly when a robust community supports the project.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes has a solid community base of a million followers spread across various social media platforms, reaffirming the token&#8217;s strong support and potential.</p>
<h2><strong>Why Should Buyers Consider WSM?</strong></h2>
<p>Apart from a thriving community, the platform has also caught the attention of influential figures like Elon Musk, who has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1636924379086077954" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">engaged with Wall Street Memes’ tweets</a> on multiple occasions.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s well-known how Musk&#8217;s tweets have previously caused the price of meme coins like Dogecoin to spike massively and his engagement with the platform could turn out well for WSM, helping the coin gain even more followers.</p>
<p>The WSM token&#8217;s distribution underlines the project&#8217;s community-centric approach. Of the capped supply of 2 billion tokens, 50% has been allocated for the presale, 30% for community rewards, and 20% for exchange liquidity.</p>
<p>Notably, no allocation has been made for the team, indicating the project&#8217;s transparency and commitment towards ensuring a &#8216;rug pull&#8217; scenario is off the table.</p>
<p>Moreover, Wall Street Memes has announced a <a href="https://t.me/jd1234_d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">massive airdrop</a> for presale investors. By participating in the project’s social media channels and completing simple tasks, five lucky winners will stand a chance to win $50,000 worth of WSM tokens.</p>
<h2><strong>The Strategic Growth and Potential of Wall Street Memes</strong></h2>
<p>The Wall Street Memes project sets an ambitious target, aiming to disrupt the traditional financial landscape and democratize investing through the power of memes.</p>
<p>A clear roadmap has been set to achieve this, with the journey divided into three parts: Foundation, Launch, and Community Empowerment.</p>
<p>The WSM token&#8217;s growth roadmap comprises three phases &#8211; phase one establishes a strong community and a secure smart contract, alongside initiating a branding campaign.</p>
<p>Phase two involves the WSM token&#8217;s launch, strategic partnerships, and listings on multiple exchanges. The final phase targets community empowerment and seeking listings on top-tier exchanges.</p>
<p>Also, many analysts point out that a dedicated, vibrant community, a strong brand, and a timely entry into the meme coin market make WSM a potential <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bDbEfCiPYy4" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">next huge meme crypto</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/could-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin-as-it-hits-10m-in-presale/" rel="nofollow">Could Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Meme Coin As It Hits $10M in Presale?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Doubles Down on AI by Investing $100 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-doubles-down-on-ai-by-investing-100-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256781</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/amazon1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/amazon1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ai is going to be "the next big thing that pushes even more customers to want to be in the cloud," CEO Selipsky forecasted.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amazon Web Services (AWS) &#8211; the cloud unit of the e-commerce giant &#8211; said it will distribute $100 million for a center to help entities employ generative artificial intelligence (AI). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Microsoft and Google &#8211; two other giant corporations &#8211; have made even bigger investments in AI. </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">AWS&#8217; CEO Adam Selipsky revealed the plans in a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/22/aws-invests-100-million-in-generative-ai-as-it-sees-a-long-race-ahead.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for CNBC, showing that the company realizes the potential of the new technology:</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;You ask yourself the question — where are the different runners three steps into a 10K race? Does it really matter? The point is, you&#8217;re three steps in, and it&#8217;s a 10K race.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exec explained that the new feature will not function as a physical center but rather as a &#8220;program.&#8221; He added that RyanAir, Lonely Planet, Highspot, and Twilio have already jumped on board.</span></li>
<li>Selipsky sees an optimistic future for artificial intelligence, calling it &#8220;the next wave of innovation in the cloud.&#8221; According to him, it will be &#8220;the next big thing&#8221; that pushes clients to want to be in the cloud.</li>
<li>Amazon has already hopped on the AI bandwagon by introducing the virtual assistant technology Alexa. However, those efforts and the upcoming $100 million investment are no match for what other leading corporations have done.</li>
<li>The multinational tech giant &#8211; Microsoft &#8211; <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-23/microsoft-makes-multibillion-dollar-investment-in-openai" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">distributed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $10 billion into OpenAI several months ago. This has been the third investment into the AI startup, with the previous made in 2019 and 2021. </span></li>
<li>Shortly after, Google <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.ft.com/content/583ead66-467c-4bd5-84d0-ed5df7b5bf9c" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">invested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $300 million in Anthropic. Formed in 2021 by former members of OpenAI, the latter is an artificial intelligence safety and research company based in San Francisco.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-doubles-down-on-ai-by-investing-100-million/" rel="nofollow">Amazon Doubles Down on AI by Investing $100 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jim Cramer&#8217;s Latest Change of Heart, Says He is Not Against Crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jim-cramers-latest-change-of-heart-says-he-is-not-against-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256725</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Jim_Cramer5.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Jim_Cramer5.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Many Twitter users reminded Cramer about his entirely different position displayed several months ago.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jim Cramer &#8211; the host of CNBC&#8217; financial TV show &#8220;Mad Money&#8221; &#8211; clarified that he is &#8220;not against crypto&#8221; but opposes such projects that scam people. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is yet another controversial statement coming from the American who has changed his view on the industry countless times over the years. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The crypto community often mocks him for making not-so-accurate price predictions and investment guidance. For one, Cramer advised people to sell their &#8220;awful&#8221; positions in December last year when bitcoin was hovering around $17,000. Recall that the leading digital asset has recently surpassed $30,000.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Only Against Bogus Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cramer took it to Twitter to explain that he is not a critic of the digital asset industry. Instead, he is against &#8220;BOGUS crypto and outfits&#8221; that drain money from investors and never give it back.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Understand i am not against crypto and done quite well with it. I am against BOGUS crypto and outfits that stole your money and wouldn&#8217;t let you have it back</p>
<p>— Jim Cramer (@jimcramer) <a href="https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1671897936471392257?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hundreds of users noted under the post that Cramer&#8217;s latest statement is much different than what he had shared before. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For example, he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/mad-money-jim-cramer-says-the-fed-will-take-down-speculative-assets-like-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">urged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> investors last September to avoid delving into digital currencies, calling the latter &#8220;speculative assets.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Look, Fed chief Jay Powell told us that we need to stop doing stupid things with our money… What matters is that we just have to get through it intact. Don&#8217;t get named. Don&#8217;t get SPAC&#8217;d. Don&#8217;t get crypto. And you&#8217;ll get through this thicket and find yourself in a much better time when we are sufficiently oversold for a huge bounce,&#8221; Cramer added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bull-market-signal-jim-cramer-advises-crypto-investors-to-sell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">launched </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">another bashing manifest in December, claiming that people who have exposure to cryptocurrencies should sell their &#8220;awful&#8221; positions.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cramer&#8217;s &#8220;Spot-on&#8221; Forecasts</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from being a prominent TV personality, Cramer has gained popularity through his controversial crypto predictions, which in many cases turn wrong.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cnbcs-jim-cramer-believes-bitcoin-and-ethereums-selloff-could-be-over/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suggested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at the beginning of 2022 that BTC and ETH selloffs could be over, hinting at the start of a new bull run. Nonetheless, last year was devastating for the sector and saw the meltdown of multiple giants, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>, Three Arrows Capital (3AC), Celsius Network, and others, whereas bitcoin and ether lost a significant chunk of their USD valuation.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, the crypto market started ascending shortly after he told investors, &#8220;It&#8217;s never too late to sell&#8221; in December last year. BTC has surged over 75% since that moment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jim-cramers-latest-change-of-heart-says-he-is-not-against-crypto/" rel="nofollow">Jim Cramer&#8217;s Latest Change of Heart, Says He is Not Against Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert F. Kennedy to Enforce Pro-Bitcoin Laws Should he Become President</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/robert-f-kennedy-to-enforce-pro-bitcoin-laws-should-he-become-president/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256766</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The only crypto regulation that Kennedy plans to impose as an eventual President of the US would be focused on preventing money laundering.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy Jr, who recently announced he will run for President of the US as part of the Democratic Party, vowed to implement Bitcoin-friendly policies if elected. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Republicans also have a crypto-loving candidate and his name is Francis Suarez. The 45-year-old, who currently serves as mayor of Miami, involved the city in numerous Bitcoin initiatives and became the first American politician to receive his salary in BTC instead of fiat currency.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTC Could Thrive Under Kennedy&#8217;s Leadership</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://nypost.com/2023/06/22/robert-f-kennedy-jr-interview-why-im-not-an-anti-vaxxer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Robert F. Kennedy Jr (the nephew of former President John F. Kennedy) reiterated his positive stance towards the cryptocurrency sector, more specifically, Bitcoin. He said he will &#8220;make sure&#8221; that America introduces rules that aid BTC and enable people to control their passwords, wallets, and nodes. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I will make sure that we have policies that support Bitcoin and the freedom to transact and that allow individuals to manage their own Bitcoin wallets, nodes, and passwords.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy also promised that his eventual cabinet would apply only necessary control to the industry to prevent money laundering. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, he opposed central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), labeling them as financial products used for &#8220;oppression.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-proponent-robert-f-kennedy-announces-run-for-president-of-the-usa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">described</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> himself as an opponent of the US Federal Reserve, claiming it had collaborated with numerous banking institutions between 2008-2022 to print a colossal amount of money. In his view, the outcome of the controversial policy could cause a further monetary imbalance in the future, whereas Bitcoin could serve as an &#8220;escape route from the splatter zone.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Could We Witness a Competition Between BTC Fans?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Francis Suarez &#8211; the mayor of Miami &#8211; is the presidential candidate who stands as a Bitcoin advocate from the Republican side. His cabinet has allowed Florida&#8217;s financial heart to go through a digital transformation by digitizing the process of securing a license to start a business. As such, the city had become much more attractive to investors and entrepreneurs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Suarez, who had personally bought BTC and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miamis-mayor-continues-to-receive-his-salary-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his paychecks in the primary cryptocurrency, has also contemplated investing 1% of Miami&#8217;s treasure reserves in it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Still, direct competition between Kennedy and Suarez seems unlikely since they first need to prevail over Joe Biden and Donald Trump, respectively.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robert-f-kennedy-to-enforce-pro-bitcoin-laws-should-he-become-president/" rel="nofollow">Robert F. Kennedy to Enforce Pro-Bitcoin Laws Should he Become President</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Pumps Toward $31K But is a Correction Imminent? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-pumps-toward-31k-but-is-a-correction-imminent-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256862</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After an extended period of consolidation, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has successfully surpassed the critical $30K resistance level. However, it is important to exercise caution within the market, particularly in the short term. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart On the daily timeframe, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has experienced a rapid upward movement in the past week, following [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After an extended period of consolidation, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has successfully surpassed the critical $30K resistance level. However, it is important to exercise caution within the market, particularly in the short term.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: Edris</p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has experienced a rapid upward movement in the past week, following a strong bounce from the $25K support level. The resistance at $30K has been exceeded, and the price is attempting to maintain its position above it.</p>
<p>However, the RSI indicator currently signals an overbought condition, suggesting a probable correction. If it occurs, the 50-day moving average might act as a support level around $27,500, followed by the 200-day moving average near the $25K region.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256866" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256866" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256866 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2406231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-24-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256866" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The 4-hour timeframe reflects a similar scenario to the daily chart, with a strong upward movement and breakthrough of resistance levels. The recent rally commenced following the breakout from the descending channel, propelling the price to higher highs above $30K.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it is important to exercise caution due to a clear bearish divergence observed on the RSI indicator. This suggests the possibility of consolidation or correction shortly, prompting investors to remain vigilant.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256865" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256865" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256865 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2406232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-24-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256865" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">On-chain Analysis</span></p>
<h3>Bitcoin Long-term holder SOPR</h3>
<p>After Bitcoin&#8217;s recent rally, many holders who had been experiencing losses for several months are now able to sell and realize profits.</p>
<p>The Long-term holder SOPR metric, depicted in the chart along with a 100-day moving average, indicates the ratio of profits or losses realized by long-term holders. Values above 1 indicate profit-taking, while values below 1 signify losses.</p>
<p>The chart clearly shows that long-term holders, who had been experiencing losses for nearly a year, have now begun to sell at a profit due to the recent price surge. While this situation is not necessarily harmful, it could increase the supply of Bitcoin, and without sufficient demand, it could potentially lead to a subsequent decline in price.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256864" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256864" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256864 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_long_term_holder_sopr_chart_2406231" width="2560" height="1616" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-1024x646.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-768x485.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-1536x969.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-2048x1293.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-LTH-SOPR-Jun-24-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256864" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-pumps-toward-31k-but-is-a-correction-imminent-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Pumps Toward $31K But is a Correction Imminent? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan&#8217;s Biggest Bank Might Launch Global Stablecoins (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/japans-biggest-bank-might-launch-global-stablecoins-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256666</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Japan_Flag.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Japan_Flag.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[MUFG's Vice President of Product - Tatsuya Saito - believes Japan could emerge as a global center for stablecoin issuance. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group (MUFG) &#8211; the largest finance institution in Japan &#8211; is reportedly considering issuing global stablecoins via its blockchain platform. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The bank has previously revealed plans to introduce such tokens tied to the value of the Japanese yen. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">MUFG&#8217;s New Crypto Idea</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/japan-s-biggest-bank-mufg-is-in-talks-to-issue-global-stablecoins-1.1936820" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Bloomberg, the entity is in talks with industry leaders and other companies on minting stablecoins pegged to foreign currencies, such as the US dollar. To do so, it intends to use its blockchain platform Progmat, Vice President of Product Tatsuya Saito said.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The executive added that potential partners in the move are several local financial institutions, entertainment firms, and other non-financial businesses. Inquiries also come from foreign organizations, meaning Japan could become a global hub for stablecoins, Saito envisioned. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Such financial products have been the subject of enhanced scrutiny in the Asian country, especially after the collapse of the algorithmic stablecoin UST last year, which triggered multi-billion investor losses. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Japanese authorities </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/japan-reportedly-introduces-a-bill-focused-on-stablecoins-in-the-aftermath-of-lunas-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">recognized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> stablecoins as digital money but said they could only be issued by licensed banks, money transfer agents, or trust companies. Saito praised the recently-enforced legislation, maintaining it could bring additional consumer protection:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Issuers and users can feel safe using stablecoins.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Japan&#8217;s government, under the lead of Prime Minister Fumio Kishida, has allowed the local crypto industry to thrive by introducing favorable rules. It approved a policy last summer that should advance the Web3 sector in the country.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, leading lobbying groups have raised their voices on crypto taxation, insisting that the ruling body reduces the rates. Should their wish receives approval, domestic companies will be excluded from paying taxes on paper gains on cryptocurrency holdings if they own them for purposes other than short-term trades. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Previous Efforts</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The trust banking arm of MUFG <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mitsubishi-ufj-trust-to-issue-a-stablecoin-to-accelerate-settlement-processes-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">displayed</a> its first interest in the matter in February 2022 when exploring the possibilities of launching a stablecoin pegged to Japan&#8217;s official currency. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Experts have claimed that such a token could allow the entity to boost its payment network by instantly settling securities transactions. Those types of monetary procedures are currently quite pricey and can take a couple of days to be finalized. </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/japans-biggest-bank-might-launch-global-stablecoins-report/" rel="nofollow">Japan&#8217;s Biggest Bank Might Launch Global Stablecoins (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC Charges Man for Defrauding Investors of $21M in Crypto Ponzi Scheme</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-charges-man-for-defrauding-investors-of-21m-in-crypto-ponzi-scheme/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256731</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cftc.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cftc.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC and DOJ have also brought parallel actions against Ichioka.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has charged William Koo Ichioka for defrauding investors of tens of millions of dollars by claiming to be a digital asset and foreign exchange (forex) trader.</p>
<p>According to an <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/SpeechesTestimony/johnsonstatement062223" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">official statement</a>, the CFTC filed a complaint against Ichioka in the U.S. District Court for the Northern District of California, accusing him of mishandling over $21 million of investor assets and using new customer funds to create the illusion of profits in a Ponzi scheme.</p>
<h2>CFTC Charges Man for Defrauding Investors</h2>
<p>The commodities regulator said Ichioka solicited millions from more than 100 individuals and entities, promising to engage in forex trades through a commodity interest pool operating as Ichioka Ventures. While advertising the services on his website, Ichioka claimed that the promised returns aligned with his track record as he was a self-made investor already earning millions of dollars.</p>
<p>Based on his trading strategies, Ichioka had promised participants of his scheme 10% returns every 30 business days. However, he sustained massive losses. To hide the losses, he provided fake documents to inflate the amount of funds in the commodity interest pool accounts and false statements of accounts to participants. The alleged fraudster also paid the purported gains to investors using funds from other participants.</p>
<p>Despite Ichioka&#8217;s claims, he was, in reality, misappropriating customer funds for personal expenses. He commingled participants&#8217; assets with his and used them to purchase luxury items like jewelry, cars, and watches.</p>
<h2>Parallel Action From the SEC and DOJ</h2>
<p>The CFTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-sues-5-individuals-for-bitcoin-trading-services-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> Ichioka of running an &#8220;old-school&#8221; Ponzi Scheme and engaging in &#8220;garden-variety&#8221; fraud. The alleged fraudster has proposed a settlement to resolve the Commission&#8217;s charges. On the other hand, the agency is seeking the court&#8217;s order to impose trading and registration bans and a monetary penalty on Ichioka.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Investor education and enforcement actions are critical to our efforts to prevent fraudsters from bilking hard-working investors. Accordingly, I strongly encourage all members of the public to stay informed about the potential scams and abuses in digital assets markets by visiting our investor advisory page. Fraudsters offering guaranteed, or unusually high, returns—or both—should in particular prompt scrutiny and additional diligence before transferring any funds,&#8221; Commissioner Kristin N. Johnson said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Department of Justice (DOJ) have begun parallel investigations into Ichioka&#8217;s actions, and they are set to be settled soon.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-charges-man-for-defrauding-investors-of-21m-in-crypto-ponzi-scheme/" rel="nofollow">CFTC Charges Man for Defrauding Investors of $21M in Crypto Ponzi Scheme</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Tests $31K as Bitcoin Cash Soars 30%: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-tests-31k-as-bitcoin-cash-soars-30-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 08:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256847</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH_BTC_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH_BTC_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin tested $31K but failed to sustain above it so far. BCH is up a whopping 30%.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past 24 hours saw Bitcoin&#8217;s price attempt a shot at $31K and maintain its dominance over the rest of the market.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that some altcoins performed incredibly well, charting gains close to 30%. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Taps $31K</h2>
<p>As <em>CryptoPotato </em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-to-31k-sparking-108-million-in-liquidations/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> yesterday, Bitcoin&#8217;s price soared to $31K, sparking a wave of liquidations totaling upward of $100 million.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256848" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256848" style="width: 1183px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-256848" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47.png" alt="BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47" width="1183" height="491" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47.png 1183w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47-300x125.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47-1024x425.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47-768x319.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-24_11-16-47-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1183px) 100vw, 1183px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256848" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance &#8211; the metric which tracks its share relative to that of the rest of the market &#8211; is also up. This signifies that the primary cryptocurrency has been performing a lot better compared to altcoins.</p>
<p>Unfortunately for the bulls, they were unable to sustain the price above $31K. Sellers stepped in and pushed it below this level to where it currently trades at around $31,600.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Leads Altcoins Push</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is today&#8217;s best performer by a long shot. The cryptocurrency is up 30% in the past 24 hours alone, adding to its total gains of more than 70% for the week.</p>
<p>A close second is Bitcoin SV (BSV), which is up over 21% during the day and over 44% during the week. Ethereum Classic (ETC) is right behind them with 11.4% daily gains.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256849" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256849" style="width: 1492px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-256849" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623" width="1492" height="726" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623.jpg 1492w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623-300x146.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623-1024x498.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623-768x374.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_240623-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1492px) 100vw, 1492px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256849" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>As seen in the heatmap, most of the market is trading well in the green. Litecoin (LTC) increased by a total of 5.4%, followed by Polkadot (DOT), and Solana (SOL).</p>
<p>Maker (MKR) is today&#8217;s worst performer, down about 4.6%. SUI, Optimism (OP), Conflux (CFX), and Injective (INJ), are also down by about 3% each.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-tests-31k-as-bitcoin-cash-soars-30-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">BTC Tests $31K as Bitcoin Cash Soars 30%: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How The Ripple v. SEC Lawsuit Could Affect The Entire Crypto Industry: A Lawyer&#8217;s Take</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-the-ripple-v-sec-lawsuit-could-affect-the-entire-crypto-industry-a-lawyers-take/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 21:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256828</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Ripple lawsuit is approaching its conclusion. Here's what lawyers have to say, and what the result could mean for all of crypto. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launching a full offensive against crypto this year, an ongoing lawsuit against one of the agency’s first industry targets – Ripple – remains as prevalent as ever.</p>
<p>Given recent developments, many parties close to the case believe the court’s ruling may be imminent. How might the result of the Ripple v. SEC lawsuit affect the crypto market and regulatory landscape as a whole?</p>
<p>Let’s dive in.</p>
<h2>Recap: Ripple v. SEC</h2>
<p>In December 2020, the SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2020-338" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">charged</a> Ripple and its two top executives – CEO Brad Garlinghouse and former CEO Chris Larsen – with conducting a $1.3 billion unregistered securities offering in the form of XRP, dating back to 2013.</p>
<p>The lawsuit caused the price of XRP to plummet at the time, and incited many crypto exchanges to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-exchanges-that-delisted-xrp-following-the-ripple-sec-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">delist</a> the asset to remain compliant with federal securities laws.</p>
<p>Ripple didn’t back down, however. According to Garlinghouse, the company has <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/08/ripple-will-have-spent-200-million-fighting-sec-lawsuit-ceo-says.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">spent</a> roughly $200 million defending itself from the SEC’s allegations. The company’s core argument is that XRP itself is not a security or investment contract, but a digital currency used to facilitate cross-border payments.</p>
<p>Garlinghouse expressed <a href="https://twitter.com/XRPnewt/status/1661547535062769669?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">confidence</a> last month that the case could be approaching its conclusion within a few weeks – implying its resolution could be announced any day now.</p>
<h2>Who is Correct?</h2>
<p>Thus far, U.S. Congress hasn’t passed any legislation clarifying how crypto assets ought to be classified under the law – whether as securities or commodities.</p>
<p>The country’s chief market regulators – the SEC and Commodities and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) – are at odds on the subject, with the former seemingly believing that all cryptos <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-reasserts-every-crypto-is-a-security-aside-from-bitcoin-lawyers-disagree/" data-wpel-link="internal">besides Bitcoin</a> are securities.</p>
<p>SEC chairman Gary Gensler keeps a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-ether-a-security-sec-chair-gary-gensler-avoids-a-direct-answer/" data-wpel-link="internal">tight lip</a> when asked to publicly discuss which specific cryptocurrencies are securities. Instead, he often refers the industry to the Howey Test – a decades-old legal standard for identifying whether financial assets qualify as investment contracts, and therefore as securities under the Securities Act of 1933.</p>
<p>According to the SEC&#8217;s analysis on its <a href="https://www.sec.gov/corpfin/framework-investment-contract-analysis-digital-assets" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">website</a>, there are four prongs required for a digital asset to pass the Howey Test. The agency states:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Under the Howey test, an &#8220;investment contract&#8221; exists when there is the investment of money in a common enterprise with a reasonable expectation of profits to be derived from the efforts of others. Whether a particular digital asset at the time of its offer or sale satisfies the Howey test depends on the specific facts and circumstances.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Industry leaders like Ripple often contest the SEC’s interpretation of the Howey Test when applied to digital assets. For example, Coinbase <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase/status/1625670800031219712" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">argues</a> that stablecoins like the Paxos-issued BUSD (which the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stablecoin-race-dai-surpasses-busd-amid-binance-sec-regulatory-row/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged</a> is a security this month) are not investments, as their value remains “stable” across time.</p>
<h2>What Do Lawyers Think Of XRP?</h2>
<p>John Deaton – founder of Crypto Law.US – is a lawyer representing over 75,000 XRP holders in the Ripple v. SEC lawsuit. He is firmly against the SEC’s position, asserting that XRP is not a security, and that Gensler ought to be fired from his position.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">So when you take all the law into consideration, the SEC has NOTHING to support its theory that secondary market sales are also securities. Some may argue that the SEC has a right to pursue novel theories, unsupported by the law. I disagree.</p>
<p>&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1670861912035164191?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Sandy Seth – a patent lawyer of 25 years – also expressed skepticism of the SEC’s case in a Twitter thread on Monday, arguing that XRP does not meet all of the requirements of an investment contract under Howey. Though not a securities lawyer by profession, Seth’s analysis received <a href="https://twitter.com/johnedeaton1/status/1670944780023480320?s=21&amp;t=wrnPxlnnedgK7f-A78lsZw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">high praise</a> from Deaton as “good or better than any of mine or anyone else’s.”</p>
<p>Seth spoke with <em>CryptoPotato</em> this week about his case against the SEC, and what implications the lawsuit carries for the entire industry. He argued that the real Howey Test contains a sparsely mentioned fifth prong that XRP fails to satisfy.</p>
<p>“The most basic requirement [of] a security is an instrument that evidences a financial stake in a common enterprise, like the Howey contracts did,” he said. The SEC, by contrast, has “bogusly” tried to eliminate that requirement.</p>
<p>His claims are in line with Deaton’s who has often <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1671910549473337344" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> Ripple’s success as a company is not necessarily tied to XRP’s gains or losses on the market.</p>
<p>As referenced by Seth, court records from <a href="https://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/328/293/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">SEC v. W.J. Howey Co</a> provide the following definition of an investment contract.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For purposes of the Securities Act, an investment contract (undefined by the Act) means a contract, transaction, or scheme whereby a person invests his money in a common enterprise and is led to expect profits solely from the efforts of the promoter or a third party, it being immaterial whether the shares in the enterprise are evidenced by formal certificates or by nominal interests in the physical assets employed in the enterprise.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Seth said he hopes that Judge Torres is not “bamboozled” by the SEC’s Howey interpretation, and finds that none of the contracts under which Ripple sold XRP are securities, since they do not “convey any interest in a common enterprise.”</p>
<h2>The Hinman Emails</h2>
<p>Another of Ripple’s common arguments is that the crypto industry received faulty and contradictory guidance from the SEC about how digital assets are classified. They cite a 2018 speech from former commissioner William Hinman as an example, in which he describes how cryptos that were once commodities could potentially transition into being securities, among other criteria.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, the SEC was forced to leak internal communications about the speech. The emails <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-and-the-hinman-speech-what-happened-behind-the-scenes/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that Hinman published the speech despite receiving multiple warnings from his fellow agency members that the speech could confuse readers about which characteristics factored into an asset being a security.</p>
<p>While showing proof of potential SEC corruption, Seth said those emails are likely just a “red herring.”</p>
<p>“The fair notice defense is *NOT* implicated (if the Court rules, as it should, that neither XRP itself nor the Ripple contracts under which it was sold were investment contracts),” he explained.</p>
<h2>What Does This Mean For Crypto?</h2>
<p>Like many in the crypto industry, Seth believes that a ruling in Ripple’s favor can “clarify in one fell swoop” that the SEC does not have broad authority over the crypto industry.</p>
<p>This would effectively protect crypto companies from the agency’s future enforcement actions until clarifying legislation is passed in Congress. Until then, another agency – like the CFTC – could take charge.</p>
<p>The SEC sued crypto exchanges Binance and Coinbase this month, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleging</a> that over a dozen cryptos listed on their platforms were securities in the process. Many of these coins – including Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) – were sold and behave in a similar manner to XRP, and suffered similar losses to XRP after the SEC’s allegations.</p>
<p>Seth is himself a crypto investor, who spent months reaching his conclusion on the case after reading the SEC’s summary judgment filings.</p>
<p>“Through bogus enforcement action the SEC has terrorized the crypto industry,” he said. “The SEC has hurt crypto investors and what’s more it knew it was hurting the investors when it brought these lawsuits.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-the-ripple-v-sec-lawsuit-could-affect-the-entire-crypto-industry-a-lawyers-take/" rel="nofollow">How The Ripple v. SEC Lawsuit Could Affect The Entire Crypto Industry: A Lawyer&#8217;s Take</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum &#038; Solana Price Growth Slows, But Ecoterra Continues to Rise</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-solana-price-growth-slows-but-ecoterra-continues-to-rise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256786</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ecoterra_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ecoterra_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It’s been a hectic few days in the crypto market, with an abundance of coins and tokens producing double-digit returns. However, there’s been a marked slowdown in the growth of Ethereum (ETH) and Solana (SOL), leading investors to debate whether their recent uptick in momentum was only temporary. Meanwhile, eco-friendly crypto project Ecoterra (ECOTERRA) continues [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s been a hectic few days in the crypto market, with an abundance of coins and tokens producing double-digit returns.</p>
<p>However, there’s been a marked slowdown in the growth of Ethereum (ETH) and Solana (SOL), leading investors to debate whether their recent uptick in momentum was only temporary.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, eco-friendly crypto project Ecoterra (ECOTERRA) continues making headlines – and has now breached the $5.3 million mark in its ongoing presale.</p>
<h2>Turbulent Market Forces Prompt ETH &amp; SOL Slowdown</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, ETH is hovering around the $1,870 level, following a surprise surge earlier in the week.</p>
<p>This surge culminated in ETH breaching $1,900 before immediately retracing.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s recent price movements suggest a high volume of sell orders located around $1,900, which has halted the bullish momentum.</p>
<p>Moreover, although price has soared above the 20-day and 50-day Exponential Moving Averages (EMAs), movement over the past 24 hours suggests that a potential retest of these indicators is on the cards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-23.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256791" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-23.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="308" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-23.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-23-300x153.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-23-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>If this occurs, the price could drop back to $1,815 to use the 50-day EMA as a springboard for another push.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, fellow Proof-of-Stake (PoS) cryptocurrency Solana has also experienced a much-needed price rise, with the token briefly surpassing the $17 level.</p>
<p>However, much like Ethereum, the bullish momentum looks to have been temporary – with the SOL price dropping nearly 8% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/solana/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">reveals</a> that the SOL trading volume has sunk by 40% in that time frame, indicating that traders are becoming increasingly cautious about Solana’s prospects.</p>
<p>Moreover, analytics from Solscan.io <a href="https://analytics.solscan.io/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">shows</a> that the number of active Solana wallets has dropped from Monday’s high.</p>
<h2>Long-Term Potential Still Positive for Ethereum &amp; Solana</h2>
<p>Despite these bearish indicators, investors are still relatively optimistic, given the broader context of the crypto market.</p>
<p>BlackRock&#8217;s recent application for a spot Bitcoin ETF has sparked life back into the market since it highlights that large institutions are still bullish on crypto.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256790" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-21.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="269" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-21-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-21-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>In addition, a recent <a href="https://www.marketresearchfuture.com/reports/decentralized-finance-market-11510" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">report</a> from Market Research Future forecasts that the value of the decentralized finance (DeFi) market could grow to a whopping $446.43 billion by 2032.</p>
<p>Since both Ethereum and Solana are deeply involved in the DeFi market, this projection implies a massive growth opportunity for both cryptos in the long term.</p>
<p>Thus, while ETH and SOL have undoubtedly seen a slowdown in price momentum, the long-term outlook remains promising – making them attractive considerations for crypto-savvy investors.</p>
<h2>Which Cryptos Are Still Growing Amid the Market Rebound?</h2>
<p>Amid the market fluctuations, several other cryptocurrencies are experiencing renewed interest alongside Ethereum and Solana.</p>
<p>A particularly noteworthy example is Ecoterra, which has now raised over $5.3 million during its highly-successful presale phase.</p>
<h2>Crypto Sensation Ecoterra Gamifies Recycling to Promote Sustainability</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra (ECOTERRA)</a> is an Ethereum-based ecosystem that aims to combat climate change by promoting recycling.</p>
<p>The ecosystem has several sustainability-focused features, although the groundbreaking Recycle2Earn mobile app is undoubtedly the most compelling.</p>
<p>This app allows users to scan the barcodes of various items and earn ECOTERRA tokens for recycling them – with no cap on how much a user can make.</p>
<p>Per Ecoterra’s <a href="https://www.ecoterra.io/documents/whitepaper-ecoterra.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, this setup is designed to incentivize individuals (and businesses) to recycle more, thereby positively impacting the environment.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-17.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256789" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-17.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="269" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-17.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-17-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-17-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Since rewards are denominated in ECOTERRA, users could also benefit if the token&#8217;s price increased once listed on centralized exchanges (CEXs).</p>
<p>Alongside the Recycle2Earn app, the Ecoterra ecosystem will have a carbon offset marketplace, a recycled materials marketplace, and a trackable &#8220;Impact Profile.&#8221;</p>
<p>The potential of these features has caused significant hype around the Ecoterra project, with over 6,500 people participating in the official <a href="https://t.me/ecoterraio" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a>.</p>
<p>Ecoterra has even caught the attention of several crypto influencers; for example, Crypto Moonlight released a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0uwSEwDDrJo&amp;pp=ygUPZWNvdGVycmEgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> stating that Ecoterra could make investors &#8220;insane profit.&#8221;</p>
<p>All in all, Ecoterra seems poised to make significant strides in promoting sustainability on the blockchain, making it an appealing option for eco-conscious investors worldwide.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-solana-price-growth-slows-but-ecoterra-continues-to-rise/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum &#038; Solana Price Growth Slows, But Ecoterra Continues to Rise</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
