<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bears Pull BTC Down to $29,000 Level – Where is BTC Heading Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-pull-btc-down-29000-level-where-btc-heading-next.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has recently held above $29,000, signaling potential positivity, but hasn't reached $30,000 yet. It's been trading between roughly $28,900 and $29,280, reflecting uncertainty. &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, significant Bitcoin holders are selling less, possibly indicating their confidence in its future value increase. &lt;br /&gt;
The recent increase in the value of Bitcoin may be connected to PayPal's announcement of their new digital currency, PayPal USD (PYUSD)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-pull-btc-down-29000-level-where-btc-heading-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bears Pull BTC Down to $29,000 Level – Where is BTC Heading Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-pull-btc-down-29000-level-where-btc-heading-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121817/322560/8-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="533139"/></item><item><title>Russian Banks Say Citizens Are ‘Wary’ of CBDC Plans – Digital Ruble Faces Roadblock?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-banks-say-citizens-are-wary-of-cbdc-plans-digital-ruble-faces-roadblock.htm</link><description>Russia’s biggest banking association has demanded clarification on Moscow’s CBDC plans, and says citizens are “wary” of the digital ruble. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Komersant and BFM, the Association of Russian Banks (ARB) sent a letter to the Central Bank with “a request to clarify certain issues pertaining to the digital ruble.” &lt;br /&gt;
The Central Bank is currently working with over a dozen commercial banks on a “real-world” pilot. &lt;br /&gt;
But, the ARB wrote:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-banks-say-citizens-are-wary-of-cbdc-plans-digital-ruble-faces-roadblock.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Banks Say Citizens Are ‘Wary’ of CBDC Plans – Digital Ruble Faces Roadblock?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-banks-say-citizens-are-wary-of-cbdc-plans-digital-ruble-faces-roadblock.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121774/322442/adobestock-619979221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="473630"/></item><item><title>Belarus Prepares to Launch ‘Cross-Border’ CBDC – Russia’s Digital Ruble an Inspiration?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-prepares-to-launch-cross-border-cbdc-russias-digital-ruble-an-inspiration.htm</link><description>Belarus is set to follow suit with Russia’s CBDC development plans – and plans to launch a digital version of the Belarusian ruble for use in “cross-border” payments. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Minsk-Novosti and Interfax, the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus (NBRB) has earmarked the launch of CBDC as one of its most “significant” projects of recent years. &lt;br /&gt;
Dmitry Kalechits, the NRBR’s Board’s Deputy Chairman, said:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-prepares-to-launch-cross-border-cbdc-russias-digital-ruble-an-inspiration.htm"&gt;Read More: Belarus Prepares to Launch ‘Cross-Border’ CBDC – Russia’s Digital Ruble an Inspiration?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Belarus</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-prepares-to-launch-cross-border-cbdc-russias-digital-ruble-an-inspiration.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121700/322310/adobestock-615575824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="685848"/></item><item><title>Investors Have Stopped Shorting Bitcoin for First Time in 3 Months: CoinShares Report</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/investors-stopped-shorting-bitcoin-for-first-time-3-months-coinshares-report-1.htm</link><description>According to the latest Coinshares Fund Report, outflows into short Bitcoin (BTC) products have ceased for the first time in fourteen weeks.  &lt;br /&gt;
This notable shift in the market suggests that significant digital asset funds are now adopting a different strategy towards the leading cryptocurrency, seeking alternative opportunities for returns....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/investors-stopped-shorting-bitcoin-for-first-time-3-months-coinshares-report-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Investors Have Stopped Shorting Bitcoin for First Time in 3 Months: CoinShares Report&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>CoinShares</category><category>Report</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Volatility</category><category>Shorting</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/investors-stopped-shorting-bitcoin-for-first-time-3-months-coinshares-report-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121801/322511/getpaidstock-com-64d17106.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="203916"/></item><item><title>Web3 Utility Coin LPX Raises $1.2 Million in Funding for AI Trading Analytics Platform – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-raises-12-million-funding-for-ai-trading-analytics-platform-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Web3 represents the new age of internet technology where everything is decentralized. Unlike traditional internet services where a few companies control data, Web3 allows people to own and control their data. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-raises-12-million-funding-for-ai-trading-analytics-platform-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 Utility Coin LPX Raises $1.2 Million in Funding for AI Trading Analytics Platform – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Central Crypto Hub</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Utility Coin</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-raises-12-million-funding-for-ai-trading-analytics-platform-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121793/322502/f2n0-kuxcaiw1f4.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="111620"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 August – XDC Network, Kaspa, Algorand</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-august-xdc-network-kaspa-algorand.htm</link><description>PayPal, the global payments giant, continued its journey into the cryptocurrency space with the launch of its own stablecoin today, PayPal USD (PYUSD). &lt;br /&gt;
This development marks a significant stride since PayPal's initial foray into the cryptocurrency industry in late 2020. &lt;br /&gt;
Given this development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-august-xdc-network-kaspa-algorand.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 August – XDC Network, Kaspa, Algorand&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>XDC Network</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Kaspa</category><category>Xrp20</category><category>Algorand</category><category>XDC</category><category>XDC price</category><category>Kas</category><category>KAS price</category><category>ALGO</category><category>ALGO PRICE</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptos</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>WSM</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Memecoins</category><category>Staking</category><category>Passive income</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-august-xdc-network-kaspa-algorand.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121798/322503/bctbt-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260398"/></item><item><title>Mega Dice Telegram Casino App: World’s First Crypto Casino Offering Licensed Gambling Through TG</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mega-dice-telegram-casino-app-worlds-first-crypto-casino-offering-licensed-gambling-through-tg.htm</link><description>In a breakthrough for crypto casino adoption, Mega Dice is leading the way by opening the world’s first licensed crypto casino accessible via the Telegram app.  &lt;br /&gt;
The crypto casino sector is a big business and growing in popularity because it leverages blockchain's unique transparency and trust features to create a new standard for fairness in the industry....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mega-dice-telegram-casino-app-worlds-first-crypto-casino-offering-licensed-gambling-through-tg.htm"&gt;Read More: Mega Dice Telegram Casino App: World’s First Crypto Casino Offering Licensed Gambling Through TG&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mega-dice-telegram-casino-app-worlds-first-crypto-casino-offering-licensed-gambling-through-tg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121797/322496/mega-dice-homepage.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1988120"/></item><item><title>Crypto Hedge Funds Grapple with Shutdowns and Lackluster Returns in 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-hedge-funds-grapple-with-shutdowns-lackluster-returns-2023.htm</link><description>Crypto hedge funds have on average underperformed Bitcoin (BTC) by a significant margin in the first half of 2023, while about 13% of funds have shut down so far this year. &lt;br /&gt;
On average, crypto hedge funds generated a 15.2% return in the first six months of this year, well below the 83.3% that an investor would earn by simply holding spot BTC over the same period, Bloomberg reported this weekend. &lt;br /&gt;
The report cited data from Switzerland-based investment adviser 21e6 Capital AG....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-hedge-funds-grapple-with-shutdowns-lackluster-returns-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Hedge Funds Grapple with Shutdowns and Lackluster Returns in 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Altcoins</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-hedge-funds-grapple-with-shutdowns-lackluster-returns-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121789/322477/lackluster-returns.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="258327"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: August 7, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-august-7-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Knights of Degen (DGEN) &lt;br /&gt;
BitForexListings: Novem Gold (NVM)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-august-7-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: August 7, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exhange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-august-7-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121775/322439/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – 科太币, Toshi, Kitty, Evil Pepe</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-ke-tai-bi-toshi-kitty-evil-pepe.htm</link><description>Major blue-chip crypto prices are under modest pressure on Monday, with Bitcoin (BTC) recently dipping below $29,000 once again and eyeing a retest of monthly lows, and Ether (ETH) testing the $1,800 and eyeing a retest of its 200DMA. &lt;br /&gt;
There doesn’t seem to be any news driving the bearish price action, with traders likely booking some profit ahead of the release of the highly anticipated monthly US Consumer Price Index inflation report later in the week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-ke-tai-bi-toshi-kitty-evil-pepe.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – 科太币, Toshi, Kitty, Evil Pepe&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DEXTools</category><category>Shitcoins</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>ETH</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-ke-tai-bi-toshi-kitty-evil-pepe.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121795/322490/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Crypto Analyst Highlights Germany's Economic Challenges and Its Surprising Implications for Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-analyst-highlights-germanys-economic-challenges-its-surprising-implications-for-crypto.htm</link><description>A weakening economy and potential recession in Germany could be positive for Bitcoin (BTC) prices, crypto analyst Marcel Pechman believes. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Pechman, a further fall in Germany’s gross domestic product (GDP) will likely mean that the European Central Bank (ECB) will start easing its monetary policy, simply because European governments can’t afford to pay higher interest rates on their bonds....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-analyst-highlights-germanys-economic-challenges-its-surprising-implications-for-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Analyst Highlights Germany's Economic Challenges and Its Surprising Implications for Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Germany</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-analyst-highlights-germanys-economic-challenges-its-surprising-implications-for-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121782/322459/germany.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="183641"/></item><item><title>Global Payment Firm PayPal Launches Crypto Stablecoin – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payment-firm-paypal-launches-crypto-stablecoin-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>Global digital payments giant PayPal Holdings Inc. is stepping into the stablecoin market. &lt;br /&gt;
The fintech behemoth, which was founded more than 25 years ago, is set to become the first major financial institution to launch its own US dollar-backed stablecoin, which will be called PayPal USD (PYUSD). &lt;br /&gt;
The stablecoin is going to be issued by Paxos Trust Co. and will be fully backed by US dollar bank deposits and other liquid equivalents, such as short-term treasuries....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payment-firm-paypal-launches-crypto-stablecoin-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: Global Payment Firm PayPal Launches Crypto Stablecoin – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>PYUSD</category><category>USDT</category><category>UST</category><category>Terra</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payment-firm-paypal-launches-crypto-stablecoin-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121788/322473/paypal.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6712975"/></item><item><title>Buckle Up for the COWABUNGA Coin Presale: A Radical New Meme Coin in the World of Pizza and Ninja Turtles</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/buckle-up-for-cowabunga-coin-presale-radical-new-meme-coin-world-of-pizza-ninja-turtles.htm</link><description>The echo of "Cowabunga!" still resonates with many children of the 90's, a reminder of pizzas, vigilante turtles, and carefree childhoods. The cry, iconicized by the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (TMNT), transcended animated frames to become a staple in popular culture. &lt;br /&gt;
Now, this nostalgic term finds a new home, not in another cartoon series or movie, but as a digital currency—Cowabunga Coin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/buckle-up-for-cowabunga-coin-presale-radical-new-meme-coin-world-of-pizza-ninja-turtles.htm"&gt;Read More: Buckle Up for the COWABUNGA Coin Presale: A Radical New Meme Coin in the World of Pizza and Ninja Turtles&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Tmnt Coin</category><category>Cowabunga Coin</category><category>Best Presale</category><category>Best Meme Coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/buckle-up-for-cowabunga-coin-presale-radical-new-meme-coin-world-of-pizza-ninja-turtles.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121768/322449/f23phasxkaa5-u6.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="281803"/></item><item><title>Rumors of Insolvency and Chinese Probes Cause Huobi Crypto Exchange TVL to Drop to $2.5 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rumors-of-insolvency-chinese-probes-cause-huobi-crypto-exchange-tvl-drop-25-billion.htm</link><description>Popular cryptocurrency exchange Huobi has experienced significant outflows of funds and a decline in its total value locked (TVL) amidst rumors of insolvency and Chinese investigations.  &lt;br /&gt;
Between August 5 and 6, Huobi saw outflows totaling $64 million, causing its TVL to drop to $2.5 billion, down from $3.09 billion on July 6, according to data from DefiLlama. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rumors-of-insolvency-chinese-probes-cause-huobi-crypto-exchange-tvl-drop-25-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: Rumors of Insolvency and Chinese Probes Cause Huobi Crypto Exchange TVL to Drop to $2.5 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Huobi</category><category>Huobi Global</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Justin Sun</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rumors-of-insolvency-chinese-probes-cause-huobi-crypto-exchange-tvl-drop-25-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121773/322437/9e06ab12a1-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="73762"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Kenyan Police Reportedly Raided Worldcoin Warehouse, US FBI Issues Warnings About NFT Scammers, Curve Finance Offers a $1.85 Million Bounty to Identify &amp; Convict the Hacker</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-kenyan-police-reportedly-raided-worldcoin-warehouse-us-fbi-issues-warnings-about-nft-scammers-curve-finance-offers-a-185-million-bounty-to-identify-convict-the-hacker.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-kenyan-police-reportedly-raided-worldcoin-warehouse-us-fbi-issues-warnings-about-nft-scammers-curve-finance-offers-a-185-million-bounty-to-identify-convict-the-hacker.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Kenyan Police Reportedly Raided Worldcoin Warehouse, US FBI Issues Warnings About NFT Scammers, Curve Finance Offers a $1.85 Million Bounty to Identify &amp; Convict the Hacker&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Kenya</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>Police</category><category>Crime</category><category>USA</category><category>FBI</category><category>NFT</category><category>North Korea</category><category>UK</category><category>Career</category><category>Curve Finance</category><category>Hack</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-kenyan-police-reportedly-raided-worldcoin-warehouse-us-fbi-issues-warnings-about-nft-scammers-curve-finance-offers-a-185-million-bounty-to-identify-convict-the-hacker.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121752/322413/adobestock-kristina-blokhin-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="736669"/></item><item><title>Eyeball Scanning Crypto Project Worldcoin Warehouse Raided by Kenyan Police</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eyeball-scanning-crypto-project-worldcoin-warehouse-raided-by-kenyan-police.htm</link><description>Worldcoin, the eyeball-scanning crypto project launched by OpenAI founder Sam Altman, is under increased scrutiny in Kenya, as local police reportedly raided the project’s warehouse in Nairobi, in search of data. &lt;br /&gt;
Per a local news report Monday, a team of Kenyan police officers raided Worldcoin’s warehouse in Nairobi and seized documents and machines to investigate stored data collected by the crypto project....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eyeball-scanning-crypto-project-worldcoin-warehouse-raided-by-kenyan-police.htm"&gt;Read More: Eyeball Scanning Crypto Project Worldcoin Warehouse Raided by Kenyan Police&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eyeball-scanning-crypto-project-worldcoin-warehouse-raided-by-kenyan-police.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121756/322420/eye-7173262-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="448703"/></item><item><title>UK Set To Expand Its National Crypto Crime Unit As Organized Blockchain Fraud Surges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-set-expand-its-national-crypto-crime-unit-as-organized-blockchain-fraud-surges.htm</link><description>The United Kingdom’s National Crime Agency (NCA) is set to increase its cryptocurrency fraud investigation unit as part of wider plans to halt the increase in financial crimes. &lt;br /&gt;
The new move will see the agency hire four new senior investigators to join the financial crime unit to tackle all forms of corruption and fraud cases on the blockchain....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-set-expand-its-national-crypto-crime-unit-as-organized-blockchain-fraud-surges.htm"&gt;Read More: UK Set To Expand Its National Crypto Crime Unit As Organized Blockchain Fraud Surges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>UK</category><category>Regulator</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>NCA</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-set-expand-its-national-crypto-crime-unit-as-organized-blockchain-fraud-surges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121761/322429/adobestock-94685515-media.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="284838"/></item><item><title>NFT Trader Hanwe Chang's Ingenious Move Nets $1.5 Million on Blur Marketplace – Here's What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-trader-hanwe-changs-ingenious-move-nets-15-million-blur-marketplace-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>An NFT trader that goes by the name Hanwe Chang has made 800 ETH, worth almost $1.5 million, after tricking a bot into buying his NFTs at elevated prices. &lt;br /&gt;
Writing on the social media platform X on this weekend, Hanwe Chang claimed that a bot was copying all of his NFT bids on Blur, a new NFT marketplace that has recently overtaken the previously dominant OpenSea as the top marketplace by volume....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-trader-hanwe-changs-ingenious-move-nets-15-million-blur-marketplace-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: NFT Trader Hanwe Chang's Ingenious Move Nets $1.5 Million on Blur Marketplace – Here's What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>NFT</category><category>Blur</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-trader-hanwe-changs-ingenious-move-nets-15-million-blur-marketplace-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121765/322428/profit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="567260"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Hedera? HBAR Price Shoots Up 11% in 24 Hours as Shibie Raises $150,000</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-hedera-hbar-price-shoots-up-11-24-hours-as-shibie-raises-150000.htm</link><description>Hedera Hashgraph (HBAR) has seen a third test of resistance from the 200DMA rejected as 3-months of suffocating price action seems set to continue. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes as the enterprise grade layer-1 blockchain has struggled to breakout from rock-bottom technical structure following a painful -90% bleed-out from its all-time high (ATH)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-hedera-hbar-price-shoots-up-11-24-hours-as-shibie-raises-150000.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Hedera? HBAR Price Shoots Up 11% in 24 Hours as Shibie Raises $150,000&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-hedera-hbar-price-shoots-up-11-24-hours-as-shibie-raises-150000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121742/322408/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="991161"/></item><item><title>JD Sports Teams Up With ZERO10 To Offer Virtual Fitting Of Nike Collection In Stores</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jd-sports-teams-up-with-zero10-offer-virtual-fitting-of-nike-collection-stores.htm</link><description>AR try-on store, Zero10 has announced its recent partnership with JD Sports to animate the new Need It Now Collection, a new release by Nike in collaboration with JD Sports. &lt;br /&gt;
Zero10 will deploy its AR Mirrors to allow users to virtually try on each outfit with advanced features and design to display subtle effects like water droplets.  &lt;br /&gt;
The main venues for the latest IRL collaboration will be JD Sport’s Time Square New York and State Street Chicago stores. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jd-sports-teams-up-with-zero10-offer-virtual-fitting-of-nike-collection-stores.htm"&gt;Read More: JD Sports Teams Up With ZERO10 To Offer Virtual Fitting Of Nike Collection In Stores&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>JD Sports</category><category>ZERO10</category><category>Nike</category><category>Need It Now</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jd-sports-teams-up-with-zero10-offer-virtual-fitting-of-nike-collection-stores.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121750/322432/ho20-sisterhood-pure-02-0.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="576980"/></item></channel></rss>
