<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Bulls Hold $0.50 Support Level – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-050-support-level-time-buy.htm</link><description>Ripple's (XRP) price has recently been trading at around $0.50, which is good news for those hoping for a price increase.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, its value has dropped significantly in the past months due to an ongoing legal issue with the SEC and Ripple Labs, the company behind XRP. &lt;br /&gt;
Currently priced at $0.50, stability has been found which may indicate the market is stabilizing after a drop. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-050-support-level-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Bulls Hold $0.50 Support Level – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-050-support-level-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122864/325107/xrp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="283473"/></item><item><title>Yuga Labs Plans to Part Ways with OpenSea NFT Marketplace Following Royalty Model Change</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/yuga-labs-plans-part-ways-with-opensea-nft-marketplace-following-royalty-model-change.htm</link><description>Yuga Labs, the entity behind the popular NFT collection Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), is set to halt support for OpenSea due to a change in the platform's royalty model.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Saturday tweet, Yuga Labs announced that it plans to wind down support for OpenSea following the upcoming removal of Operator Filter, an on-chain royalty enforcement tool. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/yuga-labs-plans-part-ways-with-opensea-nft-marketplace-following-royalty-model-change.htm"&gt;Read More: Yuga Labs Plans to Part Ways with OpenSea NFT Marketplace Following Royalty Model Change&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Yuga Labs</category><category>Opensea</category><category>NFTs</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/yuga-labs-plans-part-ways-with-opensea-nft-marketplace-following-royalty-model-change.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122857/325088/adobestock-alexandarilich.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="83825"/></item><item><title>Binance NotConnect, Coinbase Significant, PayPal Integrate and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/binance-notconnect-coinbase-significant-paypal-integrate-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/binance-notconnect-coinbase-significant-paypal-integrate-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance NotConnect, Coinbase Significant, PayPal Integrate and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/binance-notconnect-coinbase-significant-paypal-integrate-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122678/324699/crypr0s-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="224558"/></item><item><title>FTX Co-Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Appeals for Temporary Jail Release</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-co-founder-sam-bankman-fried-appeals-for-temporary-jail-release.htm</link><description>FTX co-founder Sam Bankman-Fried is seeking temporary release from jail in order to work on his defense with his lawyers at the federal courthouse in Manhattan.  &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, Bankman-Fried's lawyers sent a letter to US District Judge Lewis Kaplan, stating that their client was unable to adequately review the extensive documents related to his case while detained at the Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC) in Brooklyn. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-co-founder-sam-bankman-fried-appeals-for-temporary-jail-release.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Co-Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Appeals for Temporary Jail Release&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-co-founder-sam-bankman-fried-appeals-for-temporary-jail-release.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122844/325067/107150385-1668177437483-1-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="164115"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Crash – Will BTC Keep Falling?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-crash-will-btc-keep-falling.htm</link><description>The volatile world of cryptocurrency has once again captured global attention, with prices experiencing a sharp downturn. As Bitcoin, the leading digital currency, faces a significant price drop, many are left speculating on its future trajectory. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-crash-will-btc-keep-falling.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Crash – Will BTC Keep Falling?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-crash-will-btc-keep-falling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122843/325066/19.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="534242"/></item><item><title>Russian Analyst: Digital Ruble ‘Brings No Benefits’ for Ordinary Citizens</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-analyst-digital-ruble-brings-no-benefits-for-ordinary-citizens.htm</link><description>A Russian analyst has claimed that the digital ruble, the nation’s CBDC, will bring no benefits to ordinary citizens. &lt;br /&gt;
The comments were made by Anastasia Tselykh, a special correspondent at RTVI in her most recent column for the media outlet. &lt;br /&gt;
The Central Bank launched a pilot this week, which will see retailers in 11 cities join, along with the Moscow Metro network and over a dozen banks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-analyst-digital-ruble-brings-no-benefits-for-ordinary-citizens.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Analyst: Digital Ruble ‘Brings No Benefits’ for Ordinary Citizens&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-analyst-digital-ruble-brings-no-benefits-for-ordinary-citizens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122769/324654/rus-1808.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="976139"/></item><item><title>Pro: Evergrande Group chapter 15 'indirectly influenced Bitcoin sentiment'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pro-evergrande-group-chapter-15-indirectly-influenced-bitcoin-sentiment.htm</link><description>In a surprising turn of events, the recent developments surrounding the Evergrande Group's Chapter 15 filing have reverberated beyond traditional finance, indirectly influencing the sentiment around Bitcoin (BTC) and the cryptocurrency market. &lt;br /&gt;
Around 9:35 pm UTC on August 17, the price of Bitcoin plummeted by 8% in just 10 minutes. This sudden drop had a ripple effect on the broader cryptocurrency market, leaving crypto enthusiasts puzzled....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pro-evergrande-group-chapter-15-indirectly-influenced-bitcoin-sentiment.htm"&gt;Read More: Pro: Evergrande Group chapter 15 'indirectly influenced Bitcoin sentiment'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Evergrande</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><category>Yuan</category><category>Btc Price</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pro-evergrande-group-chapter-15-indirectly-influenced-bitcoin-sentiment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122839/325056/getpaidstock-com-64e00641.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="284258"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Tether Discontinues USDT Support on BTC Blockchain – Will Crypto Prices Keep Falling?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-tether-discontinues-usdt-support-btc-blockchain-will-crypto-prices-keep-falling.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC), the largest cryptocurrency globally, has experienced a downward trajectory in recent months, with its price sliding from $28,000 to approximately $26,220 today.  &lt;br /&gt;
This decline can be attributed in part to Tether's recent move. Tether, the leading stablecoin, decided to stop supporting USDT on the Bitcoin blockchain. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-tether-discontinues-usdt-support-btc-blockchain-will-crypto-prices-keep-falling.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Tether Discontinues USDT Support on BTC Blockchain – Will Crypto Prices Keep Falling?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-tether-discontinues-usdt-support-btc-blockchain-will-crypto-prices-keep-falling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122836/325050/img-0014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="517327"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – TELE, SBONK, XRP</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-tele-sbonk-xrp.htm</link><description>Major cryptocurrencies have been in free fall on Friday, with Bitcoin (BTC) last down around 8% in the last 24 hours and Ether (ETH) last down around 5.0% in the $25,700s and $1,650 areas respectively. &lt;br /&gt;
That takes losses on the week for Bitcoin and Ether to over 11% and 9% respectively, marking one of the worst weeks so far this year. &lt;br /&gt;
The broader crypto market’s total capitalization has dropped around $110 billion this week to only slightly above $1 trillion....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-tele-sbonk-xrp.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – TELE, SBONK, XRP&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Shitcoin</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>DEXTools</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-tele-sbonk-xrp.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122833/325036/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Mastercard Launches Forum for Crypto Industry Players to Discuss CBDCs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercard-launches-forum-for-crypto-industry-players-discuss-cbdcs.htm</link><description>Payments giant Mastercard has established a forum to facilitate discussions and collaboration among industry players in the cryptocurrency sphere regarding central bank digital currencies (CBDCs). &lt;br /&gt;
In a Thursday blog post, Mastercard said that the CBDC Partner Program has already attracted key participants such as Ripple, Fireblocks, and Consensys. &lt;br /&gt;
The primary objective of this program is to foster dialogue and encourage innovation and efficiency within the industry....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercard-launches-forum-for-crypto-industry-players-discuss-cbdcs.htm"&gt;Read More: Mastercard Launches Forum for Crypto Industry Players to Discuss CBDCs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>mastercard</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercard-launches-forum-for-crypto-industry-players-discuss-cbdcs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122821/324997/adobestock-emagnetic-1-me.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="207035"/></item><item><title>OpenSea NFT Marketplace Implements Changes to Creator Fees and Royalty Rules – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/opensea-nft-marketplace-implements-changes-creator-fees-royalty-rules-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The major non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace OpenSea has implemented changes that makes creator fees optional for new collections. &lt;br /&gt;
Specifically, the OpenSea said it would retire the Operator Filter, which functioned as an enforcement tool for creator royalties on the platform. &lt;br /&gt;
Instead, OpenSea will now move to optional royalties for all NFT sales on the secondary market, meaning the ordinary market where NFT collectors and traders sell to each other....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/opensea-nft-marketplace-implements-changes-creator-fees-royalty-rules-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: OpenSea NFT Marketplace Implements Changes to Creator Fees and Royalty Rules – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Opensea</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/opensea-nft-marketplace-implements-changes-creator-fees-royalty-rules-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122820/324996/opensea.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="75819"/></item><item><title>SpaceX Reports $373 Million Bitcoin Write-Down in Financial Documents</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/spacex-reports-373-million-bitcoin-write-down-in-financial-documents.htm</link><description>Elon Musk’s SpaceX is among many alleged culprits behind a seismic crypto market crash on Thursday, which has triggered over $1 billion in liquidations over the past 24 hours. Here's the latest. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC)’s sudden collapse to nearly $25,300 shortly followed the Wall Street Journal (WSJ) published a report offering rare insight into the privately owned aerospace company’s financials....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spacex-reports-373-million-bitcoin-write-down-in-financial-documents.htm"&gt;Read More: SpaceX Reports $373 Million Bitcoin Write-Down in Financial Documents&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/spacex-reports-373-million-bitcoin-write-down-in-financial-documents.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122827/325011/adobestock-310563156-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96118"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Judge Torres Grants SEC's Ripple Case Appeal Process – Will XRP Fall to 1 Cent?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-judge-torres-grants-secs-ripple-case-appeal-process-will-xrp-fall-1-cent.htm</link><description>While XRP is trading more than 16% up from Thursday’s lows and is back to the north of its 200DMA and the psychologically important $0.50 level, the world’s fifth-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization continues to trade lower by around 20% on the week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-judge-torres-grants-secs-ripple-case-appeal-process-will-xrp-fall-1-cent.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Judge Torres Grants SEC's Ripple Case Appeal Process – Will XRP Fall to 1 Cent?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>Ripple</category><category>SEC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-judge-torres-grants-secs-ripple-case-appeal-process-will-xrp-fall-1-cent.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122828/325009/xrp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="544495"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Halts USDT Trading for Canadian Users Starting August 31</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-halts-usdt-trading-for-canadian-users-starting-august-31.htm</link><description>In an email dated August 17, Coinbase, a cryptocurrency exchange, revealed its decision to halt trading of Tether USDT, Dai DAI, and RAI stablecoins for Canadian users starting August 31. &lt;br /&gt;
This surprising development comes shortly after Coinbase's recent announcement of its complete expansion into the Canadian market, including trading the largest stablecoin globally, Tether. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-halts-usdt-trading-for-canadian-users-starting-august-31.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Halts USDT Trading for Canadian Users Starting August 31&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Canada</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Tether</category><category>USDT</category><category>USDC</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-halts-usdt-trading-for-canadian-users-starting-august-31.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122825/325008/canada-2704154-1280-media.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="708242"/></item><item><title>North Korean Attackers Have Stolen $200 Million Across 30 Crypto Heists in 2023: TRM Labs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-attackers-stolen-200-million-across-30-crypto-heists-2023-trm-labs.htm</link><description>A new report from blockchain analytics firm TRM Labs noted that North Korean hackers have stolen more than $2 billion in cryptocurrencies in the past five years. It estimated around $200 million in crypto heists this year alone. &lt;br /&gt;
According to TRM Labs insights, the stolen amount accounts for 30 hacks so far in 2023, which is less than 2022, but still “10 times larger than attacks by other actors.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-attackers-stolen-200-million-across-30-crypto-heists-2023-trm-labs.htm"&gt;Read More: North Korean Attackers Have Stolen $200 Million Across 30 Crypto Heists in 2023: TRM Labs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-attackers-stolen-200-million-across-30-crypto-heists-2023-trm-labs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122822/324998/hacker-6512174-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="267470"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Mastercard Forms a CBDC Program with Ripple, Consensys &amp; Fireblocks, OpenSea is Set to Disable its Operator Filter, Taiwan Proposes Business Category for Crypto Firms to Self-regulate &amp; Form Industry Associations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-mastercard-forms-a-cbdc-program-with-ripple-consensys-fireblocks-opensea-is-set-to-disable-its-operator-filter-taiwan-proposes-business-category-for-crypto-firms-to-self-regulate-form-industry-associations.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-mastercard-forms-a-cbdc-program-with-ripple-consensys-fireblocks-opensea-is-set-to-disable-its-operator-filter-taiwan-proposes-business-category-for-crypto-firms-to-self-regulate-form-industry-associations.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Mastercard Forms a CBDC Program with Ripple, Consensys &amp; Fireblocks, OpenSea is Set to Disable its Operator Filter, Taiwan Proposes Business Category for Crypto Firms to Self-regulate &amp; Form Industry Associations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ConsenSys</category><category>Fireblocks</category><category>CBDC</category><category>NFT</category><category>Opensea</category><category>Taiwan</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Trading</category><category>Institutions</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Hack</category><category>Australia</category><category>Helio Lending</category><category>Legal</category><category>AI</category><category>chatGPT</category><category>Media</category><category>mastercard</category><category>Ripple</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-mastercard-forms-a-cbdc-program-with-ripple-consensys-fireblocks-opensea-is-set-to-disable-its-operator-filter-taiwan-proposes-business-category-for-crypto-firms-to-self-regulate-form-industry-associations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122779/324883/adobestock-pixieme-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="474082"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Toncoin? TON Price Up 10% as AI Crypto Signals Platform LPX Secures $1.3 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-toncoin-ton-price-up-10-as-ai-crypto-signals-platform-lpx-secures-13-million.htm</link><description>Despite broader anxieties in the market, Toncoin (TON) is on the climb, after a +10% bounce off the 20DMA leaves price poised for technical rally. &lt;br /&gt;
TON is the native token for 'The Open Network'; an ecosystem for decentralised apps (dApps) and services built using scalable sharding blockchain technology. &lt;br /&gt;
Following the bounce from support, TON is now trading at a current price of $1.34 (representing a 24-hour change of +1.73%)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-toncoin-ton-price-up-10-as-ai-crypto-signals-platform-lpx-secures-13-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Toncoin? TON Price Up 10% as AI Crypto Signals Platform LPX Secures $1.3 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-toncoin-ton-price-up-10-as-ai-crypto-signals-platform-lpx-secures-13-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122783/324880/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1368982"/></item><item><title>Celsius Sends Bankruptcy Restructuring Plan To Creditors Vote After Court’s Approval</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-sends-bankruptcy-restructuring-plan-creditors-vote-after-courts-approval.htm</link><description>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius is set to hold a vote on a plan to sell its asset to Fahrenheit Group following the approval by a judge as the proceeding winds down. &lt;br /&gt;
Celsius will send its creditors ballots to vote on the proposal between Aug 24 and Sept 22 and if approved, creditors could receive as high as $2 billion with each creditor getting returns ranging from 67% for Earn holders and 85% for those who were in the Borrow Program....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-sends-bankruptcy-restructuring-plan-creditors-vote-after-courts-approval.htm"&gt;Read More: Celsius Sends Bankruptcy Restructuring Plan To Creditors Vote After Court’s Approval&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius</category><category>Fahrenheit</category><category>Machinsky</category><category>Bankrupt</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-sends-bankruptcy-restructuring-plan-creditors-vote-after-courts-approval.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122810/324980/celsius-altcoins-1-media-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="103418"/></item><item><title>Bobby Zagotta, US CEO of Bitstamp, on US Crypto Regulation, The Banking Crisis, and Web3 Innovation | Ep. 257</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/bobby-zagotta-us-ceo-of-bitstamp-us-crypto-regulation-banking-crisis-web3-innovation-ep-257.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Bobby Zagotta, US CEO &amp; Chief Commercial Officer at Bitstamp, talks about 2023 market movements, Web3 innovation, navigating regulation, and the banking crisis. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/bobby-zagotta-us-ceo-of-bitstamp-us-crypto-regulation-banking-crisis-web3-innovation-ep-257.htm"&gt;Read More: Bobby Zagotta, US CEO of Bitstamp, on US Crypto Regulation, The Banking Crisis, and Web3 Innovation | Ep. 257&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/bobby-zagotta-us-ceo-of-bitstamp-us-crypto-regulation-banking-crisis-web3-innovation-ep-257.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122800/324887/bobby-zagotta-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="123122"/></item><item><title>Analysts: Coinbase's Derivatives Approval Shows Crypto's Resilience in the US</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/analysts-coinbases-derivatives-approval-shows-cryptos-resilience-us.htm</link><description>Analysts at investment bank JMP Securities have said that an approval received by Coinbase to offer crypto futures trading can be taken as evidence of crypto’s resilience in the US. &lt;br /&gt;
In a note to clients that was cited by The Block, the analysts said the approval "adds validation" to the domestic crypto sector in the US, and is a step on the way in countering a narrative that the American crypto industry is being pushed offshore....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/analysts-coinbases-derivatives-approval-shows-cryptos-resilience-us.htm"&gt;Read More: Analysts: Coinbase's Derivatives Approval Shows Crypto's Resilience in the US&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/analysts-coinbases-derivatives-approval-shows-cryptos-resilience-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122806/324966/coinbase-lgoo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2093026"/></item></channel></rss>
