<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>USD+ Token Just Shot Up 1,000% But Crypto Whales are Accumulating This Other Token Before it Lists on Exchanges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/usd-token-just-shot-up-1000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges.htm</link><description>In a major move sending shockwaves through DEX markets, leading ZKSYNC DEX stablecoin USD+ has destabilized creating seismic price moves. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes amid a significant period for stablecoins, which are becoming increasingly mainstreamed by the emergence of government-issued CBDCs. &lt;br /&gt;
Following the dramatic instability for USD+, the leading DEX stablecoin is currently trading below-price at $0.9952 as algorithms fight to stabilize against more than 600,000 transactions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/usd-token-just-shot-up-1000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges.htm"&gt;Read More: USD+ Token Just Shot Up 1,000% But Crypto Whales are Accumulating This Other Token Before it Lists on Exchanges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/usd-token-just-shot-up-1000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122343/323729/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1152917"/></item><item><title>XRP20 Blasts Off as 22% of Presale Supply Staked For 109% APY in Less Than 24 Hours – Presale Raises $2.7m, Selling Out Fast</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp20-blasts-off-as-22-of-presale-supply-staked-for-109-apy-less-than-24-hours-presale-raises-27m-selling-out-fast.htm</link><description>Monday, August 14, 2023 – The XRP price might be declining, but XRP20 coin buyers have staked 22.7% of its presale-allocated supply as the project hurtles toward sell-out after raising $2.74 million, with only $949,000 to go. &lt;br /&gt;
The XRP20 presale will finish early this week at the current rate as the stake-to-earn coin closes in on its target of $3,680,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp20-blasts-off-as-22-of-presale-supply-staked-for-109-apy-less-than-24-hours-presale-raises-27m-selling-out-fast.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP20 Blasts Off as 22% of Presale Supply Staked For 109% APY in Less Than 24 Hours – Presale Raises $2.7m, Selling Out Fast&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp20-blasts-off-as-22-of-presale-supply-staked-for-109-apy-less-than-24-hours-presale-raises-27m-selling-out-fast.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122385/323753/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="478453"/></item><item><title>DeFi Value Locked Reaches Nearly $42 Billion as Token Market Experiences Significant Growth – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-value-locked-reaches-nearly-42-billion-as-token-market-experiences-significant-growth-heres-latest.htm</link><description>The total value locked (TVL) across DeFi projects has experienced a resurgence after teetering below the $40 billion mark last week. &lt;br /&gt;
According to data from DeFi TVL aggregator DefiLlama, the DeFi market cap is currently valued at over $41 billion, with approximately $1.6 billion in trading volume over the past day. &lt;br /&gt;
The surge indicates a daily rise of around 6%, accompanied by a 6.39% increase in trade volume. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-value-locked-reaches-nearly-42-billion-as-token-market-experiences-significant-growth-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: DeFi Value Locked Reaches Nearly $42 Billion as Token Market Experiences Significant Growth – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>DeFi</category><category>DefiLlama</category><category>TVL</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-value-locked-reaches-nearly-42-billion-as-token-market-experiences-significant-growth-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122363/323717/8c53f6a846.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="87542"/></item><item><title>Former SEC Official: Bitcoin ETF Approval Will Not Happen Soon, Could Occur After 2024</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-official-bitcoin-etf-approval-will-not-happen-soon-could-occur-after-2024.htm</link><description>A spot Bitcoin-backed exchange-traded fund (ETF) will not be approved in the US until at least 2024 when the election is over, according to a former SEC official. &lt;br /&gt;
Writing on social media platform X this weekend, John Reed Stark, a former chief of the SEC’s Office of Internet Enforcement, said he does not expect much to change with regards to crypto enforcement action this year, and that a spot ETF approvals will have to wait until next year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-official-bitcoin-etf-approval-will-not-happen-soon-could-occur-after-2024.htm"&gt;Read More: Former SEC Official: Bitcoin ETF Approval Will Not Happen Soon, Could Occur After 2024&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-official-bitcoin-etf-approval-will-not-happen-soon-could-occur-after-2024.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122375/323739/bitcoin-etf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="65885"/></item><item><title>Former US President Donald Trump Holds Around $500,000 In Digital Assets</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-us-president-donald-trump-holds-around-500000-digital-assets.htm</link><description>A new financial filing reveals that former United States President Donald Trump holds between $250,000 to $500,000 in digital assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The filing submitted to the Office of Government Ethics (OGE) showed a list of assets from various sources belonging to the ex-President.  &lt;br /&gt;
An item that caught the eye of crypto enthusiasts was described as a “Cryptocurrency Wallet (Ethereum)”, a value Trump places between $250k to $500k....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-us-president-donald-trump-holds-around-500000-digital-assets.htm"&gt;Read More: Former US President Donald Trump Holds Around $500,000 In Digital Assets&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Donald Trump</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>NFTs</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-us-president-donald-trump-holds-around-500000-digital-assets.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122372/323737/c911318571-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="62408"/></item><item><title>DeFi Protocol Zunami Loses Over $2.1 Million in a Major Price Manipulation Attack</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-protocol-zunami-loses-over-21-million-major-price-manipulation-attack.htm</link><description>Decentralized Finance (DeFi) platform Zunami Protocol has confirmed a price manipulation attack on its “zStables” stablecoin pools on Curve Finance, causing potential losses of over $2.1 million. &lt;br /&gt;
The attack is the latest among the list of protocols affected by the recent vulnerability in the popular DeFi platform Curve Finance, which drained funds from a number of the protocol’s liquidity pools, exposing $100+ million worth of cryptocurrencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-protocol-zunami-loses-over-21-million-major-price-manipulation-attack.htm"&gt;Read More: DeFi Protocol Zunami Loses Over $2.1 Million in a Major Price Manipulation Attack&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-protocol-zunami-loses-over-21-million-major-price-manipulation-attack.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122348/323655/hacker-3342696-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="215980"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Shiba Inu? SHIB Price Pumps Up After Developer Teases New 'Exclusive' Update and LPX Token Raises $1.2 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-shib-price-pumps-up-after-developer-teases-new-exclusive-update-lpx-token-raises-12-million.htm</link><description>As Shiba Inu's Summer of Shibarium continues to gain traction ahead of the highly-anticipated Q3 Shibarium launch, SHIB is once again on the climb amid excitement around an upcoming new utility for sister-token LEASH holders. &lt;br /&gt;
Doge Killer (LEASH) token is an important cousin of SHIB, playing an important role in the Shiba Inu ecosystem as the native utility token for the ShibaSwap DEX....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-shib-price-pumps-up-after-developer-teases-new-exclusive-update-lpx-token-raises-12-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Shiba Inu? SHIB Price Pumps Up After Developer Teases New 'Exclusive' Update and LPX Token Raises $1.2 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-shib-price-pumps-up-after-developer-teases-new-exclusive-update-lpx-token-raises-12-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122357/323718/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="837517"/></item><item><title>THORChain Price Prediction as RUNE Pumps Up 46% – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/thorchain-price-prediction-as-rune-pumps-up-46-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The price of THORChain (RUNE) has risen to $1.35 today, representing an impressive 46% gain in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
RUNE is also up by 30% in the past month and by 5% since the beginning of the year, although the coin has actually fallen by 54% in the last 12 months and by 93.5% since reaching an all-time high of $20.87 in May 2021....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/thorchain-price-prediction-as-rune-pumps-up-46-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: THORChain Price Prediction as RUNE Pumps Up 46% – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/thorchain-price-prediction-as-rune-pumps-up-46-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122352/323710/thorchain-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1132574"/></item><item><title>Rollbit Coin is Going to Zero as RLB Price Drops 10% While XRP20 Surges Past $2.6 Million – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rollbit-coin-going-zero-as-rlb-price-drops-10-while-xrp20-surges-past-26-million-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>As the GambleFi narrative continues to send shockwaves through crypto markets, leading crypto gamling platform Rollbit coin (RLB) appears to be facing a breakdown - and amid the tumble many are asking is Rollbit going to zero? &lt;br /&gt;
With markets excited about the growth prospects for crypto projects taking aim at the $63Bn global online gambling space, top online casino projects have exploded across the summer tailing market leader RLB which surged +197% so far this month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rollbit-coin-going-zero-as-rlb-price-drops-10-while-xrp20-surges-past-26-million-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Rollbit Coin is Going to Zero as RLB Price Drops 10% While XRP20 Surges Past $2.6 Million – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rollbit-coin-going-zero-as-rlb-price-drops-10-while-xrp20-surges-past-26-million-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122346/323720/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1234361"/></item><item><title>20 Million Reddit Collectible Avatars Minted on 0xPolygon Platform – NFTs Making a Comeback?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/20-million-reddit-collectible-avatars-minted-0xpolygon-platform-nfts-making-comeback.htm</link><description>Reddit non-fungible tokens (NFTs) minted on layer-2 network Polygon have surpassed 20 million in the face of general quiet on the NFT front.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to Dune Analytics (on Monday morning, 9:00 UTC), a total of 20,323,749 collectible avatars has been minted since the launch of the project in July 2022, now in the hands of 16,361,793 holders.  &lt;br /&gt;
Collectible Avatars are unique digital goods made by independent creators in partnership with Reddit. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/20-million-reddit-collectible-avatars-minted-0xpolygon-platform-nfts-making-comeback.htm"&gt;Read More: 20 Million Reddit Collectible Avatars Minted on 0xPolygon Platform – NFTs Making a Comeback?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>reddit</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><category>Polygon</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/20-million-reddit-collectible-avatars-minted-0xpolygon-platform-nfts-making-comeback.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122337/323658/screenshot-2023-08-14-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="655382"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as $1,800 Level Holds Strong – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-1800-level-holds-strong-time-buy.htm</link><description>The Ethereum price has barely budged today, with its current level of $1,846 representing a 0.1% fall in the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
ETH remains up by 1% in the past week, and while it is down by 5% in the past month, it remains up by 54% since the beginning of the year. &lt;br /&gt;
And while it has, like most of the market, had a disappointing few weeks, it has held firmly to the $1,800 support level, indicating that it's unlikely to fall much further....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-1800-level-holds-strong-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as $1,800 Level Holds Strong – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-1800-level-holds-strong-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122347/323682/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1306031"/></item><item><title>PEPE Price Prediction as $100 Million Trading Volume Floods In – Are Meme Coins Back?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-100-million-trading-volume-floods-are-meme-coins-back.htm</link><description>The PEPE price has surged by 5% in the past 24 hours, with the meme token's move to $0.00000142 also representing a 23% gain in a week. &lt;br /&gt;
This means PEPE has easily outperformed the wider cryptocurrency market, which has barely moved today amid ongoing investor uncertainty (particularly in the face of the SEC's ongoing legal crusades)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-100-million-trading-volume-floods-are-meme-coins-back.htm"&gt;Read More: PEPE Price Prediction as $100 Million Trading Volume Floods In – Are Meme Coins Back?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-100-million-trading-volume-floods-are-meme-coins-back.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122338/323654/pepe-price-prediction-as-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1330216"/></item><item><title>PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub: A New Crypto-Inclusive Feature</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-unveils-cryptocurrencies-hub-a-new-crypto-inclusive-feature.htm</link><description>Payments giant PayPal has launched a new feature that allows users to hold and interact with Bitcoin (BTC) and other cryptocurrencies in their accounts.  &lt;br /&gt;
The new functionality, called Cryptocurrencies Hub, will allow users to not only hold a balance in various cryptocurrencies but also engage in transactions involving these digital assets. &lt;br /&gt;
By accessing the Cryptocurrencies Hub, PayPal users will be able to buy, sell, receive, and send cryptocurrencies. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-unveils-cryptocurrencies-hub-a-new-crypto-inclusive-feature.htm"&gt;Read More: PayPal Unveils Cryptocurrencies Hub: A New Crypto-Inclusive Feature&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-unveils-cryptocurrencies-hub-a-new-crypto-inclusive-feature.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122345/323651/paypal-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103256"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Former SEC Insider Voices Concerns on BTC ETF Amidst Regulatory Gridlock</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-former-sec-insider-voices-concerns-btc-etf-amidst-regulatory-gridlock.htm</link><description>As the world of cryptocurrency continues its volatile dance, the BTC/USD pair is currently witnessing a marginal increase, showing gains of nearly 0.10% and trading at a noteworthy $29,442 as of Monday.  &lt;br /&gt;
Amid this backdrop, recent revelations have stirred the crypto community. A former SEC official has stepped into the limelight, voicing apprehensions regarding approving Bitcoin Spot ETFs. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-former-sec-insider-voices-concerns-btc-etf-amidst-regulatory-gridlock.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Former SEC Insider Voices Concerns on BTC ETF Amidst Regulatory Gridlock&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-former-sec-insider-voices-concerns-btc-etf-amidst-regulatory-gridlock.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122333/323632/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1676212"/></item><item><title>Pepe Price Prediction as PEPE Blasts Up 20% with $100 Million Trading Volume – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-20-with-100-million-trading-volume-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>Pepe Coin has experienced a notable resurgence, grabbing the attention of many investors. Its consistent upward trend has surged from $0.000001185 to roughly $0.000001356 with a trading volume of $100 million.  &lt;br /&gt;
This highlights the increasing passion and engagement towards this cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
Pepe coin is performing well, providing a promising outlook for investors. The cryptocurrency, known for its frog theme, has seen a remarkable resurgence....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-20-with-100-million-trading-volume-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Price Prediction as PEPE Blasts Up 20% with $100 Million Trading Volume – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-20-with-100-million-trading-volume-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122330/323629/pepe.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="314125"/></item><item><title>Legal Twist: Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder's Citizenship Renunciation Disrupts Court's Jurisdiction in Bankruptcy Case</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/legal-twist-three-arrows-capital-co-founders-citizenship-renunciation-disrupts-courts-jurisdiction-in-bankruptcy-case.htm</link><description>In the bankruptcy case of Three Arrows Capital (3AC), a crypto hedge fund that ceased operations, a judge has rejected a request to hold co-founder Kyle Davies in contempt of Court and impose sanctions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/legal-twist-three-arrows-capital-co-founders-citizenship-renunciation-disrupts-courts-jurisdiction-in-bankruptcy-case.htm"&gt;Read More: Legal Twist: Three Arrows Capital Co-Founder's Citizenship Renunciation Disrupts Court's Jurisdiction in Bankruptcy Case&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>3AC</category><category>Three Arrows Capital</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><category>Legal</category><category>Kyle Davies</category><category>citizenship</category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/legal-twist-three-arrows-capital-co-founders-citizenship-renunciation-disrupts-courts-jurisdiction-in-bankruptcy-case.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122321/323621/getpaidstock-com-64d9709d.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="107084"/></item><item><title>Russia Will Use CBDC Pay Benefits &amp; Evade Sanctions, Experts Claim</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russia-will-use-cbdc-pay-benefits-evade-sanctions-experts-claim.htm</link><description>Russian experts say they think that the government will use the digital ruble to pay state benefits – and think the CBDC could be used to evade sanctions. &lt;br /&gt;
With just days to go until Russia pilots the coin, experts have been examining the scant details that have thus far been forthcoming prior to August 15....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russia-will-use-cbdc-pay-benefits-evade-sanctions-experts-claim.htm"&gt;Read More: Russia Will Use CBDC Pay Benefits &amp; Evade Sanctions, Experts Claim&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 21:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russia-will-use-cbdc-pay-benefits-evade-sanctions-experts-claim.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122307/323577/adobestock-14614042.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="544894"/></item><item><title>The MET Embraces the Metaverse with Roblox to Engage Young Visitors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/met-embraces-metaverse-with-roblox-engage-young-visitors.htm</link><description>The Metropolitan Museum of Art (The Met) in New York has partnered with the popular gaming platform, Roblox, in order to offer a virtual experience for its younger audience.  &lt;br /&gt;
As part of this collaboration, Roblox users can now obtain digital versions of famous artworks and artifacts for their avatars, including Van Gogh's iconic straw hat. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/met-embraces-metaverse-with-roblox-engage-young-visitors.htm"&gt;Read More: The MET Embraces the Metaverse with Roblox to Engage Young Visitors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>NFTs</category><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/met-embraces-metaverse-with-roblox-engage-young-visitors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122312/323591/pink-gbe3c6aaff-1920-medi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="228965"/></item><item><title>Binance Labs Fuels Helio Protocol's Liquid Staking Pivot with $10M Investment in LSDfi Expansion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-fuels-helio-protocols-liquid-staking-pivot-with-10m-investment-lsdfi-expansion.htm</link><description>Binance Labs, the venture arm of Binance, injected $10 million into Helio Protocol on August 11th. This investment supports Helio Protocol's ongoing shift towards becoming a liquid staking platform.  &lt;br /&gt;
The substantial funding from Binance Labs highlights Helio Protocol's promising potential and underscores the rising importance of liquid staking within decentralized finance (DeFi)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-fuels-helio-protocols-liquid-staking-pivot-with-10m-investment-lsdfi-expansion.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Labs Fuels Helio Protocol's Liquid Staking Pivot with $10M Investment in LSDfi Expansion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Helio Protocol</category><category>Liquid Staking</category><category>Binance Labs</category><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-fuels-helio-protocols-liquid-staking-pivot-with-10m-investment-lsdfi-expansion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122299/323568/getpaidstock-com-64d8a983bb7fc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="130247"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin on Ethereum Coin BTC20 Price Pumps 600% 48 Hours After Launch, Heading for $100m Market Cap</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-coin-btc20-price-pumps-600-48-hours-after-launch-heading-100-market-cap.htm</link><description>Bitcoin on Ethereum Coin BTC20 has seen its price explode 600% 48 hours after launch, with 10x gains imminent. As crypto traders start to pile into the hot coin, it is on course to hit a market cap of $100 million. &lt;br /&gt;
The BTC20 stake-to-earn coin mirrors the tokenomics of Bitcoin and is currently priced at $4.06, up more than 300% after listing for $1; the price has already briefly touched $6 for a 600% return, setting a marker for the near-term price target today....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-coin-btc20-price-pumps-600-48-hours-after-launch-heading-100-market-cap.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin on Ethereum Coin BTC20 Price Pumps 600% 48 Hours After Launch, Heading for $100m Market Cap&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ethereum-coin-btc20-price-pumps-600-48-hours-after-launch-heading-100-market-cap.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122295/323566/btc20-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="781826"/></item></channel></rss>
