<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 22:11:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bali Warns Tourists Against Using Crypto for Payments</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bali-warns-tourists-against-using-crypto-for-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 23:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252891</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bali.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bali.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Foreign tourists coming in to Bali have been warned agaisnt using crypto as payment, or risk tough sanctions from the government. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Indonesian province Bali has stated that tourists are not allowed to make payments with cryptocurrency, warning that violators &#8220;will be dealt with firmly.&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The government is looking to curb the influx of foreign tourists as a way to tackle problematic foreigners who violate local laws.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Offending Foreign Tourists to Face Tough Sanctions</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Bali will take action against foreign tourists who use cryptocurrency for payment, according to the province&#8217;s Governor Wayan Koster, who spoke at a tourism development press conference on Sunday, May 28. Koster <a href="https://en.antaranews.com/news/283182/bali-to-crack-down-on-foreign-tourists-using-crypto-as-payment" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> offenders could face deportation, criminal penalties, and other tough sanctions.</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;Foreign tourists who behave inappropriately, do activities that are not allowed in their visa permit, use crypto as a means of payment, and violate other provisions will be dealt with firmly.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">The Bali provincial Governor buttressed that the Indonesian rupiah was the only legal currency allowed as a payment means, stating that the use of any other currency contravened Indonesia&#8217;s law and offenders could face one-year imprisonment along with a fine of up to 200 million rupiah ($13,000).</p>
<p dir="ltr">Koster&#8217;s warning comes amid reports about the Governor&#8217;s plan to implement a <a href="https://asumsi.co/post/78608/pemprov-bali-akan-terapkan-sistem-kuota-bagi-wisatawan-asing/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">quota system</a> to limit the number of foreign tourists entering the province and also curb the influx of foreigners who violate local rules. Bali&#8217;s tourism sector, which peaked in 2019, took a hit in 2020 during the COVID-19 pandemic, causing the island to close international flights, thereby severely restricting foreign tourists into the country.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Bali has since reopened its borders, the province stated that there has been a rise in unruly behavior from tourists, which is seemingly <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/travel/2023/04/11/bali-bad-tourists-deported/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">causing </a>headaches for locals and the government.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Crypto is Allowed, But Not for Payments</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Head of the Bank of Indonesia for Bali, Trisno Nugroho, said that while crypto was acceptable in the province, its use for payment was not. As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indonesias-central-bank-bans-the-use-of-cryptocurrencies-for-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the Bank of Indonesia warned financial institutions against facilitating cryptocurrency payments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Koster also stated that foreign exchange business activities can only happen with permission from Indonesia&#8217;s central bank, adding that operating without a license could attract a maximum prison sentence of five years and a maximum fine of 22 billion rupiah ($1.4 million).</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;Violations will be subject to administrative sanctions in the form of written reprimands, obligations to pay fines, and prohibitions from payment transactions.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bali-warns-tourists-against-using-crypto-for-payments/" rel="nofollow">Bali Warns Tourists Against Using Crypto for Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Now Has Over 10 Million Ordinals Inscriptions</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-now-has-over-10-million-ordinals-inscriptions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 22:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252961</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/NFT_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/NFT_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Let’s review how Ordinals grew so big, so fast. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin users have registered over 10 million inscriptions into the Bitcoin blockchain using the newly popular Ordinals protocol. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The milestone comes shortly after Ordinals founder Casey Rordamor stepped down as the project’s lead maintainer on Saturday.</span></p>
<h2>Ordinals’ Blistering Growth</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to data from </span><a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Dune Analytics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Bitcoin sports exactly 10,018,046 Ordinals inscriptions at writing time – the vast majority of which were recorded over the past month alone. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">An inscription refers to data embedded into a Bitcoin transaction’s witness data. Inscriptions have always been possible on Bitcoin, but Ordinals allows users to inscribe data into a single identifiable satoshi, opening up a range of potential applications.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When Ordinals inscriptions first gained traction in February, their primary use case was for producing </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-support-bitcoin-ordinals-in-its-ntf-marketplace/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">non-fungible tokens (NFTs)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. This has already turned Bitcoin into the second most popular network for trading NFTs next to Ethereum, according to </span><a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoSlam</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, Ordinals inscriptions ramped up in April as users started leveraging the technology to issue fungible crypto tokens, through the experimental </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pros-and-cons-for-bitcoin-related-to-brc-20-token-standard-bitfinex-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">BRC-20</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> token standard. The standard was highly popular for issuing memecoins at first, but is now used to host the first Bitcoin-based stablecoin </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stably-launches-bitcoins-first-brc-20-stablecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Stably USD (USD)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After its unveiling in early March, BRC-20 triggered an avalanche of new inscriptions beginning in late April, and peaking in early May. The transition in Ordinals&#8217; dominance from NFTs to BRC-20 tokens is visible on the blockchain, through the takeover of text-based inscriptions over image-based ones at that time. </span></p>
<h2>Roaring Inscriptions and Fees</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As of April 20, Ordinals inscriptions totaled 1,193,102, per data from Dune. That number more than tripled by May 5 to 3,776,366, at which time daily transaction fees generated by related transactions </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">skyrocketed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. To this day, Ordinals has netted Bitcoin miners an additional $44 million in fees, and 91% of inscriptions have been text-based. </span></p>
<p>Certain Bitcoiners like Blockstream CEO Adam Back have <a href="https://twitter.com/adam3us/status/1619824591580598272?lang=en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">objected</a> to Ordinals &#8216;clogging&#8217; Bitcoin&#8217;s blockchain by making transfers more expensive for those using the for its intended purpose. On the other hand, billionaire Bitcoin investor Michael Saylor <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6kFltZAqk4U" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">sees</a> Ordinals as a potential foundation of future innovation, including trading digital securities on Bitcoin.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ordinals proponents were quick to celebrate the protocol’s milestone on Monday. Dan Held – former Product Manager at Kraken – said on Twitter that he’s confident Ordinals is more than just a fad. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/danheld/status/1663200791358832640</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ordinals founder Casey Rodarmor </span><a href="https://twitter.com/rodarmor/status/1662617512700420096" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">handed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> lead maintainer status to @raphjaph on Twitter on Saturday, saying he hasn’t been “able to give [Ordinals] the attention it deserves.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-now-has-over-10-million-ordinals-inscriptions/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Now Has Over 10 Million Ordinals Inscriptions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Publishes 7th PoR Report With $10B in Crypto Assets, Continues Expansion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-publishes-7th-por-report-with-10b-in-crypto-assets-continues-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKEx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252842</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/OKX_Bitcoin_Ethereum.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/OKX_Bitcoin_Ethereum.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[OKX's seventh PoR shows that the exchange holds bitcoin, ether, and USDT worth $10 billion in its reserve. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seychelles-based cryptocurrency exchange OKX published its seventh proof-of-reserves (PoR) report in line with efforts to push the new industry standard of transparency and trust within the crypto community.</p>
<p>The new <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/okx-publishes-seventh-monthly-proof-of-reserves-showing-usd10-billion-in-btc-eth-and-usdt-301836318.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> shows that OKX has reserves of $10 billion in bitcoin (BTC), ether (ETH), Tether (USDT), and other assets.</p>
<h2>OKX Releases Seventh PoR Report</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">audit</a>, which was concluded on May 19, 2023, shows that OKX&#8217;s current reserve ratios are 103% for BTC, 103% for ETH, and 103% for USDT. The PoR also covers 19 other widely-used crypto assets like USD Coin (USDC), Ripple (XRP), Dogecoin (DOGE), Solana (SOL), and Tron (TRX).</p>
<p>Since April, users have been able to independently verify OKX&#8217;s solvency through the Zero-Knowledge Scalable Transparent Argument of Knowledge (zk-STARK) technology. The zk-STARK technology keeps the account balances of other parties hidden, thereby safeguarding their privacy.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-releases-fifth-por-report-with-8-9b-in-clean-assets-plans-to-halt-canadian-branch/" data-wpel-link="internal">disclosed</a> its intentions to implement the zk-STARK technology upgrade in March so users could verify that all clients&#8217; deposits were accounted for by comparing the net equity of user assets to exchange reserves.</p>
<h2>Over 30% Increase Since January</h2>
<p>It is worth noting that the USD value of OKX&#8217;s BTC, ETH, and USDT reserves for May collectively declined by $400 million from the $10.4 billion published in April. However, the figure is 33% higher than January&#8217;s reserve, when OKX reported $7.5 million in assets.</p>
<p>Lennix Lai, OKX Global Chief Commercial Officer, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Since late 2022, OKX has set the highest industry standards for security and transparency via Proof of Reserves. Our pledge to users is to further improve our PoR system and streamline our use of zero-knowledge technology. We see PoR as a dynamic process that is an absolute imperative to earn and maintain the trust of our users in the long run.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>OKX Continues Expansion</h2>
<p>While OKX continues its push for transparency in the crypto industry, it has embarked on an expansion mission, hoping to stretch to other locations.</p>
<p>Last week, the Seychelles-based firm <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-applies-for-regulatory-approval-in-france/" data-wpel-link="internal">applied</a> to become a registered Digital Asset Service Provider (DASP) in France under the Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF) and the Autorité de Contrôle Prudentiel et de Résolution (ACPR).</p>
<p>Earlier this month, OKX also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-expands-its-global-reach-with-a-turkish-office/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> its plans to set up a Turkish office as it considers the country a &#8220;growing center of innovation and blockchain expertise with a user base that has a strong appetite for crypto.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-publishes-7th-por-report-with-10b-in-crypto-assets-continues-expansion/" rel="nofollow">OKX Publishes 7th PoR Report With $10B in Crypto Assets, Continues Expansion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fastest Growing Cryptocurrency Wall Street Memes Raises $1 Million in Viral Meme Token ICO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fastest-growing-cryptocurrency-wall-street-memes-raises-1-million-in-viral-meme-token-ico/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 19:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252898</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CryptoPotato-1200x780-1-1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/CryptoPotato-1200x780-1-1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the meme coin mania continues to rage, 1000x meme tokens are seeing a strong surge in demand. With Dogecoin and Shiba Inu’s underwhelming performance, traders are looking for alternative tokens with the potential for explosive price growth. The Wall Street Memes token is quickly becoming the next global meme coin phenomenon after raising $1 [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the meme coin mania continues to rage, 1000x meme tokens are seeing a strong surge in demand. With Dogecoin and Shiba Inu’s underwhelming performance, traders are looking for alternative tokens with the potential for explosive price growth.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252904" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-7.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="384" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-7.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-7-300x191.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-7-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> token is quickly becoming the next global meme coin phenomenon after raising $1 million in a record 2 days. Analysts are already backing WSM to mirror Pepe’s bull rally and generate heavy profits for investors. In this article, we look at the strengths of the WSM project and why so many traders are backing this token.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Hits $1 Million &#8211; Will It Outperform DOGE &amp; PEPE?</h2>
<p>Internet’s trendiest investing group Wall Street Memes recently announced their flagship meme coin, the Wall Street Memes token. Like every other initiative from the WSM group, the token is turning out to be a remarkable success. Launched on the 26th of May, the WSM token has already surpassed the $1 million milestone, selling out its second stage of the presale. It is currently priced at $0.0256 and is expected to surge as demand continues to skyrocket.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> is quickly filling in the vacuum created by Dogecoin’s sluggishness, which is trading 90% down from its all-time high of $0.74. Investors are worried that the explosive Doge has maxed out its potential. While the global crypto market cap expanded by 2.5% in the last 24 hours, DOGE surged by a mere 0.8% over the same period.</p>
<p>The token’s sideways price movement has made it extremely unlikely that it will ever breach the $1 mark once considered a surety. The token would have to surpass the total market cap of $139 billion to hit the $1 trading price. Even Elon Musk-induced DOGE rallies have been limited and temporary. While Dogecoin surged when Musk changed the Twitter logo to the Doge symbol, it soon corrected heavily when Twitter reverted to its blue bird logo.</p>
<p>In terms of growth prospects and profitability, the Wall Street Memes token looks to be closer to Pepe than Doge. WSM’s strong presale performance and social media buzz are reminiscent of Pepe’s 8000% surge after launch.</p>
<p>Pepe coin generated millions of percentages in profits for traders, turning small traders into millionaires. Experts are <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ILBQj18gbZw" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">expecting similar price explosiveness</a> from WSM after the token launches on various exchanges.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Token Receives Strong Community Support &#8211; Binance Listing Next?</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes token</a> is an ideal candidate for several Tier 1 exchange listings, including Binance and Coinbase. Its biggest strength is the popularity and financial expertise of the Wall Street Memes group.</p>
<p>The group gained global fame in 2021 when it inspired the historic GameStop short squeeze and the explosive GME and AMC bull run. It is one of the rare incidents when an army of small internet traders took on established financial institutions and won.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252903" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-6.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="384" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-6-300x191.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-6-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The WSM group looks to bring the same community strength to the crypto market and dominate the meme coin season. The group already has had a few successful forays in Web3. In 2021, WSM sold out its popular <a href="https://wallstreetbulls.io/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls NFT collection</a> in 32 minutes, netting over $2.5 million. It also launched Bitcoin Ordinal NFTs in May 2023. The WSM token will look to capitalise on the brand value and the user base the community has already built in the Web3 space.</p>
<p>Similar to Pepe, the <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes token</a> is a fully community-driven project. It highlights its commitment to user adoption through its community-first tokenomics. The entire WSM token supply is available for investors, with no separate allocation to teams or private sales.</p>
<p>50% of the total 2 billion token supply is available during the presale, while 30% is allocated to community rewards. Centralized and decentralized exchanges will be allotted 10% of the tokens each to maintain liquidity.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252902" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-6.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="289" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-6-300x144.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-6-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The project looks to further boost its user adoption through a $50k WSM airdrop. Investors can complete a few easy steps on the Gleam.io platform to register for the airdrop. 5 lucky token holders will be selected and rewarded $10k WSM tokens each.</p>
<p>Just as Pepe received a Binance listing due to its strong community and explosive bull rally, experts believe that WSM will be listed on several Tier 1 CEXs and DEXs after launch. In certain aspects, WSM may even have an advantage over Pepe.</p>
<p>A recent report highlighted that while the token generated 8000x growth, it received no backing from retail investors. Due to the WSM group’s reputation and its <a href="https://twitter.com/wallstmemes?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">1 million strong social media army</a>, the WSM token is not expected to face similar problems.</p>
<p>The WSM token is not stopping its surge after hitting the $1 million milestone. Investors have limited opportunity to jump on the WSM bandwagon early and purchase the tokens at a low price. Users can acquire the WSM token by swapping ETH, USDT, or BNB. Alternatively, they can purchase the token through bank cards.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fastest-growing-cryptocurrency-wall-street-memes-raises-1-million-in-viral-meme-token-ico/" rel="nofollow">Fastest Growing Cryptocurrency Wall Street Memes Raises $1 Million in Viral Meme Token ICO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Scraps Plans for Bitcoin Mining Excise Tax, Congressman Confirms</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-scraps-plans-for-bitcoin-mining-excise-tax-congressman-confirms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 19:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252943</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners in the United States will not be taxed for consuming energy, following US debt ceiling negotiations. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Biden Administration’s federal budget proposal to charge a 30% tax on all Bitcoin miners in the United States has been scrapped, a national policymaker confirmed on Sunday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The withdrawal is part of a series of tax-related concessions made by the administration in negotiations surrounding the nation’s fast-approaching debt ceiling.</span></p>
<h2>No More Mining Tax</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ohio Rep. Warren Davidson </span><a href="https://twitter.com/WarrenDavidson/status/1662994140844400640" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">shared</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the text for the newly proposed debt ceiling deal on Sunday – a culmination of negotiations between Democratic President Joe Biden and Republican House Speaker Kevin McCarthy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The bill would suspend the debt limit entirely until January 1, 2025, removing it as an issue going into the 2024 Federal election. On the flip side, it would implement a number of spending cuts including caps on non-defense spending and reductions in IRS funding.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In response to Davidson, Pierre Rochard – VP of Research at Bitcoin mining company Riot Platforms – noted that the bill was absent any mention of the administration’s previously proposed Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) tax. Davidson </span><a href="https://twitter.com/WarrenDavidson/status/1663001207651155970" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">confirmed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the proposal was gone, and that blocks on Democrat-proposed taxes were among Republicans’ negotiating victories.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The proposed tax would have made proof of work cryptocurrency miners pay a 30% tax on all energy spent during the mining process – effectively raising the cost of running a mining business in the United States. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The administration </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">justified</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the tax in guidance to Congress earlier this month as a way to make miners “pay for the full cost they impose on others” through “higher energy prices” and “greenhouse gas emissions.” </span></p>
<h2>Critics of the Excise Tax</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Critics, however, claimed that the energy tax was arbitrarily targeting a specific industry, and would drive mining out of the US – which is currently the most popular mining hub worldwide. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Among them was Senator Cynthia Lummis, who told spectators at Bitcoin Miami 2023 that the burdensome tax “isn’t going to happen.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“It’s absolutely important that the development of this technology, as well as Bitcoin mining itself, to occur in the United States,” she said at the time. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Many Bitcoin proponents contest the idea that mining is much of a harm to the environment in the first place. In September, MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor published a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-energy-concerns-are-lobbyist-propaganda-says-michael-saylor/" data-wpel-link="internal">blog post</a> arguing that miners’ carbon emissions would “hardly be noticed if it were not for the competitive guerrilla marketing activities of other crypto promoters &amp; lobbyists.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ripple co-founder Chris Larson funded a $5 million environmental campaign last year to encourage Bitcoiners to move their protocol to a less energy-intensive consensus mechanism like proof of stake. Organizations like the Environmental Working Group and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/greenpeace-blasts-bitcoin-with-artwork-depicting-environmental-damage-bitcoiners-love-it/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Greenpeace</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> have taken part. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-scraps-plans-for-bitcoin-mining-excise-tax-congressman-confirms/" rel="nofollow">US Scraps Plans for Bitcoin Mining Excise Tax, Congressman Confirms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini and Genesis File Motion for Dismissal of SEC Lawsuit Against Earn Products</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-and-genesis-file-motion-for-dismissal-of-sec-lawsuit-against-earn-products/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252855</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto exchange and lender argued that the agreement for the program is a commercial agreement and not an investment contract or security note.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Gemini and bankrupt digital asset lender Genesis Global Capital have jointly filed a motion to dismiss a lawsuit from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against the former&#8217;s Earn program.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://jfblegal.egnyte.com/dl/EgiiPyjDym" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">document</a> filed at the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York on Friday, May 26, Gemini and Genesis insisted that the SEC has no basis in law to describe the Earn product as the sale of unregistered securities, as it was a crypto asset lending service.</p>
<h2>Gemini and Genesis Ask Court to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit</h2>
<p>Recall that the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-files-complaint-against-gemini-and-genesis-for-allegedly-selling-unregistered-securities/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> a complaint against Gemini and Genesis in January for allegedly selling unregistered securities to retail investors in the U.S. through the Gemini Earn program.</p>
<p>The program, launched in December 2020, was shut down earlier this year after Genesis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-halts-withdrawals-for-its-lending-arm-following-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">halted withdrawals</a> and could no longer pay interest to Gemini’s clients due to insufficient liquid assets stemming from the crypto market’s downturn. The fate of the hundreds of thousands of Gemini investors <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">owed</a> over $900 million by Genesis remains unknown as the latter filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in January.</p>
<p>The SEC alleged that Gemini and Genesis bypassed disclosure requirements created to protect investors and violated federal securities laws.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Notwithstanding the unambiguous nature of the MDALA, and the limitations on how it could be used, the SEC seeks to turn the Earn program into something it was not: the sale of unregistered securities. While the SEC suggests that application of the federal securities laws is obvious here, the Complaint is a novel attempt to expand their scope beyond any reasonable reading of the relevant statutory language,” Gemini and Genesis said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>A Commercial Agreement, Not an Investment Contract</h2>
<p>The defendants further insisted that the Master Digital Asset Loan Agreement (MDALA) for the Gemini Earn program was not an investment contract. The agreement was never sold or offered for sale, could not be traded on any secondary market, did not involve the transfer of title of any asset, and did not require any lending or borrowing by anyone.</p>
<p>Gemini and Genesis argued that the MDALA was a commercial agreement not covered by Section 5 of the Securities Act, which requires the sale of or offer to sell a security.</p>
<p>The crypto entities told the court that allowing the SEC to proceed with the case would mean ignoring the Securities Act’s “plain meaning.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-and-genesis-file-motion-for-dismissal-of-sec-lawsuit-against-earn-products/" rel="nofollow">Gemini and Genesis File Motion for Dismissal of SEC Lawsuit Against Earn Products</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Bulls Take Charge, Targeting $0.56 Next (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-bulls-take-charge-targeting-0-56-next-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252911</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s overall outlook currently appears optimistic, with recent price movements indicating a bullish trend. Notably, the cryptocurrency has found support at both the 100-day and 200-day moving averages and has continued to rise. As a result, there is potential to target the significant resistance at the $0.55 region. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s overall outlook currently appears optimistic, with recent price movements indicating a bullish trend. Notably, the cryptocurrency has found support at both the 100-day and 200-day moving averages and has continued to rise.</p>
<p>As a result, there is potential to target the significant resistance at the $0.55 region.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By<a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>After a period of consolidation and correction, the price found support around $0.41, which coincided with the 200-day moving average. This led to an uptrend and a breakout above the 100-day moving average at $0.445. Interestingly, the price experienced a pullback to the 100-day moving average and continued its upward rally, confirming the breakout.</p>
<p>Moreover, the XRP price has recently surpassed the upper boundary of a descending flag pattern of around $0.4644. This breakout serves as a strong indication of buying pressure in this range.</p>
<p>These recent movements suggest that XRP investors could be looking to breach the critical zone at $0.56. If successful, it might embark on a long-term bullish rally, with occasional short-term correction phases.</p>
<h3><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252914" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></h3>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour timeframe, the primary barrier at the moment is a significant resistance area located around the $0.48 price zone, which aligns with the midline boundary of the ascending channel.</p>
<p>If the price continues to surge and then retraces back to the broken trendline, the breakout will be considered valid. Participants should anticipate another bullish leg toward the subsequent resistance levels in such a scenario.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252913" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-bulls-take-charge-targeting-0-56-next-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Bulls Take Charge, Targeting $0.56 Next (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Pumps 3% Daily but Is $2K Back in the Cards? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-pumps-3-daily-but-is-2k-back-in-the-cards-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252901</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum has recently flashed a bullish signal by finding support at the 100-day moving average of $1791 and experienced a spike in its price. Also, it has now encountered a crucial resistance level, and surpassing it would likely trigger another surge. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Ethereum had a period of steady price [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum has recently flashed a bullish signal by finding support at the 100-day moving average of $1791 and experienced a spike in its price. Also, it has now encountered a crucial resistance level, and surpassing it would likely trigger another surge.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Ethereum had a period of steady price action around the 100-day moving average of $1790 before finding support and proceeding upward.</p>
<p>However, during the recent consolidation correction phase since mid-April, the price formed a descending wedge pattern (marked by yellow).</p>
<p>Presently, the price has reached the upper boundary of the wedge at $1.9K due to its recent surge and is on the verge of surpassing this critical level.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price is currently confined within a narrow range, between approximately $1791 and the static resistance zone of $2K. A breakout from the wedge is likely to trigger another rally toward the $2K resistance zone.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252906" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252906" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-252906 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2905231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-daily-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252906" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Zooming in on the 4-hour chart, we can identify three crucial price regions: the static resistance at $2K, the dynamic resistance of the ascending channel&#8217;s trend-line midpoint, and the static support at $1710.</p>
<p>Based on the current price action, the price seems more likely to continue its upward trend toward the $2K resistance and attempt to break out. However, considering the current market conditions and the prevailing uncertainty among participants, it is also likely that a consolidation phase between the $2K resistance and the $1710 support regions will take place.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252905" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252905" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-252905 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2905232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252905" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p>Price fluctuations in the market result from the dynamic interplay between supply and demand forces. Demand plays a crucial role among these forces, and closely monitoring market participants&#8217; behavior is critical to assessing the existing demand.</p>
<p>One effective way to gain insights is by analyzing the Active Addresses metric. It measures the total number of unique active addresses, including both senders and receivers. During the recent consolidation phase, it has fallen into a downtrend, indicating a decrease in demand and a period of uncertainty among market participants.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the metric has recently hit its lowest point of the year, suggesting that the current level of demand is insufficient to signal the beginning of the next bull run. As a result, the market needs increased activity to kickstart a healthy bullish cycle. This could potentially be achieved if the price successfully breaks through the significant resistance region at $2K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252907" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252907" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-252907 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_active_addresses_chart_2905231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252907" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-pumps-3-daily-but-is-2k-back-in-the-cards-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Pumps 3% Daily but Is $2K Back in the Cards? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Price Analysis: This is What Needs to Happen for PEPE to Target Critical Resistance</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-price-analysis-this-is-what-needs-to-happen-for-pepe-to-target-critical-resistance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252847</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE continues to range as market participants are waiting for something to happen. Key Support levels: $0.0000013, $0.0000011  Key Resistance levels: $0.0000020 PEPE&#8217;s volatility is extremely low right now with the price unable to make any significant moves. It appears that both sellers and buyers are exhausted or absent from the market. PEPE has support [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">PEPE continues to range as market participants are waiting for something to happen.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.0000013, $0.0000011 </strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.0000020</strong></p>
<p>PEPE&#8217;s volatility is extremely low right now with the price unable to make any significant moves. It appears that both sellers and buyers are exhausted or absent from the market. PEPE has support at $0.0000013, and if broken the price could go to $0.0000011 next. The resistance is at $0.0000020, and so far, bulls failed to surpass it.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252849" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252849" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252849" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-04-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252849" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume: </strong>The volume almost disappeared from the chart. This has led to low volatility.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The daily RSI is somewhat flat but may turn bearish if bulls can&#8217;t sustain the price at the current support.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The daily MACD is bearish. However, considering the lack of conviction from sellers, the price has not reacted to this.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252848" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252848" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252848" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55" width="1834" height="850" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55-300x139.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55-1024x475.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55-768x356.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55-1536x712.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-29_14-05-55-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252848" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for PEPE is neutral.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for PEPE Price</h2>
<p>The spotlight on PEPE appears to have turned off. Interest in this meme coin has disappeared, and unless excitement returns to the overall market, it is unlikely we will see much action at this time.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-price-analysis-this-is-what-needs-to-happen-for-pepe-to-target-critical-resistance/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Price Analysis: This is What Needs to Happen for PEPE to Target Critical Resistance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memevengers (MMVG) Lists on MEXC Following Uniswap Deployment</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/memevengers-mmvg-lists-on-mexc-following-uniswap-deployment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252882</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MEXC_Listing_1685367867P7GkWDnqON.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MEXC_Listing_1685367867P7GkWDnqON.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, New York, USA, May 29th, 2023] Memevengers coin ($MMVG) has been gaining attention following a Uniswap listing on May 25th. $MMVG reached a market cap of over $20 Million and a $1 Million trading volume. The Memevengers coin $MMVG can be traded on Uniswap, where it is paired against WETH. [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, New York, USA, May 29th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Memevengers coin ($MMVG) has been gaining attention following a Uniswap listing on May 25th. $MMVG reached a market cap of over $20 Million and a $1 Million trading volume.</p>
<p>The Memevengers coin $MMVG can be traded on Uniswap, where it is paired against WETH. In addition, liquidity for the token is set to increase further when $MMVG <a href="https://twitter.com/MEXC_Global/status/1663094173434789895?s=20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">lists on MEXC at 10am UTC on May 30th</a>. The team hopes that Memevengers will improve global access to the memecoin and provide interested users with a new opportunity to be a part of the ecosystem as it begins the next leg of its journey.</p>
<h2>About Memevengers:</h2>
<p>Memevengers $MMVG(ETH) is a memecoin that represents the War of Memes. The Final War that will Change the Destiny of Memes Unfolds. Crushing Villains and Preserving Peace.</p>
<p>Memevengers are the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/memevengers-mmvg-lists-on-mexc-following-uniswap-deployment/" rel="nofollow">Memevengers (MMVG) Lists on MEXC Following Uniswap Deployment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
