<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Draft Legislation From House Republicans Drums Up Support From Crypto Advocates</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/draft-legislation-from-house-republicans-drums-up-support-from-crypto-advocates.htm</link><description>New draft legislation is drumming up support among cryptocurrency advocates who cheered its focus on defining what constitutes a security versus a commodity. &lt;br /&gt;
Republican lawmakers teamed up on Friday in the US House Financial Services Committee and the House Agriculture Committee on a discussion draft to regulate digital assets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/draft-legislation-from-house-republicans-drums-up-support-from-crypto-advocates.htm"&gt;Read More: Draft Legislation From House Republicans Drums Up Support From Crypto Advocates&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>SEC</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/draft-legislation-from-house-republicans-drums-up-support-from-crypto-advocates.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115789/311241/adobestock-230599906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="533273"/></item><item><title>More China CBDC Public Transport Options Unveiled – Digital Yuan Readies Asian Games Debut</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/more-china-cbdc-public-transport-options-unveiled-digital-yuan-readies-asian-games-debut.htm</link><description>Digital yuan payment adoption is stepping up in China ahead of the Asian Games, with venue cities rolling out a range of central bank digital currency (CBDC) transport options. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Shanghai Securities News, preparations are in advanced stages in the host city of Hangzhou, Zhejiang Province. &lt;br /&gt;
The city was slated to host the event in September last year, but the games were eventually delayed by a year due to the coronavirus pandemic....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/more-china-cbdc-public-transport-options-unveiled-digital-yuan-readies-asian-games-debut.htm"&gt;Read More: More China CBDC Public Transport Options Unveiled – Digital Yuan Readies Asian Games Debut&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/more-china-cbdc-public-transport-options-unveiled-digital-yuan-readies-asian-games-debut.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115696/278882/zhejiang.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="490095"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Association Files Amicus Brief To Support Coin Center’s Lawsuit Over Tornado Cash Sanctions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-support-coin-centers-lawsuit-over-tornado-cash-sanctions.htm</link><description>Washington DC-based Blockchain Association filed an amicus brief in support of crypto think tank Coin Center’s lawsuit against the US Treasury Department over its sanctions against Tornado Cash. &lt;br /&gt;
Treasury sanctioned the crypto mixer in August, claiming that it laundered more than $7 billion worth of virtual currency and effectively banning Americans from using it.  &lt;br /&gt;
Coin Center sued Treasury in October over that sanction and said the service has legitimate use cases. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-support-coin-centers-lawsuit-over-tornado-cash-sanctions.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Association Files Amicus Brief To Support Coin Center’s Lawsuit Over Tornado Cash Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Blockchain Association</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Coin Center</category><category>Tornado Cash</category><category>Treasury</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-support-coin-centers-lawsuit-over-tornado-cash-sanctions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115785/311240/adobestock-19789947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="433501"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Becomes One of the Best Performing Coins of the Week – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-becomes-one-of-best-performing-coins-of-week-time-buy.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC), the cryptocurrency that powers the payments-focused Litecoin blockchain, has been on a great run recently. &lt;br /&gt;
LTC was last changing hands just below $95 per token, having pumped over 3% this week despite a 1.5% fall in the broader cryptocurrency’s market capitalization. &lt;br /&gt;
That means Litecoin is one of the best-performing coins of the week and price predictions thus remains bullish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-becomes-one-of-best-performing-coins-of-week-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Becomes One of the Best Performing Coins of the Week – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-becomes-one-of-best-performing-coins-of-week-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115780/311238/ltc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="531951"/></item><item><title>Crypto Assets Should Be Classified as Securities, Says European Parliament Study</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-should-classified-as-securities-says-european-parliament-study.htm</link><description>A study commissioned by the European Parliament has proposed that all crypto assets should be treated as transferable securities by default. &lt;br /&gt;
To avoid being classified as a security, the study’s authors proposed that the intermediary behind a crypto asset can get an exemption from a national competent authority (NCA), meaning the relevant regulatory authority in an EU member state....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-should-classified-as-securities-says-european-parliament-study.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Assets Should Be Classified as Securities, Says European Parliament Study&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>EU</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-should-classified-as-securities-says-european-parliament-study.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115758/311205/eu-parliament.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="160377"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Hinman Documents Set to be Released – Can XRP 100x After Lawsuit Ends?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-hinman-documents-set-released-can-xrp-100x-after-lawsuit-ends.htm</link><description>XRP is back above $0.50 per token once again on Friday, as the world’s sixth-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization looks to reignite momentum following a strong bullish run in the past three weeks. &lt;br /&gt;
XRP is the native cryptocurrency of the XRP Ledger, a decentralized layer-1 blockchain protocol launched by US fintech company Ripple back in June 2012 to facilitate their revolutionary cross-border payment and liquidity business....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-hinman-documents-set-released-can-xrp-100x-after-lawsuit-ends.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Hinman Documents Set to be Released – Can XRP 100x After Lawsuit Ends?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>XRP Ledger</category><category>Ripple</category><category>SEC</category><category>Hinman</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-hinman-documents-set-released-can-xrp-100x-after-lawsuit-ends.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115775/311224/xrp-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="592360"/></item><item><title>House Republican Leaders Release Discussion Draft To Draw Clear Lines on Digital Asset Definitions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-republican-leaders-release-discussion-draft-draw-clear-lines-digital-asset-definitions.htm</link><description>Republican lawmakers teamed up in the US House Financial Services Committee and the House Agriculture Committee on a discussion draft to regulate digital assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The legislation, released on Friday, seeks clarity on when a digital asset would be considered a security and thereby regulated by the Securities and Exchange Commission, while creating a process on how digital assets are treated and how intermediaries can register with the SEC or Commodity Futures Trading Commission....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/house-republican-leaders-release-discussion-draft-draw-clear-lines-digital-asset-definitions.htm"&gt;Read More: House Republican Leaders Release Discussion Draft To Draw Clear Lines on Digital Asset Definitions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-republican-leaders-release-discussion-draft-draw-clear-lines-digital-asset-definitions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115771/311217/screen-shot-2023-06-02-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="598662"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Justin Sun Says Huobi's ID Token Could Grant Citizenship in Dominica – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-says-huobis-id-token-could-grant-citizenship-dominica-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Billionaire Tron (TRX) founder Justin Sun has predicted that tokenized know-your-customer (KYC) checks will become increasingly prevalent as regulations tighten, while offering his own identity token that grants holders "citizenship" in Dominica’s metaverse....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-says-huobis-id-token-could-grant-citizenship-dominica-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Justin Sun Says Huobi's ID Token Could Grant Citizenship in Dominica – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Tron</category><category>Justin Sun</category><category>Huobi</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-says-huobis-id-token-could-grant-citizenship-dominica-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115742/311161/justin-sun.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="36286"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Mike Novogratz Says Crypto Market Rally is Stalling as Bitcoin Posts First Monthly Loss – Here's What's Happening</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mike-novogratz-says-crypto-market-rally-stalling-as-bitcoin-posts-first-monthly-loss-heres-whats-happening.htm</link><description>Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz believes the crypto market lacks momentum to move higher as Bitcoin posts its first monthly loss of the year. &lt;br /&gt;
The flagship cryptocurrency lost 6% of its value in May, while Ethereum fell by 1%. Both remain well over 50% year to date, however. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mike-novogratz-says-crypto-market-rally-stalling-as-bitcoin-posts-first-monthly-loss-heres-whats-happening.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Mike Novogratz Says Crypto Market Rally is Stalling as Bitcoin Posts First Monthly Loss – Here's What's Happening&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Mike Novogratz</category><category>Galaxy Digital</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mike-novogratz-says-crypto-market-rally-stalling-as-bitcoin-posts-first-monthly-loss-heres-whats-happening.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115752/311192/screenshot-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="31060"/></item><item><title>TikTok Influencer Uses Bitcoin to Launder Fraudulent COVID Relief Funds - Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tiktok-influencer-uses-bitcoin-to-launder-fraudulent-covid-relief-funds-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Denish Sahadevan, a 31-year-old social media influencer, has pleaded guilty to a series of criminal charges related to money laundering using cryptocurrency.  &lt;br /&gt;
The US prosecutors have alleged that Sahadevan fraudulently obtained more than $1.2 million in government relief loans. &lt;br /&gt;
On May 31, the US Department of Justice (DoJ) issued a press release stating that Denish Sahadevan, a TikTok influencer, has admitted to committing several criminal offenses. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tiktok-influencer-uses-bitcoin-to-launder-fraudulent-covid-relief-funds-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: TikTok Influencer Uses Bitcoin to Launder Fraudulent COVID Relief Funds - Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tiktok-influencer-uses-bitcoin-to-launder-fraudulent-covid-relief-funds-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115760/311208/tiktok-influencer-uses-bi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="383568"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Derivatives Exchange to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures for Institutions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-derivatives-exchange-launch-bitcoin-ether-futures-for-institutions.htm</link><description>Coinbase Derivatives Exchange, a CFTC-regulated derivatives trading platform, is set to launch institutional Bitcoin and Ether futures contract trading.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a June 1 announcement, this offering will commence on June 5, enabling institutional investors to manage risk and target attractive returns with lower fees. &lt;br /&gt;
The demand for advanced derivatives increased after Coinbase Derivatives Exchange launched its nano Bitcoin (BIT) and nano Ether (ET) contracts. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-derivatives-exchange-launch-bitcoin-ether-futures-for-institutions.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Derivatives Exchange to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures for Institutions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-derivatives-exchange-launch-bitcoin-ether-futures-for-institutions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115759/311206/ethereum-g94680e2a8-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="200975"/></item><item><title>Animoca Brands' Chairman Attributes Delayed 2020 Accounts to Recent Turbulence</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/animoca-brands-chairman-attributes-delayed-2020-accounts-recent-turbulence.htm</link><description>A leading Hong Kong-based blockchain gaming and Web3 investor, Animoca Brands, has delayed its financial report since 2020. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm received an extension until the end of Q1 2023 to publish its 2020 audited accounts but has yet to do so. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent report, the company’s chairman, Yat Siu, blamed the 2021 and 2022 market turbulence for this delay....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/animoca-brands-chairman-attributes-delayed-2020-accounts-recent-turbulence.htm"&gt;Read More: Animoca Brands' Chairman Attributes Delayed 2020 Accounts to Recent Turbulence&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/animoca-brands-chairman-attributes-delayed-2020-accounts-recent-turbulence.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115756/311203/game-console-g3e12bb2c6-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="131326"/></item><item><title>yPredict Raises $2 Million for Making AI Crypto Trading Easy – 100x Potential in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-raises-2-million-for-making-ai-crypto-trading-easy-100x-potential-2023.htm</link><description>In the ever-expanding arena of crypto markets, the rules of the game have evolved beyond recognition - no longer does longevity in the market guarantee dominance or gains. &lt;br /&gt;
Today, the winners are those who ride the crest of innovation, adeptly navigating the shifting tides of a rapidly changing market. &lt;br /&gt;
At the forefront of this digital renaissance is yPredict.ai, an AI-driven crypto trading platform, trailblazing the industry with their recent milestone in fundraising....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-raises-2-million-for-making-ai-crypto-trading-easy-100x-potential-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: yPredict Raises $2 Million for Making AI Crypto Trading Easy – 100x Potential in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-raises-2-million-for-making-ai-crypto-trading-easy-100x-potential-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115748/311198/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="980178"/></item><item><title>Will Worldcoin Be the Next Cryptocurrency to Explode As AI Crypto Coins yPredict, Launchpad, AiDoge Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/will-worldcoin-next-cryptocurrency-explode-as-ai-crypto-coins-ypredict-launchpad-aidoge-explode.htm</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) has taken a giant leap forward in the last six months. &lt;br /&gt;
OpenAI stunned the world with the release of its generative AI chatbot ChatGPT last November. &lt;br /&gt;
ChatGPT quickly became the fastest platform in the world to reach 100 million users, with users shocked at the AI-powered bot’s ability to process information, problem-solve and generate high-quality human-like responses to queries....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/will-worldcoin-next-cryptocurrency-explode-as-ai-crypto-coins-ypredict-launchpad-aidoge-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Will Worldcoin Be the Next Cryptocurrency to Explode As AI Crypto Coins yPredict, Launchpad, AiDoge Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>WLD</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>AI</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/will-worldcoin-next-cryptocurrency-explode-as-ai-crypto-coins-ypredict-launchpad-aidoge-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115750/311210/world.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1668266"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Non Farm Payroll Data is Announced – Bull Market Starting Soon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-non-farm-payroll-data-announced-bull-market-starting-soon.htm</link><description>The recent release of the Non-Farm Payroll data has caused a notable impact on the price of Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
With the data revealing positive job growth in the United States, market sentiment has favored a bullish outlook for the US dollar.  &lt;br /&gt;
Therefore, Bitcoin experienced a downward movement in response to the positive report.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors are closely analyzing this reaction and assessing its implications for the future trajectory of Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-non-farm-payroll-data-announced-bull-market-starting-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Non Farm Payroll Data is Announced – Bull Market Starting Soon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-non-farm-payroll-data-announced-bull-market-starting-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115736/311174/2-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481504"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Elon Musk Accused of DOGE-Related Insider Trading, Xapo Integrates with the Single Euro Payments Area Network, US CFTC Mulls Rules Change to Include Crypto Risk</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-elon-musk-accused-of-doge-related-insider-trading-xapo-integrates-with-the-single-euro-payments-area-network-us-cftc-mulls-rules-change-to-include-crypto-risk.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-elon-musk-accused-of-doge-related-insider-trading-xapo-integrates-with-the-single-euro-payments-area-network-us-cftc-mulls-rules-change-to-include-crypto-risk.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Elon Musk Accused of DOGE-Related Insider Trading, Xapo Integrates with the Single Euro Payments Area Network, US CFTC Mulls Rules Change to Include Crypto Risk&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Legal</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>Barry Silbert. Court</category><category>Banking</category><category>Silvergate</category><category>USA</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><category>Xapo</category><category>Europe</category><category>EU</category><category>UK</category><category>Norway</category><category>Liechtenstein</category><category>Iceland</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Monaco</category><category>Regulation</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Nigeria</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Twitter</category><category>OpenAI</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>chatGPT</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-elon-musk-accused-of-doge-related-insider-trading-xapo-integrates-with-the-single-euro-payments-area-network-us-cftc-mulls-rules-change-to-include-crypto-risk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115705/309132/em-media-library-original.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="65134"/></item><item><title>While Hong Kong Inu Rallies 50,000%, Experts Believe Wall Street Memes is the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/while-hong-kong-inu-rallies-50000-experts-believe-wall-street-memes-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</link><description>Momentum in crypto markets shows no sign of slowing down, as Hong Kong Inu ($HONG) explodes +50,000% in earth-shattering pump dawning a return to February's Chinese narrative. &lt;br /&gt;
As many traders will remember, February 2023 saw a surge of interest and traction for Chinese-linked crypto projects following the seismic news that Beijing had greenlighted Hong Kong's crypto ambitions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/while-hong-kong-inu-rallies-50000-experts-believe-wall-street-memes-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: While Hong Kong Inu Rallies 50,000%, Experts Believe Wall Street Memes is the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/while-hong-kong-inu-rallies-50000-experts-believe-wall-street-memes-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115738/311176/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="986643"/></item><item><title>US Regulator Sets It Sights on Crypto Risks in Potential Risk Management Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-sets-it-sights-crypto-risks-potential-risk-management-rules.htm</link><description>The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission is taking a closer look at its rules governing risk management, with an eye towards digital assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The agency published an advanced notice of proposed rulemaking on Thursday, asking for public comment on risk management requirements for swap dealers and futures commission merchants.  &lt;br /&gt;
CFTC Commissioner Christy Goldsmith Romero said one of those risks could be crypto, in a statement on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-sets-it-sights-crypto-risks-potential-risk-management-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: US Regulator Sets It Sights on Crypto Risks in Potential Risk Management Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Risks</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-sets-it-sights-crypto-risks-potential-risk-management-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115745/311171/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="426841"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 2 June – The Sandbox, Injective, The Graph</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-june-sandbox-injective-graph.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency markets are choppy in wake of a mixed US labor market report that saw a beat on the headline non-farm payrolls number (i.e. the number of jobs added in May), but also a larger than expected rise in the unemployment rate and a slowdown in the MoM pace of average hourly earnings growth. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin was last changing hands close to but just below $27,000, with its recent technical downtrend seemingly still intact, while Ethereum was last trading in the upper-$1,800s....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-june-sandbox-injective-graph.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 2 June – The Sandbox, Injective, The Graph&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>ETH</category><category>Ether</category><category>The Graph</category><category>GRT</category><category>Injective</category><category>INJ</category><category>The Sandbox</category><category>SAND</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-june-sandbox-injective-graph.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115737/311152/best-crypto-2-june.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="330071"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Cardano? ADA Price Spikes Up 2% in 7 Days While Eco Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Surges Past $4.6 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-cardano-ada-price-spikes-up-2-7-days-while-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-surges-past-46-million.htm</link><description>Crypto markets appear to be witnessing growing interest in eco-friendly cryptocurrencies this week, as analysts speculate about an emerging 'Green Crypto' breakout narrative. &lt;br /&gt;
Leading the pack is 7th ranked cryptocurrency Cardano (ADA) - posited as the first carbon neutral blockchain following the launch of Cardano Forest (a joint venture with VeriTrees)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-cardano-ada-price-spikes-up-2-7-days-while-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-surges-past-46-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Cardano? ADA Price Spikes Up 2% in 7 Days While Eco Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Surges Past $4.6 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-cardano-ada-price-spikes-up-2-7-days-while-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-surges-past-46-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115729/311144/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1411895"/></item></channel></rss>
