<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 22:27:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Razzlekhan Pleads Guilty, Husband Admits That He Hacked Bitfinex</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/razzlekhan-pleads-guilty-husband-admits-that-he-hacked-bitfinex/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264277</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/bitcoin_law-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/bitcoin_law-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitfinex’s hackers have pled guilty in court, and detailed some of the measures they took to launder stolen funds.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Heather Rhiannon Morgan (aka “Razzlekhan”, 33) pled guilty to a money laundering conspiracy in connection with the 2016 Bitfinex hack on Thursday, which saw more than 119,756 Bitcoin (BTC) robbed from customers.</p>
<p>This came moments after her husband, Ilya “Dutch” Lichtenstein (35), pleaded guilty to being the man behind the hack itself.</p>
<h2>Bitfinex Hacker Confirmed</h2>
<p>In Washington, D.C., federal court, Lichtenstein confessed to both stealing and laundering the funds, officially clearing the air on a years-long mystery around one of the largest thefts in Bitcoin history. At the time of the hack, the exchange’s stolen BTC was worth roughly $71 million but is worth $3.4 billion today.</p>
<p>“Lichtenstein used a number of advanced hacking tools and techniques to gain access to Bitfinex’s network,” wrote the Department of Justice in a <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/bitfinex-hacker-and-wife-plead-guilty-money-laundering-conspiracy-involving-billions" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">press release</a> on Thursday, citing court documents.</p>
<p>He then “enlisted” his wife, Morgan, for support in laundering the funds and covering his tracks, using “sophisticated methods” including fictitious identities, darknet markets, chain hopping, and cryptocurrency mixing services. Some popular crypto mixers (ex. Blender, Tornado Cash) have already been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-treasury-imposes-sanctions-on-north-korean-crypto-mixer/" data-wpel-link="internal">sanctioned</a> by the U.S. Treasury Department.</p>
<p>Liechtenstein confessed during his plea hearing that some of the stolen funds were converted into gold coins that were later buried by Morgan. Law enforcement officials now know the location at which they’re buried.</p>
<p>He also converted some of his crypto into cash through middlemen, during his past travels to Ukraine and Russia. He picked up that cash physically at addresses in both nations, then deposited the money into U.S. accounts to be retrieved in New York City.</p>
<h2>The Sentence</h2>
<p>For their crimes, Lichtenstein faces a maximum of 20 years in prison, while Morgan faces a maximum sentence of 5 years.</p>
<p>The defendants were arrested in February 2022, and most of their stolen Bitcoin – 95,000 BTC – was seized by the government. The reclaimed assets were worth $3.6 billion at the time, making it the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/justice-department-recovers-bitfinex-hack-funds-in-largest-ever-financial-seizure/" data-wpel-link="internal">largest financial seizure in history</a>.</p>
<p>In a statement, Bitfinex acknowledged having worked with the DOJ to recover the stolen Bitcoin and make customers whole.</p>
<blockquote><p>“After seven years, those efforts have come to fruition,” the company said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/razzlekhan-pleads-guilty-husband-admits-that-he-hacked-bitfinex/" rel="nofollow">Razzlekhan Pleads Guilty, Husband Admits That He Hacked Bitfinex</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australia&#8217;s Financial Regulator Sues eToro: Details</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/australias-financial-regulator-sues-etoro-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eToro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264112</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Australia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Australia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The ASIC believes that almost 20,000 eToro users lost money between October 2021 and June 2023 due to dealing with CFDs. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) filed a lawsuit against the trading platform eToro, alleging that its contract for difference (CFD) product could harm investors. That type of monetary tool is a leveraged derivative contract that enables customers to speculate on the prices of equities, commodities, stock market indices, and digital assets. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The platform was among the first in its field to hop on the cryptocurrency bandwagon, allowing trading services with Bitcoin (BTC) in 2013 via CFDs. It later added support to Ethereum (ETH), Cardano (ADA), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Litecoin (LTC), and others.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ASIC&#8217;s Concerns</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Australian watchdog </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://asic.gov.au/about-asic/news-centre/find-a-media-release/2023-releases/23-204mr-asic-sues-etoro-in-its-first-design-and-distribution-action-to-protect-consumers-from-high-risk-cfd-products/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that it had commenced proceedings in the Federal Court against eToro, arguing its CFD product might not have been tested properly before being introduced to users:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The case focuses on the appropriateness of eToro&#8217;s target market and the screening test used by eToro to assess whether a retail client fell within the target market for the CFD product.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ASIC went further, claiming that the financial product is highly dangerous and volatile, adding that the initial trial was &#8220;wholly inadequate to assess whether a retail client was likely to be within the target market.&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;ASIC considers that eToro&#8217;s conduct is likely to have resulted in a significant number of retail clients being exposed to the CFD product that was unlikely to be consistent with their investment objectives, financial situation, and needs, resulting in a significant risk of consumer harm,&#8221; the regulator assumed.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the ASIC&#8217;s estimations, approximately 20,000 eToro customers lost money between October 5, 2021, and June 14, 2023, due to trading CFDs. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Our message to the industry is that CFD target markets should be narrowly defined given the significant risk that retail clients may lose all of their deposited funds. CFD issuers must comply with the design and distribution regime and cannot simply reverse engineer their target markets to fit existing client bases,&#8221; </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the agency&#8217;s Deputy Chair Sarah Court stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contracts for differences (CFDs) let investors speculate on short-term market movements on different stocks and assets, including cryptocurrencies. They are illegal in some countries, including the United States of America and Hong Kong.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">eToro&#8217;s Reaction to SEC&#8217;s Lawsuits</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm had to make some amendments regarding its crypto policy shortly after the US SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, accusing the exchanges of providing trading services with a number of unregistered securities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As a result, eToro </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/etoro-imposes-restrictions-on-4-crypto-assets-labelled-as-securities-in-sec-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">banned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> US customers from purchasing ALGO, MANA, DASH, and MATIC (all of which were targeted by the Commission). However, the company asserted that it remains a supporter of the cryptocurrency industry, vowing to continue offering its clients &#8220;access to a diversified range of asset classes, which includes stocks, ETFs, and options.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/australias-financial-regulator-sues-etoro-details/" rel="nofollow">Australia&#8217;s Financial Regulator Sues eToro: Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Seeks to Exclude Dubai Unit From U.S. Bankruptcy Proceedings</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-seeks-to-exclude-dubai-unit-from-u-s-bankruptcy-proceedings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 22:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264106</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ftx_trial_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ftx_trial_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FTX Dubai has a solvent balance sheet and no likelihood of resuming its operations.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX has filed a motion to remove its Dubai unit from the ongoing bankruptcy proceedings in the United States.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MjQ1NDM0OQ==&amp;id2=-1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">document</a> submitted to the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware, FTX Dubai did not conduct any business activities in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) before the global entity filed for bankruptcy and is unlikely to resume its operations.</p>
<h2>Dismissing FTX Dubai From Bankruptcy Proceedings</h2>
<p>FTX Europe <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-ftx-to-set-up-regional-hq-in-dubai-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">established</a> the Dubai crypto exchange in February 2022. Five months later, the unit secured a virtual asset service provider license from Dubai&#8217;s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA).</p>
<p>Following VARA&#8217;s approval, FTX Dubai failed to offer any crypto-related services in the UAE until the agency suspended the license in November 2022, which expired in July 2023.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Given the absence of any historical business or resources to commence any business in the future, FTX Dubai has no reasonable likelihood of rehabilitating its operations. Additionally, FTX Dubai is balance sheet solvent,&#8221; FTX said.</p></blockquote>
<p>As a result, FTX believes the Dubai arm should be excluded from its bankruptcy proceedings and made to face a solvent voluntary procedure instead. The process would allow the distribution of a positive cash balance after paying outstanding liabilities and liquidating assets as per UAE laws.</p>
<h2>Creditors to Pursue Their Claims</h2>
<p>At the time of the filing, FTX Dubai held approximately $4.5 million in its accounts. VARA has restricted $4 million out of the funds as security for the license with the intention to release the cash when the entity commences its liquidation process.</p>
<p>FTX noted that dismissing the Dubai unit from the bankruptcy proceedings would not affect creditors&#8217; claims against the exchange as they could pursue such claims during the voluntary liquidation proceedings under UAE laws.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In order to protect the rights and claims of the Debtors in the context of the liquidation of FTX Dubai, FTX Dubai is expected to enter into an agreement with the appointed liquidator to implement basic administrative procedures to harmonize and coordinate the activities of the liquidator of FTX Dubai and promote the orderly and efficient administration of the liquidation,&#8221; the exchange added.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, FTX is looking to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-reboot-proposal-presented-as-part-of-reorganization-efforts-ftt-jumped-10-overnight/" data-wpel-link="internal">restart</a> its operations with plans to cater to only offshore customers and not investors in the U.S.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-seeks-to-exclude-dubai-unit-from-u-s-bankruptcy-proceedings/" rel="nofollow">FTX Seeks to Exclude Dubai Unit From U.S. Bankruptcy Proceedings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bear Market Things: Robinhood&#8217;s Crypto Revenue Plunged by Almost 20% in Q2</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bear-market-things-robinhoods-crypto-revenue-plunged-by-almost-20-in-q2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264055</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Robinhood_Crypto.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Robinhood_Crypto.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto revenue accounted for 16% of Robinhood's total transaction-based revenue in Q2, 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American investment platform Robinhood released its financial results for the second quarter, revealing that crypto trading revenue plunged by 18% compared to the Q1 figures.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One reason behind the downtrend could be the company&#8217;s decision to delist certain digital assets, deemed securities by the US SEC, such as Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Latest Numbers</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite reporting solid overall profits in Q2, Robinhood </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://s28.q4cdn.com/948876185/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/Q2-2023-Robinhood-Exhibit-99-1-vF.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that crypto trading revenue fell to $31 million. In comparison, that figure was $38 million in the first quarter of the year (which was still a slight decline from the sum registered in Q4, 2022).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The platform currently supports 15 digital currencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Dogecoin (DOGE), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), Shiba Inu (SHIB), and others. Its range was even wider two months ago when Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA) were also available for trading. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nonetheless, the brokerage firm </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-delists-solana-sol-cardano-ada-polygon-matic-after-secs-claims/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">delisted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> those at the end of June following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase, in which the agency named the aforementioned digital assets unregistered securities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contrary to the declining numbers, Robinhood&#8217;s CEO Vlad Tenev </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/08/33538687/robinhood-ceo-vlad-tenev-confirms-continued-investment-in-crypto-despite-q2-revenue-drop-f" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">asserted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the company will remain an active investor in the cryptocurrency sector and will continue to provide digital asset services to customers:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Our goal is to be the safest, most trusted place for customers to hold, trade, and transact with their crypto. We see our recent launches of Robinhood Wallet and Robinhood Connect resonating with customers, and we look forward to continuing to invest in crypto.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_102521" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-102521" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-102521" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev.jpg" alt="VladTenev" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/VladTenev-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-102521" class="wp-caption-text">Vlad Tenev, Source: TechCrunch</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some of the Latest Setbacks</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The crypto unit of the company has been struggling in the past year. It was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-crypto-fined-30-million-by-new-york-regulator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">slapped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with a $30 million fine by the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) in August 2022 for allegedly violating anti-money laundering and cybersecurity regulations. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite witnessing rising crypto trading volumes at the start of 2023, those figures stalled in the following months, and Robinhood </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-cuts-staff-again-as-trading-volume-and-engagement-dwindle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">dismissed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> some of its employees in June. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We&#8217;re ensuring operational excellence in how we work together on an ongoing basis. In some cases, this may mean teams make changes based on volume, workload,&#8221; the firm explained at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prior to that, Robinhood&#8217;s chief legal officer Dan Gallagher </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-actively-reviews-crypto-offering-after-sec-widens-industry-crackdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the entity weighed on its crypto offerings following the SEC&#8217;s crackdown on the sector. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bear-market-things-robinhoods-crypto-revenue-plunged-by-almost-20-in-q2/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Bear Market Things: Robinhood&#8217;s Crypto Revenue Plunged by Almost 20% in Q2</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp Offers Permanent APY on XRP Lending: Details</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitstamp-offers-permanent-apy-on-xrp-lending-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitstamp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264265</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bitstamp_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bitstamp_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lenders can now earn a “permanent” 2% yield on their XRP, though some in the community are not impressed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto trading platform Bitstamp has introduced an XRP lending service offering a “permanent” 2% yield, shortly after relisting the asset for trading last month.</p>
<p>This puts XRP on an already sizable list of coins viable for 2% APY on Bitstamp, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), USD Coin (USDC), and Tether USD (USDT).</p>
<h2>Permanent Yield On XRP?</h2>
<p>As explained by Bitstamp in a <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/earn-more-by-lending-xrp-a-permanent-2-00-apy-increase-unlocked/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> on Thursday, the company partners with Tesseract for its lending service, which “only lends to reputable institutions and undertakes rigorous risk and credit assessments for all borrowers.”</p>
<p>Tesseract breaks down counterparties into four tiers, with Tier 1 including “large top-tier market makers from traditional finance,” and Tier 4 including “smaller institutional borrowers.”</p>
<p>Per Bitstamp&#8217;s <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/2023-06-bts-lending-report.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 2023 lending report</a>, most of its lending portfolio is deployed to Tier 2 firms – regarded as “large top-tier crypto-native<br />
market makers.”</p>
<p>“The loan portfolio is demonstrating strong performance, with all borrowers making timely repayments of both interest and principal as scheduled,” wrote Bitstamp in the report.</p>
<p>At the time, XRP was the lowest-yielding asset available at 1.5% APY. Since then, Ripple has secured a legal victory over the SEC in assuring that XRP is not a security, causing demand for the asset to soar. Still, the new new 2% yield remains well below its USDT and USDC yield rate of 4.4%.</p>
<p>Respondents to Bitstamp on X were quick to point this out, finding the firm’s lending rate to be quite underwhelming. “Not going to lie, I was expecting a little bit more,” <a href="https://twitter.com/CommunityFlare/status/1687107462015721472" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> software developer Flare Community.</p>
<p>https://twitter.com/XrpGoat/status/1687109278824624129</p>
<h2>The Risks of Lending</h2>
<p>Crypto lending spiked in popularity in 2021 as a way for retail crypto holders to earn on their existing cryptocurrency, much like fiat currency in a traditional bank account. Such services tend to offer much higher savings rates than traditional finance firms, even in low-interest rate environments.</p>
<p>However, multiple major crypto lending firms have gone bankrupt since last June as crypto market prices cratered, and lenders struggled to deal with overwhelming withdrawal demand from customers. These included <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-reaches-25-million-settlement-with-series-b-holders-for-gk8-sale-proceeds-allocation/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius</a>, Voyager, BlockFi, and Genesis, alongside hedge funds like Three Arrows Capital and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/caroline-ellison-felt-unsuited-to-run-alameda-amid-sbf-relationship-drama/" data-wpel-link="internal">Alameda Research</a>.</p>
<p>Regulators across the world have repeatedly warned of the risks associated with crypto lending products, arguing that their yields are unsustainable. Due to regulatory pressure, lending on Bitstamp is unavailable to residents in the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, and Japan.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitstamp-offers-permanent-apy-on-xrp-lending-details/" rel="nofollow">Bitstamp Offers Permanent APY on XRP Lending: Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tel Aviv Stock Exchange Partners With Fireblocks to Provide Crypto Opportunities</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-partners-with-fireblocks-to-provide-crypto-opportunities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Israel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264146</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/israeli_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/israeli_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As a result of the collaboration, the stock exchange will be able to offer "institutional-grade digital asset solutions for regulated entities."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Tel Aviv Stock Exchange (TASE) inked a deal with the crypto custodian Fireblocks to offer &#8220;a comprehensive range of innovative and secure digital asset products and services.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Israel&#8217;s only public stock exchange labeled the partnership as &#8220;crucial in the new era of innovation&#8221; since it could boost the future advancement of the cryptocurrency sector across the globe. </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The TASE </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.tase.co.il/en/content/news-lobby/20230802_pr" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the collaboration with Fireblocks builds upon &#8220;the resounding success&#8221; of Project Eden: an initiative supported by the Israeli Ministry of Finance, which saw the issuance of a government digital bond on a dedicated blockchain platform. </span></li>
<li>The stock exchange has now decided to dive even deeper into the world of crypto by offering various digital asset services and products to local consumers.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;TASE will be able to provide institutional-grade digital asset solutions for regulated entities, leveraging the most advanced technology, experience, and work processes from traditional markets, while ensuring necessary protection,&#8221; the statement reads.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity&#8217;s partner in the move is the popular blockchain security service provider Fireblocks. Orly Grinfeld &#8211; EVP Head of Clearing at TASE &#8211; believes the cooperation represents a &#8220;monumental leap forward in the global digital assets landscape.&#8221;</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are unwavering in our pursuit of revolutionizing the industry and the local capital market, and this collaboration epitomizes our dedication to delivering secure, regulated, and innovative digital asset solutions,&#8221; she added.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The stock exchange went further, claiming the partnership could &#8220;unlock the full potential of digital assets within a secure, transparent, and regulated ecosystem&#8221; by combining the TASE&#8217;s market presence and Fireblocks&#8217; &#8220;state-of-the-art technology.&#8221;</span></li>
<li>The entity has previously <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-to-regulate-crypto-trading-after-turbulent-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">displayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> ambitions to allow customers of its non-banking members, such as brokerage firms, insurance organizations, exchanges, and venture capitalists, to trade cryptocurrencies. </span></li>
<li>The TASE reminded about the catastrophic events in 2022 which undermined the entire digital asset sector. As such, its proposal was focused on enhanced investor protection.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tel-aviv-stock-exchange-partners-with-fireblocks-to-provide-crypto-opportunities/" rel="nofollow">Tel Aviv Stock Exchange Partners With Fireblocks to Provide Crypto Opportunities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wintermute Loads Arkham (ARKM) Tokens But Price Fails to React</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/wintermute-loads-arkham-arkm-tokens-but-price-fails-to-react/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264219</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkham_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkham_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Arkham Intelligence, who recently launched a “Doxx-To-Earn” platform, has a new big investor.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arkham Intelligence, a leading blockchain-centric cybersecurity firm, recently launched “the world’s first on-chain intelligence exchange,” a platform where users can post bounties for whoever can uncover information related to the ownership of on-chain assets.</p>
<p>The platform – which has generated quite some <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arkham-may-have-inadvertently-doxxed-many-of-its-users/" data-wpel-link="internal">controversy</a> already, partly due to inadvertently doxing its own early adopters – was launched together with ARKM, a proprietary token meant to facilitate the exchange of information on the platform.</p>
<p>Now, the token has a new major holder – and it is none other than Wintermute.</p>
<h2>Reasons For Investment Unknown</h2>
<p>Although Wintermute has not yet released a statement regarding their <a href="https://etherscan.io/tokentxns?a=0xdbf5e9c5206d0db70a90108bf936da60221dc080" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">purchase</a> of $3.7 million worth of ARKM, an educated guess can be made, aside from the simplest explanation of wanting to get in on the ground floor.</p>
<p>Last year, Wintermute dealt with a cyberattack that left them about $160 million short. Certain analysts <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/160m-wintermute-security-exploit-could-have-been-an-insider-job-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">claimed</a> that the attack was an inside job. Since then, no further update was provided on the situation – as far as the public is concerned, the identity and motives of the hacker are still unknown.</p>
<p>At the time, Arkham offered an olive branch to the attacker, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-09-20/wintermute-hacked-for-about-160-million-in-its-defi-operations" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcing</a> that if 90% of the stolen funds were returned, it would be treated as a white-hat exploit. Since this would leave the attacker with about $16 million to spare, it’s quite possible that at least some of the $3.7 million worth of ARKM tokens will soon be offered up as a reward for whoever uncovers the hackers’ identity.</p>
<h2>Leading Investor</h2>
<p>Today’s purchase, which marked an increase of over 700% in Wintermute’s ARKM holdings, has made the company the 10<sup>th</sup> largest holder of ARKM tokens, giving them quite a say in the future of the platform.</p>
<p>Regardless of the motives for the purchase, the <a href="https://pro.nansen.ai/wallet-profiler-for-token?address=0xdbf5e9c5206d0db70a90108bf936da60221dc080&amp;token_address=0x6e2a43be0b1d33b726f0ca3b8de60b3482b8b050" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">transactions</a> count as a strong vote of confidence in the platform, regardless of the potentially controversial nature of a platform whose main purpose goes against one of the most common values of crypto enthusiasts. The nature of the platform has already raised concerns from fans of the project that some uses of the platform – such as uncovering the identities of whales – could be immoral, if not downright dangerous.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/arkham" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to CoinGecko, the price of the token is currently hovering around the $0.45 mark and is on a downward trend ever since a post-launch spike that sent the value of the token to nearly $0.80.</p>
<figure id="attachment_264223" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-264223" style="width: 856px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkm_chart_0308231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-264223" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkm_chart_0308231.jpg" alt="arkm_chart_0308231" width="856" height="722" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkm_chart_0308231.jpg 856w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkm_chart_0308231-300x253.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkm_chart_0308231-768x648.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/arkm_chart_0308231-50x42.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 856px) 100vw, 856px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-264223" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wintermute-loads-arkham-arkm-tokens-but-price-fails-to-react/" rel="nofollow">Wintermute Loads Arkham (ARKM) Tokens But Price Fails to React</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Senator Shorts the US Economy After Calling it Resilient</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-shorts-the-us-economy-after-calling-it-resilient/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264174</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/tom-carper.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/tom-carper.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Delaware Senator has made several bearish bets on the US economy. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Records show one of United States President Joe Biden&#8217;s Senate closest allies placed a substantial financial wager against the country&#8217;s economy last month.</p>
<p>The latest development comes amidst mounting regulatory pressures on the cryptocurrency industry by the US regulatory watchdogs that have argued that the asset class poses a serious threat to the economy.</p>
<h2>Shorting the US Economy</h2>
<p>According to reports, Senator Thomas Carpel, a member of the Senate Finance Committee, revealed this week that his wife purchased up to $95,000 in shares of Ranger Equity Bear ETF and ProShares Short QQQ on July 13.These funds short stocks as a precautionary measure against economic downturns.</p>
<p>Notably, this isn&#8217;t the only time the Carpers made a comparable bearish bet on the economy. Reports suggest that they made a similar wager last year by acquiring up to $110,000 in Ranger Equity Bear ETC.</p>
<p>The bets stand in stark contrast to Carper&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/SenatorCarper/status/1654502085612691459" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">comments</a> on May 25th when he thanked the POTUS for a &#8220;resilient&#8221; economy that is &#8220;growing stronger every day.&#8221; Last year, the Senator even <a href="https://twitter.com/SenatorCarper/status/1578458399255076864" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">lauded</a> Biden&#8217;s leadership for a &#8220;huge&#8221; increase in jobs in the US.</p>
<p>A sitting Congressman <a href="https://twitter.com/unusual_whales/status/1686783179485491200" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">shorting</a> the US economy did not sit well with many in the digital asset industry that have been at the receiving end of a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/president-biden-refuses-debt-deal-friendly-to-crypto-traders/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">hostile</a> regulatory climate over several years.</p>
<p>Several crypto players took a jibe at the bets, especially since Carper had called Biden a &#8220;dear friend&#8221; earlier this year in a <a href="https://twitter.com/SenatorCarper/status/1661091040244187155" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweet</a> that&#8217;s still pinned to his Twitter profile.</p>
<p>The Biden administration, on the other hand, has expressed concern over the turmoil in the cryptocurrency markets and the subsequent impact on average Americans&#8217; financial health several times.</p>
<p>Carper’s office has previously downplayed the former military officer&#8217;s stock transactions, claiming that the family’s financial adviser &#8220;independently&#8221; conducts transactions.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, experts highlight that monitoring lawmakers&#8217; investments for potential conflicts of interest is challenging because Capitol Hill rules have not kept pace with the significant changes in the investment landscape over the past five decades.</p>
<p>While employees of the White House and its departments face stricter regulations concerning funds targeting specific sectors or countries, members of Congress have more leeway to invest in non-diversified funds as long as they are publicly traded or accessible.</p>
<h2>Reform?</h2>
<p>The Stop Trading on Congressional Knowledge (Stock) Act was passed in 2012 following several scandals of insider trading during the global financial crisis. The Act effectively banned lawmakers from trading based on &#8220;material, non-public information&#8221; extracted from their positions or obtained through their job, regardless of whether they utilize stocks, investment funds, or other means.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e3ed73d1-c97c-41c6-9993-6c1023da418c" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">enforcing</a> insider trading laws against members of Congress is not easy due to constitutional protections that shield them from judicial questioning regarding information obtained during their political duties.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-shorts-the-us-economy-after-calling-it-resilient/" rel="nofollow">US Senator Shorts the US Economy After Calling it Resilient</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>As Dogecoin and Pepe Prices Slide, Could New Meme Coin Shibie Token Be an Alternative?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/as-dogecoin-and-pepe-prices-slide-could-new-meme-coin-shibie-token-be-an-alternative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264188</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/doge_shibie_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/doge_shibie_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coin space has been hit hard in the past 24 hours, with Dogecoin ($DOGE) and Pepe ($PEPE) experiencing significant price slides. This slide comes after a period of sustained volatility, prompting many investors to look for alternative meme coin options that could provide clearer price prospects. One token that has emerged as a [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coin space has been hit hard in the past 24 hours, with Dogecoin ($DOGE) and Pepe ($PEPE) experiencing significant price slides.</p>
<p>This slide comes after a period of sustained volatility, prompting many investors to look for alternative meme coin options that could provide clearer price prospects.</p>
<p>One token that has emerged as a viable option is Shibie Coin ($SHIBIE) &#8211; a brand-new meme project combining the popular worlds of Shiba Inu and Barbie.</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Price Slump Extends as Token Hits $0.0735</h2>
<p>The original meme coin Dogecoin has been suffering recently, with the $DOGE price shedding 5% of its value since Wednesday morning.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/dogecoin/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap</a>, $DOGE is now hovering around the $0.0735 level, with its market cap falling to $10.3 billion.</p>
<p>The price drop over the past 24 hours has extended a broader $DOGE slide, which commenced after the token peaked on July 25.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264208" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-4.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="303" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-4-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-4-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>For 2023 as a whole, $DOGE is now only up around 4%; although the coin’s value was up by 49% in April before it crashed.</p>
<p>These price movements highlight that the hype around Dogecoin might be cooling off, which could be due to the growing popularity of low-cap meme coins being launched on DEXs like Uniswap.</p>
<p>These coins have shown themselves capable of producing quadruple-digit (or more) returns, which is something that $DOGE is no longer able to do.</p>
<p>As such, meme coin buyers are looking elsewhere – hence why Dogecoin is struggling.</p>
<h2>Pepe’s Prolonged Slide Shows No Signs of Stopping as Investors Look Elsewhere</h2>
<p>Pepe is also struggling, with the token’s value down 6% in the past day.</p>
<p>It’s been a tough few weeks for $PEPE holders, with the price rejecting the resistance zone around $0.00000188, prompting an aggressive selloff.</p>
<p>This has sent the token plunging 35% from July&#8217;s high, and 72% from May&#8217;s all-time high.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264206" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-4.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="285" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-4-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-4-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>With momentum and interest waning, many meme coin market participants speculate that $PEPE&#8217;s heyday might be firmly behind it.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Data from CoinGecko</a> reveals that only $64.9 million worth of $PEPE was traded in the past 24 hours, a significant decrease from last month.</p>
<p>Pepe&#8217;s lack of an actual use case has hampered its ability to sustain long-term growth, which isn&#8217;t the case with more utility-driven meme coins.</p>
<p>Overall, things don&#8217;t look like they will get much better for $PEPE in the short term, meaning holders may be in for a challenging period ahead.<strong> </strong></p>
<h2>Which Meme Coin Could Be an Alternative to $DOGE and $PEPE?</h2>
<p>While major meme coins like Dogecoin and Pepe struggle, new tokens are emerging, vying to steal the spotlight.</p>
<p>One of these tokens is Shibie Coin ($SHIBIE) – which many believe could be a breakout star in the meme coin niche after it raised $75,000 in the first two days of its presale.</p>
<h2>Limited-Time Shibie Coin Presale Starts with a Bang &amp; Raises $75,000</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_8dd75c94.finbold.care/?referrer=as-dogecoin-and-pepe-prices-slide-could-new-meme-coin-shibie-token-be-an-alternative" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shibie Coin ($SHIBIE)</a> is a unique project that combines the iconic worlds of Barbie and Shiba Inu in a lighthearted manner.</p>
<p>The project has just started its presale phase, allowing early adopters to purchase $SHIBIE tokens for the low price of $0.000167.</p>
<p>This discounted presale price has primed $SHIBIE for future, given that the creators intend to list the token on a decentralized exchange (DEX) once the presale ends.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264205" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-3.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="365" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-3-300x182.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-3-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://shibie.io/whitepaper/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shibie Coin’s whitepaper</a>, 60% of the total token supply is reserved for this presale – highlighting the community-centric focus of the creators.</p>
<p>The project is already beginning to generate hype on social media, with the official <a href="https://twitter.com/ShibieCoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shibie Coin Twitter account</a> seeing an influx of new followers over the past two days.</p>
<p>This hype is being bolstered further by Shibie Coin’s timely emergence, given that it coincides with the buzz around the new Barbie movie, which has made headlines worldwide.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-264204" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-1.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="364" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-1-300x181.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txQR4Toe1JY&amp;ab_channel=JacobCryptoBury" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">YouTube analyst Jacob Bury</a>, who has an audience of over 20,000 people, has even taken note of Shibie Coin – speculating that it could potentially be a &#8220;Shiba Inu alternative.&#8221;</p>
<p>Given this endorsement and the project’s clever leveraging of the Barbie phenomenon, Shibie Coin seems well-positioned to capture investor interest in the weeks ahead.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_8dd75c94.finbold.care/?referrer=as-dogecoin-and-pepe-prices-slide-could-new-meme-coin-shibie-token-be-an-alternative" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Shibie Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-dogecoin-and-pepe-prices-slide-could-new-meme-coin-shibie-token-be-an-alternative/" rel="nofollow">As Dogecoin and Pepe Prices Slide, Could New Meme Coin Shibie Token Be an Alternative?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Sets Date for Base Mainnet Launch, Addresses Token Rumors</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sets-date-for-base-mainnet-launch-addresses-token-rumors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264203</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coinbase_base.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coinbase_base.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Over 100 ETH and $125,000 in grants are available to those who start building on Base this month.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase has revealed its launch date for Base – the Ethereum layer 2 blockchain designed to make transactions faster and cheaper than the underlying network.</p>
<p>As of today, users can begin bridging ETH to base, with dapps “across the on-chain ecosystem” starting to enable Base support.</p>
<h2>Base: A Bridge To Crypto</h2>
<p>As published in a <a href="https://base.mirror.xyz/h028XVTdP7QtZZfWAHuJ9OYmMNs0Fyi4e4fJZH_5ik4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> from Base on Thursday, the Base mainnet will go live “for everyone and everything” on August 9.</p>
<p>To commemorate the launch, the firm also announced “Onchain Summer” – a month-long festival by 50 creators and developers with a daily showcase of novel things that can be done on-chain.</p>
<p>Participants in the festival will be open to ~100 ETH in grants from Coinbase, <a href="https://prop.house/base" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">spread across</a> participants in four different events: Onchain Summer, Build on Base, Stand With Crypto, and Base Accounts. The company will also host a virtual hackathon – Superhack – from August 4 to 18, which includes another $125,000 in prizes.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our mission has been clear and consistent: bring the next million builders and billion users onchain,” said Base. “We believe that change is an onchain future that enables an open, global economy that increases economic freedom and puts everyone on a level playing field.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Base was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launch-eth-layer-2-network-based-on-optimism-op-token-pumps-6/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> in February as a “bridge” for new crypto users into the crypto economy. Besides Ethereum, it’s designed to provide interoperability with and access to products on other L1 and L2 networks, such as Solana.</p>
<p>The platform was built using the Optimism (OP) stack and leverages the power of rollups, a method of cheaply batching transactions together off-chain before settling them on-chain.</p>
<h2>Will Base Get A Token?</h2>
<p>Unlike other Ethereum scaling networks such as Optimism, Arbitrum (ARB), or Polygon (MATIC), Coinbase stated from the outset that it has no plans to release an accompanying token for Base.</p>
<p>That said, those who bridge their ETH to Base may receive both an ETH reward and a commemorative NFT for their efforts. This can be done using a variety of methods, including through Onchain Summer’s <a href="http://onchainsummer.xyz/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">website</a>, Coinbase’s app, and using <a href="http://bridge.base.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Base Bridge</a>, among other things.</p>
<p>Base is compatible with multiple wallet apps, including “<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-releases-encrypted-decentralized-messaging-functionality-in-wallets/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase Wallet</a>, Rainbow, Safe, Brave, Rabby, Frame, Exodus, Trust Wallet, rhino.fi, and Frontier,” according to Base.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sets-date-for-base-mainnet-launch-addresses-token-rumors/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Sets Date for Base Mainnet Launch, Addresses Token Rumors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
