<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 23:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gemini&#8217;s Non-US Derivatives Platform Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/geminis-non-us-derivatives-platform-goes-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 23:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248922</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Gemini.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Gemini.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gemini Foundation is not available to customers in the United States of America, the United Kingdom, or the European Union.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amidst regulatory headwinds back home, the Winklevoss twins have doubled down their efforts to expand Gemini&#8217;s offerings to non-US residents. The new service aims to target both retail and institutional traders but will exclude users from UK and EU.</p>
<p>Gemini Foundation &#8211; the highly anticipated non-US derivatives platform &#8211; went live on May 1st for customers in all 29 available jurisdictions, including Singapore, Hong Kong, India, Argentina, Bahamas, Bermuda, British Virgin Islands (BVI), Bhutan, Brazil, Cayman Islands, Chile, Egypt, El Salvador, among others.</p>
<p>At launch, Gemini Foundation will offer BTC perpetual contracts denominated in Gemini dollars (GUSD) with up to 100x leverage. In the coming weeks, the platform plans to launch ETH/GUSD perpetual contract as well.</p>
<h2>Regulatory Headwinds in the US</h2>
<p>Since founding Gemini in 2014, it has long worked with regulators in the United States. A year after launch, Gemini received a trust charter from the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS).</p>
<p>It hit a serious operational challenge in 2022 after the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) sued the company, alleging it of making &#8220;false and misleading statements&#8221; to deploy the first US-regulated Bitcoin futures contract in 2017.</p>
<p>More recently, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-files-complaint-against-gemini-and-genesis-for-allegedly-selling-unregistered-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">charged</a> Gemini alongside Genesis with the unregistered offer and sale of securities. The regulator took aim at Gemini Earn lending service, the yield-bearing product which thousands of US investors entrusted with their crypto.</p>
<p>However, the offshore <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-foundation-a-non-us-derivatives-platform-is-now-live" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">division</a> marks Gemini&#8217;s first product focused outside the United States, indicating a crucial stage for the company as it joins the bandwagon of crypto firms taking their business elsewhere. Despite the hurdles, the Winklevoss twins <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/05/02/gemini-launches-offshore-crypto-derivatives-platform/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> they still hope to launch a derivatives product in the home country.</p>
<h2>Asia Pivot</h2>
<p>In addition to the launch of a new division, Gemini has also pivoted to Asia. After Singapore&#8217;s expansion, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to set up a new engineering hub in Gurgaon, India.</p>
<p>The products and features developed in India could be used by institutional and retail clients in over 70 nations. The newly-formed team, which will be headed by the newly appointed CEO of Gemini Asia Pacific, Pravjit Tiwana, will aim to develop next-generation Web and mobile user experience and introduce feature sets for NFT and crypto marketplaces.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/geminis-non-us-derivatives-platform-goes-live/" rel="nofollow">Gemini&#8217;s Non-US Derivatives Platform Goes Live</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Democratic Presidential Candidate Blames &#8220;War on Crypto&#8221; for Recent Bank Failures</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/democratic-presidential-candidate-blames-war-on-crypto-for-recent-bank-failures/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 23:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249146</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[America’s political left still has crypto defenders on its side – one being Robert Kennedy. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A Democratic presidential candidate is pushing against the growing anti-crypto sentiment within his party by blaming regulatory agencies’ “war on crypto” for various bank failures that transpired in March. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In recent days, environmental lawyer Robert Kennedy Jr. has spoken out against the Biden administration&#8217;s general handling of the ongoing banking crisis, opposing the bailout approach used by financial agencies. </span></p>
<h2>The War on Crypto</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1653412637844144128" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, Kennedy backed an article written by Ellen Brown titled “How the War on Crypto Triggered a Banking Crisis.” The article outlined how actions taken by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) and Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) contributed to the downfall of Silicon Valley Bank (SVB), Signature Bank, and Silvergate Bank in March</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“FDIC and SEC have no authority to wage an extra-legal war on crypto that leaves major banks as collateral damage,” said Kennedy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto industry leaders have been up in arms in recent months about a suspected government conspiracy colloquially termed “Operation Chokepoint 2.0” – a subtle effort to dissuade the banking sector from servicing crypto companies and scare blockchain businesses offshore with unclear and arbitrary enforcement actions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Caitlin Long, CEO of the crypto-friendly Custodia Bank, claimed last April that the SEC is punishing crypto firms attempting to be compliant with a deliberate signal to “stay the fuck away.” Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has also </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">suggested</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Coinbase could seek to relocate its headquarters outside the United States if local regulatory challenges persist.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Even Barney Frank – a former US congressman and Signature Bank board member at the time of its closure –  claimed that the crypto-friendly bank’s closure was unnecessary, and specifically meant to send an “</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/signature-banks-seizure-meant-to-send-strong-anti-crypto-message-claims-board-member/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">anti-crypto message</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">” to other banks.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While some crypto-supportive politicians have </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-under-fire-by-congress-is-ether-a-commodity-or-a-security/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">called attention</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to the SEC’s “regulation by enforcement” approach, most have come from the Republican isle. Congressional Democrats, by contrast, are showing weariness around the crypto sector and beginning to question whether it even has a legitimate use case. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On Tuesday, the White House </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">published</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> guidance to Congress encouraging policymakers to pass a 30% excise tax on Bitcoin mining as part of the federal budget to make miners pay for the “economic and environmental costs” they impose. </span></p>
<h2>Kennedy’s Crypto Support</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A respondent to Kennedy’s tweet criticized the presidential candidate for defending crypto, questioning his claims of environmentalism given the “enormous amounts of energy” used by the technology. In response, the lawyer assured that this criticism was a “misunderstanding,” and promised to write about the issue this week. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Kenedy has also stood against Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) – a government-backed form of money that traditional crypto proponents frequently </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/republican-congressman-tom-emmer-introduces-bill-to-ban-feds-cbdc/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">blast </span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">as an invasion of privacy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“A CBDC tied to digital ID and social credit score will allow the government to freeze your assets or limit your spending to approved vendors if you fail to comply with arbitrary diktats,” argued Kennedy in a tweet last month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The candidate’s comments were in specific reference to the central bank’s new FedNow payments service, which the Federal Reserve </span><a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/faqs/is-fednow-replacing-cash-is-it-a-central-bank-digital-currency.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">clarified</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> days later is “not related to a digital currency. </span></p>
<p><em>Feature Image Courtesy of People Magazine.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/democratic-presidential-candidate-blames-war-on-crypto-for-recent-bank-failures/" rel="nofollow">Democratic Presidential Candidate Blames &#8220;War on Crypto&#8221; for Recent Bank Failures</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Operation SpecTor Results in Another Halted Dark Market and 288 Arrested Individuals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/operation-spector-results-in-another-halted-dark-market-and-288-arrested-individuals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 21:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249038</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Dark_Web.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Dark_Web.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The resulting arrests and seizures placed sizable amounts of weapons, drugs, crypto, and cash under the control of the authorities.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Europol announced on May 3 the conclusion of Operation SpecTor, which spans through multiple jurisdictions and recently brought down Monopoly Market, another dark market that sprang up after previous ones were hated.</p>
<h2>Hundreds of Arrests and Seizures</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.europol.europa.eu/media-press/newsroom/news/288-dark-web-vendors-arrested-in-major-marketplace-seizure" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">press release</a> published early this morning, Europol coordinated authorities across the U.S., Austria, France, Germany, the Netherlands, Poland, Brazil, Switzerland, and the U.K. to unravel the threads exposed by the 2021 shutdown of Monopoly Market.</p>
<p>The operation yielded similar results to the one used to take down <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/hansa-dutch-police-sting-operation/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Hansa</a>, in which Dutch authorities managed to hijack the platform and allowed its operation for several months in order to cast as wide a dragnet as possible.</p>
<p>Furthermore, some of those arrested have been <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/2/23708094/international-police-dark-web-monopoly-market-bust" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">confirmed</a> to be users of other dark markets, hinting at possible future law enforcement action against similar platforms.</p>
<p>In total, 117 firearms, 850 kg worth of drugs, and 50 million euros worth of cash and crypto were seized across all jurisdictions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 288 dark web vendors arrested in major marketplace seizure.</p>
<p>Operation <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SpecTor?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#SpecTor</a> led to the seizure of:<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4b6.png" alt="💶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> EUR 50.8 million<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f48a.png" alt="💊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 850 kg of drugs<br />
<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f52b.png" alt="🔫" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> 117 firearms</p>
<p>The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MonopolyMarket?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#MonopolyMarket</a> vendors arrested were also active on other illicit marketplaces.</p>
<p>More <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2935.png" alt="⤵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/fDbWJbeFiM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/fDbWJbeFiM</a> <a href="https://t.co/086e1XMCUo" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/086e1XMCUo</a></p>
<p>— Europol (@Europol) <a href="https://twitter.com/Europol/status/1653369324587843586?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Authorities Promise Further Results</h2>
<p>The operation resulted in the arrest of 288 individuals buying and selling contraband, the <a href="https://www.europol.europa.eu/media-press/newsroom/news/288-dark-web-vendors-arrested-in-major-marketplace-seizure" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">overwhelming</a> majority of which were located in the United States (155). Authorities in the U.K. and Germany arrested 55 and 52 individuals, respectively, with several more in the Netherlands, Austria, France, Switzerland, and Poland.</p>
<p>Commenting on the situation, Europol’s Executive Director Catherine de Bolle stated that cooperation between members of the international community has never been stronger and will continue to improve in order to yield similar results.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our coalition of law enforcement authorities across three continents proves that we all do better when we work together. This operation sends a strong message to criminals on the dark web: international law enforcement has the means and the ability to identify and hold you accountable for your illegal activities, even on the dark web.”</p></blockquote>
<p>These results show an increased efficiency in cooperation across jurisdictions. Operation SpecTor resulted in more arrests than either of its predecessors, DisrupTor, which resulted in 179 arrests in 2020, and Dark HunTor, which took place in 2021 and resulted in 150 arrests.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/02/operation-spector-288-arrests-made-in-international-drug-takedown.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to CNBC, the impressive number of arrests and seizures is partly due to the more recent takedowns of Genesis and Hydra Market, which allegedly pointed to the real identity of some users active on Monopoly Market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/operation-spector-results-in-another-halted-dark-market-and-288-arrested-individuals/" rel="nofollow">Operation SpecTor Results in Another Halted Dark Market and 288 Arrested Individuals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bhutan Seeks to Raise $500 Million to Bolster Bitcoin Mining Operations: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bhutan-seeks-to-raise-500-million-to-bolster-bitcoin-mining-operations-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249041</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bitcoinmining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bitcoinmining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The joint fund between Bhutan's investment arm and Bitdeer could strengthen the country's efforts in the BTC mining sector.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Druk Holding &amp; Investments &#8211; the investment arm of the Royal Government of Bhutan &#8211; partnered with the Nasdaq-listed company &#8211; Bitdeer Technologies Group &#8211; to introduce a $500 million fund that should support bitcoin mining activities in the Himalayan country.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recent sources suggested that the nation might have been secretly producing BTC since 2017, using its vast amount of hydropower. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bhutan&#8217;s Mission to Become a BTC Mining Hub</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The government of the landlocked country in South Asia seems determined to establish the region as a leading factor in the bitcoin mining scene. For that purpose, Druk Holding &amp; Investments </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bhutan-plans-a-500-million-fund-for-crypto-mining-in-the-himalayas-1.1915217" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">collaborated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with Bitdeer to raise half a billion-dollar fund. The financing could develop green crypto mining in the area by deploying Bhutan&#8217;s hydroelectricity resources. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The fund is expected to start targeting institutional investors at the end of May, whereas Druk and Bitdeer will also participate as financial backers. Ujjwal Deep Dahal &#8211; CEO of Bhutan&#8217;s investment arm &#8211; believes entering the BTC mining sector is the least risky way for the country to join the industry.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It&#8217;s important for us to look at assets that are low volume, high value, or digital assets for that matter, and try to position ourselves in a way that we can be competitive globally over time to build our economy,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitdeer &#8211; a crypto mining giant based in Singapore &#8211; aims to establish a 100-megawatt operation in Bhutan. Construction should start during the second quarter of the year and be completed by September. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recent sources </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/has-bhutan-been-quietly-mining-bitcoin-since-2017-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hinted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that Bhutan might have hopped on the BTC mining bandwagon as early as 2017. A government representative told Forbes earlier this week that the country joined the ecosystem &#8220;a few years ago as one of the early entrants when the price of bitcoin was around $5,000.&#8221; </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bhutan&#8217;s Other Crypto Forays</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides its massive bitcoin mining plans, the country has also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-partners-with-bhutans-central-bank-to-pilot-a-cbdc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">displayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> intentions to launch a digital version of its national currency. The enterprise blockchain provider &#8211; Ripple &#8211; said in 2021 it would allow the Royal Monetary Authority (Bhutan&#8217;s central bank) to use its network for that goal:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Today, we are proud to announce our partnership with Bhutan&#8217;s central bank, the Royal Monetary Authority (RMA), which will use Ripple&#8217;s CBDC solution to pilot a central bank digital currency (CBDC) in phases.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The bank expects the potential move to improve cross-border payments and expand financial inclusion. Ripple said it will take into account Bhutan&#8217;s green policies, explaining that the CBDC solution would be a match for its principles:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Ripple&#8217;s commitment to sustainability was important for Bhutan. The CBDC solution is carbon-neutral and, because it&#8217;s based on the public XRP Ledger, is 120,000x more energy efficient than proof-of-work blockchains.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bhutan-seeks-to-raise-500-million-to-bolster-bitcoin-mining-operations-report/" rel="nofollow">Bhutan Seeks to Raise $500 Million to Bolster Bitcoin Mining Operations: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fed Announces 25bps Rate Hike to 5%, Bitcoin Remains Flat</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fed-announces-25bps-rate-hike-to-5-bitcoin-remains-flat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 18:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249133</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/JeromePowell2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/JeromePowell2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Fed confirmed what economists expect will be its final interest rate increase before a long-awaited pause. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Federal Reserve announced another small increase to its benchmark rate on Wednesday, bringing it between 5% and 5.25%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin’s price remained relatively flat on the announcement, fluctuating between $28,000 and $28,500. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The increase was largely in line with expectations, with the market only pricing in an 11.8% chance that the Federal Open Markets Committee (FOMC) would keep its rate flat, per the <a href="https://www.cmegroup.com/markets/interest-rates/cme-fedwatch-tool.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">CME FedWatch tool</a>. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The central bank has been increasing its interest rate since last year in an effort to quell red-hot consumer price index inflation, which rose to a 40+ year high of 9.1% last June. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Financial commentators like BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/buy-the-fing-pivot-arthur-hayes-on-bank-bailouts-and-bitcoins-endgame/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">predicted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the Fed might stop raising rates, and even begin lowering them far sooner than expected after multiple bank failures took place before the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fed-hikes-interest-rates-by-25-points-prompting-bitcoin-volatility/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">previous rate hike</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in May. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Others such as Former Richmond Fed Chief Jeffrey Lacker </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fed-will-continue-to-hike-despite-banking-crisis-predicts-former-richmond-fed-chief/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">assumed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the Fed would remain firm in hiking rates in the face of bank failures, rather than signal to markets that something is amiss. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As of March 2023, inflation has been reduced to 5% – though some believe this may not last due to the Federal Reserve’s efforts to protect the banking system, which have already injected hundreds of billions of dollars back into the economy. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The U.S. banking system is sound and resilient,” stated the Fed in a <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/monetary20230503a.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">press release</a> accompanying its rate hike announcement. “Tighter credit conditions for households and businesses are likely to weigh on economic activity, hiring, and inflation.”</span></p></blockquote>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The central bank added that it would adjust its monetary policy stance “if risks emerge that could impede the attainment of the Committee&#8217;s goals.” </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fed-announces-25bps-rate-hike-to-5-bitcoin-remains-flat/" rel="nofollow">Fed Announces 25bps Rate Hike to 5%, Bitcoin Remains Flat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Loss of Confidence in Fiat Boosting Bitcoin Adoption: Michael Saylor</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/global-loss-of-confidence-in-fiat-boosting-bitcoin-adoption-michael-saylor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249118</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/MichaelSaylor.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/MichaelSaylor.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin adoption has picked up the pace recently as investors acquire more of the leading crypto asset.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With several market analysts giving their takes on the key driver behind this renewed surge, MicroStrategy&#8217;s former CEO, Michael Saylor, recently expressed his view on the matter.</p>
<h2>Inflation and Counterparty Risks Drive Bitcoin Adoption</h2>
<p>In a recent CNBC <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1653508990335172611?t=zTMIXtTelH0keV9n6Ky8UA&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a>, Saylor noted that two dynamics are pushing the broad adoption of Bitcoin. He revealed that the first one is the concern about inflation.</p>
<p>Saylor believes these issues result in the loss of confidence in fiat currencies, causing investors to turn to risk-off assets like Bitcoin:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There&#8217;s the macroeconomic concern about inflation and as inflation takes place, people lose confidence in fiat currencies. That means they start to realize that everything valued on cash flow is a currency derivative and bitcoin is not valued on cash flows,” he explained.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Bitcoin proponent further explained that the recent banking crisis, including the failure of Silvergate Bank, Signature Bank, Silicon Valley Bank, and the latest one, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-slide-while-bitcoin-pumps-after-first-republic-failure/" data-wpel-link="internal">First Republic Bank</a>, has undermined investors&#8217; faith in the banking system.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The failure of the banks… causes people in the Western world to start to lose a little bit of faith in the banking system and they remember that bitcoin is a bank in cyberspace run by incorruptible software… So the combination of that concern about inflation and counterparty risks with banks is driving bitcoin&#8217;s adoption,&#8221; he said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>MicroStrategy Not Backing Down From Long-term BTC Plan</h2>
<p>Saylor reiterated that MicroStrategy has maintained its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-sees-first-quarterly-profit-in-2-years-due-to-bitcoin-bet/" data-wpel-link="internal">confidence</a> in Bitcoin&#8217;s potential. Saylor noted that the business intelligence and software firm will continue to accumulate more of the digital asset despite suffering massive paper losses at one point on its approximately 140,000 BTC portfolio.</p>
<p>He explained that MicroStrategy, which recorded significant growth in Q1, was &#8220;a cash cow&#8221; to pay off interest on its debts while acquiring more bitcoin. He added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The real key with bitcoin is being able to hold on to it and stomach the volatility. We have conditioned our shareholders and our bondholders to understand that we&#8217;re long-term HODLers and because everybody is aligned in that interest, we&#8217;re able to weather that volatility and we end up doing very well as Bitcoin recovers.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/global-loss-of-confidence-in-fiat-boosting-bitcoin-adoption-michael-saylor/" rel="nofollow">Global Loss of Confidence in Fiat Boosting Bitcoin Adoption: Michael Saylor</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Consolidates Below $29K but is This the Calm Before the Storm? (BItcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-consolidates-below-29k-but-is-this-the-calm-before-the-storm-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249069</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been consolidating between the 50-day moving average at $28,310 and the $30K resistance region. However, it seems likely to break out of this decisive range, determining its upcoming rally’s direction. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart After finding support at the 50-day moving average of roughly $27K, the price started a [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been consolidating between the 50-day moving average at $28,310 and the $30K resistance region. However, it seems likely to break out of this decisive range, determining its upcoming rally’s direction.</p>
<h1>Technical Analysis</h1>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h2>The Daily Chart</h2>
<p>After finding support at the 50-day moving average of roughly $27K, the price started a steady uptrend, aiming to surpass the $30K region for the second time. However, Bitcoin failed to surpass this crucial resistance zone, resulting in a slight decline.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the BTC price is currently consolidating within the tight range of the 50-day moving average at $28K and $30K.</p>
<p>A breakout beyond the $30K region will significantly impact market sentiment, as it is a crucial psychological resistance. Conversely, a decline below the 50-day moving average may result in volatility and consolidation in lower price ranges.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249072" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249072" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249072 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0305231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249072" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>The 4-Hour Chart</h2>
<p>Monitoring the 4-hour timeframe, it is apparent that the price has been stuck inside a static range between $30K and $27K. Recently, BTC experienced high volatility, resulting in big red and green candles without showing any clear sign of the overall market bias.</p>
<p>Ultimately, Bitcoin&#8217;s price is likely to break out of this range in the upcoming weeks, and the direction of the cryptocurrency&#8217;s following trend will heavily depend on the breakout&#8217;s direction. However, with the RSI indicator standing at the 50 mark, indicating a state of equilibrium between the bulls and the bears, BTC is expected to undergo a consolidation stage alongside volatility.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249074" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249074" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249074 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0305232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249074" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h1>On-chain Analysis</h1>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been on the rise since rebounding from the $16K level a few months ago, leaving many investors hopeful that the bear market is finally over and a new bullish phase has begun. However, miners seem a lot more pessimistic.</p>
<p>This chart demonstrates the miners’ position index (MPI) metric, which displays the ratio of total miner outflow to its one-year moving average of total miner outflow. High values indicate mass selling by the miners, who are one of the most critical cohorts in the market.</p>
<p>The MPI has spiked recently, showing its highest values since January 2021, indicating that the miners have sold their coins at a significant rate near the recent highs. This could be considered a bearish signal, and if continued, their selling pressure could lead to a reversal and continuation of the bear market in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249073" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249073" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249073 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_miners_position_index_chart" width="2560" height="1614" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-1024x646.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-1536x969.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-2048x1292.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-MPI-May-3-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249073" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-consolidates-below-29k-but-is-this-the-calm-before-the-storm-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Consolidates Below $29K but is This the Calm Before the Storm? (BItcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky Files Defense Motion in Response to NYAG&#8217;s Complaint</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-files-defense-motion-in-response-to-nyags-complaint/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249060</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky had previously denied allegations filed in the civil lawsuit against him. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celsius Network founder Alex Mashinsky &#8211; who was accused of defrauding investors out of billions of dollars in crypto by concealing the failing health of his now-bankrupt lending platform &#8211; has filed a response seeking to dismiss the New York State complaint against him.</p>
<p>The complaint was filed by New York State Attorney General Letitia James in January. It claimed that Mashinsky persisted in promoting Celsius as a safe alternative to banks, but users had to pay interest as high as 17% on deposits.</p>
<p>The civil lawsuit seeks to prohibit the exec from doing business in the New York state and compel him to compensate damages for violating laws such as the state&#8217;s Martin Act, which gives the NYAG broad power to pursue securities fraud cases.</p>
<h2>Mashinsky&#8217;s Response</h2>
<p>In a newly <a href="https://iapps.courts.state.ny.us/nyscef/ViewDocument?docIndex=/mPuBL5LQ5Z2OEWZ70pvhw==" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filed</a> defense motion, the 57-year-old Mashinsky argued that the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-ag-sues-celsius-co-founder-alex-mashinsky-for-alleged-fraud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">complaint</a> composed by NYAG &#8220;parrots misinformation&#8221; about him and Celsius Network and &#8220;borrows others&#8217; baseless conclusions.&#8221; The former exec further added that the civil lawsuit against him &#8220;demonstrates a fundamental misunderstanding&#8221; of the lender&#8217;s business, as well his role.</p>
<p>The filing contended NYAG of falsely pinning Celsius&#8217; losses on the alleged misstatements on Mashinsky alone. It claimed that the company&#8217;s fall was a result of a liquidity crisis and circumstances outside of the exec&#8217;s (and Celsius’) control.</p>
<p>The response further alleges James&#8217;s lawsuit of &#8220;cherry-picking&#8221; fragments of statements and sound bites without broader context and denied claims of Celsius offering in securities nor commodities services.</p>
<h2>Messy Record-Keeping</h2>
<p>The latest development comes amidst an auction with bidders vying to take over Celsius&#8217; business. Leading crypto exchanges Coinbase and Gemini have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-and-gemini-join-bid-race-for-celsius-networks-assets-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">joined</a> the bidding race.</p>
<p>The embattled lender was also accused of poor record-keeping and glaring deficiencies in its internal systems. As a result, Celsius sought to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-calls-for-consolidating-us-and-uk-entities-amidst-poor-record-keeping-allegations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">consolidate</a> its UK-based entity, Celsius Network Limited (CNL), and its US-based entity, Celsius Network (LLC), in hopes of getting its books in order.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-files-defense-motion-in-response-to-nyags-complaint/" rel="nofollow">Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky Files Defense Motion in Response to NYAG&#8217;s Complaint</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ex Ankr and Blockdaemon Execs Launch Tenet, A Layer-1 Ecosystem to Maximize LSD Utility</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-execs-launch-tenet-a-layer-1-ecosystem-to-maximize-lsd-utility/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 13:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249103</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tenet.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tenet.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Mahe, Seychelles, May 3rd, 2023] Former executives from Ankr and Blockdaemon have joined their expertise to create Tenet, the first Layer 1 blockchain built to create a hub for Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSDs). Tenet is emerging from stealth mode and unveiling its Testnet today, enabling developers to interact and experiment with the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Mahe, Seychelles, May 3rd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Former executives from Ankr and Blockdaemon have joined their expertise to create Tenet, the first Layer 1 blockchain built to create a hub for Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSDs). Tenet is emerging from stealth mode and unveiling its Testnet today, enabling developers to interact and experiment with the platform.</p>
<p>Tenet is an EVM-compatible L1 protocol, designed to bring additional liquidity and yield opportunities to LSDs by allowing users to re-stake their assets on Tenet&#8217;s network and participate in Tenet&#8217;s DeFi ecosystem. Unlike other Cosmos chains that rely on their own native token for Proof of Stake security, Tenet validators can make use of a unique mechanism called Diversified Proof of Stake (DiPoS).</p>
<p>In a nutshell, DiPoS allows validating the Tenet network by re-staking the LSDs from other L1 ecosystems supported by Tenet, such as ETH, BNB, ATOM, SOL and Matic. This ensures the long-term security of the Tenet chain by leveraging the joint security of each L1 ecosystem it services. The lack of shared security has been long-recognized as an adoption roadblock for many chains in the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The LSDs re-staked to the Tenet network will be usable like other LSDs (or, an LLSD) to take advantage of DeFi opportunities on Tenet. In addition to DEXs and lending pools, they will also be able to mint the Universal Stablecoin interest free, allowing them to receive an “advance” on their future LSD yields, which became the largest market vertical in Defi this year, surpassing DEX&#8217;s with $17.5B in TVL.</p>
<p>Tenet also offers the first L1 ecosystem with native gauges, which allow veTenet token holders to direct rewards to the pools they choose. Oftentimes, projects will offer “bribes” to direct rewards to their tokens, increasing the utility of veTenet.</p>
<p>The Tenet product vision is aimed at simplifying the staking experience for users. One of the pillars of this vision is the Eva mobile wallet, a retail-friendly mobile app that uses an AI chat-bot to educate users about DeFi and automates interactions with the Tenet chain through optimized yield strategies.</p>
<p>The project is co-founded by Greg Gopman, previously CMO at major LSD protocol Ankr, and Dan Peterson, formerly the Revenue Operations Specialist at Blockdaemon, the largest independant infrastructure and staking firm in crypto, valued at +$3B. Four more experienced core members round out technical and BD expertise, while advisors from Lido, Ankr and OpenAI will offer invaluable support to expand and grow the protocol.</p>
<p>Greg Gopman, co-founder of Tenet, said, &#8220;At Ankr, we helped bring Liquid Staking Tokens to eight Blockchains and built out some of the best LSD infrastructure in the industry, but no one used it. Tenet was really a golden opportunity for being first to market in utilizing best in class technology with almost $20B in untapped liquidity.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We analyzed what other projects like Berachain and Eigen Layer were doing and realized that there was a better way to position ourselves to best address the market,&#8221; added Dan Peterson, co-founder of Tenet. “We’ve chosen to take a user-centric path, making the staking and LSD experience simpler and more secure for the average user.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Tenet is inviting DeFi protocols and developers interested in taking advantage of LSD liquidity to sign up for the Testnet and familiarize themselves with the platform. In the coming months, Tenet plans to roll out a grants program and a global DeFi hackathon series to engage developers worldwide, while preparing for the fair community launch of the Tenet blockchain.</p>
<h2>About Tenet</h2>
<p>Tenet is a DeFi-focused Layer-1 ecosystem built on the Cosmos network, providing liquidity and yield opportunities for liquid staking derivatives (LSDs). Co-founded by Greg Gopman, former CMO of Ankr, and Dan Peterson, former Revenue Operations at Blockdaemon, Tenet aims to unlock the potential of the rapidly growing LSD market, which is currently valued at over $17 billion. Tenet takes a unique approach by sharing security through Diversified Proof of Stake, while using L1-native gauges to let users earn yield on their liquid staking assets and participate in the platform&#8217;s governance. <a href="https://tenet.org/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Tenet Website</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/tenet_org" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Tenet Twitter</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ex-ankr-and-blockdaemon-execs-launch-tenet-a-layer-1-ecosystem-to-maximize-lsd-utility/" rel="nofollow">Ex Ankr and Blockdaemon Execs Launch Tenet, A Layer-1 Ecosystem to Maximize LSD Utility</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Symmetry Launches Platform for Decentralized Crypto Indices and Actively Managed Funds on Solana</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/symmetry-launches-platform-for-decentralized-crypto-indices-and-actively-managed-funds-on-solana/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249097</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Symmetri.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Symmetri.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Paris, France, May 3rd, 2023] Today marks a groundbreaking step for decentralized finance (DeFi) on the Solana blockchain as Symmetry launches its highly anticipated User Interface at https://app.symmetry.fi/. The platform aims to revolutionize the way users manage their portfolios through crypto indices and actively managed funds by providing an all-in-one solution for [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Paris, France, May 3rd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Today marks a groundbreaking step for decentralized finance (DeFi) on the Solana blockchain as <a href="https://symmetry.fi/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Symmetry</a> launches its highly anticipated User Interface at <a href="https://app.symmetry.fi/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://app.symmetry.fi/</a>.</p>
<p>The platform aims to revolutionize the way users manage their portfolios through crypto indices and actively managed funds by providing an all-in-one solution for creating, managing, buying, and selling funds.</p>
<p>Symmetry is a decentralized Crypto Indices and Actively Managed Funds infrastructure layer built on Solana, powered by the Symmetry Engine. This innovative on-chain asset management infrastructure covers everything from on-chain funds, indices, and multi-token liquidity pools, to liquidity routing between indices and decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregators, and public APIs for other DeFi projects to integrate Symmetry products seamlessly.</p>
<p>The platform offers a wide range of opportunities for both fund managers and users. Managers can create and manage funds with multiple tokens that reweigh, rebalance, and refilter according to custom rules defined by the manager, or create a trustless Crypto Index with predefined rules. Users can create their own actively managed funds or indices and buy and sell funds created by other users or protocols.</p>
<p>Symmetry&#8217;s liquidity provision feature allows indices and actively managed funds to act as liquidity providers on DeFi aggregators such as PRISM and Jupiter when their token weights deviate from the target weights. This groundbreaking feature not only enables funds to rebalance at zero cost but also generates fees from aggregator users for fund managers and holders, a significant departure from traditional approaches where indices and funds typically pay fees on exchanges to rebalance.</p>
<p>The Symmetry Engine relies on Pyth, a reliable price oracle, to determine true prices for each asset utilized in Symmetry products. This is crucial for funds to accurately determine fund values, rebalancing triggers, and buy/sell values for users.</p>
<p>Example use-cases for Symmetry include decentralized index fund apps, decentralized fund management apps, treasury management tools, retail onboarding apps, copy-trading apps, and investing apps. The platform envisions a future where anyone can create an index fund, manage on-chain funds and portfolio strategies, convert wallet portfolios to funds, and integrate index or actively managed fund tokens for trading.</p>
<p>With the launch of the Symmetry User Interface, the world of decentralized finance on the Solana blockchain is poised to experience a paradigm shift in how users interact with and manage their crypto portfolios. As the platform continues to roll out its full suite of features to all users, the future of Solana DeFi looks brighter than ever.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/symmetry-launches-platform-for-decentralized-crypto-indices-and-actively-managed-funds-on-solana/" rel="nofollow">Symmetry Launches Platform for Decentralized Crypto Indices and Actively Managed Funds on Solana</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
