<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Doge Rush is a Meme Coin You Can’t Miss Out on - Presale Raises Over $300K Already</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-rush-is-a-meme-coin-you-cant-miss-out-on-presale-raises-over-300k-already.htm</link><description>Investors are always on the lookout for the next big meme coins that are gaining popularity. Even if they have missed out on tokens that have already experienced a significant surge, the market consistently offers promising opportunities. By identifying the right one, your investment portfolio has the chance to achieve substantial growth....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-rush-is-a-meme-coin-you-cant-miss-out-on-presale-raises-over-300k-already.htm"&gt;Read More: Doge Rush is a Meme Coin You Can’t Miss Out on - Presale Raises Over $300K Already&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-rush-is-a-meme-coin-you-cant-miss-out-on-presale-raises-over-300k-already.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115426/278218/doge-rush-crypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="338288"/></item><item><title>Coinbase CEO Criticizes US Lawmakers, Regulators Over Regulatory Approach, Warns of Upcoming Innovation in China</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ceo-criticizes-us-lawmakers-regulators-over-regulatory-approach-warns-of-upcoming-innovation-china.htm</link><description>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong criticized US lawmakers and regulators over their approach to bringing “regulatory clarity” to cryptocurrency and warned that innovation is moving offshore. &lt;br /&gt;
Countries like China will benefit from “restrictive U.S. crypto policies,” Armstrong said in a MarketWatch opinion article on Tuesday. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ceo-criticizes-us-lawmakers-regulators-over-regulatory-approach-warns-of-upcoming-innovation-china.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase CEO Criticizes US Lawmakers, Regulators Over Regulatory Approach, Warns of Upcoming Innovation in China&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>CBDC</category><category>China</category><category>SEC</category><category>Brian Armstrong</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ceo-criticizes-us-lawmakers-regulators-over-regulatory-approach-warns-of-upcoming-innovation-china.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115441/278225/brian-armstrong-coinbase-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115644"/></item><item><title>S Korean Police Bust Two ‘Crypto Scam Rings’ Worth a Combined $350m – Crypto Fraud on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-police-bust-two-crypto-scam-rings-worth-combined-350m-crypto-fraud-rise.htm</link><description>South Korean police have shut down two suspected crypto scams they think are worth a combined $350 million, with hundreds of victims believed to have been duped. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Joongboo Ilbo, one case involved a “virtual fashion items” marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;
This appears to have tricked at least 435 “victims” out of a whopping $333 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-police-bust-two-crypto-scam-rings-worth-combined-350m-crypto-fraud-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: S Korean Police Bust Two ‘Crypto Scam Rings’ Worth a Combined $350m – Crypto Fraud on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-police-bust-two-crypto-scam-rings-worth-combined-350m-crypto-fraud-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115427/278219/skor-3005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="400526"/></item><item><title>Crypto Too Risky for ‘Most’ Russians, Says Finance Ministry – But Could Be ‘Suitable’ for ‘Some’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-too-risky-for-most-russians-says-finance-ministry-but-could-suitable-for-some.htm</link><description>Crypto is too risky for “most” Russians, the nation’s Finance Ministry has claimed. But the ministry claimed tokens could be “suitable” for “professional investors.” &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Nizhny Novgorod, the comments were made by Ivan Chebeskov, the director of the ministry’s financial policy department. &lt;br /&gt;
Chebeskov said that most Russians should not “consider cryptocurrencies” to be a “form of savings.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-too-risky-for-most-russians-says-finance-ministry-but-could-suitable-for-some.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Too Risky for ‘Most’ Russians, Says Finance Ministry – But Could Be ‘Suitable’ for ‘Some’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-too-risky-for-most-russians-says-finance-ministry-but-could-suitable-for-some.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115424/278214/ru-3005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="469974"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Mining Set to Hit New Record High – What’s Driving the Surge?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-set-hit-new-record-high-whats-driving-surge.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin mining difficulty is about to be adjusted to a fresh record high, reflecting a continued rise in the number of mining machines competing to secure the network. &lt;br /&gt;
According to data presented by CoinWarz.com, the BTC mining difficulty will be lifted from its current level of 49.55 trillion to 50.91 trillion at tomorrow’s bi-weekly adjustment. &lt;br /&gt;
That means a more than 2.7% jump in the difficulty that individual miners face as they attempt to discover a Bitcoin block....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-set-hit-new-record-high-whats-driving-surge.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Mining Set to Hit New Record High – What’s Driving the Surge?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Bitcoin Mining</category><category>btc</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-set-hit-new-record-high-whats-driving-surge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115440/278224/btc-37.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="7056329"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 30 May – Quant, Injective, Lido DAO</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-30-may-quant-injective-lido-dao.htm</link><description>Conservative Republicans are opposing the bipartisan agreement to raise the U.S. debt ceiling, which could result in a U.S. default if it doesn't pass its first test in Congress. &lt;br /&gt;
Both President Joe Biden, a Democrat, and the leading Republican figure in Congress, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy, anticipate the requisite votes to enact the bill before June 5. &lt;br /&gt;
With debt default looming and financial markets on edge, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-30-may-quant-injective-lido-dao.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 30 May – Quant, Injective, Lido DAO&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>WSM</category><category>QNT</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>INJ</category><category>YPRED</category><category>LDO</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Quant</category><category>Injective</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Lido Dao</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>Freelancing</category><category>Freelance Work</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Web 3</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Best Crypto Presales</category><category>US debt</category><category>US default</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-30-may-quant-injective-lido-dao.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115439/278222/best-crypto-30-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="379225"/></item><item><title>Former Coinbase Manager and His Brother Agree To Settle SEC Insider Trading Charges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-coinbase-manager-his-brother-agree-settle-sec-insider-trading-charges.htm</link><description>A former Coinbase manager and his brother have agreed to settle insider trading charges brought by a US regulator. &lt;br /&gt;
Ishan Wahi and his brother, Nikhil Wahi, agreed to settle those charges on Tuesday, according to the US Securities and Exchange Commission. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-coinbase-manager-his-brother-agree-settle-sec-insider-trading-charges.htm"&gt;Read More: Former Coinbase Manager and His Brother Agree To Settle SEC Insider Trading Charges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>Civil</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-coinbase-manager-his-brother-agree-settle-sec-insider-trading-charges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115431/278221/adobestock-521876474-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="389077"/></item><item><title>Solana’s Blockchain May Become 'Apple of Crypto', Says Co-founder</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solanas-blockchain-may-become-apple-of-crypto-says-co-founder.htm</link><description>The Solana (SOL) blockchain could become the crypto world’s equivalent of tech giant Apple given its strong focus on user experience, according to Solana co-founder Raj Gokal. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking in a recent interview with TechCrunch, Gokal likened Solana to Apple, saying the Mac and iPhone maker’s “relentless focus on simple interaction” is something Solana has learned from....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solanas-blockchain-may-become-apple-of-crypto-says-co-founder.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana’s Blockchain May Become 'Apple of Crypto', Says Co-founder&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solanas-blockchain-may-become-apple-of-crypto-says-co-founder.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115383/278094/solana.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="98932"/></item><item><title>US Regulator Issues Warning for Firms Providing Clearings Services for Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-issues-warning-for-firms-providing-clearings-services-for-crypto.htm</link><description>A US regulator warned firms on Tuesday of the risks that come with the clearing of digital assets.   &lt;br /&gt;
The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission issued an advisory titled, “Review of Risks Associated with Expansion of DCO Clearing of Digital Assets.”   &lt;br /&gt;
Derivatives clearing organizations, or DCOs, are registered with the CFTC and provide clearing services for products such as futures contracts, options or swaps. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-issues-warning-for-firms-providing-clearings-services-for-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: US Regulator Issues Warning for Firms Providing Clearings Services for Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Binance</category><category>Clearing</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-issues-warning-for-firms-providing-clearings-services-for-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115423/278215/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="426841"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Meme Coins Take Off – Is Now a Good Entry Point on SHIB?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-take-off-now-good-entry-point-shib.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the world’s second-largest meme coin by market capitalization, is going sideways in the $0.0000087 area, with the 21-Day Moving Average (DMA) having acted as a magnet to the price action for the last three days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-take-off-now-good-entry-point-shib.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Meme Coins Take Off – Is Now a Good Entry Point on SHIB?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-take-off-now-good-entry-point-shib.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115422/278211/shib-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="693342"/></item><item><title>Ledger’s CEO Claims New Key Recovery Service Streamlines Crypto Self-Custody Amid Ongoing Controversy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ledgers-ceo-claims-new-key-recovery-service-streamlines-crypto-self-custody-amid-ongoing-controversy.htm</link><description>Crypto hardware wallet provider Ledger believes its recently-launched “Recover” product makes self-custody easier.  &lt;br /&gt;
Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier has said that the company's new security feature, which allows users to recover their secret recovery phrase, would make it easier for crypto users to take custody of their assets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ledgers-ceo-claims-new-key-recovery-service-streamlines-crypto-self-custody-amid-ongoing-controversy.htm"&gt;Read More: Ledger’s CEO Claims New Key Recovery Service Streamlines Crypto Self-Custody Amid Ongoing Controversy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ledger</category><category>Security</category><category>Hardware</category><category>Hardware wallet</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ledgers-ceo-claims-new-key-recovery-service-streamlines-crypto-self-custody-amid-ongoing-controversy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115407/278156/ledger-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="161134"/></item><item><title>Wall Street Memes Presale Surges Past $1.3 Million as Investors Rush to Partake in Hottest Meme Coin Presale in Years</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-presale-surges-past-13-million-as-investors-rush-partake-hottest-meme-coin-presale-years.htm</link><description>Tuesday, 30th May - The most exciting crypto meme coin presale in years is selling out fast, and here's why it's time to pay attention. &lt;br /&gt;
Wall Street Memes, one of the internet’s most powerful retail investing communities, launched a presale of its $WSM token on Friday and it has already surpassed $1 million in funds raised....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-presale-surges-past-13-million-as-investors-rush-partake-hottest-meme-coin-presale-years.htm"&gt;Read More: Wall Street Memes Presale Surges Past $1.3 Million as Investors Rush to Partake in Hottest Meme Coin Presale in Years&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-presale-surges-past-13-million-as-investors-rush-partake-hottest-meme-coin-presale-years.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115418/278179/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="515683"/></item><item><title>Is Launchpad XYZ the Best Crypto App for Newcomers? Here's How to Find the Next Meme Coin to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/launchpad-xyz-best-crypto-app-for-newcomers-heres-how-find-next-meme-coin-explode.htm</link><description>Web3 can be very daunting for beginners. &lt;br /&gt;
There are so many strange concepts, and so much jargon. &lt;br /&gt;
Non-crypto natives need to wrap their heads around the concept of blockchains, wallets, gas fees, the difference between cryptocurrencies and crypto tokens (of the ERC-20 and BEP-20 ilk), as well as familiarise themselves with decentralized finance protocols and other decentralized applications, such as metaverses and play-to-earn (P2E) games....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/launchpad-xyz-best-crypto-app-for-newcomers-heres-how-find-next-meme-coin-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Is Launchpad XYZ the Best Crypto App for Newcomers? Here's How to Find the Next Meme Coin to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><category>Web3</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/launchpad-xyz-best-crypto-app-for-newcomers-heres-how-find-next-meme-coin-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115409/278159/lpx-preasl.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="469444"/></item><item><title>Binance in Talks To Let Traders Keep Collateral at a Bank: Bloomberg</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-talks-let-traders-keep-collateral-at-bank-bloomberg.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange, is in the midst of discussing a proposal to let some of its institutional clients keep their trading collateral at a bank, instead of with the crypto platform, according to Bloomberg News. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-talks-let-traders-keep-collateral-at-bank-bloomberg.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance in Talks To Let Traders Keep Collateral at a Bank: Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Exchanges</category><category>Bloomberg</category><category>SEC</category><category>Banking</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-talks-let-traders-keep-collateral-at-bank-bloomberg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115405/278154/adobestock-456009336-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="125292"/></item><item><title>Fantom Blockchain to Return 15% of Gas Fees to Boost Network Usage – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-blockchain-return-15-of-gas-fees-boost-network-usage-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The Fantom (FTM) blockchain has introduced a new initiative called the "dApp Gas Monetization Program," aiming to reward projects that utilize its network and contribute to increased gas fee usage. &lt;br /&gt;
The new program, which recently received community support through a governance vote, seeks to redirect a portion of Fantom's network fees directly to decentralized applications (dApps) that are being built on the platform....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-blockchain-return-15-of-gas-fees-boost-network-usage-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Fantom Blockchain to Return 15% of Gas Fees to Boost Network Usage – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Fantom</category><category>DeFi</category><category>FTM</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-blockchain-return-15-of-gas-fees-boost-network-usage-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115366/278078/fantom.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="93294"/></item><item><title>Binance Readies Japan-Focused Crypto Platform, Set for Summer Launch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-launch-new-local-platform-for-japanese-residents.htm</link><description>Binance has begun the process of transitioning Japanese users of its international crypto exchange to a specialized local platform, the company confirmed in a blog post on Friday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The separate exchange is designed to comply with local regulations that the international exchange cannot meet.  &lt;br /&gt;
Binance has already launched similar entities in countries like the United States such as Binance.US, which supports much lower volume and fewer trading pairs than the main branch. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-launch-new-local-platform-for-japanese-residents.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Readies Japan-Focused Crypto Platform, Set for Summer Launch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-launch-new-local-platform-for-japanese-residents.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115401/278148/adobestock-558087473-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="165065"/></item><item><title>Hacker Robs Tornado Cash, Launders Loot Through the Same Service</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hacker-robs-tornado-cash-launders-loot-through-same-service.htm</link><description>In a surprising turn of events, the hacker responsible for the Tornado Cash heist has unexpectedly handed back control of the protocol to the team.  &lt;br /&gt;
Adding to the irony, the criminal utilized the very same service to launder the funds stolen during the attack. &lt;br /&gt;
Tornado Cash, which has long been associated with aiding cybercriminals and facilitating money laundering for entities like North Korean hackers, now finds itself caught in the web it helped weave....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hacker-robs-tornado-cash-launders-loot-through-same-service.htm"&gt;Read More: Hacker Robs Tornado Cash, Launders Loot Through the Same Service&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hacker-robs-tornado-cash-launders-loot-through-same-service.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115402/278147/pexels-pixabay-60504.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115202"/></item><item><title>Huobi HK Starts Offering Crypto Spot Trading to Hong Kong's Retail and Institutional Clients Amid New License Submission</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/huobi-hk-starts-offering-crypto-spot-trading-hong-kongs-retail-institutional-clients-amid-new-license-submission.htm</link><description>Huobi, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, is forging ahead with its expansion efforts in Hong Kong. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the recent announcement from Huobi Global, the company's subsidiary in Hong Kong has introduced services for crypto spot trading and virtual asset custody. &lt;br /&gt;
Furthermore, Huobi HK has officially applied for a license from the Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission, expressing confidence in obtaining the virtual assets license in the near future....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/huobi-hk-starts-offering-crypto-spot-trading-hong-kongs-retail-institutional-clients-amid-new-license-submission.htm"&gt;Read More: Huobi HK Starts Offering Crypto Spot Trading to Hong Kong's Retail and Institutional Clients Amid New License Submission&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/huobi-hk-starts-offering-crypto-spot-trading-hong-kongs-retail-institutional-clients-amid-new-license-submission.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115398/278145/hd-wallpaper-g331dda40c-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="180048"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Key App Reveals Bridge Connecting Solana &amp; Ethereum, ECB Publishes Two Reports on Digital Euro, Russia Abandons National Crypto Exchange Plans, CoinEx Launches BitHK</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-key-app-reveals-bridge-connecting-solana-ethereum-ecb-publishes-two-reports-on-digital-euro-russia-abandons-national-crypto-exchange-plans-coinex-launches-bithk.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-key-app-reveals-bridge-connecting-solana-ethereum-ecb-publishes-two-reports-on-digital-euro-russia-abandons-national-crypto-exchange-plans-coinex-launches-bithk.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Key App Reveals Bridge Connecting Solana &amp; Ethereum, ECB Publishes Two Reports on Digital Euro, Russia Abandons National Crypto Exchange Plans, CoinEx Launches BitHK&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Payments</category><category>Solana</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Europe</category><category>ECB</category><category>Russia</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>China</category><category>Web3</category><category>USA</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-key-app-reveals-bridge-connecting-solana-ethereum-ecb-publishes-two-reports-on-digital-euro-russia-abandons-national-crypto-exchange-plans-coinex-launches-bithk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115363/278087/adobestock-4kclips-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="148405"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Blockchain Transaction Fee Revenue Soars Amid Ordinals Popularity – Can BTC Reach a New High in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blockchain-transaction-fee-revenue-soars-amid-ordinals-popularity-can-btc-reach-new-high-2023.htm</link><description>As the popularity of Bitcoin continues to rise, accompanied by a significant increase in blockchain transaction fee revenue, many are speculating about the potential for BTC to reach new highs in 2023.  &lt;br /&gt;
The surge in transaction fees reflects the growing demand for Bitcoin and the increasing adoption of cryptocurrencies to conduct financial transactions. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blockchain-transaction-fee-revenue-soars-amid-ordinals-popularity-can-btc-reach-new-high-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Blockchain Transaction Fee Revenue Soars Amid Ordinals Popularity – Can BTC Reach a New High in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blockchain-transaction-fee-revenue-soars-amid-ordinals-popularity-can-btc-reach-new-high-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115390/278131/30-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482155"/></item></channel></rss>
