<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Halving Event in 2024 Sparks Bullish Sentiments – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm</link><description>The BTC/USD is currently witnessing a decline of nearly 0.50%, with its value standing at $29,400.  &lt;br /&gt;
As the cryptocurrency market navigates this shift, Bitcoin faces intensified price pressure in anticipation of the Bitcoin halving event in 2024 and a crucial decision by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding an ETF application.  &lt;br /&gt;
Moreover, releasing US inflation data adds an additional layer of uncertainty to the market's trajectory. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Halving Event in 2024 Sparks Bullish Sentiments – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122264/323494/12-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="533850"/></item><item><title>S Korean Prosecutors Want to Jail $651m ‘Crypto Scammers’ for 12-15 Years</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-prosecutors-want-to-jail-651m-crypto-scammers-for-12-15-years.htm</link><description>South Korean prosecutors say they hope to jail executives thought to be behind a $651 million crypto scam to prison for up to 15 years. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Asia Kyungjae, the alleged scam saw 8,000 people left out of pocket. &lt;br /&gt;
The scammers allegedly offered individuals “payouts” if they paid their utilities bills using cryptoassets via a dedicated platform named OnNetworks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-prosecutors-want-to-jail-651m-crypto-scammers-for-12-15-years.htm"&gt;Read More: S Korean Prosecutors Want to Jail $651m ‘Crypto Scammers’ for 12-15 Years&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Scam</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-prosecutors-want-to-jail-651m-crypto-scammers-for-12-15-years.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122205/323369/skor-1108.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="539716"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 August – Fantom, Rocket Pool, Sui</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-august-fantom-rocket-pool-sui.htm</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has opted to postpone its decision on Ark Invest's proposal for a Bitcoin ETF, continuing a longstanding challenge for cryptocurrency assets seeking inclusion on mainstream U.S. financial platforms. &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC announced on Friday its move to solicit public opinion regarding a particular amendment in the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF application, potentially prolonging the decision-making process into 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-august-fantom-rocket-pool-sui.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 August – Fantom, Rocket Pool, Sui&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Fantom</category><category>Shibie</category><category>Rocket Pool</category><category>Chimpanzee</category><category>SUI</category><category>Sui Price</category><category>FTM Price</category><category>FTM</category><category>RPL</category><category>Rpl Price</category><category>CHMPZ</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Memecoins</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Cryptos</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Barbie</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>US SEC</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Staking</category><category>NFT</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Chatbots</category><category>Telegram</category><category>Chatbot</category><category>Merchandise</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-august-fantom-rocket-pool-sui.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122258/323481/bctbt-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260398"/></item><item><title>AI Crypto Signals Made Easy for Newcomers with New Crypto Startup yPredict – $3.4 Million Raised So Far</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-made-easy-for-newcomers-with-new-crypto-startup-ypredict-34-million-raised-so-far.htm</link><description>Financial markets have always been unpredictable. Investors have traditionally sought assistance from experts, charts, and algorithms to make informed decisions. But the rise of technology, particularly artificial intelligence, has brought about tools that are changing the face of trading.  &lt;br /&gt;
With crypto signals becoming increasingly popular, traders are also searching for reliable platforms offering these essential cues....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-made-easy-for-newcomers-with-new-crypto-startup-ypredict-34-million-raised-so-far.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Crypto Signals Made Easy for Newcomers with New Crypto Startup yPredict – $3.4 Million Raised So Far&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Price Predictions</category><category>Best Utility Coin</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-made-easy-for-newcomers-with-new-crypto-startup-ypredict-34-million-raised-so-far.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122228/323480/f3q1xjexiaazdtv.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="112896"/></item><item><title>Bank of America Says PayPal’s Stablecoin Will Not Record Significant Adoption In The Coming Months</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-says-paypals-stablecoin-will-not-record-significant-adoption-coming-months.htm</link><description>A new report by the Bank of America suggests that PayPal’s new stablecoin, PYUSD  will not record the projected adoption in the near term citing tougher competition and indifference of investors. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the report, the launch of the new stablecoin by the financial giant is great for the digital asset community and the company itself but it will struggle going head to head against USD Tether (USDT) and USD Coin (USDC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-says-paypals-stablecoin-will-not-record-significant-adoption-coming-months.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of America Says PayPal’s Stablecoin Will Not Record Significant Adoption In The Coming Months&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Bank of America</category><category>PYUSD</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-says-paypals-stablecoin-will-not-record-significant-adoption-coming-months.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122256/323479/paypal-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103256"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried is Heading Back to Jail For Witness Tampering After Judge Ruling</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sam-bankman-fried-is-heading-back-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-after-judge-ruling.htm</link><description>Disgraced former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is being sent back to jail over alleged witness tampering. &lt;br /&gt;
US District Judge Lewis Kaplan stated that there is probable cause to believe that the defendant attempted to tamper with witnesses on at least two occasions. &lt;br /&gt;
Bankman-Fried had been staying at his parents' house in California on a $250 million bail....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sam-bankman-fried-is-heading-back-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-after-judge-ruling.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried is Heading Back to Jail For Witness Tampering After Judge Ruling&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>People In Crypto</category><category>FTX</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sam-bankman-fried-is-heading-back-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-after-judge-ruling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122257/323477/adobestock-544467568-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2842826"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Alternative BTC20 Price Ready to Pump as Buybacks Kick in and 54% of Supply Staked</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-alternative-btc20-price-ready-pump-as-buy-backs-kick-54-of-supply-staked.htm</link><description>Launched on Uniswap decentralized exchange yesterday, 'Bitcoin on Ethereum' coin BTC20 is proving an excellent advert for staking, with 54% of tokens now deposited into the smart contract.  &lt;br /&gt;
At the time of writing, $3,303,345 has been staked at a current annual percentage yield of 79.47%, according to the latest BTC20 website real-time dashboard data. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-alternative-btc20-price-ready-pump-as-buy-backs-kick-54-of-supply-staked.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Alternative BTC20 Price Ready to Pump as Buybacks Kick in and 54% of Supply Staked&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-alternative-btc20-price-ready-pump-as-buy-backs-kick-54-of-supply-staked.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122252/323471/btc20-usd-uni-dextools-io.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="281168"/></item><item><title>Coinbase's New Base Blockchain Draws $10 Million Inflows Day After Launch – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-new-base-blockchain-draws-10-million-inflows-day-after-launch-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Base, a new Ethereum layer 2 blockchain that has been developed by crypto exchange Coinbase, saw inflows worth just over $10 million on its first day after launch. &lt;br /&gt;
According to data from Dune Analytics, the $10 million were transferred to the network by over the course of 24 hours on Thursday, one day after its launch. &lt;br /&gt;
A little more than 15,000 new users joined Base on Thursday, and the day saw 40% fewer transactions than on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-new-base-blockchain-draws-10-million-inflows-day-after-launch-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase's New Base Blockchain Draws $10 Million Inflows Day After Launch – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Base</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-new-base-blockchain-draws-10-million-inflows-day-after-launch-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122249/323462/coinbase-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="708345"/></item><item><title>Venture Firm a16z Dives into ZK Technology Research with 'Jolt' and 'Lasso' Projects</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/venture-firm-a16z-dives-into-zk-technology-research-with-jolt-lasso-projects.htm</link><description>Prominent VC firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) has unveiled two open-source software projects focused on zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs. &lt;br /&gt;
These projects aim to accelerate the core technology behind ZK proofs, a promising type of cryptography that can help scale blockchains by increasing transaction throughput, reducing costs, and enhancing privacy, the firm said in a recent announcement. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/venture-firm-a16z-dives-into-zk-technology-research-with-jolt-lasso-projects.htm"&gt;Read More: Venture Firm a16z Dives into ZK Technology Research with 'Jolt' and 'Lasso' Projects&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>a16z crypto</category><category>a16z</category><category>zkSnarks</category><category>Scaling</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/venture-firm-a16z-dives-into-zk-technology-research-with-jolt-lasso-projects.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122245/323456/fugqgvnwaaq-yqs-media-lib.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="58061"/></item><item><title>Binance Labs Supports Curve DAO Token with $5 Million Investment, Plans BNB Chain Deployment</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-supports-curve-dao-token-with-5-million-investment-plans-bnb-chain-deployment.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Binance’s investment arm, Binance Labs, has announced a $5 million investment in Curve DAO Token (CRV) in a display of support for Curve and decentralized finance (DeFi) at large. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-supports-curve-dao-token-with-5-million-investment-plans-bnb-chain-deployment.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Labs Supports Curve DAO Token with $5 Million Investment, Plans BNB Chain Deployment&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-supports-curve-dao-token-with-5-million-investment-plans-bnb-chain-deployment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122243/323455/adobestock-286536391-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="124988"/></item><item><title>DCG and Barry Silbert Seek Dismissal of Lawsuit by Gemini Trust Company Over Alleged Misrepresentations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-barry-silbert-seek-dismissal-of-lawsuit-by-gemini-trust-company-over-alleged-misrepresentations.htm</link><description>Digital Currency Group (DCG) has filed a motion to dismiss Gemini's lawsuit, claiming fraud by the company and its founder, Barry Silbert, through DCG's subsidiary, Genesis, which held funds for Gemini's Earn program. &lt;br /&gt;
On July 7, Gemini and its founders, Cameron, and Tyler Winklevoss, filed a lawsuit alleging that DCG and Barry Silbert provided false information about the financial status of their lending subsidiary, Genesis....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-barry-silbert-seek-dismissal-of-lawsuit-by-gemini-trust-company-over-alleged-misrepresentations.htm"&gt;Read More: DCG and Barry Silbert Seek Dismissal of Lawsuit by Gemini Trust Company Over Alleged Misrepresentations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>DCG</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Genesis</category><category>FTX</category><category>Winklevoss</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-barry-silbert-seek-dismissal-of-lawsuit-by-gemini-trust-company-over-alleged-misrepresentations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122237/323454/digital-currency-group-1-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="66296"/></item><item><title>Argentina Becomes Latest Country to Conduct Probe Into Iris-Scanning Worldcoin's Privacy Issues</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-becomes-latest-country-to-conduct-probe-into-iris-scanning-worldcoins-privacy-issues.htm</link><description>Argentina has joined the list of jurisdictions investigating the recently launched AI-meets-crypto project Worldcoin and its privacy practices that stirred endless controversies. &lt;br /&gt;
The Argentinian Agency for Access to Public Information (AAIP) published a notice on Aug. 8, which will conduct an investigation into the processing of personal data carried out by the Worldcoin Foundation in Argentina....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-becomes-latest-country-to-conduct-probe-into-iris-scanning-worldcoins-privacy-issues.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina Becomes Latest Country to Conduct Probe Into Iris-Scanning Worldcoin's Privacy Issues&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-becomes-latest-country-to-conduct-probe-into-iris-scanning-worldcoins-privacy-issues.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122239/323447/eye-1132531-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="211900"/></item><item><title>SEC Delays Decision on Ark Invest’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Application, Calls For Public Input</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-delays-decision-ark-invests-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-calls-for-public-input.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) just delayed a decision on Ark Invest’s spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application by at least eight weeks by calling for a period of public comment. &lt;br /&gt;
The agency published an order calling for public input on Ark Invest’s Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF application, a standard move employed by the agency to buy time. &lt;br /&gt;
Ark Invest and 21Shares have been pursuing the approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF since 2021....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-delays-decision-ark-invests-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-calls-for-public-input.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Delays Decision on Ark Invest’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Application, Calls For Public Input&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>spot bitcoin ETF</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>Cathie Wood</category><category>Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF</category><category>Blackrock</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-delays-decision-ark-invests-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-calls-for-public-input.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122238/323446/adobestock-302242411-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="14976909"/></item><item><title>Worldcoin Extends WLD Reservation Access to Unverified Users</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/worldcoin-extends-wld-reservation-access-unverified-users.htm</link><description>The controversial iris-scanning crypto project Worldcoin is now allowing unverified users to reserve their Worldcoin (WLD) tokens. &lt;br /&gt;
The project, launched on July 24 following three years of development, aims to establish a comprehensive global database for human identification, setting itself apart from automated bots that may populate the digital landscape in the future....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/worldcoin-extends-wld-reservation-access-unverified-users.htm"&gt;Read More: Worldcoin Extends WLD Reservation Access to Unverified Users&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>WLD</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/worldcoin-extends-wld-reservation-access-unverified-users.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122234/323444/worldcoin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="216319"/></item><item><title>Can 1 BTC Make You a Millionaire? Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-1-btc-make-you-millionaire-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Could owning one Bitcoin (BTC) make you a millionaire? &lt;br /&gt;
According to prominent figures in the crypto space like Ark Invest’s CEO Cathie Wood and MicroStrategy executive chairman (and former CEO) Michael Saylor, yes. &lt;br /&gt;
In a report released by Ark Invest earlier this year, Cathie Wood and co. predicted that Bitcoin could hit a price of $1.48 million by 2030, a rise of 6,300% in just seven years....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/can-1-btc-make-you-millionaire-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Can 1 BTC Make You a Millionaire? Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Millionaire</category><category>MicroStrategy</category><category>Michael Saylor</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>Cathie Wood</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-1-btc-make-you-millionaire-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122231/323433/btc-4.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="138227"/></item><item><title>United States CBDC Debate Goes Mainstream As Post Malone Takes Swipe At “Digital Dollar”</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/united-states-cbdc-debate-goes-mainstream-as-post-malone-takes-swipe-at-digital-dollar.htm</link><description>American rapper, Post Malone has criticized the idea of a potential United States Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) describing it as a means of government control.  &lt;br /&gt;
The celebrity dropped his two cents on the issue on the popular podcast, the “Joe Rogan Experience” where the duo fired shots at the government highlighting the problems the digital currency will create in the country....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/united-states-cbdc-debate-goes-mainstream-as-post-malone-takes-swipe-at-digital-dollar.htm"&gt;Read More: United States CBDC Debate Goes Mainstream As Post Malone Takes Swipe At “Digital Dollar”&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Joe Rogan</category><category>Post Malone</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/united-states-cbdc-debate-goes-mainstream-as-post-malone-takes-swipe-at-digital-dollar.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122227/323419/adobestock-514809399-1-me.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="257762"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Argentine Opens Investigation Into Worldcoin, Canada is Seeking Solution to Facilitate Seizure and Storage of Crypto and NFTs, Canadians Don't Have a Reason to Adopt a CBDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-argentine-opens-investigation-into-worldcoin-canada-is-seeking-solution-to-facilitate-seizure-and-storage-of-crypto-and-nfts-canadians-dont-have-a-reason-to-adopt-a-cbdc.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-argentine-opens-investigation-into-worldcoin-canada-is-seeking-solution-to-facilitate-seizure-and-storage-of-crypto-and-nfts-canadians-dont-have-a-reason-to-adopt-a-cbdc.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Argentine Opens Investigation Into Worldcoin, Canada is Seeking Solution to Facilitate Seizure and Storage of Crypto and NFTs, Canadians Don't Have a Reason to Adopt a CBDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Police</category><category>NFT</category><category>Canada</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Bakkt</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-argentine-opens-investigation-into-worldcoin-canada-is-seeking-solution-to-facilitate-seizure-and-storage-of-crypto-and-nfts-canadians-dont-have-a-reason-to-adopt-a-cbdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122186/323367/adobestock-jason-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="817162"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – STRONGX, M87, 0x1</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-strongx-m87-0x1.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH) and the broader crypto market are little moved in wake of US Producer Price Index inflation data for July that came in ever so slightly above expectations but still fits with the narrative that the US inflation picture is quickly improving. &lt;br /&gt;
The two largest cryptocurrencies by market cap were last trading close to the $29,500 and $1,850 levels, with the crypto market’s total capitalization unchanged on the day at just $1.136 trillion....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-strongx-m87-0x1.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – STRONGX, M87, 0x1&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DEXTools</category><category>Shit Coins</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-strongx-m87-0x1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122224/323417/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Xverse Secures $5 Million in Seed Funding Round for Bitcoin Web3 Wallet, Led by Jump Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xverse-secures-5-million-seed-funding-round-for-bitcoin-web3-wallet-led-by-jump-crypto.htm</link><description>Yesterday, Hong Kong-based startup Xverse, the provider of a Bitcoin Web3 wallet that supports Ordinals and BRC-20 inscriptions, successfully raised $5 million in a seed funding round led by Jump Crypto.  &lt;br /&gt;
The company, known for driving mainstream adoption through its user-friendly interface on iOS, Android, and its Chrome extension, is set to accelerate the development of advanced features around DeFi, Stacks, and other Bitcoin scalability solutions. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xverse-secures-5-million-seed-funding-round-for-bitcoin-web3-wallet-led-by-jump-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Xverse Secures $5 Million in Seed Funding Round for Bitcoin Web3 Wallet, Led by Jump Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Xverse Wallet</category><category>Crypto Startup</category><category>Bitcoin Ordinals</category><category>Bitcoin Wallet</category><category>Bitcoin Web3 Wallet</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xverse-secures-5-million-seed-funding-round-for-bitcoin-web3-wallet-led-by-jump-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122199/323362/andre-francois-mckenzie-i.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="457924"/></item><item><title>Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether, on $USDT Fud and Tether’s Diversification into Energy | Ep. 255</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/paolo-ardoino-cto-of-tether-usdt-fud-tethers-diversification-into-energy-ep-255.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Bitfinex and Tether, talks about Tether ($USDT) FUD, Tether’s Diversification into Energy, and Tether fostering the use of P2P technology....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/paolo-ardoino-cto-of-tether-usdt-fud-tethers-diversification-into-energy-ep-255.htm"&gt;Read More: Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether, on $USDT Fud and Tether’s Diversification into Energy | Ep. 255&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/paolo-ardoino-cto-of-tether-usdt-fud-tethers-diversification-into-energy-ep-255.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122218/323410/paolo-ardoino-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="110044"/></item></channel></rss>
