<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 04:16:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Terminal 3 Raises Pre-Seed Funding for Decentralized User Data Infrastructure]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/terminal-3-raises-pre-seed-funding-for-decentralized-user-data-infrastructure</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/T3_PRESS_RELEASE_IMG_LQ_16907813316nCZVpDeAI.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/T3_PRESS_RELEASE_IMG_LQ_16907813316nCZVpDeAI.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/T3_PRESS_RELEASE_IMG_LQ_16907813316nCZVpDeAI.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:05:25 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/terminal-3-raises-pre-seed-funding-for-decentralized-user-data-infrastructure</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, Hong Kong, August 2nd, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Terminal 3, a Hong Kong-based Web3 startup, has successfully raised an oversubscribed pre-seed round to build user data infrastructure for a decentralized future. The company announced today a world-class investor group comprising 500 Global, CMCC Global, Consensys Mesh, Bixin Ventures, BlackPine, DWeb3, Hard Yaka, Bored Room Ventures, Mozaik Capital, and others.</p><p>The company aims to replace centralized data storage that deprives users of privacy and saddles enterprises with compliance and security issues and their associated costs. Terminal 3 leverages decentralized storage and zero-knowledge proofs to empower an equitable Web3, where user data is freely composable while remaining fully private and secure.</p>&ldquo;The continued growth in blockchain allows us to reimagine digital data ownership and security,&rdquo; said Gary Liu, CEO of Terminal 3. &ldquo;We believe that data should flow freely between applications to drive innovation and improve user experience, but not at the expense of personal privacy and control.&rdquo;<p>Terminal 3 was co-founded by Gary Liu alongside his partners Malcolm Ong (CPO) and Joey Liu (COO). All three were former entrepreneurs and business leaders who have built, scaled, and transformed some of the world&rsquo;s leading technology companies. The co-founders previously worked together at the South China Morning Post, where they led the historic newspaper&rsquo;s successful digital transformation. Gary was the Post&rsquo;s CEO, while Malcolm and Joey were SVP of Product and Head of Strategy respectively.</p><p>Malcolm was also the Co-founder and CTO of Skillshare, the world&rsquo;s largest online learning community for creativity, while Gary and Joey co-founded Artifact Labs, a Web3 startup backed by Blue Pool Capital and Animoca Brands that is preserving historical assets on the blockchain. Gary is also the Founding Chair of Web3 Harbour, an association in Hong Kong serving Web3 builders, investors, users, and leaders.</p>&ldquo;I believe Gary, Malcolm, and Joey are perfectly suited to address data privacy problems that plague the internet,&rdquo; said Vishal Harnal, Managing Partner at 500 Global. &ldquo;Their mix of consumer startup success and expertise in enterprise technology could help bridge a critical gap between the old world of centralized data and the new world of decentralized identity.&rdquo;<p>Growing Need for Alternative Data Infrastructure</p><p>Over the past five years, new regulations on data privacy have created a stringent environment for the storage and use of personal information worldwide. Led by Europe&rsquo;s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and China&rsquo;s Personal Information Protection Law (PIPL), global regulators and lawmakers are increasingly holding enterprises accountable for the protection of individual privacy. This trend is set to continue with the approval of the Digital Market Act in Europe and upcoming GDPR-inspired laws in the United States and around the world.</p><p>US and UK corporations have spent over US$9 billion on GDPR compliance since 2018, with those investing incurring average costs of US$1 million annually. However, over 40% of companies still lack any budget for such compliance while GDPR fines continue to grow, with Meta alone sustaining over US$2.3 billion in penalties.&nbsp;</p><p>Data security is also a costly enterprise concern as data breaches accelerate in frequency. Global spending on data security and risk management products is projected to exceed US$188 billion in 2023. However, in a world where 90% of companies rely on multi-cloud environments, data privacy and security issues will grow regardless of investment.</p><p>Blockchain technology is increasingly viewed by corporate executives as a solution for user data privacy and security. In a recent survey of US Fortune 500 companies, Coinbase found that 51% of enterprises that use or plan to use blockchain employ the technology for &lsquo;Data Collection and Management&rsquo;.</p>&ldquo;Terminal 3 is a compelling alternative to the non-compliant and unsecured data infrastructure that enterprises rely on today,&rdquo; said Shawn Cheng, Partner at Consensys Mesh. &ldquo;Data regulations and security laws are becoming more stringent around the world, and companies are finally realizing that self-sovereign data is a great solution for both users and enterprises. We are excited to be involved in this important project.&rdquo;&nbsp;&ldquo;Scaling Web3 will require the re-invention of core enterprise technologies,&rdquo; added Gary Liu. &ldquo;Terminal 3 is building solutions that serve both corporations and individuals, to enable this critical shift in our digital world.&rdquo;<p>About Terminal 3</p><p>Terminal 3 is a Hong Kong-based Web3 startup building user data infrastructure for a decentralized future. The company&rsquo;s solutions are an alternative to centralized data storage that deprives users of privacy and saddles enterprises with compliance and security concerns. Terminal 3 leverages decentralized storage and zero-knowledge proofs to empower an equitable Web3 where user data is freely composable while remaining fully private and secure. The company&rsquo;s founders are successful corporate executives and entrepreneurs, who have built, scaled, and transformed some of the world&rsquo;s most important companies. Terminal 3 is also backed by world-class investors including 500 Global, CMCC Global, Consensys Mesh, Bixin Ventures, BlackPine, DWeb3, Hard Yaka, and Bored Room Ventures.</p><p>For more information about Terminal 3, please visit Terminal 3's: Official Website | Twitter | LinkedIn</p>ContactJoey LiuTerminal 3joey@terminal3.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, Hong Kong, August 2nd, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Terminal 3, a Hong Kong-based Web3 startup, has successfully raised an oversubscribed pre-seed round to build user data infrastructure for a decentralized future. The company announced today a world-class investor group comprising 500 Global, CMCC Global, Consensys Mesh, Bixin Ventures, BlackPine, DWeb3, Hard Yaka, Bored Room Ventures, Mozaik Capital, and others.</p><p>The company aims to replace centralized data storage that deprives users of privacy and saddles enterprises with compliance and security issues and their associated costs. Terminal 3 leverages decentralized storage and zero-knowledge proofs to empower an equitable Web3, where user data is freely composable while remaining fully private and secure.</p>&ldquo;The continued growth in blockchain allows us to reimagine digital data ownership and security,&rdquo; said Gary Liu, CEO of Terminal 3. &ldquo;We believe that data should flow freely between applications to drive innovation and improve user experience, but not at the expense of personal privacy and control.&rdquo;<p>Terminal 3 was co-founded by Gary Liu alongside his partners Malcolm Ong (CPO) and Joey Liu (COO). All three were former entrepreneurs and business leaders who have built, scaled, and transformed some of the world&rsquo;s leading technology companies. The co-founders previously worked together at the South China Morning Post, where they led the historic newspaper&rsquo;s successful digital transformation. Gary was the Post&rsquo;s CEO, while Malcolm and Joey were SVP of Product and Head of Strategy respectively.</p><p>Malcolm was also the Co-founder and CTO of Skillshare, the world&rsquo;s largest online learning community for creativity, while Gary and Joey co-founded Artifact Labs, a Web3 startup backed by Blue Pool Capital and Animoca Brands that is preserving historical assets on the blockchain. Gary is also the Founding Chair of Web3 Harbour, an association in Hong Kong serving Web3 builders, investors, users, and leaders.</p>&ldquo;I believe Gary, Malcolm, and Joey are perfectly suited to address data privacy problems that plague the internet,&rdquo; said Vishal Harnal, Managing Partner at 500 Global. &ldquo;Their mix of consumer startup success and expertise in enterprise technology could help bridge a critical gap between the old world of centralized data and the new world of decentralized identity.&rdquo;<p>Growing Need for Alternative Data Infrastructure</p><p>Over the past five years, new regulations on data privacy have created a stringent environment for the storage and use of personal information worldwide. Led by Europe&rsquo;s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and China&rsquo;s Personal Information Protection Law (PIPL), global regulators and lawmakers are increasingly holding enterprises accountable for the protection of individual privacy. This trend is set to continue with the approval of the Digital Market Act in Europe and upcoming GDPR-inspired laws in the United States and around the world.</p><p>US and UK corporations have spent over US$9 billion on GDPR compliance since 2018, with those investing incurring average costs of US$1 million annually. However, over 40% of companies still lack any budget for such compliance while GDPR fines continue to grow, with Meta alone sustaining over US$2.3 billion in penalties.&nbsp;</p><p>Data security is also a costly enterprise concern as data breaches accelerate in frequency. Global spending on data security and risk management products is projected to exceed US$188 billion in 2023. However, in a world where 90% of companies rely on multi-cloud environments, data privacy and security issues will grow regardless of investment.</p><p>Blockchain technology is increasingly viewed by corporate executives as a solution for user data privacy and security. In a recent survey of US Fortune 500 companies, Coinbase found that 51% of enterprises that use or plan to use blockchain employ the technology for &lsquo;Data Collection and Management&rsquo;.</p>&ldquo;Terminal 3 is a compelling alternative to the non-compliant and unsecured data infrastructure that enterprises rely on today,&rdquo; said Shawn Cheng, Partner at Consensys Mesh. &ldquo;Data regulations and security laws are becoming more stringent around the world, and companies are finally realizing that self-sovereign data is a great solution for both users and enterprises. We are excited to be involved in this important project.&rdquo;&nbsp;&ldquo;Scaling Web3 will require the re-invention of core enterprise technologies,&rdquo; added Gary Liu. &ldquo;Terminal 3 is building solutions that serve both corporations and individuals, to enable this critical shift in our digital world.&rdquo;<p>About Terminal 3</p><p>Terminal 3 is a Hong Kong-based Web3 startup building user data infrastructure for a decentralized future. The company&rsquo;s solutions are an alternative to centralized data storage that deprives users of privacy and saddles enterprises with compliance and security concerns. Terminal 3 leverages decentralized storage and zero-knowledge proofs to empower an equitable Web3 where user data is freely composable while remaining fully private and secure. The company&rsquo;s founders are successful corporate executives and entrepreneurs, who have built, scaled, and transformed some of the world&rsquo;s most important companies. Terminal 3 is also backed by world-class investors including 500 Global, CMCC Global, Consensys Mesh, Bixin Ventures, BlackPine, DWeb3, Hard Yaka, and Bored Room Ventures.</p><p>For more information about Terminal 3, please visit Terminal 3's: Official Website | Twitter | LinkedIn</p>ContactJoey LiuTerminal 3joey@terminal3.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Terraform Labs vs SEC: Judge Rejects Ripple’s Case Arguments]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/terraform-labs-vs-sec-judge-rejects-ripples-case-arguments</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/terra-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/terra-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/terra-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/terraform-labs-vs-sec-judge-rejects-ripples-case-arguments</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Judge Rakoff has denied a motion to dismiss the Terraform Labs lawsuit against the SEC and expressed disagreement with the recent ruling in Ripple&rsquo;s case.</p>
Terraform Labs Fails to Follow the Road taken by Ripple against SEC
<p>Last month, Ripple Labs celebrated its partial but remarkable victory in the 3-year-long battle against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Judge Analisa Torres partially ruled in favor of Ripple, stating that XRP should not be considered a security in regard to programmatic sales and &ldquo;other distributions&rdquo; (although it is considered a security in regard to institutional sales).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Facing a similar lawsuit, another crypto company Terraform Labs tried to take advantage of the Ripple&rsquo;s case ruling and filed a motion for the dismissal of the suit using the Ripple&rsquo;s victory as an argument.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, Judge Jed Rakoff of the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York denied the motion and firmly confirmed that the civil case against Terraform and its founder Do Kwon would move forward.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Moreover, Judge Rakoff rejected to consider the categorization of sales used in the Ripple case, thus criticizing the approach taken by Judge Torres:</p>

<p>"It may also be mentioned that the Court declines to draw a distinction between these coins based on their manner of sale, such that coins sold directly to institutional investors are considered securities and those sold through secondary market transactions to retail investors are not. In doing so, the Court rejects the approach recently adopted by another judge of this District in a similar case," wrote Judge Rakoff.</p>

What Does It Mean for Ripple?&nbsp;
<p>Even though Judge Rakoff&rsquo;s criticism doesn&rsquo;t overturn Judge Torres&rsquo; decision in the Ripple case, it might increase the chances of the SEC filing an appeal.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Last week, a law expert James Murphy outlined four major paths that the SEC could take next. He believes that the SEC is much more likely to file a request for an interlocutory appeal than settle.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ripple CTO David Schwart reacted to Judge Rakoff&rsquo;s ruling on his Twitter observing that the reasoning seems to be unusual and doesn&rsquo;t apply to typical cryptocurrencies. Schwart then suggested the worst-case and the best-case future scenarios regarding Ripple Labs:&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;1) The worst case for fans of the decision in Ripple: The court is saying it disagrees with the Ripple decision because it applies additional tests that are not part of the Howey test and so it won't apply/follow the ruling here.</p>
<p>2) The best case for fans of the decision in Ripple: The court is saying it disagrees with the argument that it should follow the Ripple decision because the reasoning relied on in Ripple makes sense not because it directly implicates the Howey factors but because it indirectly implicates them due to facts not applicable in this case.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Judge Rakoff has denied a motion to dismiss the Terraform Labs lawsuit against the SEC and expressed disagreement with the recent ruling in Ripple&rsquo;s case.</p>
Terraform Labs Fails to Follow the Road taken by Ripple against SEC
<p>Last month, Ripple Labs celebrated its partial but remarkable victory in the 3-year-long battle against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Judge Analisa Torres partially ruled in favor of Ripple, stating that XRP should not be considered a security in regard to programmatic sales and &ldquo;other distributions&rdquo; (although it is considered a security in regard to institutional sales).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Facing a similar lawsuit, another crypto company Terraform Labs tried to take advantage of the Ripple&rsquo;s case ruling and filed a motion for the dismissal of the suit using the Ripple&rsquo;s victory as an argument.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, Judge Jed Rakoff of the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York denied the motion and firmly confirmed that the civil case against Terraform and its founder Do Kwon would move forward.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Moreover, Judge Rakoff rejected to consider the categorization of sales used in the Ripple case, thus criticizing the approach taken by Judge Torres:</p>

<p>"It may also be mentioned that the Court declines to draw a distinction between these coins based on their manner of sale, such that coins sold directly to institutional investors are considered securities and those sold through secondary market transactions to retail investors are not. In doing so, the Court rejects the approach recently adopted by another judge of this District in a similar case," wrote Judge Rakoff.</p>

What Does It Mean for Ripple?&nbsp;
<p>Even though Judge Rakoff&rsquo;s criticism doesn&rsquo;t overturn Judge Torres&rsquo; decision in the Ripple case, it might increase the chances of the SEC filing an appeal.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Last week, a law expert James Murphy outlined four major paths that the SEC could take next. He believes that the SEC is much more likely to file a request for an interlocutory appeal than settle.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ripple CTO David Schwart reacted to Judge Rakoff&rsquo;s ruling on his Twitter observing that the reasoning seems to be unusual and doesn&rsquo;t apply to typical cryptocurrencies. Schwart then suggested the worst-case and the best-case future scenarios regarding Ripple Labs:&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;1) The worst case for fans of the decision in Ripple: The court is saying it disagrees with the Ripple decision because it applies additional tests that are not part of the Howey test and so it won't apply/follow the ruling here.</p>
<p>2) The best case for fans of the decision in Ripple: The court is saying it disagrees with the argument that it should follow the Ripple decision because the reasoning relied on in Ripple makes sense not because it directly implicates the Howey factors but because it indirectly implicates them due to facts not applicable in this case.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[FTX Exchange Might Relaunch, FTT Jumps in Value]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/ftx-exchange-might-relaunch-ftt-jumps-in-value</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1920-3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1920-3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-1920-3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/ftx-exchange-might-relaunch-ftt-jumps-in-value</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Defunct crypto exchange FTX announced its plans for rebooting the platform and paying back its creditors; the FTT token reacted by a sudden 15% surge in price.</p>
The Restart of the FTX Offshore Exchange Will Depend on its Creditors
<p>On July 31, 2023, the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX Trading Ltd. filed a Draft Plan of Reorganization and a Term Sheet, confirming the rumors about a possible relaunch of the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the plan, FTX divided its claimants into different categories: FTX.com offshore exchange customers, referred to as &ldquo;dotcom customers&rdquo;; the U.S. exchange customers; customers of the non-fungible token (NFT) exchange; general unsecured claims; secured claims; and subordinated claims.</p>
<p>The international &ldquo;dotcom&rdquo; users have the option to pool their assets and create a &ldquo;rebooted&rdquo; offshore FTX exchange, not available in the US. In this case, these customers are entitled to get a stake in the new platform instead of receiving a cash payout:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Rather than all cash, the Debtors may determine that the Offshore Exchange Company remit non-cash consideration to the Dotcom Customer Pool in the form of equity securities, tokens or other interests in the Offshore Exchange Company, or rights to invest in such equity securities, tokens or other interests.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The proposal stated that FTX administrators will use &ldquo;the waterfall approach&rdquo; to determine the priority of claims. This means that each class will receive a pro-rata payout from the pool of remaining assets after the payout to the preceding class is finished.</p>
What about FTT and its Holders?
<p>In response to the news, the FTX token jumped by about 15% reaching the mark of $1.55, even though it pulled back to $1.4 shortly after.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the plan clarified that the FTT holders won&rsquo;t receive any compensation for their losses as their claims are to be canceled and extinguished:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Claims by holders of FTT (whether or not held on any FTX exchange), preferred stock and equity investors in the Debtors and related claims. All these claims and interests will be canceled and extinguished as of the Effective Date and holders will not receive any distribution.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Moreover, there are rumors that the FTX token will be eliminated altogether, and the claimants will receive their payout in USD as of the date of bankruptcy. It&rsquo;s also worth mentioning that FTT was previously labeled an unregistered security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
The FTX Drama Continues
<p>The defunct exchange still struggles to deal with other consequences of its sudden fall in November, 2022. Earlier today, it has been announced that FTX almost reached a resolution in its dispute with another bankrupt crypto company Genesis.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, ex-CEO of FTX Sam Bankman-Fried is still facing seven charges related to wire fraud, securities fraud, and money laundering, partly for misappropriating the FTX customer funds. As of recent developments, Bankman-Fried agreed to a gag order while waiting for an update on his bail status.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Defunct crypto exchange FTX announced its plans for rebooting the platform and paying back its creditors; the FTT token reacted by a sudden 15% surge in price.</p>
The Restart of the FTX Offshore Exchange Will Depend on its Creditors
<p>On July 31, 2023, the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX Trading Ltd. filed a Draft Plan of Reorganization and a Term Sheet, confirming the rumors about a possible relaunch of the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the plan, FTX divided its claimants into different categories: FTX.com offshore exchange customers, referred to as &ldquo;dotcom customers&rdquo;; the U.S. exchange customers; customers of the non-fungible token (NFT) exchange; general unsecured claims; secured claims; and subordinated claims.</p>
<p>The international &ldquo;dotcom&rdquo; users have the option to pool their assets and create a &ldquo;rebooted&rdquo; offshore FTX exchange, not available in the US. In this case, these customers are entitled to get a stake in the new platform instead of receiving a cash payout:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Rather than all cash, the Debtors may determine that the Offshore Exchange Company remit non-cash consideration to the Dotcom Customer Pool in the form of equity securities, tokens or other interests in the Offshore Exchange Company, or rights to invest in such equity securities, tokens or other interests.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The proposal stated that FTX administrators will use &ldquo;the waterfall approach&rdquo; to determine the priority of claims. This means that each class will receive a pro-rata payout from the pool of remaining assets after the payout to the preceding class is finished.</p>
What about FTT and its Holders?
<p>In response to the news, the FTX token jumped by about 15% reaching the mark of $1.55, even though it pulled back to $1.4 shortly after.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the plan clarified that the FTT holders won&rsquo;t receive any compensation for their losses as their claims are to be canceled and extinguished:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Claims by holders of FTT (whether or not held on any FTX exchange), preferred stock and equity investors in the Debtors and related claims. All these claims and interests will be canceled and extinguished as of the Effective Date and holders will not receive any distribution.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Moreover, there are rumors that the FTX token will be eliminated altogether, and the claimants will receive their payout in USD as of the date of bankruptcy. It&rsquo;s also worth mentioning that FTT was previously labeled an unregistered security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
The FTX Drama Continues
<p>The defunct exchange still struggles to deal with other consequences of its sudden fall in November, 2022. Earlier today, it has been announced that FTX almost reached a resolution in its dispute with another bankrupt crypto company Genesis.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, ex-CEO of FTX Sam Bankman-Fried is still facing seven charges related to wire fraud, securities fraud, and money laundering, partly for misappropriating the FTX customer funds. As of recent developments, Bankman-Fried agreed to a gag order while waiting for an update on his bail status.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Hit Below 28672 - 2 August 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-hit-below-28672-2-august-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-hit-below-28672-2-august-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below the 28672:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 2 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from bearish momentum early in the Asian session as the pair depreciated sharply to the 28477 level after Stops were elected below the 29089.49 and 28775.19 levels, downside price objectives associated with selling pressure around the 29851.28 area.&nbsp; Additional Stops were elected below the 28999, 28874, and 28672 areas during the acute selloff, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 29526 and 29344 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 27979, 27409, 27246, and 26501 levels.&nbsp; Below the market, additional downside price objectives include the 28213, 28137, 27757, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Traders are monitoring the recent depreciating range from 31862.21 to 28850 with upside retracement levels around the 30000, 30356, 30711, 31151, and 31217 areas.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29268.97 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29214.97.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below the 28672:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 2 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from bearish momentum early in the Asian session as the pair depreciated sharply to the 28477 level after Stops were elected below the 29089.49 and 28775.19 levels, downside price objectives associated with selling pressure around the 29851.28 area.&nbsp; Additional Stops were elected below the 28999, 28874, and 28672 areas during the acute selloff, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 29526 and 29344 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 27979, 27409, 27246, and 26501 levels.&nbsp; Below the market, additional downside price objectives include the 28213, 28137, 27757, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Traders are monitoring the recent depreciating range from 31862.21 to 28850 with upside retracement levels around the 30000, 30356, 30711, 31151, and 31217 areas.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29268.97 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29214.97.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price Prediction – Maker (MKR) and Borroe ($ROE) Surge]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-btc-price-prediction-maker-mkr-and-borroe-roe-surge</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-154434.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-154434.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-154434.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-btc-price-prediction-maker-mkr-and-borroe-roe-surge</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">According to experts, Bitcoin (BTC) may surge in early August 2023, thanks to the options expiry exercise. Also, Maker (MKR) recorded a massive price surge in July, and analysts are monitoring to see if this bullish momentum will hold through Q3 2023. On the other hand, Borroe ($ROE) is ready to disrupt decentralized fundraising, and the platform has already sold all of the Borroe ($ROE) tokens listed for its Beta presale stage.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY $ROE TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) May Record a Price Surge in Late July 2023
<p class="s7">Today, July 28, 2023, $2 billion worth of Bitcoin (BTC) options will expire. Historically, this monthly Bitcoin (BTC) options expiry is always associated with bullish volatility for Bitcoin (BTC). This time we could see Bitcoin&rsquo;s (BTC) support level rise from $29,000 to $29,500. According to experts, the effects of Bitcoin (BTC) options expiry often take a few days to consolidate, and we may see Bitcoin (BTC) rise to $31,000 in the first few days of August 2023.</p>
<p class="s7">Also, requests for Bitcoin (BTC) Spot ETFs could propel Bitcoin (BTC) to a greater price surge. If the US SEC approves the requests from Blackrock and Fidelity, Bitcoin (BTC) should break through its 2023 high. Interestingly, Bitcoin (BTC) hit this $31,657 high on July 13 after a US federal court ruling dealt a blow to the SEC&rsquo;s crypto regulatory efforts. Bitcoin (BTC) turned bearish shortly after this price surge, and the token is currently trading at $29,180 on July 28.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY $ROE TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Maker (MKR) Ecosystem Developments Trigger Massive Price Surge
<p class="s7">In May 2023, MakerDAO released a five-phase roadmap tagged &lsquo;Endgame.&rsquo; According to Maker (MKR) developers, this upgrade will include a rebrand, a new blockchain, and the introduction of two new tokens. During this period, Rune Christensen (co-founder of Maker DAO) also revealed that Maker (MKR) users could initiate hard forks in response to power attacks or abuse.</p>
<p class="s7">These ecosystem developments and the Maker (MKR) token burn led to a massive price surge last month. Maker (MKR) launched a Smart Burn Engine program that recently cleaned more than $230,000 worth of Maker (MKR) tokens from the market.</p>
<p class="s7">As a result, we saw Maker (MKR) rise from $672 on June 28 to a current price of $1,167 on July 28. The token gained 72.84% this last month, and only a few tokens, like XRP and Borroe ($ROE), can match this surge in Q3 2023. &nbsp;</p>
Investors Are Betting on Borroe ($ROE) in August 2023, Token Set to Gain 300% 
<p class="s7">Borroe ($ROE) is the world&rsquo;s first web3 blockchain invoice discounting NFT marketplace. As a decentralized funding platform, Borroe ($ROE) helps web3 participants and content creators generate instant cash by selling future verifiable income. Borroe ($ROE) users can mint their subscriptions, royalties, digital payments, and invoices into NFTs. Afterwards, they sell these NFTs at discounted prices to supportive community members. &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Currently, Borroe ($ROE) is moving from its Beta stage to Stage 1 of its presale, as it has sold more than 25 million tokens so far. Borroe ($ROE) has surged by 25%, and it is selling at $0.0125. After all presale stages, Borroe ($ROE) will hit the mainstream crypto and sell for $0.0400. So if you invest in Borroe ($ROE) now, you&rsquo;ll see a 220% rise in the value of your tokens in a few weeks.</p>
Learn more about the Borroe ($ROE) presale here:
<p class="s12">Buy Presale: https://borroe.finance/ &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://borroe.finance/ &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Telegram: https://t.me/borroe_finance &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Borroe_Finance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">According to experts, Bitcoin (BTC) may surge in early August 2023, thanks to the options expiry exercise. Also, Maker (MKR) recorded a massive price surge in July, and analysts are monitoring to see if this bullish momentum will hold through Q3 2023. On the other hand, Borroe ($ROE) is ready to disrupt decentralized fundraising, and the platform has already sold all of the Borroe ($ROE) tokens listed for its Beta presale stage.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY $ROE TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) May Record a Price Surge in Late July 2023
<p class="s7">Today, July 28, 2023, $2 billion worth of Bitcoin (BTC) options will expire. Historically, this monthly Bitcoin (BTC) options expiry is always associated with bullish volatility for Bitcoin (BTC). This time we could see Bitcoin&rsquo;s (BTC) support level rise from $29,000 to $29,500. According to experts, the effects of Bitcoin (BTC) options expiry often take a few days to consolidate, and we may see Bitcoin (BTC) rise to $31,000 in the first few days of August 2023.</p>
<p class="s7">Also, requests for Bitcoin (BTC) Spot ETFs could propel Bitcoin (BTC) to a greater price surge. If the US SEC approves the requests from Blackrock and Fidelity, Bitcoin (BTC) should break through its 2023 high. Interestingly, Bitcoin (BTC) hit this $31,657 high on July 13 after a US federal court ruling dealt a blow to the SEC&rsquo;s crypto regulatory efforts. Bitcoin (BTC) turned bearish shortly after this price surge, and the token is currently trading at $29,180 on July 28.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY $ROE TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Maker (MKR) Ecosystem Developments Trigger Massive Price Surge
<p class="s7">In May 2023, MakerDAO released a five-phase roadmap tagged &lsquo;Endgame.&rsquo; According to Maker (MKR) developers, this upgrade will include a rebrand, a new blockchain, and the introduction of two new tokens. During this period, Rune Christensen (co-founder of Maker DAO) also revealed that Maker (MKR) users could initiate hard forks in response to power attacks or abuse.</p>
<p class="s7">These ecosystem developments and the Maker (MKR) token burn led to a massive price surge last month. Maker (MKR) launched a Smart Burn Engine program that recently cleaned more than $230,000 worth of Maker (MKR) tokens from the market.</p>
<p class="s7">As a result, we saw Maker (MKR) rise from $672 on June 28 to a current price of $1,167 on July 28. The token gained 72.84% this last month, and only a few tokens, like XRP and Borroe ($ROE), can match this surge in Q3 2023. &nbsp;</p>
Investors Are Betting on Borroe ($ROE) in August 2023, Token Set to Gain 300% 
<p class="s7">Borroe ($ROE) is the world&rsquo;s first web3 blockchain invoice discounting NFT marketplace. As a decentralized funding platform, Borroe ($ROE) helps web3 participants and content creators generate instant cash by selling future verifiable income. Borroe ($ROE) users can mint their subscriptions, royalties, digital payments, and invoices into NFTs. Afterwards, they sell these NFTs at discounted prices to supportive community members. &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Currently, Borroe ($ROE) is moving from its Beta stage to Stage 1 of its presale, as it has sold more than 25 million tokens so far. Borroe ($ROE) has surged by 25%, and it is selling at $0.0125. After all presale stages, Borroe ($ROE) will hit the mainstream crypto and sell for $0.0400. So if you invest in Borroe ($ROE) now, you&rsquo;ll see a 220% rise in the value of your tokens in a few weeks.</p>
Learn more about the Borroe ($ROE) presale here:
<p class="s12">Buy Presale: https://borroe.finance/ &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://borroe.finance/ &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Telegram: https://t.me/borroe_finance &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Borroe_Finance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Jia Expands Credit Solution on Huma to Foster Growth and Opportunity in Emerging Markets]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/jia-expands-credit-solution-on-huma-to-foster-growth-and-opportunity-in-emerging-markets</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Huma-Jia_PR_1690809946C3qisAa1RX.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Huma-Jia_PR_1690809946C3qisAa1RX.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Huma-Jia_PR_1690809946C3qisAa1RX.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:00:42 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/jia-expands-credit-solution-on-huma-to-foster-growth-and-opportunity-in-emerging-markets</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco, California, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Addressing a $5 trillion global credit gap in emerging markets, Jia, which connects capital to small businesses in every corner of the world, scales up its credit solution on Huma, which builds infrastructure for real-world lending.</p><p>Two months after launching its credit solution on the Huma platform, Jia is expanding its reach to accommodate the robust demand for credit in emerging markets, along with an increase in liquidity supply.</p>&ldquo;We are delighted to facilitate Jia's innovative approach to lending. Our platform's infrastructure is designed to foster next generation lending solutions, and together we're showcasing what fair and transparent lending looks like, making a tangible difference in people's lives." says Erbil Karaman, CEO and Co-founder of Huma Finance.<p>There is a $5 trillion credit gap in emerging markets, with many individuals lacking access to formal credit and the small business financing ($500-$2,000) they need, halting their day-to-day business interactions and ability to serve their communities.</p><p>By utilizing Huma's DeFi infrastructure, Jia can expedite transactions with fairness and transparency, creating opportunities for entrepreneurs to grow their businesses.&nbsp;</p><p>Jia is dedicated to serving small businesses in emerging markets. The company launched a $100,000 pool on Huma in May, which it has used to originate loans to more than 500 borrowers in Kenya and the Philippines.&nbsp;</p><p>Within the next six months, Jia is planning to scale up their credit solution even more to $500k, an increase of 400%. This growth projection sets the tone for a further 5x increase in a year's time given the borrower and lender demand.</p><p>Jia's pool reached full subscription less than 24 hours after launching, signaling a strong interest from accredited investors interested in this asset class.&nbsp;</p><p>The capital raised has already created transformative change in these small businesses.</p><p>With stories of borrowers like Dr. Elishaphan Obuya, a medical practitioner from Kisumu, Kenya, Jia&rsquo;s impact becomes tangible. Dr. Obuya, the founder of Shepher Lifecare, offers a range of medical services to hundreds of patients monthly. With Jia&rsquo;s credit solution, facilitated in partnership with Ilara Health, Dr. Obuya borrowed 142,800 KES ($1,012) to maintain a crucial supply of lifesaving medicines in his clinic.</p><p>Another inspiring story comes from Kristel Erestingcol in Manila, Philippines. Kristel operates a sari-sari store, serving her community with essential food items and school supplies. With a Jia loan of PHP 10,000 ($182), her second from the platform, Kristel has not only been able to buy more inventory in bulk at lower prices, but also expand her store's offering into new product lines including school uniforms and clothing.&nbsp;</p>"Our mission is to drive economic growth in emerging markets by breaking down financial barriers. The extension of our credit solution on Huma is a testament to the potential we see in these markets," says Zach Marks, CEO and Co-founder of Jia.<p>Jia's expansion on the Huma platform is a strong signal of how DeFi can move away from speculative use cases, and allow entrepreneurs and small businesses in emerging markets to access digital financial resources.&nbsp;</p><p>Together, Jia and Huma are working on a roadmap to roll out features for a seamless real-world lending experience.</p><p>With the financial ecosystem becoming increasingly borderless and inclusive, the realization of global financial freedom seems within grasp.</p><p>About Jia</p><p>Jia is expanding financial freedom across the globe. Jia provides blockchain-based financing to small businesses, then rewards borrowers who repay with ownership, enabling them to create wealth and prosperity for themselves and their communities. Learn more https://www.jia.xyz/.</p><p>About Huma Finance</p><p> Huma Finance builds the infrastructure powering an ecosystem for real-world lending solutions. With a mission to make the crypto industry more accessible and supportive of practical use cases, Huma Finance enables borrowing against cash flows and receivables, opening up new possibilities for individuals and businesses around the world. Learn more https://huma.finance/.</p>ContactCommunications &amp; PRMia GrodskyHuma Financemcgrodsky@gmail.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco, California, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Addressing a $5 trillion global credit gap in emerging markets, Jia, which connects capital to small businesses in every corner of the world, scales up its credit solution on Huma, which builds infrastructure for real-world lending.</p><p>Two months after launching its credit solution on the Huma platform, Jia is expanding its reach to accommodate the robust demand for credit in emerging markets, along with an increase in liquidity supply.</p>&ldquo;We are delighted to facilitate Jia's innovative approach to lending. Our platform's infrastructure is designed to foster next generation lending solutions, and together we're showcasing what fair and transparent lending looks like, making a tangible difference in people's lives." says Erbil Karaman, CEO and Co-founder of Huma Finance.<p>There is a $5 trillion credit gap in emerging markets, with many individuals lacking access to formal credit and the small business financing ($500-$2,000) they need, halting their day-to-day business interactions and ability to serve their communities.</p><p>By utilizing Huma's DeFi infrastructure, Jia can expedite transactions with fairness and transparency, creating opportunities for entrepreneurs to grow their businesses.&nbsp;</p><p>Jia is dedicated to serving small businesses in emerging markets. The company launched a $100,000 pool on Huma in May, which it has used to originate loans to more than 500 borrowers in Kenya and the Philippines.&nbsp;</p><p>Within the next six months, Jia is planning to scale up their credit solution even more to $500k, an increase of 400%. This growth projection sets the tone for a further 5x increase in a year's time given the borrower and lender demand.</p><p>Jia's pool reached full subscription less than 24 hours after launching, signaling a strong interest from accredited investors interested in this asset class.&nbsp;</p><p>The capital raised has already created transformative change in these small businesses.</p><p>With stories of borrowers like Dr. Elishaphan Obuya, a medical practitioner from Kisumu, Kenya, Jia&rsquo;s impact becomes tangible. Dr. Obuya, the founder of Shepher Lifecare, offers a range of medical services to hundreds of patients monthly. With Jia&rsquo;s credit solution, facilitated in partnership with Ilara Health, Dr. Obuya borrowed 142,800 KES ($1,012) to maintain a crucial supply of lifesaving medicines in his clinic.</p><p>Another inspiring story comes from Kristel Erestingcol in Manila, Philippines. Kristel operates a sari-sari store, serving her community with essential food items and school supplies. With a Jia loan of PHP 10,000 ($182), her second from the platform, Kristel has not only been able to buy more inventory in bulk at lower prices, but also expand her store's offering into new product lines including school uniforms and clothing.&nbsp;</p>"Our mission is to drive economic growth in emerging markets by breaking down financial barriers. The extension of our credit solution on Huma is a testament to the potential we see in these markets," says Zach Marks, CEO and Co-founder of Jia.<p>Jia's expansion on the Huma platform is a strong signal of how DeFi can move away from speculative use cases, and allow entrepreneurs and small businesses in emerging markets to access digital financial resources.&nbsp;</p><p>Together, Jia and Huma are working on a roadmap to roll out features for a seamless real-world lending experience.</p><p>With the financial ecosystem becoming increasingly borderless and inclusive, the realization of global financial freedom seems within grasp.</p><p>About Jia</p><p>Jia is expanding financial freedom across the globe. Jia provides blockchain-based financing to small businesses, then rewards borrowers who repay with ownership, enabling them to create wealth and prosperity for themselves and their communities. Learn more https://www.jia.xyz/.</p><p>About Huma Finance</p><p> Huma Finance builds the infrastructure powering an ecosystem for real-world lending solutions. With a mission to make the crypto industry more accessible and supportive of practical use cases, Huma Finance enables borrowing against cash flows and receivables, opening up new possibilities for individuals and businesses around the world. Learn more https://huma.finance/.</p>ContactCommunications &amp; PRMia GrodskyHuma Financemcgrodsky@gmail.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Yuga Labs To Acquire Roar Studios For Otherside Metaverse]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/yuga-labs-to-acquire-roar-studios-for-otherside-metaverse</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yuga-labs-ordinals-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yuga-labs-ordinals-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yuga-labs-ordinals-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/yuga-labs-to-acquire-roar-studios-for-otherside-metaverse</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Leading web3 company Yuga Labs has announced its agreement to acquire tech innovator Roar Studios to bolster its ambitions Otherside project.&nbsp;</p>
Adopting Roar&rsquo;s Tech For Otherside
<p>The announcement was made on July 31 by Yuga Labs, home of popular NFT collections like Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), CryptoPunks, Meebits, and 10KTF. On the other end of the deal is tech innovator Roar Studios, working at the intersection of gaming, social media, and the metaverse. As per the announcement, Yuga Labs is seeking to add more value to its Otherside project, which is being designed to be an interoperable metaverse that will revolutionize virtual experiences.</p>
Roar CEO In Charge Of Otherside
<p>Following the acquisition, Roar Studio&rsquo;s CEO, Eric Reid, will take on the role of General Manager of Otherside. With over two decades of experience in building teams and creating and distributing film, television, and music content for global audiences, including work on film franchises like UNDERWORLD, Reid brings valuable expertise to lead the development and production of the Otherside platform.</p>
<p>Addressing the acquisition by Yuga Labs, Reid stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Our team's mission is to empower players to create and be social in a community-driven, open media experience, so our work fundamentally aligns with Yuga's larger web3 metaverse strategy. When Daniel and Mike Seavers opened the door for us to contribute to Yuga's paradigm-shifting approach to content and immersive experiences, we jumped at the opportunity."</p>

More about Roar&nbsp;
<p>Roar Studios has been making waves with its creation, ROAR, an immersive media platform where artists and fans can connect, collaborate, and compete in real time from anywhere. The platform combines cutting-edge proprietary technology with established MMO games and platform systems, resulting in an entirely new product category&mdash;an experiential, semi-autonomous music and entertainment world driven by individual content creators and community consensus.</p>
Yuga's Expansive Vision and Roar's Complementary Expertise
<p>Otherside, one of the most ambitious interactive metaverse projects to date, is designed with community participation in mind, rejecting the concept of traditional walled gardens in gaming spaces. The project's success is evidenced by its $450M seed funding round in March 2022, valuing Yuga Labs at $4B.</p>
<p>The acquisition of Roar Studios will bring in a team that has experience in redefining how media content is experienced in virtual environments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Daniel Alegre, CEO of Yuga Labs, has welcomed Roar's talented team to the Yuga family, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Roar Studios has redefined what it means to experience media content in the metaverse. Yuga's North Star is creating new ways for communities to connect and express themselves, and I am excited to welcome Roar's talented team to our Yuga family. Roar's dedication to creative content creation and social connections will accelerate our execution of our bold vision for Otherside and Yuga's ecosystem more broadly."</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading web3 company Yuga Labs has announced its agreement to acquire tech innovator Roar Studios to bolster its ambitions Otherside project.&nbsp;</p>
Adopting Roar&rsquo;s Tech For Otherside
<p>The announcement was made on July 31 by Yuga Labs, home of popular NFT collections like Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), CryptoPunks, Meebits, and 10KTF. On the other end of the deal is tech innovator Roar Studios, working at the intersection of gaming, social media, and the metaverse. As per the announcement, Yuga Labs is seeking to add more value to its Otherside project, which is being designed to be an interoperable metaverse that will revolutionize virtual experiences.</p>
Roar CEO In Charge Of Otherside
<p>Following the acquisition, Roar Studio&rsquo;s CEO, Eric Reid, will take on the role of General Manager of Otherside. With over two decades of experience in building teams and creating and distributing film, television, and music content for global audiences, including work on film franchises like UNDERWORLD, Reid brings valuable expertise to lead the development and production of the Otherside platform.</p>
<p>Addressing the acquisition by Yuga Labs, Reid stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Our team's mission is to empower players to create and be social in a community-driven, open media experience, so our work fundamentally aligns with Yuga's larger web3 metaverse strategy. When Daniel and Mike Seavers opened the door for us to contribute to Yuga's paradigm-shifting approach to content and immersive experiences, we jumped at the opportunity."</p>

More about Roar&nbsp;
<p>Roar Studios has been making waves with its creation, ROAR, an immersive media platform where artists and fans can connect, collaborate, and compete in real time from anywhere. The platform combines cutting-edge proprietary technology with established MMO games and platform systems, resulting in an entirely new product category&mdash;an experiential, semi-autonomous music and entertainment world driven by individual content creators and community consensus.</p>
Yuga's Expansive Vision and Roar's Complementary Expertise
<p>Otherside, one of the most ambitious interactive metaverse projects to date, is designed with community participation in mind, rejecting the concept of traditional walled gardens in gaming spaces. The project's success is evidenced by its $450M seed funding round in March 2022, valuing Yuga Labs at $4B.</p>
<p>The acquisition of Roar Studios will bring in a team that has experience in redefining how media content is experienced in virtual environments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Daniel Alegre, CEO of Yuga Labs, has welcomed Roar's talented team to the Yuga family, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Roar Studios has redefined what it means to experience media content in the metaverse. Yuga's North Star is creating new ways for communities to connect and express themselves, and I am excited to welcome Roar's talented team to our Yuga family. Roar's dedication to creative content creation and social connections will accelerate our execution of our bold vision for Otherside and Yuga's ecosystem more broadly."</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Is Tether the Safest Stablecoin To Store Your Crypto? Tradecurve Skyrockets, Hits $4Million]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/is-tether-the-safest-stablecoin-to-store-your-crypto-tradecurve-skyrockets-hits-4million</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-145656.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-145656.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-145656.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/is-tether-the-safest-stablecoin-to-store-your-crypto-tradecurve-skyrockets-hits-4million</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">According to CoinMarketCap, Tether (USDT) is the largest stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market. However, its safety has come under question in recent times. The question now is if Tether is the safest option for storing your crypto? Meanwhile, Tradecurve, a hybrid platform, has raised over $3 million in its presale, causing excitement among investors.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Is Tether (USDT) the Safest Stablecoin To Store Your Crypto?
<p class="s6">Tether (USDT) is the top stablecoin in the crypto market with a market capitalization of over $83 billion. Meanwhile, there are several factors to consider when ascertaining the safety of a stablecoin. One is the assets backing the stablecoin like gold, government treasury bills, etc. Also, the stablecoin issuer must have sufficient funds available to fulfill all redemption requests.</p>
<p class="s6">Despite being embroiled in controversy over the past year, the Tether coin has recently implemented measures to enhance transparency within its operations. Notably, the platform now publishes regular audits of its USD reserves. Additionally, Tether has made efforts to bolster its USD reserves.</p>
<p class="s6">According to the Q1 attestation conducted by financial services firm, BDO Italia, Tether possessed approximately $2.44 billion in excess reserves. Although the token has de-pegged from the USD more than 3 times in the past year, it has always rebounded.</p>
Tradecurve (TCRV) Presale Run Skyrockets With $3M Raise in Presale
<p class="s6">Tradecurve, a trading platform that has generated significant attention, has raised $4 million during its presale so far. The team anticipates raising a total of $20 million by Q3. Meanwhile, Tradecurve adopts a hybrid approach, blending elements of CEXs and DEXs, to establish a private trading environment. Safety is particularly crucial in the present era of data breaches, especially for traders who prioritize privacy.</p>
<p class="s6">Unfortunately, many traditional trading exchanges have yet to implement a Proof of Reserves (PoR) system, causing diminishing trust from traders. Interestingly, Tradecurve is out to fill this void, enhance user trust and promote the exchange's integrity by implementing PoR.</p>
Tradecurve (TCRV) To Hit &nbsp;$0.025 in Stage 5
<p class="s6">Tradecurve's TCRV token has captured significant attention in the crypto community. Over the past month, Tradecurve's price has skyrocketed by 150%, with the token surging from $0.015 to $0.025. What sets Tradecurve apart from rivals like Huobi and Coinbase is its emphasis on decentralization, user anonymity, and privacy.</p>
<p class="s6">Moreover, Tradecurve ensures that traders enjoy a smooth trading experience by providing quick withdrawals, deposits, and trade execution. At present, the token is in stage five of its presale, enabling investors to acquire it for $0.025 per token. Analysts predict that with the current bullish trend, the token could reach $0.029 in stage 6.</p>
How High Can Tradecurve Go?
<p class="s6">While the forthcoming 40% surge appears like a remarkable price jump, it doesn&rsquo;t compare with the long-term prediction for Tradecurve. Experts have predicted that the launch of the platform will attract a wave of traders to Tradecurve. This spike in activity is expected to cause a 50xsurge for Tradecurve in 2023 for TCRV to trade as high as $1 per token.</p>
<p class="s16">For more information about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale:</p>
<p class="s16">Website: https://tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s16">Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s16">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p class="s16">Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">According to CoinMarketCap, Tether (USDT) is the largest stablecoin in the cryptocurrency market. However, its safety has come under question in recent times. The question now is if Tether is the safest option for storing your crypto? Meanwhile, Tradecurve, a hybrid platform, has raised over $3 million in its presale, causing excitement among investors.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Is Tether (USDT) the Safest Stablecoin To Store Your Crypto?
<p class="s6">Tether (USDT) is the top stablecoin in the crypto market with a market capitalization of over $83 billion. Meanwhile, there are several factors to consider when ascertaining the safety of a stablecoin. One is the assets backing the stablecoin like gold, government treasury bills, etc. Also, the stablecoin issuer must have sufficient funds available to fulfill all redemption requests.</p>
<p class="s6">Despite being embroiled in controversy over the past year, the Tether coin has recently implemented measures to enhance transparency within its operations. Notably, the platform now publishes regular audits of its USD reserves. Additionally, Tether has made efforts to bolster its USD reserves.</p>
<p class="s6">According to the Q1 attestation conducted by financial services firm, BDO Italia, Tether possessed approximately $2.44 billion in excess reserves. Although the token has de-pegged from the USD more than 3 times in the past year, it has always rebounded.</p>
Tradecurve (TCRV) Presale Run Skyrockets With $3M Raise in Presale
<p class="s6">Tradecurve, a trading platform that has generated significant attention, has raised $4 million during its presale so far. The team anticipates raising a total of $20 million by Q3. Meanwhile, Tradecurve adopts a hybrid approach, blending elements of CEXs and DEXs, to establish a private trading environment. Safety is particularly crucial in the present era of data breaches, especially for traders who prioritize privacy.</p>
<p class="s6">Unfortunately, many traditional trading exchanges have yet to implement a Proof of Reserves (PoR) system, causing diminishing trust from traders. Interestingly, Tradecurve is out to fill this void, enhance user trust and promote the exchange's integrity by implementing PoR.</p>
Tradecurve (TCRV) To Hit &nbsp;$0.025 in Stage 5
<p class="s6">Tradecurve's TCRV token has captured significant attention in the crypto community. Over the past month, Tradecurve's price has skyrocketed by 150%, with the token surging from $0.015 to $0.025. What sets Tradecurve apart from rivals like Huobi and Coinbase is its emphasis on decentralization, user anonymity, and privacy.</p>
<p class="s6">Moreover, Tradecurve ensures that traders enjoy a smooth trading experience by providing quick withdrawals, deposits, and trade execution. At present, the token is in stage five of its presale, enabling investors to acquire it for $0.025 per token. Analysts predict that with the current bullish trend, the token could reach $0.029 in stage 6.</p>
How High Can Tradecurve Go?
<p class="s6">While the forthcoming 40% surge appears like a remarkable price jump, it doesn&rsquo;t compare with the long-term prediction for Tradecurve. Experts have predicted that the launch of the platform will attract a wave of traders to Tradecurve. This spike in activity is expected to cause a 50xsurge for Tradecurve in 2023 for TCRV to trade as high as $1 per token.</p>
<p class="s16">For more information about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale:</p>
<p class="s16">Website: https://tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s16">Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s16">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p class="s16">Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Beginners Top Cryptocurrencies Picks – Pepe, Floki and Pomerdoge]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/crypto-beginners-top-cryptocurrencies-picks-pepe-floki-and-pomerdoge</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-150059.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-150059.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-01-at-150059.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/crypto-beginners-top-cryptocurrencies-picks-pepe-floki-and-pomerdoge</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Pepe (PEPE), Floki (FLOKI), and Pomerdoge (POMD) - these projects have garnered attention for their growth potential in the crypto space. Today, we will examine all three of these tokens in greater detail and determine their appeal. Moreover, we'll discuss why many crypto beginners gravitate toward them.</p>
Summary
- Pepe shows a bullish technical analysis
- Floki continues its uptrend
- Pomerdoge expected to skyrocket by 17x
<p>Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</p>
Pepe (PEPE): A Fun Meme-Coin 
<p>Pepe (PEPE) was one of the top gainers in the meme coin market, offering early investors enormous gains in late June and early July. Given that the Pepe coin was created with no intrinsic value, this performance has been noteworthy. </p>
<p>The Pepe coin price currently sits at $0.000001336 with a market cap of $523M, down 1.23% overnight. However, the Pepe technical analysis displays a bullish picture. In fact, all moving averages are showing buy signals. </p>
<p>As a result, experts remain bullish on Pepe's long-term growth potential. Thus, forecast a jump to $0.00000179 for Pepe by December 2023. </p>
Floki (FLOKI): On an Upward Trajectory
<p>Inspired by the viral popularity of Elon Musk's pet Floki, the Floki Inu token quickly gained traction. Like other meme coins, Floki's price dynamics are influenced by market sentiment and social media buzz.</p>
<p>In recent Floki Inu news, Binance Liquid Swap will sunset 31 liquidity pools, including FLOKI/USDT, as of August 4, 2023, at 4:00 a.m. UTC. But, this news did not impact the FlokiInu price, which now sits at $0.00002268 with a market cap of $213M. Hence, an increase of 1.43% in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>In addition, the Floki trading volume increased by 47.54% in that same time, reaching $15,579,332. With all these bullish signs, experts forecast Floki could surge to $0.00002986 within Q4 of 2023. </p>
Pomerdoge (POMD): Excellent Long-Term Growth Potential
<p>Pomerdoge (POMD) presents an enticing proposition for crypto beginners who want to combine gaming and earning. The project combines P2E mechanics with NFTs to create an immersive and rewarding gaming experience. Players can build up their characters, trade in-game items in the Pomerplace, and participate in exciting arena battles. </p>
<p>One of the standout features of the project is the promise to reward presale investors with a percentage of the revenue generated from the game. This unique revenue-sharing model allows investors to earn rewards proportionately to their tokens, adding a lucrative element to the gaming experience.</p>
<p>Moreover, to deliver a memorable and valuable gaming experience, Pomerdoge has curated a collection of 7,777 exclusive NFTs. Each NFT will be priced at 0.2 ETH, unlocking a world of possibilities for their owners. Nevertheless, the project has kept the benefits of owning these NFTs closely guarded until closer to the launch. </p>
<p>To participate in the acquisition of these exclusive NFTs, investors must hold POMD tokens. Currently, POMD has a presale price of only $0.007. But, this price will not be this low for too long as the presale is in Phase One. Many experts are forecasting that it will surge by 17x before it finishes. With all these features, POMD may leave Pepe and Floki in the dust.</p>
<p class="s13">Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://pomerdoge.com/</p>
<p>Telegram Community: https://t.me/pomerdoge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pepe (PEPE), Floki (FLOKI), and Pomerdoge (POMD) - these projects have garnered attention for their growth potential in the crypto space. Today, we will examine all three of these tokens in greater detail and determine their appeal. Moreover, we'll discuss why many crypto beginners gravitate toward them.</p>
Summary
- Pepe shows a bullish technical analysis
- Floki continues its uptrend
- Pomerdoge expected to skyrocket by 17x
<p>Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</p>
Pepe (PEPE): A Fun Meme-Coin 
<p>Pepe (PEPE) was one of the top gainers in the meme coin market, offering early investors enormous gains in late June and early July. Given that the Pepe coin was created with no intrinsic value, this performance has been noteworthy. </p>
<p>The Pepe coin price currently sits at $0.000001336 with a market cap of $523M, down 1.23% overnight. However, the Pepe technical analysis displays a bullish picture. In fact, all moving averages are showing buy signals. </p>
<p>As a result, experts remain bullish on Pepe's long-term growth potential. Thus, forecast a jump to $0.00000179 for Pepe by December 2023. </p>
Floki (FLOKI): On an Upward Trajectory
<p>Inspired by the viral popularity of Elon Musk's pet Floki, the Floki Inu token quickly gained traction. Like other meme coins, Floki's price dynamics are influenced by market sentiment and social media buzz.</p>
<p>In recent Floki Inu news, Binance Liquid Swap will sunset 31 liquidity pools, including FLOKI/USDT, as of August 4, 2023, at 4:00 a.m. UTC. But, this news did not impact the FlokiInu price, which now sits at $0.00002268 with a market cap of $213M. Hence, an increase of 1.43% in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p>In addition, the Floki trading volume increased by 47.54% in that same time, reaching $15,579,332. With all these bullish signs, experts forecast Floki could surge to $0.00002986 within Q4 of 2023. </p>
Pomerdoge (POMD): Excellent Long-Term Growth Potential
<p>Pomerdoge (POMD) presents an enticing proposition for crypto beginners who want to combine gaming and earning. The project combines P2E mechanics with NFTs to create an immersive and rewarding gaming experience. Players can build up their characters, trade in-game items in the Pomerplace, and participate in exciting arena battles. </p>
<p>One of the standout features of the project is the promise to reward presale investors with a percentage of the revenue generated from the game. This unique revenue-sharing model allows investors to earn rewards proportionately to their tokens, adding a lucrative element to the gaming experience.</p>
<p>Moreover, to deliver a memorable and valuable gaming experience, Pomerdoge has curated a collection of 7,777 exclusive NFTs. Each NFT will be priced at 0.2 ETH, unlocking a world of possibilities for their owners. Nevertheless, the project has kept the benefits of owning these NFTs closely guarded until closer to the launch. </p>
<p>To participate in the acquisition of these exclusive NFTs, investors must hold POMD tokens. Currently, POMD has a presale price of only $0.007. But, this price will not be this low for too long as the presale is in Phase One. Many experts are forecasting that it will surge by 17x before it finishes. With all these features, POMD may leave Pepe and Floki in the dust.</p>
<p class="s13">Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://pomerdoge.com/</p>
<p>Telegram Community: https://t.me/pomerdoge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[QuickNode Now Available in AWS Marketplace]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/quicknode-now-available-in-aws-marketplace</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QuickNode-Logo-AWS-Release_1690575736EvmcZeo7EB.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QuickNode-Logo-AWS-Release_1690575736EvmcZeo7EB.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QuickNode-Logo-AWS-Release_1690575736EvmcZeo7EB.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:20:36 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/quicknode-now-available-in-aws-marketplace</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Miami, Florida, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Developers and businesses worldwide can now easily access QuickNode's cutting-edge blockchain infrastructure on AWS.</p><p>QuickNode, a pioneering platform for Web3 development, today announced the availability of Core Node API, its cutting-edge blockchain accessibility infrastructure, in AWS Marketplace. AWS Marketplace is a digital catalog with thousands of software listings from independent software vendors that make it easy to find, test, buy, and deploy software that runs on Amazon Web Services (AWS). QuickNode customers can now benefit from AWS, simplifying blockchain deployment and management processes.</p>"AWS is a go-to platform for businesses of all sizes that are looking to build and deploy innovative applications," said Alexander Nabutovsky, Co-founder and CEO of QuickNode. "We are excited to bring QuickNode to AWS Marketplace, making it even easier for developers and businesses to access the next-gen blockchain infrastructure they need to build the future of the internet."<p>Availability of QuickNode in AWS Marketplace significantly streamlines the process for businesses to begin blockchain development. Businesses can seamlessly deploy a QuickNode endpoint on AWS through a simple, user-friendly process and start accessing blockchain data almost instantaneously. QuickNode's primary mission is to aid enterprises and Web3 developer teams with trustworthy, efficient solutions for blockchain data access that are further fortified by the security offered by AWS. As a result, businesses now have the opportunity to:</p><ul><li>Easily deploy enterprise RPC nodes tailored to their business goals.</li><li>Optimize blockchain data querying for high levels of speed and reliability with certified SOC 2 security.</li><li>Effortlessly track the performance of their nodes anytime, anywhere, with access to usage data and advanced telemetry.</li><li>Access a comprehensive Web3 developer toolkit with supercharged APIs, a one-click Web3 app store, world-class developer resources, and around-the-clock support.</li></ul><p>QuickNode's fully managed node hosting solution is engineered to lighten the load of blockchain infrastructure operational expenses (OpEx), allowing businesses to focus on innovation and scaling. By launching QuickNode in AWS Marketplace, a new gateway has been opened for developers and enterprises ready to harness the innovation made possible by blockchain technology. This platform sets the stage for a future where decentralized technology is seamlessly integrated into every web system stratum, propelling the growth and adoption of the internet's next iteration.</p><p>About QuickNode</p><p>Since its founding in 2017, QuickNode has emerged as a go-to solution for businesses and innovators requiring world-class blockchain development tools for speed, reliability, and security. Handling over eight billion blockchain requests daily, QuickNode boasts a 2.5X faster response time than competitors and unparalleled uptime across 24+ chains and 35+ networks. With a user-friendly interface and a robust multi-chain developer tool suite, QuickNode is an ideal choice for top Web3 businesses and global brands.</p>ContactVP of EcosystemJason HuntQuickNodeecosystem@quicknode.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami, Florida, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Developers and businesses worldwide can now easily access QuickNode's cutting-edge blockchain infrastructure on AWS.</p><p>QuickNode, a pioneering platform for Web3 development, today announced the availability of Core Node API, its cutting-edge blockchain accessibility infrastructure, in AWS Marketplace. AWS Marketplace is a digital catalog with thousands of software listings from independent software vendors that make it easy to find, test, buy, and deploy software that runs on Amazon Web Services (AWS). QuickNode customers can now benefit from AWS, simplifying blockchain deployment and management processes.</p>"AWS is a go-to platform for businesses of all sizes that are looking to build and deploy innovative applications," said Alexander Nabutovsky, Co-founder and CEO of QuickNode. "We are excited to bring QuickNode to AWS Marketplace, making it even easier for developers and businesses to access the next-gen blockchain infrastructure they need to build the future of the internet."<p>Availability of QuickNode in AWS Marketplace significantly streamlines the process for businesses to begin blockchain development. Businesses can seamlessly deploy a QuickNode endpoint on AWS through a simple, user-friendly process and start accessing blockchain data almost instantaneously. QuickNode's primary mission is to aid enterprises and Web3 developer teams with trustworthy, efficient solutions for blockchain data access that are further fortified by the security offered by AWS. As a result, businesses now have the opportunity to:</p><ul><li>Easily deploy enterprise RPC nodes tailored to their business goals.</li><li>Optimize blockchain data querying for high levels of speed and reliability with certified SOC 2 security.</li><li>Effortlessly track the performance of their nodes anytime, anywhere, with access to usage data and advanced telemetry.</li><li>Access a comprehensive Web3 developer toolkit with supercharged APIs, a one-click Web3 app store, world-class developer resources, and around-the-clock support.</li></ul><p>QuickNode's fully managed node hosting solution is engineered to lighten the load of blockchain infrastructure operational expenses (OpEx), allowing businesses to focus on innovation and scaling. By launching QuickNode in AWS Marketplace, a new gateway has been opened for developers and enterprises ready to harness the innovation made possible by blockchain technology. This platform sets the stage for a future where decentralized technology is seamlessly integrated into every web system stratum, propelling the growth and adoption of the internet's next iteration.</p><p>About QuickNode</p><p>Since its founding in 2017, QuickNode has emerged as a go-to solution for businesses and innovators requiring world-class blockchain development tools for speed, reliability, and security. Handling over eight billion blockchain requests daily, QuickNode boasts a 2.5X faster response time than competitors and unparalleled uptime across 24+ chains and 35+ networks. With a user-friendly interface and a robust multi-chain developer tool suite, QuickNode is an ideal choice for top Web3 businesses and global brands.</p>ContactVP of EcosystemJason HuntQuickNodeecosystem@quicknode.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Nomura's Laser Digital: A New Crypto Force in Dubai]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/nomura-laser-digital-a-new-crypto-force-in-dubai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/dub.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/dub.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/dub.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:01:57 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/nomura-laser-digital-a-new-crypto-force-in-dubai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai's financial landscape has witnessed a significant development with the awarding of a full crypto licence to Laser Digital Middle East FZE, a subsidiary of Nomura Holdings Inc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This move marks one of the initial full permits granted by Dubai since its revamp of the digital asset regulatory framework. Laser Digital, with its roots in Nomura, is poised to make a significant impact in the crypto space. The newly acquired licence empowers the firm to offer Virtual Asset Broker-Dealer Services and Virtual Asset Management and Investment Services.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As reported by Bloomberg and Reuters, Laser Digital is gearing up to introduce over-the-counter (OTC) trading services and a diverse array of digital asset investment products tailored for institutional investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The inception of Laser Digital can be traced back to last year, a venture co-founded by Steven Ashley, former leader of Nomura's wholesale division, and Jez Mohideen, who once held the roles of Nomura&rsquo;s Chief Digital Officer and Co-Head of Global Markets EMEA.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With headquarters in Switzerland and other offices in Dubai and London, Laser Digital blends the best practices of global investment banking with the expertise of a team deeply rooted in the crypto domain. Jez Mohideen, the driving force behind Laser Digital, expressed his gratitude towards the Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA) for the licence approval.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are very grateful to VARA for approving our Operating Licence. VARA&rsquo;s thorough and consultative process provides institutional investors with the assurance they require to engage in this asset class. With the licence now in place, we are looking forward to Laser&rsquo;s growth over the coming years.&rdquo;</p>

Slow but sure global adoption&nbsp;
<p>Perhaps it is still happening quite slowly, but the world contenders to become the main hub for the global crypto market appear to be getting their regulatory ducks in a line and are starting to attract the kind of institutional firms, such as Nomura, that will take the crypto sector forward into the next stage of adoption.</p>
<p>Dubai is likely to have some heavy competition from its fellow Asian jurisdictions of Hong Kong and Singapore, while in Europe, the UK, France and others are looking to become crypto hubs. However, in the US, the regulatory environment is still sluggish and anything but clear. A move en masse out of this jurisdiction could still happen.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai's financial landscape has witnessed a significant development with the awarding of a full crypto licence to Laser Digital Middle East FZE, a subsidiary of Nomura Holdings Inc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This move marks one of the initial full permits granted by Dubai since its revamp of the digital asset regulatory framework. Laser Digital, with its roots in Nomura, is poised to make a significant impact in the crypto space. The newly acquired licence empowers the firm to offer Virtual Asset Broker-Dealer Services and Virtual Asset Management and Investment Services.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As reported by Bloomberg and Reuters, Laser Digital is gearing up to introduce over-the-counter (OTC) trading services and a diverse array of digital asset investment products tailored for institutional investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The inception of Laser Digital can be traced back to last year, a venture co-founded by Steven Ashley, former leader of Nomura's wholesale division, and Jez Mohideen, who once held the roles of Nomura&rsquo;s Chief Digital Officer and Co-Head of Global Markets EMEA.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With headquarters in Switzerland and other offices in Dubai and London, Laser Digital blends the best practices of global investment banking with the expertise of a team deeply rooted in the crypto domain. Jez Mohideen, the driving force behind Laser Digital, expressed his gratitude towards the Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA) for the licence approval.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are very grateful to VARA for approving our Operating Licence. VARA&rsquo;s thorough and consultative process provides institutional investors with the assurance they require to engage in this asset class. With the licence now in place, we are looking forward to Laser&rsquo;s growth over the coming years.&rdquo;</p>

Slow but sure global adoption&nbsp;
<p>Perhaps it is still happening quite slowly, but the world contenders to become the main hub for the global crypto market appear to be getting their regulatory ducks in a line and are starting to attract the kind of institutional firms, such as Nomura, that will take the crypto sector forward into the next stage of adoption.</p>
<p>Dubai is likely to have some heavy competition from its fellow Asian jurisdictions of Hong Kong and Singapore, while in Europe, the UK, France and others are looking to become crypto hubs. However, in the US, the regulatory environment is still sluggish and anything but clear. A move en masse out of this jurisdiction could still happen.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LeetSwap And $BALD Rug Plague Coinbase Ecosystem]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/leetswap-and-bald-rug-plague-coinbase-ecosystem</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-hack-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-hack-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-hack-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/leetswap-and-bald-rug-plague-coinbase-ecosystem</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized exchange LeetSwap, built on Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer 2 blockchain Base, recently suspended trading due to fears of a potential exploit. Furthermore, Coinbase and Base are also dealing with the aftermath of the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
LeetSwap Halts Trading Amid Security Concerns
<p>Trouble is brewing in the Coinbase ecosystem as multiple challenges loom ahead. On the one hand, is the BALD coin crash, which has prompted leading DEX on the Base blockchain, LeetSwap, to halt trading. The DEX tweeted that they detected a security vulnerability in their factory, leading them to suspect compromised pool liquidity. As a result, trading was temporarily stopped for further investigation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>PeckShield, a crypto-security firm, reported that approximately 340 ETH (equivalent to $630,000) had been exploited from liquidity pairs on Base, highlighting the severity of the situation.</p>
Bald Memecoin's Crash
<p>Shortly before the trading pause, Bald, a popular memecoin, experienced a significant crash in value. The token's developer withdrew a substantial sum of 6,800 ETH ($12.5 million) from the liquidity pool on LeetSwap. This sudden move raised eyebrows and further added to the challenges faced by Base's leading DEX.</p>
Base and Coinbase's Regulatory Woes
<p>Base, as an Ethereum Layer 2 (L2) chain, empowers developers to build decentralized apps using Coinbase's products, users, and tools. However, Coinbase has been dealing with its own regulatory challenges after falling in the crosshairs of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The latter has demanded Coinbase suspend all cryptocurrency trading except for Bitcoin, and upon questioning the decision, the regulatory body filed a lawsuit against the exchange.</p>
SEC&rsquo;s Lawsuit Against Coinbase
<p>According to the lawsuit filed by the SEC, the regulatory body deemed 13 assets on Coinbase, including Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), FIL, SAND, AXS, ICP, NEAR, CHZ, DASH, VGX, and NEXO, as securities. The SEC also accused Coinbase of failing to register as a broker, clearing agency, or national securities exchange, indicating that the exchange was not adhering to the established disclosure regime for the U.S. securities markets.</p>
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong stated that the exchange had limited choices in dealing with the SEC's demands. Following the regulator's instructions would have set a dangerous precedent and conveyed the wrong message. Therefore, it found itself caught between compliance and potential harm to the cryptocurrency industry's principles.</p>
Issues Pile Up For Coinbase&nbsp;
<p>LeetSwap's trading halt and the exploits on Base's liquidity pairs have raised serious concerns about security vulnerabilities on the Coinbase-backed blockchain. Additionally, Bald's dramatic crash and Coinbase's ongoing legal battle with the SEC have further complicated matters for the platform. The situation highlights the challenges and uncertainties surrounding the crypto industry's regulatory landscape and emphasizes the need for continued vigilance and security measures to protect investors and users alike.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized exchange LeetSwap, built on Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer 2 blockchain Base, recently suspended trading due to fears of a potential exploit. Furthermore, Coinbase and Base are also dealing with the aftermath of the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
LeetSwap Halts Trading Amid Security Concerns
<p>Trouble is brewing in the Coinbase ecosystem as multiple challenges loom ahead. On the one hand, is the BALD coin crash, which has prompted leading DEX on the Base blockchain, LeetSwap, to halt trading. The DEX tweeted that they detected a security vulnerability in their factory, leading them to suspect compromised pool liquidity. As a result, trading was temporarily stopped for further investigation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>PeckShield, a crypto-security firm, reported that approximately 340 ETH (equivalent to $630,000) had been exploited from liquidity pairs on Base, highlighting the severity of the situation.</p>
Bald Memecoin's Crash
<p>Shortly before the trading pause, Bald, a popular memecoin, experienced a significant crash in value. The token's developer withdrew a substantial sum of 6,800 ETH ($12.5 million) from the liquidity pool on LeetSwap. This sudden move raised eyebrows and further added to the challenges faced by Base's leading DEX.</p>
Base and Coinbase's Regulatory Woes
<p>Base, as an Ethereum Layer 2 (L2) chain, empowers developers to build decentralized apps using Coinbase's products, users, and tools. However, Coinbase has been dealing with its own regulatory challenges after falling in the crosshairs of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The latter has demanded Coinbase suspend all cryptocurrency trading except for Bitcoin, and upon questioning the decision, the regulatory body filed a lawsuit against the exchange.</p>
SEC&rsquo;s Lawsuit Against Coinbase
<p>According to the lawsuit filed by the SEC, the regulatory body deemed 13 assets on Coinbase, including Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), FIL, SAND, AXS, ICP, NEAR, CHZ, DASH, VGX, and NEXO, as securities. The SEC also accused Coinbase of failing to register as a broker, clearing agency, or national securities exchange, indicating that the exchange was not adhering to the established disclosure regime for the U.S. securities markets.</p>
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong stated that the exchange had limited choices in dealing with the SEC's demands. Following the regulator's instructions would have set a dangerous precedent and conveyed the wrong message. Therefore, it found itself caught between compliance and potential harm to the cryptocurrency industry's principles.</p>
Issues Pile Up For Coinbase&nbsp;
<p>LeetSwap's trading halt and the exploits on Base's liquidity pairs have raised serious concerns about security vulnerabilities on the Coinbase-backed blockchain. Additionally, Bald's dramatic crash and Coinbase's ongoing legal battle with the SEC have further complicated matters for the platform. The situation highlights the challenges and uncertainties surrounding the crypto industry's regulatory landscape and emphasizes the need for continued vigilance and security measures to protect investors and users alike.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Charges Hex Founder Richard Heart with Securities Violations]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-charges-hex-founder-richard-heart-with-securities-violations</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hex-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hex-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hex-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:03:10 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-charges-hex-founder-richard-heart-with-securities-violations</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC continues its crackdown on alleged securities violations. In its latest move, the agency charged Richard Heart, founder of Hex, with conducting unregistered securities offerings that raised over $1 billion. </p>
<p>The US SEC charged Richard Heart and three unincorporated entities under his control for allegedly conducting unregistered crypto asset securities offerings.</p>
SEC Charges Richard Heart, Hex, PulseChain, and PulseX
<p>In a press release, the SEC announced it charged Richard Heart and three unincorporated entities under his control with conducting unregistered offerings of crypto asset securities that raised over $1 billion in crypto assets from investors. The entities controlled by Heart are Hex, PulseX, and PulseChain.</p>
<p>The agency further charged Heart and PulseChain with fraud, alleging they misappropriated at least $12 million in the offering proceeds to purchase luxury goods, including a 555-carat black diamond called &ldquo;The Enigma.&rdquo;</p>
<p>According to the SEC&rsquo;s press release:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Heart began marketing Hex in 2018, claiming it was the first high-yield &ldquo;blockchain certificate of deposit,&rdquo; and began promoting Hex tokens as an investment designed to make people &ldquo;rich.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The agency also claims:</p>

<p>&ldquo;From at least December 2019 through November 2020, Heart and Hex allegedly offered and sold Hex tokens in an unregistered offering, collecting more than 2.3 million Ethereum (ETH), including through so-called &ldquo;recycling&rdquo; transactions that enabled Heart to surreptitiously gain control of more Hex tokens.&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to the SEC, Heart also created and marketed a so-called &ldquo;staking&rdquo; feature for Hex tokens in which he claimed he could deliver returns as high as 38%. The SEC also takes issue with Heart&rsquo;s attempt to evade securities laws by asking investors to &ldquo;sacrifice&rdquo; instead of &ldquo;invest&rdquo; their assets in exchange for PLS and PLSX tokens.</p>
<p>Eric Werner, Director of the Forth Worth Regional Office, commented:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Heart called on investors to buy crypto asset securities in offerings that he failed to register. He then defrauded those investors by spending some of their crypto assets on exorbitant luxury goods.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He added the SEC&rsquo;s actions against the founder seek to protect the &ldquo;investing public and hold Heart accountable for his actions.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The SEC filed its lawsuit in the US District Court for the Eastern District of New York. The agency said Heart claimed Hex &ldquo;was built to be the highest appreciating asset that has ever existed in the history of man.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC continues its crackdown on alleged securities violations. In its latest move, the agency charged Richard Heart, founder of Hex, with conducting unregistered securities offerings that raised over $1 billion. </p>
<p>The US SEC charged Richard Heart and three unincorporated entities under his control for allegedly conducting unregistered crypto asset securities offerings.</p>
SEC Charges Richard Heart, Hex, PulseChain, and PulseX
<p>In a press release, the SEC announced it charged Richard Heart and three unincorporated entities under his control with conducting unregistered offerings of crypto asset securities that raised over $1 billion in crypto assets from investors. The entities controlled by Heart are Hex, PulseX, and PulseChain.</p>
<p>The agency further charged Heart and PulseChain with fraud, alleging they misappropriated at least $12 million in the offering proceeds to purchase luxury goods, including a 555-carat black diamond called &ldquo;The Enigma.&rdquo;</p>
<p>According to the SEC&rsquo;s press release:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Heart began marketing Hex in 2018, claiming it was the first high-yield &ldquo;blockchain certificate of deposit,&rdquo; and began promoting Hex tokens as an investment designed to make people &ldquo;rich.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The agency also claims:</p>

<p>&ldquo;From at least December 2019 through November 2020, Heart and Hex allegedly offered and sold Hex tokens in an unregistered offering, collecting more than 2.3 million Ethereum (ETH), including through so-called &ldquo;recycling&rdquo; transactions that enabled Heart to surreptitiously gain control of more Hex tokens.&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to the SEC, Heart also created and marketed a so-called &ldquo;staking&rdquo; feature for Hex tokens in which he claimed he could deliver returns as high as 38%. The SEC also takes issue with Heart&rsquo;s attempt to evade securities laws by asking investors to &ldquo;sacrifice&rdquo; instead of &ldquo;invest&rdquo; their assets in exchange for PLS and PLSX tokens.</p>
<p>Eric Werner, Director of the Forth Worth Regional Office, commented:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Heart called on investors to buy crypto asset securities in offerings that he failed to register. He then defrauded those investors by spending some of their crypto assets on exorbitant luxury goods.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He added the SEC&rsquo;s actions against the founder seek to protect the &ldquo;investing public and hold Heart accountable for his actions.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The SEC filed its lawsuit in the US District Court for the Eastern District of New York. The agency said Heart claimed Hex &ldquo;was built to be the highest appreciating asset that has ever existed in the history of man.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Enjinstarter IDO investors win big with AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Top_Launchpad_1690793927i9E9UoEXOu.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Top_Launchpad_1690793927i9E9UoEXOu.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Top_Launchpad_1690793927i9E9UoEXOu.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:05:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/enjinstarter-ido-investors-win-big-with-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">Launchpad delivers 142.4% ROI YTD thanks to carefully curated selection of AI projects</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Leading IDO launchpad, Enjinstarter, announced today that its stable of AI-powered Web3 projects has earned investors an average ROI of 142.4% YTD in 2023. This puts Enjinstarter firmly in the top 3 of IDO providers worldwide, according to industry-leading ranking service, CryptoRank.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Continued success in Q2 comes on the back of a successful Q1 in which Enjinstarter was ranked by TokenHunter as the top-performing IDO launchpad with an average ROI of 538.49%.</p>&ldquo;Our number one goal is to deliver maximum value to our IDO participants. We conduct an exhaustive study of every launchpad applicant to bring our token holders a carefully curated selection of projects set to revolutionize the industry,&rdquo; said Prakash Somosundram, co-founder and CEO of Enjinstarter. &ldquo;At the beginning of the year, our team correctly identified the growing trend towards generative AI and was quick to adapt. Our overall success this year can be attributed to our team&rsquo;s ability to find the best among a proliferation of AI-powered Web3 projects.&rdquo;<p class="ql-align-justify">2023 has been the year of AI. The continued evolution of OpenAI&rsquo;s GPT algorithm has led to a proliferation of generative AI-powered apps. Of the 13 IDOs conducted by Enjinstarter so far this year, 8 leverage the power of AI:</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">ChainGPT - Infrastructure enabling the future of Web3 innovation with AI</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Orbofi AI - Advanced platform for creating AI-generated content and fine-tuned AI models.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Eldarune - AI-powered RPG with PvE and PvP modes</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Cogito Protocol - A decentralized and AI-driven tracercoin called GCOIN</li><li class="ql-align-justify">KAIF Platform - AI-powered decentralized society (DeSoc) platform.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">HyperGPT - A Web3-based AI marketplace</li><li class="ql-align-justify">DexCheck - AI-boosted analytics for crypto and NFT trading</li><li class="ql-align-justify">SophiaVerse - An advanced artificial general intelligence initiative revolutionizing the world of AI and gaming</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">The top performing IDO launched through Enjinstarter in 2023 is ChainGPT with an ROI of 704% at the time of writing. SophiaVerse is a close second at 602%. Data provided by CryptoRank.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Building on the success of its IDO launchpad, Enjinstarter plans to build two additional launchpads. The first is an INO platform to connect utility-driven NFT projects with investors. The second is a platform specifically designed for Web3 climate startups to raise funds from impact investors.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Looking ahead, Enjinstarter has 5 IDO projects in the pipeline: SeaPad, Kvants AI, Boss Fighters, AITECH, and Backstage. It is also planning the release of an expansive storytelling AI NFT game based on an advanced earth concept where factions are embarking on quests and battles throughout the Enjinstarter ecosystem to gather resources and earn rewards.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">To date, the company has helped launch over 80 Web3 projects and platforms since its inception in 2021.</p><p>For further media enquiries, please contact:</p><p>media@pariahdao.xyz</p><p>About Enjinstarter</p><p>Launched in 2021, Enjinstarter is a next-generation ecosystem and launchpad for promising Web3 gaming, entertainment and metaverse projects. They have supported 70 companies since</p><p>inception. They have a collective community of more than 200,000 across various social platforms and manage localised communities in South East Asia, India, Turkey and Spain. They have also launched dedicated market-launchers for North America and Indonesia.</p><p>Enjinstarter also has a fast growing Web3 Innovation Consulting practice that works with brands, large corporates and Web2 companies looking to develop a Web3 strategy. Clients that they have supported include Hatten Land and GCEX. Enjinstarter is also a member of the Open Metaverse Alliance.</p><p>Enjinstarter raised US$5 million in their Series A round from True Global Ventures 4 Plus, an equity venture capital firm that invests in serial tech entrepreneurs globally. The company has also received initial approval from Dubai&rsquo;s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority, indicating progress in obtaining full permission to operate within Dubai.</p><p>Get connected with Enjinstarter:</p><p>https://linktr.ee/enjinstarter</p>ContactSocial Media LeadChris Sylvester BasilEnjinstarterchris@enjinstarter.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">Launchpad delivers 142.4% ROI YTD thanks to carefully curated selection of AI projects</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Leading IDO launchpad, Enjinstarter, announced today that its stable of AI-powered Web3 projects has earned investors an average ROI of 142.4% YTD in 2023. This puts Enjinstarter firmly in the top 3 of IDO providers worldwide, according to industry-leading ranking service, CryptoRank.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Continued success in Q2 comes on the back of a successful Q1 in which Enjinstarter was ranked by TokenHunter as the top-performing IDO launchpad with an average ROI of 538.49%.</p>&ldquo;Our number one goal is to deliver maximum value to our IDO participants. We conduct an exhaustive study of every launchpad applicant to bring our token holders a carefully curated selection of projects set to revolutionize the industry,&rdquo; said Prakash Somosundram, co-founder and CEO of Enjinstarter. &ldquo;At the beginning of the year, our team correctly identified the growing trend towards generative AI and was quick to adapt. Our overall success this year can be attributed to our team&rsquo;s ability to find the best among a proliferation of AI-powered Web3 projects.&rdquo;<p class="ql-align-justify">2023 has been the year of AI. The continued evolution of OpenAI&rsquo;s GPT algorithm has led to a proliferation of generative AI-powered apps. Of the 13 IDOs conducted by Enjinstarter so far this year, 8 leverage the power of AI:</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">ChainGPT - Infrastructure enabling the future of Web3 innovation with AI</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Orbofi AI - Advanced platform for creating AI-generated content and fine-tuned AI models.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Eldarune - AI-powered RPG with PvE and PvP modes</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Cogito Protocol - A decentralized and AI-driven tracercoin called GCOIN</li><li class="ql-align-justify">KAIF Platform - AI-powered decentralized society (DeSoc) platform.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">HyperGPT - A Web3-based AI marketplace</li><li class="ql-align-justify">DexCheck - AI-boosted analytics for crypto and NFT trading</li><li class="ql-align-justify">SophiaVerse - An advanced artificial general intelligence initiative revolutionizing the world of AI and gaming</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">The top performing IDO launched through Enjinstarter in 2023 is ChainGPT with an ROI of 704% at the time of writing. SophiaVerse is a close second at 602%. Data provided by CryptoRank.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Building on the success of its IDO launchpad, Enjinstarter plans to build two additional launchpads. The first is an INO platform to connect utility-driven NFT projects with investors. The second is a platform specifically designed for Web3 climate startups to raise funds from impact investors.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Looking ahead, Enjinstarter has 5 IDO projects in the pipeline: SeaPad, Kvants AI, Boss Fighters, AITECH, and Backstage. It is also planning the release of an expansive storytelling AI NFT game based on an advanced earth concept where factions are embarking on quests and battles throughout the Enjinstarter ecosystem to gather resources and earn rewards.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">To date, the company has helped launch over 80 Web3 projects and platforms since its inception in 2021.</p><p>For further media enquiries, please contact:</p><p>media@pariahdao.xyz</p><p>About Enjinstarter</p><p>Launched in 2021, Enjinstarter is a next-generation ecosystem and launchpad for promising Web3 gaming, entertainment and metaverse projects. They have supported 70 companies since</p><p>inception. They have a collective community of more than 200,000 across various social platforms and manage localised communities in South East Asia, India, Turkey and Spain. They have also launched dedicated market-launchers for North America and Indonesia.</p><p>Enjinstarter also has a fast growing Web3 Innovation Consulting practice that works with brands, large corporates and Web2 companies looking to develop a Web3 strategy. Clients that they have supported include Hatten Land and GCEX. Enjinstarter is also a member of the Open Metaverse Alliance.</p><p>Enjinstarter raised US$5 million in their Series A round from True Global Ventures 4 Plus, an equity venture capital firm that invests in serial tech entrepreneurs globally. The company has also received initial approval from Dubai&rsquo;s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority, indicating progress in obtaining full permission to operate within Dubai.</p><p>Get connected with Enjinstarter:</p><p>https://linktr.ee/enjinstarter</p>ContactSocial Media LeadChris Sylvester BasilEnjinstarterchris@enjinstarter.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin repeating phase 1 of the bull - all is well]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-repeating-phase-1-of-the-bull-all-is-well</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bull-6.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bull-6.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bull-6.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:01:12 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-repeating-phase-1-of-the-bull-all-is-well</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin bull market is just going through the same 3 steps it has taken in its previous bull markets.</p>
<p>Seasoned trader Steve Courtney of CryptoCrewUniversity has been repeating his mantra for a good while now that Bitcoin is doing what it does every bull market, and that thus far it is following the pattern which puts it in stage one of the bull market.</p>
<p>Courtney points out that right now Bitcoin is holding above the 200-week moving average and therefore even if it comes down to test it, which would take it down to around $27,000, all would be perfectly fine as long as this huge last line in the sand holds fast.</p>
<p>The trader&rsquo;s next area to keep an eye on is the relative strength indicator (RSI) where Bitcoin needs to continue building a base structure above the mid level. Here, on the weekly time frame, support can be found at the 51 level. Courtney has the view that this is all-important, and should Bitcoin fall below and make this resistance, a lot of trouble could be heading Bitcoin&rsquo;s way.</p>
<p>The Stochastic RSI, which measures momentum is Courtney&rsquo;s next port of call. The veteran trader points out that every 6 months there is a cross on the Stochastic RSI and remarks that each one of these crosses heralds the biggest moves for Bitcoin.</p>
<p>For the previous cross, Bitcoin rallied from about $25,000 up to just under $32,000, from which it has fallen to its current level of around $29,000.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For the 3 steps, Courtney states that step number 1 is triggered by the Pi Cycle. A cross up for this indicator always leads to a huge rally which is then met by resistance that is not broken for quite some period of time.</p>
<p>However, this part of the bull market may not be plain sailing. Courtney says that if price does not hold above the red line, it will always fall to the green, quite a drop in price, leading to an extended phase 1, but which would still mean that Bitcoin stays in its bull market unless falling below the green line.</p>
<p>For his second step Courtney uses the Dynamic Traders Index which tells him when Bitcoin moves into phase 2 of the bull market. He remarks that this indicator is not showing that we are near phase 2 of the bull yet.</p>
<p>For Courtney, phase 2 is when price holds support above the resistance at $30,000 (phase 1) and then consolidates for many months. A breakout and consolidation above this would lead to stage 3 and big increases in price action until the top of this particular bull market is reached.</p>
<p>Due to reducing gains in each successive bull market, Courtney is of the opinion that Bitcoin probably won&rsquo;t reach $100,000, which runs contrary to the view of most other analysts. Time will prove him right or wrong.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin bull market is just going through the same 3 steps it has taken in its previous bull markets.</p>
<p>Seasoned trader Steve Courtney of CryptoCrewUniversity has been repeating his mantra for a good while now that Bitcoin is doing what it does every bull market, and that thus far it is following the pattern which puts it in stage one of the bull market.</p>
<p>Courtney points out that right now Bitcoin is holding above the 200-week moving average and therefore even if it comes down to test it, which would take it down to around $27,000, all would be perfectly fine as long as this huge last line in the sand holds fast.</p>
<p>The trader&rsquo;s next area to keep an eye on is the relative strength indicator (RSI) where Bitcoin needs to continue building a base structure above the mid level. Here, on the weekly time frame, support can be found at the 51 level. Courtney has the view that this is all-important, and should Bitcoin fall below and make this resistance, a lot of trouble could be heading Bitcoin&rsquo;s way.</p>
<p>The Stochastic RSI, which measures momentum is Courtney&rsquo;s next port of call. The veteran trader points out that every 6 months there is a cross on the Stochastic RSI and remarks that each one of these crosses heralds the biggest moves for Bitcoin.</p>
<p>For the previous cross, Bitcoin rallied from about $25,000 up to just under $32,000, from which it has fallen to its current level of around $29,000.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For the 3 steps, Courtney states that step number 1 is triggered by the Pi Cycle. A cross up for this indicator always leads to a huge rally which is then met by resistance that is not broken for quite some period of time.</p>
<p>However, this part of the bull market may not be plain sailing. Courtney says that if price does not hold above the red line, it will always fall to the green, quite a drop in price, leading to an extended phase 1, but which would still mean that Bitcoin stays in its bull market unless falling below the green line.</p>
<p>For his second step Courtney uses the Dynamic Traders Index which tells him when Bitcoin moves into phase 2 of the bull market. He remarks that this indicator is not showing that we are near phase 2 of the bull yet.</p>
<p>For Courtney, phase 2 is when price holds support above the resistance at $30,000 (phase 1) and then consolidates for many months. A breakout and consolidation above this would lead to stage 3 and big increases in price action until the top of this particular bull market is reached.</p>
<p>Due to reducing gains in each successive bull market, Courtney is of the opinion that Bitcoin probably won&rsquo;t reach $100,000, which runs contrary to the view of most other analysts. Time will prove him right or wrong.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Has The Curve Finance Exploit Put Aave And DeFi At Risk?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/has-the-curve-finance-exploit-put-aave-and-defi-at-risk</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-community-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-community-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-community-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 09:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/has-the-curve-finance-exploit-put-aave-and-defi-at-risk</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Curve Finance suffered a significant exploit over the weekend, with attackers managing to siphon off around $70 million worth of assets from users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Curve founder Michael Egorov has a loan of around $70 million in USDT on Aave v2, using CRV as collateral.&nbsp;</p>
Curve Chaos Could Have Major Implications&nbsp;
<p>The exploit at Curve Finance resulted in the price of the protocol&rsquo;s CRV token experiencing a sharp decline. This decline has put a $168 million lending position held by Curve founder Michael Egorov at risk of liquidation. If the position gets liquidated, it could have disastrous implications across the decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem. The Curve founder has around $168 million worth of CRV, which he has used to secure loans from several DeFi protocols, according to data from the blockchain analytics site DeBank. This amount equals nearly 34% of CRV&rsquo;s total market capitalization.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exploit has led to a decline of over 20% in the CRV price, putting Egorov&rsquo;s position in danger of liquidation.&nbsp;</p>
A Major Blow&nbsp;
<p>A forced liquidation would be a devastating blow to Curve after its weekend exploit. As a result of the exploit, the total value of assets locked on the DeFi protocol dropped from $3.7 billion to $2.1 billion, with investors pulling their funds as a precaution. Thanks to DeFi&rsquo;s interconnected nature, the liquidation of Egorov&rsquo;s position could put significant pressure on CRV&rsquo;s price and other decentralized lending protocols. The CRV token is extremely popular on Uniswap and Sushiswap and is used as collateral on platforms such as Aave.&nbsp;</p>
Aave&rsquo;s Exposure&nbsp;
<p>Michael Egorov has a $70 million loan in USDT on Aave v2, for which he has used CRV as collateral. Based on risk parameters set by Aave, if the CRV token&rsquo;s price drops below $65%, it would be at risk of liquidation. When liquidations occur, the collateral the borrower deposits is sold in exchange for the borrowed asset. In the case of Aave, the CRV would be sold for Aave, leading to considerable bad debt.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The concerns around bad debt were already flagged by Gauntlet, who recommended freezing CRV and setting its loan-to-value to zero on Aave v2.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The amount of CRV concentrated on Aave, relative to the circulating supply of CRV, is already high. Given the limitations of V2 mechanisms, including the possibility of circumventing an LTV of 0, the only way to truly prevent more risk of this position is to prevent borrowing of all assets on V2.&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, this proposal failed to pass.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aave&rsquo;s GHO stablecoin also lost its peg for a few hours on the 31st of July. The stablecoin subsequently regained its peg, with analysts working to determine why the de-pegging occurred. According to most, the de-pegging was a result of the reentrancy attack on Curve Finance. The GHO stablecoin had dropped to $0.96 on the 31st, losing its $1 peg for a few hours. However, it regained its peg and is currently trading at $0.98.&nbsp;</p>
Other Protocols At Risk&nbsp;
<p>Aave is not the only protocol that the Curve Finance fiasco could impact. Egorov has also borrowed $17 million worth of the FRAX stablecoin, putting $32 million worth of CRV as collateral. Since the exploit, Egorov has made several transactions to repay part of the amount he borrowed on Fraxlend. According to DeBank data, Egorov also has an $18 million loan on DeFi protocol Abracadabra.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Egorov has moved to shore up his capital by selling LDO, the governance token for liquid staking protocol Lido, in exchange for the USDC stablecoin. These transactions have been done in several batches valued at between $10,000 and $50,000, according to data from EtherScan. The developments have raised several questions for decentralized lending protocols, and whether they should implement measures to prevent large positions, such as the ones taken by Egorov, that could potentially introduce systemic risk.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Egorov came under fierce criticism in 2020 after he took control of over two-thirds of a Curve voting token, veCRV. He later apologized and called the move an overreaction to what he thought was a takeover attempt by Yearn.Finance.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curve Finance suffered a significant exploit over the weekend, with attackers managing to siphon off around $70 million worth of assets from users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Curve founder Michael Egorov has a loan of around $70 million in USDT on Aave v2, using CRV as collateral.&nbsp;</p>
Curve Chaos Could Have Major Implications&nbsp;
<p>The exploit at Curve Finance resulted in the price of the protocol&rsquo;s CRV token experiencing a sharp decline. This decline has put a $168 million lending position held by Curve founder Michael Egorov at risk of liquidation. If the position gets liquidated, it could have disastrous implications across the decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem. The Curve founder has around $168 million worth of CRV, which he has used to secure loans from several DeFi protocols, according to data from the blockchain analytics site DeBank. This amount equals nearly 34% of CRV&rsquo;s total market capitalization.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exploit has led to a decline of over 20% in the CRV price, putting Egorov&rsquo;s position in danger of liquidation.&nbsp;</p>
A Major Blow&nbsp;
<p>A forced liquidation would be a devastating blow to Curve after its weekend exploit. As a result of the exploit, the total value of assets locked on the DeFi protocol dropped from $3.7 billion to $2.1 billion, with investors pulling their funds as a precaution. Thanks to DeFi&rsquo;s interconnected nature, the liquidation of Egorov&rsquo;s position could put significant pressure on CRV&rsquo;s price and other decentralized lending protocols. The CRV token is extremely popular on Uniswap and Sushiswap and is used as collateral on platforms such as Aave.&nbsp;</p>
Aave&rsquo;s Exposure&nbsp;
<p>Michael Egorov has a $70 million loan in USDT on Aave v2, for which he has used CRV as collateral. Based on risk parameters set by Aave, if the CRV token&rsquo;s price drops below $65%, it would be at risk of liquidation. When liquidations occur, the collateral the borrower deposits is sold in exchange for the borrowed asset. In the case of Aave, the CRV would be sold for Aave, leading to considerable bad debt.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The concerns around bad debt were already flagged by Gauntlet, who recommended freezing CRV and setting its loan-to-value to zero on Aave v2.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The amount of CRV concentrated on Aave, relative to the circulating supply of CRV, is already high. Given the limitations of V2 mechanisms, including the possibility of circumventing an LTV of 0, the only way to truly prevent more risk of this position is to prevent borrowing of all assets on V2.&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, this proposal failed to pass.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Aave&rsquo;s GHO stablecoin also lost its peg for a few hours on the 31st of July. The stablecoin subsequently regained its peg, with analysts working to determine why the de-pegging occurred. According to most, the de-pegging was a result of the reentrancy attack on Curve Finance. The GHO stablecoin had dropped to $0.96 on the 31st, losing its $1 peg for a few hours. However, it regained its peg and is currently trading at $0.98.&nbsp;</p>
Other Protocols At Risk&nbsp;
<p>Aave is not the only protocol that the Curve Finance fiasco could impact. Egorov has also borrowed $17 million worth of the FRAX stablecoin, putting $32 million worth of CRV as collateral. Since the exploit, Egorov has made several transactions to repay part of the amount he borrowed on Fraxlend. According to DeBank data, Egorov also has an $18 million loan on DeFi protocol Abracadabra.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Egorov has moved to shore up his capital by selling LDO, the governance token for liquid staking protocol Lido, in exchange for the USDC stablecoin. These transactions have been done in several batches valued at between $10,000 and $50,000, according to data from EtherScan. The developments have raised several questions for decentralized lending protocols, and whether they should implement measures to prevent large positions, such as the ones taken by Egorov, that could potentially introduce systemic risk.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Egorov came under fierce criticism in 2020 after he took control of over two-thirds of a Curve voting token, veCRV. He later apologized and called the move an overreaction to what he thought was a takeover attempt by Yearn.Finance.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Upbit Suspends CRV Transactions Following Curve Finance Exploit]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/upbit-suspends-crv-transactions-following-curve-finance-exploit</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/curve-728x350.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/curve-728x350.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/curve-728x350.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/upbit-suspends-crv-transactions-following-curve-finance-exploit</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Upbit, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in South Korea, has temporarily suspended CRV withdrawals and deposits after Curve fell victim to a significant exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Other exchanges have been keeping track of the situation but have not initiated any action as of now.&nbsp;</p>
The Curve Finance Exploit&nbsp;
<p>Curve Finance tweeted over the weekend that the protocol had fallen victim to an exploit. The protocol stated that over $100 million worth of cryptocurrency was at risk thanks to a reentrancy bug in Vyper, the programming language used to power parts of the larger Curve ecosystem. As a result, several stablecoin pools used in the pricing and liquidity of several DeFi projects were drained by hackers.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A number of stablepools (alETH/msETH/pETH) using Vyper 0.2.15 have been exploited as a result of a malfunctioning reentrancy lock. We are assessing the situation and will update the community as things develop.&rdquo;</p>

<p>In another tweet on Monday, the protocol listed out the hacked pools. It also stated that the Arbitrum trycrypto pool could also have been compromised during the hack.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As a result of an issue in Vyper compiler in versions 0.2.15-0.3.0, the following pools were hacked: crv/eth aleth/eth mseth/eth peth/eth Another pool potentially affected is arbitrum&rsquo;s tricrypto. Auditors and Vyper devs could not find a profitable exploit, but please exit that one.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Re-entrancy attacks are a fairly common exploit, allowing hackers to trick smart contracts by making repeated calls to the protocol and stealing user assets. A call is basically an authorization for a smart contract address to interact with a user&rsquo;s wallet address.&nbsp;</p>
Upbit Suspends CRV Withdrawals And Deposits&nbsp;
<p>Following the exploit, Upbit, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in South Korea, announced it was temporarily suspending the withdrawal and deposit of Curve Finance&rsquo;s native CRV token. The suspension was announced by Chinese crypto reporter Wu Blockchain on Twitter, who stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;South Korea&rsquo;s largest exchange, Upbit, announced that due to the attack on some of Curve&rsquo;s stablecoin pools, CRV volatility is high, and Curve (CRV) deposit and withdrawal services have been suspended.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Upbit exchange, in its announcement, stated it had detected several vulnerabilities in some stablecoin pools associated with Curve Finance, leading to the CRV token experiencing considerable volatility. It added that it was temporarily suspending CRV deposits and withdrawals.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today, certain vulnerabilities have been discovered in some of the stablecoin pools associated with Curve (CRV). As a result, CRV is currently experiencing significant volatility. We advise exercising caution when considering any investments related to CRV. To ensure the safety of digital asset transactions, we have temporarily suspended deposits and withdrawals for CRV.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The hack has resulted in a loss of over $100 million for the protocol, with the CRV token down over 12%.&nbsp;</p>
Other Exchanges Keeping Tabs
<p>While Upbit has swung into action and suspended CRV deposits and withdrawals, other prominent exchanges have adopted a wait-and-watch approach. Upbit has also urged users to exercise caution when considering any investments related to CRV. OKX, another prominent exchange, issued a warning for users on the token&rsquo;s landing page, telling users the exchange would not be responsible for any losses incurred while trading the CRV token.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance head Changpeng Zhao stated that Binance users were unaffected by the exploit in Curve.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;CEX price feed saves DeFi. Binance users are not affected. Our team checked on the Vyper Reentrant Vulnerability. We only use version 0.3.7 or above.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Zhao explained that Binance&rsquo;s use of a centralized price feed for DeFi tokens adds an extra layer of security. Zhao also insisted on updating applications, code libraries, and operating systems.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Upbit, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in South Korea, has temporarily suspended CRV withdrawals and deposits after Curve fell victim to a significant exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Other exchanges have been keeping track of the situation but have not initiated any action as of now.&nbsp;</p>
The Curve Finance Exploit&nbsp;
<p>Curve Finance tweeted over the weekend that the protocol had fallen victim to an exploit. The protocol stated that over $100 million worth of cryptocurrency was at risk thanks to a reentrancy bug in Vyper, the programming language used to power parts of the larger Curve ecosystem. As a result, several stablecoin pools used in the pricing and liquidity of several DeFi projects were drained by hackers.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A number of stablepools (alETH/msETH/pETH) using Vyper 0.2.15 have been exploited as a result of a malfunctioning reentrancy lock. We are assessing the situation and will update the community as things develop.&rdquo;</p>

<p>In another tweet on Monday, the protocol listed out the hacked pools. It also stated that the Arbitrum trycrypto pool could also have been compromised during the hack.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As a result of an issue in Vyper compiler in versions 0.2.15-0.3.0, the following pools were hacked: crv/eth aleth/eth mseth/eth peth/eth Another pool potentially affected is arbitrum&rsquo;s tricrypto. Auditors and Vyper devs could not find a profitable exploit, but please exit that one.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Re-entrancy attacks are a fairly common exploit, allowing hackers to trick smart contracts by making repeated calls to the protocol and stealing user assets. A call is basically an authorization for a smart contract address to interact with a user&rsquo;s wallet address.&nbsp;</p>
Upbit Suspends CRV Withdrawals And Deposits&nbsp;
<p>Following the exploit, Upbit, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in South Korea, announced it was temporarily suspending the withdrawal and deposit of Curve Finance&rsquo;s native CRV token. The suspension was announced by Chinese crypto reporter Wu Blockchain on Twitter, who stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;South Korea&rsquo;s largest exchange, Upbit, announced that due to the attack on some of Curve&rsquo;s stablecoin pools, CRV volatility is high, and Curve (CRV) deposit and withdrawal services have been suspended.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Upbit exchange, in its announcement, stated it had detected several vulnerabilities in some stablecoin pools associated with Curve Finance, leading to the CRV token experiencing considerable volatility. It added that it was temporarily suspending CRV deposits and withdrawals.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today, certain vulnerabilities have been discovered in some of the stablecoin pools associated with Curve (CRV). As a result, CRV is currently experiencing significant volatility. We advise exercising caution when considering any investments related to CRV. To ensure the safety of digital asset transactions, we have temporarily suspended deposits and withdrawals for CRV.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The hack has resulted in a loss of over $100 million for the protocol, with the CRV token down over 12%.&nbsp;</p>
Other Exchanges Keeping Tabs
<p>While Upbit has swung into action and suspended CRV deposits and withdrawals, other prominent exchanges have adopted a wait-and-watch approach. Upbit has also urged users to exercise caution when considering any investments related to CRV. OKX, another prominent exchange, issued a warning for users on the token&rsquo;s landing page, telling users the exchange would not be responsible for any losses incurred while trading the CRV token.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Binance head Changpeng Zhao stated that Binance users were unaffected by the exploit in Curve.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;CEX price feed saves DeFi. Binance users are not affected. Our team checked on the Vyper Reentrant Vulnerability. We only use version 0.3.7 or above.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Zhao explained that Binance&rsquo;s use of a centralized price feed for DeFi tokens adds an extra layer of security. Zhao also insisted on updating applications, code libraries, and operating systems.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Exchange to List Seven New Tokens in a Week]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/lbank-exchange-to-list-seven-new-tokens-in-a-week</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/this_week_20230731_1690858203NWWn6W9EyL.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/this_week_20230731_1690858203NWWn6W9EyL.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/this_week_20230731_1690858203NWWn6W9EyL.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:17:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/lbank-exchange-to-list-seven-new-tokens-in-a-week</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Digital asset exchange LBank continues to focus on providing its users with quality projects to access. For the week starting July 31, LBank has announced its intention to list a total of seven new tokens. These encompass a diverse range of projects.</p><p>The first token on LBank&rsquo;s schedule, DBC, was listed on July 31. All DBC-powered platforms are interconnected like a universe, enabling users to learn, play and shop. DBC will be used for membership points and as a means of exchange within the DBear universe. DBC is headed by Man-won Chung, former CEO of SK Telecom which has a market capitalization of $8 billion.</p><p>The second token, PEPEBURN, also listed on July 31, is a low supply memecoin with less than 1 million tokens created. August 1 then sees the launch of PSUB, an abbreviation of Payment Swap Utility Board and a Klaytn-based blockchain. PSUB forms a circular ecosystem structure between a payments NFT marketplace and online commerce with its own wallet as a hub. In the future, PSUB will form partnerships with various affiliates to expand its platform ecosystem not only domestically but also abroad to solidify its own infrastructure.</p><p>&nbsp;August 1 also sees the launch of OZON on LBank. This asset takes the role of utility token on a fifth-generation blockchain network. The OZONE blockchain is mainly concerned with digital finance, metaverse, travel, and ecommerce. On the same day, LBS lists on LBank. The token powers a luxury brand distribution, management and payment system using blockchain technology.</p><p>On August 3, SMETA is to be listed on LBank. Starkmeta is a Singapore-based startup that&rsquo;s successfully integrated generative AI (ChatGPT) with Unreal Engine 5 and Web3 metaverse games for the first time. It enables users to enjoy social networking with friends and select the products they want with the help of an AI assistant.</p><p>The following day, DMC lists on LBank. Datamall Chain is an open source blockchain that aims to promote the construction of next generation internet infrastructure. Products will include decentralized storage mining, DeFi, NFTs, cross-chain bridge and cloud storage.</p><p>For the week running from July 24-30, LBank listed a total of 12 tokens covering NFTs, memecoins, public chains, and GambleFi. Of these, the best performer was Worldcoin (WLD), which rose over 350% since listing.</p><p></p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media: &nbsp;Telegram l Twitter l Facebook l LinkedIn l Instagram l YouTube</p>Contact<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p><p>marketing@lbank.info</p><p></p><p></p><p>&nbsp;</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, August 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Digital asset exchange LBank continues to focus on providing its users with quality projects to access. For the week starting July 31, LBank has announced its intention to list a total of seven new tokens. These encompass a diverse range of projects.</p><p>The first token on LBank&rsquo;s schedule, DBC, was listed on July 31. All DBC-powered platforms are interconnected like a universe, enabling users to learn, play and shop. DBC will be used for membership points and as a means of exchange within the DBear universe. DBC is headed by Man-won Chung, former CEO of SK Telecom which has a market capitalization of $8 billion.</p><p>The second token, PEPEBURN, also listed on July 31, is a low supply memecoin with less than 1 million tokens created. August 1 then sees the launch of PSUB, an abbreviation of Payment Swap Utility Board and a Klaytn-based blockchain. PSUB forms a circular ecosystem structure between a payments NFT marketplace and online commerce with its own wallet as a hub. In the future, PSUB will form partnerships with various affiliates to expand its platform ecosystem not only domestically but also abroad to solidify its own infrastructure.</p><p>&nbsp;August 1 also sees the launch of OZON on LBank. This asset takes the role of utility token on a fifth-generation blockchain network. The OZONE blockchain is mainly concerned with digital finance, metaverse, travel, and ecommerce. On the same day, LBS lists on LBank. The token powers a luxury brand distribution, management and payment system using blockchain technology.</p><p>On August 3, SMETA is to be listed on LBank. Starkmeta is a Singapore-based startup that&rsquo;s successfully integrated generative AI (ChatGPT) with Unreal Engine 5 and Web3 metaverse games for the first time. It enables users to enjoy social networking with friends and select the products they want with the help of an AI assistant.</p><p>The following day, DMC lists on LBank. Datamall Chain is an open source blockchain that aims to promote the construction of next generation internet infrastructure. Products will include decentralized storage mining, DeFi, NFTs, cross-chain bridge and cloud storage.</p><p>For the week running from July 24-30, LBank listed a total of 12 tokens covering NFTs, memecoins, public chains, and GambleFi. Of these, the best performer was Worldcoin (WLD), which rose over 350% since listing.</p><p></p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media: &nbsp;Telegram l Twitter l Facebook l LinkedIn l Instagram l YouTube</p>Contact<p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p><p>marketing@lbank.info</p><p></p><p></p><p>&nbsp;</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Genesis and FTX Trading Nearing Resolution on Bankruptcy Dispute]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/genesis-and-ftx-trading-nearing-resolution-on-bankruptcy-dispute</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/genesis-capital-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/genesis-capital-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/genesis-capital-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/genesis-and-ftx-trading-nearing-resolution-on-bankruptcy-dispute</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Genesis Global Holdco LLC, and FTX Trading Ltd., two crypto companies navigating bankruptcy, have announced an in-principle agreement to resolve a dispute central to their respective Chapter 11 cases.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Previously, FTX Trading, the now-defunct crypto exchange, had laid claim to a debt of up to $3.9 billion from Genesis Global, a contention firmly disputed by the crypto lender. This claim was subsequently downscaled to a maximum of $2 billion.</p>
Case History
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Genesis Global Capital, a lending unit under Genesis Global Holdco LLC, had raised considerable industry-wide concern when it halted customer repayments and subsequently filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy on January 20. The mega bankruptcy filing named over 100,000 creditors, with the firm's total obligations speculated to range anywhere from $1.2 billion to a staggering $11 billion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Amid the ensuing industry shock, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a complaint against Genesis and its ex-partner, Gemini, accusing them of the illegal sale of securities. This additional blow further complicated the company's predicament. Digital Currency Group, parent company of Genesis Global Holdco, assured its intent to consider options like an equity deal or sale to address the debts. DCG also revealed it had $150 million in cash reserves to aid in the restructuring process.</p>
Updates To The Bankruptcy Case
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent update to a bankruptcy judge, the legal representatives of both companies indicated that their mutual claims would be settled in line with the agreement. Details of the settlement, however, remain undisclosed as of now. The companies intend to submit motions for approval of the deal to bankruptcy courts.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This progress towards settlement is anticipated to be a welcome relief for Genesis creditors. They had been expecting the disagreement between Genesis and FTX to prolong the bankruptcy proceedings, potentially leading to delays in the payout of claims. With the dispute now seemingly close to resolution, the path to finalizing the bankruptcy proceedings appears clearer.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Genesis Global's parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), had previously affirmed its commitment to resolving the claims against Genesis. In a letter to shareholders, DCG had expressed its optimism about reaching an agreement to resolve the bankruptcy case, offering a beacon of hope amidst the ongoing legal and financial challenges.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Genesis Global Holdco LLC, and FTX Trading Ltd., two crypto companies navigating bankruptcy, have announced an in-principle agreement to resolve a dispute central to their respective Chapter 11 cases.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Previously, FTX Trading, the now-defunct crypto exchange, had laid claim to a debt of up to $3.9 billion from Genesis Global, a contention firmly disputed by the crypto lender. This claim was subsequently downscaled to a maximum of $2 billion.</p>
Case History
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Genesis Global Capital, a lending unit under Genesis Global Holdco LLC, had raised considerable industry-wide concern when it halted customer repayments and subsequently filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy on January 20. The mega bankruptcy filing named over 100,000 creditors, with the firm's total obligations speculated to range anywhere from $1.2 billion to a staggering $11 billion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Amid the ensuing industry shock, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a complaint against Genesis and its ex-partner, Gemini, accusing them of the illegal sale of securities. This additional blow further complicated the company's predicament. Digital Currency Group, parent company of Genesis Global Holdco, assured its intent to consider options like an equity deal or sale to address the debts. DCG also revealed it had $150 million in cash reserves to aid in the restructuring process.</p>
Updates To The Bankruptcy Case
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent update to a bankruptcy judge, the legal representatives of both companies indicated that their mutual claims would be settled in line with the agreement. Details of the settlement, however, remain undisclosed as of now. The companies intend to submit motions for approval of the deal to bankruptcy courts.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This progress towards settlement is anticipated to be a welcome relief for Genesis creditors. They had been expecting the disagreement between Genesis and FTX to prolong the bankruptcy proceedings, potentially leading to delays in the payout of claims. With the dispute now seemingly close to resolution, the path to finalizing the bankruptcy proceedings appears clearer.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Genesis Global's parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), had previously affirmed its commitment to resolving the claims against Genesis. In a letter to shareholders, DCG had expressed its optimism about reaching an agreement to resolve the bankruptcy case, offering a beacon of hope amidst the ongoing legal and financial challenges.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Tied to BALD Coin Rug Pull]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sam-bankman-fried-tied-to-bald-coin-rug-pull</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-rugpull-link-h-compressed.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-rugpull-link-h-compressed.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-rugpull-link-h-compressed.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sam-bankman-fried-tied-to-bald-coin-rug-pull</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">An unsettling rumor is sweeping across the crypto community following the sudden liquidity pull from the BALD meme coin. Several voices within the sector are suggesting a potential link to the already embattled ex-CEO of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">This has stirred up more confusion surrounding the former FTX leader, who is already ensnared in a legal quagmire.</p>
Piecing the Puzzle, Possible Links
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the eye of the storm, a mysterious developer has abruptly withdrawn all liquidity from the BALD meme coin, creating ripples within the crypto sphere. The aftermath has led several blockchain observers to suspect a correlation to Sam Bankman-Fried, the erstwhile FTX chief. Currently under house arrest with severely limited online access, such allegations add to the increasingly perplexing narrative surrounding Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"From the looks of it, the BALD developer could likely be SBF or someone within Alameda," shared Adam Cochran, a partner at Cinneamhain Ventures, referencing the associated wallet address&rsquo;s prior SushiSwap involvement. Cochran was further quoted stating, "I am almost certain it is either someone from Alameda, FTX, or SBF himself."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Simultaneously, distinct phrases used by the BALD Twitter account, bearing close resemblance to Bankman-Fried's own posts, have intensified the conjecture around his possible involvement. Thus, the question remains: is the former FTX head the unseen hand behind the BALD debacle? </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A crowdsourced investigation on Reddit has added fuel to the fire, suggesting that the BALD developer wallet had been a recipient of deposits from FTX and Alameda over the past two years. Currently harboring 12,331 ETH, equivalent to nearly $22 million, this wallet has emerged as a key focal point in the BALD conundrum.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Adding to the complexity, one Twitter user (@cryptobran_) highlighted that an address routinely depositing into the BALD wallet had previously been implicated in the Terra USD depegging incident last May. As these puzzle pieces fall into place, the implications could further darken the clouds over the involved entities.</p>
House Arrest and Legal Troubles
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bankman-Fried's legal troubles continue to mount. The former FTX leader, currently under house arrest following his indictment by the U.S. Department of Justice on multiple counts of conspiracy and fraud, is under scrutiny for his online activities. In the wake of the BALD incident, the growing evidentiary trail implicating his potential involvement cannot be ignored.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the focus of the crypto community is firmly on Bankman-Fried, caution is being advised as the risk of unfounded speculation remains high. Nonetheless, the suggestion that someone within Bankman-Fried's inner circle may be involved has found broad acceptance. The evolving role of Sam Trabucco, former co-CEO of Alameda, has drawn attention, leaving the crypto community in suspense.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">An unsettling rumor is sweeping across the crypto community following the sudden liquidity pull from the BALD meme coin. Several voices within the sector are suggesting a potential link to the already embattled ex-CEO of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">This has stirred up more confusion surrounding the former FTX leader, who is already ensnared in a legal quagmire.</p>
Piecing the Puzzle, Possible Links
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the eye of the storm, a mysterious developer has abruptly withdrawn all liquidity from the BALD meme coin, creating ripples within the crypto sphere. The aftermath has led several blockchain observers to suspect a correlation to Sam Bankman-Fried, the erstwhile FTX chief. Currently under house arrest with severely limited online access, such allegations add to the increasingly perplexing narrative surrounding Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"From the looks of it, the BALD developer could likely be SBF or someone within Alameda," shared Adam Cochran, a partner at Cinneamhain Ventures, referencing the associated wallet address&rsquo;s prior SushiSwap involvement. Cochran was further quoted stating, "I am almost certain it is either someone from Alameda, FTX, or SBF himself."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Simultaneously, distinct phrases used by the BALD Twitter account, bearing close resemblance to Bankman-Fried's own posts, have intensified the conjecture around his possible involvement. Thus, the question remains: is the former FTX head the unseen hand behind the BALD debacle? </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A crowdsourced investigation on Reddit has added fuel to the fire, suggesting that the BALD developer wallet had been a recipient of deposits from FTX and Alameda over the past two years. Currently harboring 12,331 ETH, equivalent to nearly $22 million, this wallet has emerged as a key focal point in the BALD conundrum.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Adding to the complexity, one Twitter user (@cryptobran_) highlighted that an address routinely depositing into the BALD wallet had previously been implicated in the Terra USD depegging incident last May. As these puzzle pieces fall into place, the implications could further darken the clouds over the involved entities.</p>
House Arrest and Legal Troubles
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bankman-Fried's legal troubles continue to mount. The former FTX leader, currently under house arrest following his indictment by the U.S. Department of Justice on multiple counts of conspiracy and fraud, is under scrutiny for his online activities. In the wake of the BALD incident, the growing evidentiary trail implicating his potential involvement cannot be ignored.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the focus of the crypto community is firmly on Bankman-Fried, caution is being advised as the risk of unfounded speculation remains high. Nonetheless, the suggestion that someone within Bankman-Fried's inner circle may be involved has found broad acceptance. The evolving role of Sam Trabucco, former co-CEO of Alameda, has drawn attention, leaving the crypto community in suspense.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
