<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 08:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Texas House of Representatives Passes Bill Requiring Proof of Reserves for Crypto Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/texas-house-of-representatives-passes-bill-requiring-proof-of-reserves-for-crypto-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 22:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247527</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Texas.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Texas.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Texas is looking for ways to avoid the next FTX scenario, by requiring proof of reserves for every registered crypto exchange.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On April 21, the Texas House of Representatives approved a bill requiring cryptocurrency exchanges to maintain sufficient reserves to fulfill their clients&#8217; payment obligations.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://digitalchamber.org/proof-of-reserves-bill-passes-texas-house-of-representatives/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcement</a> by the Texas House of Representatives, the &#8220;HB 166&#8221; bill filed by State Rep. Giovanni Capriglione was passed by a majority of 150 members, aiming to &#8220;rebuild trust in the market by requiring Proof of Reserves for digital asset exchanges.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Texas Aims to Protect Citizens</h2>
<p>Perianne Boring, Founder and CEO of the Chamber of Digital Commerce, congratulated Rep. Capriglione and the Texas House of Representatives for approving a law aimed at protecting citizens from financial issues caused by exchanges while addressing a critical problem like Proof of Reserves.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Congratulations to Rep. Giovanni Capriglione (R-TX) and the Texas House of Representatives on the passage of HB 1666, which seeks to protect Texas consumers&#8217; investments in digital assets and addresses the critical issue of Proof of Reserves for exchanges.</p></blockquote>
<p>She also stated that the approval of the HB 166 bill &#8220;represents an essential step in ensuring the stability and security of the digital asset market.&#8221; Similarly, she emphasized the importance of requiring exchanges to provide Proof of Reserves, proving their ability to cover all user funds.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Proof of Reserves requirement in this bill is exactly what should be required by custodians to demonstrate that they hold sufficient assets to cover all customer deposits.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Proof of Reserves requirement would prevent exchanges from being used to commit fraud or scams like FTX, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/13-biggest-crypto-scandals-and-controversial-stories-of-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">categorized</a> as one of the largest <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/video/2022/dec/13/one-of-the-biggest-financial-frauds-in-us-history-ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-charged-video" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">financial frauds</a> in US history, through which, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/maxine-waters-is-not-playing-with-sbf-says-it-is-imperative-that-he-attends-their-hearing/" data-wpel-link="internal">according</a> to Congresswoman Maxine Waters, thousands of American citizens lost millions of dollars.</p>
<p>Proof of Reserves is a process by which a cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binances-bitcoin-reserves-are-101-backed-confirms-auditor/" data-wpel-link="internal">demonstrates</a> that it holds sufficient funds to cover customer deposits. This transparency helps protect customers&#8217; assets and can increase trust in the exchange.</p>
<p>In contrast, traditional banks use a fractional reserve system, in which <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/monetarypolicy/reservereq.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">they are not required</a> to hold the full amount of customers&#8217; deposits in reserve, which can create liquidity issues during times of financial stress. While it is true that banks, due to their size and regulatory oversight, may be less likely to destabilize than smaller exchanges, both systems can <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/big-trouble-for-european-banking-as-credit-suisse-flashes-warning-signs/" data-wpel-link="internal">face risks</a> during extreme events or crises.</p>
<h2>Texas Becomes a Regulatory Role Model</h2>
<p>Thanks to this new law, the state of Texas has become a regulatory role model for other US jurisdictions, possibly being replicated or used as a template to improve regulations that continue to be a problem for cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-to-close-operations-in-the-us-due-to-regulatory-hurdles/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em> recently, Bittrex, one of the largest and oldest US exchanges, announced the closure of its operations due to the uncertain regulatory environment in the country that has become an obstacle for such businesses.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-cftc-sues-binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao-bitcoin-plunges-by-1400-immediately/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance</a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-is-going-offshore-unless-the-us-changes-regulatory-stance-coinbase-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> are other exchanges that have faced issues with regulators due to the lack of clear laws allowing them to operate smoothly, reaching the point of considering leaving the country.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/texas-house-of-representatives-passes-bill-requiring-proof-of-reserves-for-crypto-exchanges/" rel="nofollow">Texas House of Representatives Passes Bill Requiring Proof of Reserves for Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canada&#8217;s Largest Pension Fund to Stay Away From Crypto After Writing off FTX Investment</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/canadas-largest-pension-fund-to-stay-away-from-crypto-after-writing-off-ftx-investment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 20:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247464</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Canada-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Canada-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[“It’d be unwise for us to rush” into another crypto investment based on what happened with FTX, CEO Taylor said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ontario Teachers&#8217; Pension Plan (OTPP) &#8211; Canada&#8217;s largest single-profession pension plan &#8211; decided not to rush into another cryptocurrency investment following its bad experience with FTX. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization was among the prominent backers of the now-bankrupt exchange, investing $95 million. The dramatic crash, though, shrank that sum to virtually zero.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Change of Heart After the FTX Implosion</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jo Taylor &#8211; Chief Executive Officer of the $190 billion pension plan &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.ft.com/content/29c67711-377c-4435-9c90-280852374e93" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">told</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Financial Times that the entity will refrain from cryptocurrency investments due to the losses triggered by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">the FTX meltdown</a>. He said the decision was based in part on &#8220;feedback from our members,&#8221; who presumably criticized the fund&#8217;s initial interaction with the collapsed platform:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We&#8217;ve had some learnings from the investment. We&#8217;ve had feedback from our members. We regret any loss on their behalf.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">OTPP has previously shown support toward FTX, making two separate investments in 2021 and early 2022 for a total of $95 million. Back then, the exchange was among the leaders in its field while the crypto market was in a bull run. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the fund&#8217;s investment accounted for less than 0.05% of its total assets, OTPP faced criticism (like many others) for dealing with a company whose founder &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) &#8211; is accused of fraudulent activities.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous agencies and failed investors took turns to name the former CEO of FTX as the main culprit behind the demise, arguing his goal was to embezzle assets from customers.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After spending a brief time in a Bahamian jail at the end of last year (shortly after the collapse), he was deported to the USA. However, the local authorities </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">allowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> him to live at his parents&#8217; house under a whopping $250 million bond.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A trial set for the beginning of October will determine whether he had a hand in the event and rule out his possible punishment. If found guilty, the 31-year-old could spend his life behind bars. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CDPQ Lost Funds due to Celsius</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another Canadian pension fund giant that had a bad experience in the crypto field last year is Caisse de dépôt et placement du Québec (CDPQ). It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-pension-fund-cdpq-writes-off-investment-in-celsius/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lost</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $150 million after investing in the cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius. CEO Charles Emond outlined that his entity had conducted proper due diligence before jumping on the bandwagon, albeit it sill parted with the sum:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The due diligence was quite extensive, with many experts and consultants involved. The team came in cautiously. We had a 4% equity stake. The conversations we had internally were pretty straightforward. The teams are accountable for that.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celsius <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the US last summer after pausing withdrawals. Similar to OTPP, CDPQ vowed to stay away from any crypto forays following the unsuccessful investment.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadas-largest-pension-fund-to-stay-away-from-crypto-after-writing-off-ftx-investment/" rel="nofollow">Canada&#8217;s Largest Pension Fund to Stay Away From Crypto After Writing off FTX Investment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scottish Woman to Sell Her House After Losing Almost $200K in Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/scottish-woman-to-sell-her-house-after-losing-almost-200k-in-crypto-scam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247110</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Jennifer ended up with an outstanding debt of approximately $190,000 after being conned by crypto fraudsters.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A resident of Scotland&#8217;s county Lanarkshire was left with a £150,000 debt (almost $190,000) after falling victim to a cryptocurrency fraud. She is now forced to sell her home to avoid additional financial issues.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The woman sought support from Advice Direct Scotland and the local police, but the entities could not help her retrieve the funds.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;It&#8217;s Absolutely Horrific&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jennifer </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://news.stv.tv/west-central/woman-faced-with-selling-home-after-cryptocurrency-scam-using-martin-lewis-led-to-150k-debt" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">decided</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to invest her money into a crypto scheme after seeing a dubious advert on Facebook featuring the advice expert Martin Lewis.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Martin Lewis was exactly why I looked at investing,&#8221; she explained.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The British journalist is the creator of a website that gives advice on money-saving techniques. He has also been a vocal advocate against fraudsters who have used his image in the past.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, Jennifer believed in the legitimacy of the project and put in nearly $190,000 at the beginning of the year via Revolut. After investing for ten days in a row, her bank started blocking some of the transfers, making her doubt that something was wrong.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jennifer felt &#8220;devastated&#8221; when realizing that she was caught in the web of crypto scammers. She also said her outstanding debt was so high that she had to sell her home to avoid further financial problems:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I&#8217;ve never been in debt in my life, I&#8217;ve never taken out a loan in my life, I&#8217;ve never had a credit card bill. I can&#8217;t actually quite believe what&#8217;s happened to me, it&#8217;s absolutely horrific. It&#8217;s taken me a long time to get to where I am, and the thought of losing this home, obviously for the sake of my children, is horrific.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Scottish resident believes she has been the perfect target for the criminals since she has been &#8220;a very vulnerable person.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Words wouldn&#8217;t describe how I&#8217;m feeling at the moment. I feel sick every day,&#8221; she concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unfortunately for her, the local police and Advice Direct Scotland classified her case as a scam, so she could not reclaim the lost money.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Martin Lewis emphasized, saying this incident made him feel &#8220;sick.&#8221; He also warned people never to invest in schemes that feature his image:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If you see me in an advert, it&#8217;s a scam. I do not do adverts, and I have the inglorious title of being the person whose face is used in more scam adverts than anyone else.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scams Are Not Location-Bound</span></h2>
<p>Unfortunately, Jennifer&#8217;s case is just one in a series of scams that have recently taken place across the globe.<span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Another example is a Hong Kong woman who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-woman-loses-her-life-savings-in-a-crypto-scam-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lost</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> her life savings worth almost $900,000.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">She fell prey to a fraudster who contacted her on Instagram and urged her to invest in digital assets with the promise of great returns. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">When the woman attempted to withdraw some of her funds, she was requested to pay a certain fee. She even tried to borrow money from her daughter before realizing she had been conned. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Hong Kong law enforcement agents classified the case as &#8220;obtaining property by deception:&#8221; a crime that is punishable by up to ten years in jail. However, the authorities have not yet detained any suspects. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/scottish-woman-to-sell-her-house-after-losing-almost-200k-in-crypto-scam/" rel="nofollow">Scottish Woman to Sell Her House After Losing Almost $200K in Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenSea Pro Retaliates Blur&#8217;s Dominance in NFT Market: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/opensea-pro-retaliates-blurs-dominance-in-nft-market-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 15:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenSea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247182</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/opensea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/opensea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of new players has changed the dynamics in the NFT market. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blur appears to have lost its title as the world&#8217;s most popular NFT marketplace.</p>
<p>OpenSea Pro was rebranded and unveiled to court active traders from Blur. The latter was eating away at OpenSea&#8217;s market share since its launch last October. The counteroffensive proved somewhat successful as data suggest that the new &#8220;polished&#8221; NFT aggregator has surpassed Blur by daily transaction count.</p>
<ul>
<li>Delphi Digital&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/Delphi_Digital/status/1648360275630866434" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">analysis</a> indicates that OpenSea Pro has surpassed transactions since rebranding. This essentially means that NFT traders are conducting more transactions on OpenSea Pro than on Blur, despite both platforms offering 0% fees and similar features.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/opensea-launches-new-polished-zero-fee-nft-aggregator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of OpenSea Pro, an aggregator geared toward active traders, was highly tactical as it boasted zero fees for a promotional period and advanced order type in the wake of fierce competition from its rival.</li>
<li>Hence, one of the main reasons for OpenSea being well-received could be due to the fact that pro traders are looking to benefit from the new NFT rewards in anticipation of higher opportunity costs.</li>
<li>A potential airdrop could be another factor catalyzing this trend by enticing new users.</li>
<li>Blur&#8217;s bidding and listing incentives, on the other hand, have become relatively saturated. Delphi Digital stated that it has become difficult to earn points, despite the 2x multiplier incentives that last through May 1.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As Blur’s incentives taper off over time, we may continue to see higher transaction activity on OpenSea Pro.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>A majority of NFT trading volume originated from Blur in Q1 2023. Within six months, the platform managed to dethrone former market leader OpenSea.</li>
<li>But there appears to be a rapid shift in the NFT landscape, thanks to OpenSea Pro&#8217;s release. Blur&#8217;s market share <a href="https://dune.com/queries/2334818/3830714" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">shrunk</a> from 49.3% to 27.9% this month.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/opensea-pro-retaliates-blurs-dominance-in-nft-market-data/" rel="nofollow">OpenSea Pro Retaliates Blur&#8217;s Dominance in NFT Market: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Constantly Shaded CZ Before FTX Collapsed: Binance CSO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-constantly-shaded-cz-before-ftx-collapsed-binance-cso/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 13:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247491</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/CZ_SBF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/CZ_SBF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Binance executive clarified that SBF's degenerative remarks were not behind the CZ’s decision to liquidate Binance's FTT holdings.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Patrick Hilmann, the Chief Strategy Officer (CSO) of leading crypto exchange Binance, alleged that Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the founder and former CEO of the now-defunct rival exchange FTX, consistently criticized Binance&#8217;s CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) before FTX&#8217;s collapse, a behavior Hilmann referred to as &#8220;shading.&#8221;</p>
<p class="p2">In a recent <span class="s1">tweet</span>, the CSO disclosed that SBF was fond of spreading fake rumors about CZ and often called him an &#8220;evil Chinese.&#8221;</p>
<h2 class="p2">SBF Constantly Shaded CZ</h2>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A great read by <a href="https://twitter.com/WilliamCohan?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@WilliamCohan</a> at <a href="https://twitter.com/PuckNews?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@PuckNews</a>. One thing they missed, Sam was CONSTANTLY spreading fake rumors about <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@cz_binance</a>, because shading him as an &#8220;evil Chinese&#8221; was critical to his scam. You can&#8217;t pretend to be Luke Skywalker without Darth Vader.<a href="https://t.co/oi9JxsqPyz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/oi9JxsqPyz</a></p>
<p>— Patrick Hillmann (@PRHillmann) <a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1649163010563358722?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="p2">Hilmann&#8217;s tweet highlighted a <a href="https://t.co/oi9JxsqPyz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">report</span></a> by veteran business writer William Cohan where Anthony Scaramucci, popularly known as &#8220;The Mooch,&#8221; an American financier and the founder of SkyBridge Capital, discussed the state of his relationship with SBF before FTX met its demise.</p>
<p class="p2">Among other things, Scaramucci mentioned that he had been on a $1 billion fundraising trip with SBF to the United Arab Emirates (UAE) in the weeks leading up to the FTX saga.</p>
<p class="p2">As <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-seeking-1-billion-financing-to-raise-valuation-to-32-billion-reports/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">reported</span></a> in September, FTX had been in talks with several investors, seeking to conduct a billion-dollar raise to increase its valuation to $32 billion. Part of the funds to be raised was supposed to rescue other firms hit by the crypto winter.</p>
<p class="p2">During the trip, SBF met with some officials in Dubai, including the UAE Sovereign wealth fund, and Scaramucci was absent from most of those meetings as he had other businesses to attend to. However, a colleague eventually informed Scaramucci that SBF had been bad-mouthing CZ during those meetings.</p>
<h2 class="p2">A Norm</h2>
<p class="p2">The Mooch disclosed that SBF&#8217;s behavior was worrisome, as politeness was deemed necessary in the corporate world due to the unpredictability of life. Moreover, CZ could easily hear about the degenerating remarks.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;He was lighting CZ up. And these are small towns. They look glitzy from a travel brochure, but trust me, these are small, very connected, interconnected towns. It got back to CZ,” Scaramucci said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">Scaramucci further suggested that SBF&#8217;s remarks must have pushed CZ to announce that he would <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-will-stay-in-the-free-market-says-cz-after-rejecting-alamedas-offer/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">liquidate</span></a> his $500 million investment in FTX&#8217;s native token (FTT). However, Hilmann <a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1649163254927687683?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">clarified</span></a> that SBF&#8217;s actions had nothing to do with CZ&#8217;s decision, as the degenerative remarks had become a norm.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-constantly-shaded-cz-before-ftx-collapsed-binance-cso/" rel="nofollow">SBF Constantly Shaded CZ Before FTX Collapsed: Binance CSO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Will Be Bitcoin&#8217;s Price During the Next Halving, According to PlanB&#8217;s S2F Model</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-will-be-bitcoins-price-during-the-next-halving-according-to-planbs-s2f-model/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247535</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinMoon.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinMoon.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The controversial model sees bitcoin more than doubling its USD value within the next year or so.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite its previous success, the stock-to-flow model attracted numerous opponents in the past year, given its failure to predict bitcoin&#8217;s price in 2022.</p>
<p>Its creator, though, remains a believer and outlined the possible scenarios in play for BTC for the next halving, which is supposed to take place in a year.</p>
<h2>S2F Places BTC at $60K</h2>
<p>A lot has been said about the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stock-to-flow-s2f-model/" data-wpel-link="internal">S2F model</a> in the past several years, with most bitcoin maxis supporting it, given its bullish price predictions, while many others have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-s2f-model-is-flawed-argues-cryptoquant-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">criticized</a> it in times of inaccuracy. It takes under consideration the stock as the size of existing reserves (or stockpiles) and the flow – the annual supply of bitcoins on the market.</p>
<p>The model had a good run for the first few years after PlanB laid it out, hitting several of its targets. However, it failed to come even close to reaching its most recent predictions, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/planb-insists-s2f-model-points-to-100000-bitcoin-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">surpassing</a> the six-digit price tag by the end of last year, despite PlanB&#8217;s assertions.</p>
<p>The halving, the event that slashes BTC&#8217;s production by half approximately every four years (210,000 blocks), is an essential part of the model since it reduces the flow (annual supply). With the next one supposed to take place in roughly a year, according to current estimations, PlanB outlined where bitcoin will be in terms of USD price at that point.</p>
<p>He asserted that the asset will trade at around $60,000 (or more than 2x from its current price), and will keep going up after the fourth halving takes place.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Saying S2F model is &#8220;wrong/invalid/broken&#8221;, means saying BTC price pumps after 2012, 2016, 2020 halvings (red arrows) are coincidences, random, unrelated to halvings.<br />
Possible, but I disagree. IMO 21M cap, supply schedule, 4y halving cycle are fundamental to BTC price. IMO the… <a href="https://t.co/2ZOUGPhVtM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/2ZOUGPhVtM</a></p>
<p>— PlanB (@100trillionUSD) <a href="https://twitter.com/100trillionUSD/status/1649295671541858308?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bitcoin and Metcalfe&#8217;s Law</h2>
<p>PlanB also touched upon Metcalfe&#8217;s Law, which argues that the financial value or impact of a (telecoms) network is proportional to the number of connected and operating users, to substantiate its BTC price prediction. Although Metcalfe&#8217;s Law typically refers to a certain type of network, the Bitcoin blockchain also works as one, and it has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wholecoiner-addresses-with-more-than-1-bitcoin-doubled-since-2016/" data-wpel-link="internal">increasing</a> in terms of active users and BTC holders.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Metcalfe&#8217;s Law says: value of a network = number of users squared (N^2)</p>
<p>S2F Model says: value of an asset = scarcity cubed (S2F^3)</p>
<p>So if S2F 2x then value 8x (2x2x2)<br />
Oh, and April 2024 halving will 2x <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> S2F<br />
Probably nothing<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/UtZiMe1c4h" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/UtZiMe1c4h</a></p>
<p>— PlanB (@100trillionUSD) <a href="https://twitter.com/100trillionUSD/status/1649443018741514241?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-will-be-bitcoins-price-during-the-next-halving-according-to-planbs-s2f-model/" rel="nofollow">This Will Be Bitcoin&#8217;s Price During the Next Halving, According to PlanB&#8217;s S2F Model</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Tumbles to 25-Day Low as APT, OKB Slump 10%: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-tumbles-to-25-day-low-as-apt-okb-slump-10-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 08:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247542</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTC_APT_OKB_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTC_APT_OKB_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The altcoins have dumped hard, with Dogecoin sliding below $0.08. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s nosedives continued in the past 24 hours, with the cryptocurrency falling to its lowest position in April of $27,000.</p>
<p>Most altcoins have suffered even more. Dogecoin keeps plunging hard, while APT and OKB have dumped the most from the mid-cap alts.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s April Low</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency went on a roll on April 10 when it skyrocketed to and beyond $30,000 for the first time since last June. It went on to chart its highest price point at just over $31,000 later that week on April 14.</p>
<p>The following week was less volatile, with BTC maintaining $30,000 for most of it. However, the landscape changed on April 19 when the asset <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-struggles-at-29k-but-pepe-hype-carries-on-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">plummeted</a> to $29,000 in hours. The situation <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-lost-90b-in-2-days-as-btc-slips-below-28k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">worsened</a> in the next few days, with BTC first dumping to $28,000 before going all the way down to $27,100 earlier today.</p>
<p>The latter became the asset&#8217;s lowest price position since March 28. As of now, bitcoin still trades inches above $27,000, and it&#8217;s 3% down on the day and over 10% weekly. Its market capitalization has declined to under $530 billion after tapping $600 billion days ago. Its dominance over the alts, though, has taken a breather and is close to 46%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247543" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247543" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-247543" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-19-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247543" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>APT, OKB, DOGE Drop Hard</h2>
<p>As it typically happens when BTC heads south, so do most alternative coins. Ethereum is a prime example. The second-largest crypto stood above $2,100 less than a week ago after the completion of the Shapella update. Since then, though, it has lost over $250 and now trades at $1,850 after losing 4% on a daily scale.</p>
<p>Similar drops are evident from Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, Solana, Polkadot, Litecoin, and Shiba Inu. Dogecoin has dumped the most from the top 10 alts, with a 7% decline. As a result, DOGE currently sits beneath $0.08.</p>
<p>Further losses come from Avalanche (-7%), Chainlink (-6%), ICP (-6%), FIL (-6%), GRT (-7%), and others. Aptos and OKB have plummeted the most &#8211; by over 9% each to $10 and $48, respectively.</p>
<p>The crypto market cap has seen another $30 billion gone and is down to $1.150 trillion. The metric has lost over $130 billion in the past few days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247544" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247544" style="width: 1858px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-247544" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1858" height="738" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15.jpg 1858w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15-300x119.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15-1024x407.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15-768x305.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15-1536x610.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-15-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1858px) 100vw, 1858px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247544" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-tumbles-to-25-day-low-as-apt-okb-slump-10-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">BTC Tumbles to 25-Day Low as APT, OKB Slump 10%: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitBoy Crypto Referred to FBI After Failed Court Appearance</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitboy-crypto-referred-to-fbi-after-failed-court-appearance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 04:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247517</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A popular crypto influencer is avoiding his court appearance related to an alleged harassment campaign he launched against a lawyer representing FTX investors. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto community influencer and Youtuber Ben “BitBoy” Armstrong has been referred to the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) after refusing to appear for a court hearing surrounding his promotion of FTX. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Armstrong gloated about his decision to skip the Florida court session, posting a picture of himself online on a beach saying he “don’t give af.”</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">BitBoy </span><span style="font-weight: 400">released</span><span style="font-weight: 400"> his tweet on Thursday at 10 am ET – precisely when the hearing was scheduled to begin.</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I am supposed to be in court today.</p>
<p>I’m not. Why?</p>
<p>Because I don’t give AF</p>
<p>RECKLESSNESS SPONSORED BY <a href="https://t.co/RtFomcGS5v" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/RtFomcGS5v</a> <a href="https://t.co/t9XqsNd6da" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/t9XqsNd6da</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ben Armstrong (@Bitboy_Crypto) <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitboy_Crypto/status/1649050406247604224?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">He released another tweet </span><a href="https://twitter.com/Bitboy_Crypto/status/1649059142546407425" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">mocking</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the plaintiff in the case, Adam Moskowitz, who accused BitBoy of launching a harassment campaign against him. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Moskowitz serves as a lawyer representing plaintiffs in a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-youtube-influencers-slammed-with-class-action-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">lawsuit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against multiple Youtubers that promoted failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX – one of which includes BitBoy. Other accused influencers included Kevin Paffrath, Brian Jung, Graham Stephan </span><span style="font-weight: 400">Tom Nash, and Erika Kullberg.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Following the charges, Bitboy levied a torrent of angry messages toward Moskowitz over Twitter, sharing emails he </span><a href="https://twitter.com/Bitboy_Crypto/status/1638293656733106176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1638293656733106176%7Ctwgr%5E63bcc8ec77f7ddb7a2fd4384825ab5698078b185%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fdecrypt.co%2F125630%2Flawyer-adam-moskowitz-fbi-bitboy-threatening-emails-calls" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">sent</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to the lawyer calling him a “pussy” and a “bitch.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Moskowitz contacted his local police and the FBI about BitBoy earlier this month, saying he felt “threatened” by what he or his followers might do to him. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Multiple reports state that Judge Melissa Damian was furious about Armstrong’s absence. The influencer’s attorney Jason Rindenau said BitBoy could appear before the court in May while he attends the Miami Bitcoin conference. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In response, Damian said she would issue a warrant for Armstrong’s arrest if he doesn’t appear before Monday. She also said she’d report his conduct to the FBI, and ordered him to stop communicating publicly about Moskowitz – an order he has violated already. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">“It’s weird people don’t realize I have real lawyers who actually know how to practice law unlike the ambulance chasing Adam Moskowitz,” said BitBoy on Thursday. “I’m not flying by the seat of my pants out here.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">BitBoy himself filed a defamation suit last year against fellow Youtuber Erling Mengshoel Jr (aka “Atozy”), but later </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitboy-crypto-drops-defamation-lawsuit-against-atozy-after-backlash/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">dropped the charges</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> following major public backlash.  </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitboy-crypto-referred-to-fbi-after-failed-court-appearance/" rel="nofollow">BitBoy Crypto Referred to FBI After Failed Court Appearance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini Strengthens its Presence in Asia With a New Office in India</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 23:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247407</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gemini_India.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gemini_India.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gemini's new office in Gurgaon, India will be its second-largest engineering hub behind the one in the USA.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US-based cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Gemini &#8211; announced plans to establish a new engineering hub in Gurgaon, India. This will be the company&#8217;s second Asian location, as previously it opened an office in Singapore.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The expansion outside the US coincides with the regulatory uncertainty in the States. The CEO of Coinbase &#8211; Brian Armstrong &#8211; recently opined that many American crypto firms could relocate if the watchdogs continue their scrutiny over the industry.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Setting Eyes on Asia</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pravjit Tiwana &#8211; the newly appointed CEO of Gemini Asia Pacific &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-to-expand-global-engineering-and-operations-teams-with-new-india-office" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">explained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the company has picked India as its next destination because it has &#8220;deep respect and admiration&#8221; for its &#8220;tradition of engineering excellence.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He said the center in Gurgaon has already started looking for software engineers and technical product managers that could lead Gemini&#8217;s efforts on Asian soil. Tiwana added that the office will be the second-largest company hub behind the one in the United States. The exchange has also set foot in Singapore, the United Kingdom, and Ireland over the past few years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CEO outlined that the products and features built in the new location could be used by institutional and retail clients in more than 70 nations. The newly-formed team will aim to develop next-generation Web and mobile user experience and introduce feature sets for NFT and crypto marketplaces. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Although past experience in Web3 and crypto technologies is not a prerequisite, we are seeking builders who are inspired to learn quickly and work on cutting-edge technologies like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web3,&#8221; Tiwana added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latest foray seems like a breath of fresh air for Gemini, which took a serious beating during the bear market. It laid off a chunk of its employees in the summer of 2022 and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-lays-of-10-of-employees-due-to-crypto-industrys-bad-actors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">continued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the dismissal spree in January this year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It also faced issues with the US SEC and the New York Department of Financial Services. The securities regulator </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-files-complaint-against-gemini-and-genesis-for-allegedly-selling-unregistered-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a complaint against Gemini for allegedly selling securities to retail investors in America. For its part, the NYDFS </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/nydfs-probes-gemini-over-claims-concerning-the-earn-program-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the exchange of misleading Earn customers.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">US Crypto Exodus on its Way?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lack of a comprehensive regulatory framework on digital asset operations in the States could be one reason why some American firms have started strengthening their global presence.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase&#8217;s CEO Brian Armstrong recently urged the domestic authorities to apply pertinent rules on the space to prevent the outflow of companies and talent:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This is the reason why we need clarity about legislation and regulation onshore because if the UK doesn&#8217;t have this, if the US doesn&#8217;t have this, these firms are going to be built in offshore havens.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">secured</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a regulatory license in Bermuda earlier this week and revealed plans to establish an offshore derivatives marketplace in the region.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/" rel="nofollow">Gemini Strengthens its Presence in Asia With a New Office in India</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Californian Regulator Takes Action Against AI-Based Alleged Crypto Ponzi Schemes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/californian-regulator-takes-action-against-ai-based-alleged-crypto-ponzi-schemes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247425</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/California.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/California.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the DFPI, one of the companies may even be using an AI-generated CEO.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Californian Department of Financial Protection And Innovation (DFPI) issued cease and desist orders against five companies profiting from the hype around AI to attempt to dupe gullible investors.</p>
<h2>All Hype, Little Info</h2>
<p>According to the regulator, all five companies violate securities law by offering unregistered securities to the public.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Scammers like to deceive investors by using phony CEOs, sham algorithms, &amp; Ponzi schemes. Today, we&#8217;ve issued desist and refrain orders to five entities/individuals who violated CA securities laws. For more information: <a href="https://t.co/gj13z2OE4G" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/gj13z2OE4G</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/investing?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#investing</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/hyip?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#hyip</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cryptonews?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Cryptonews</a> <a href="https://t.co/MXHPYwVIny" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/MXHPYwVIny</a></p>
<p>— CA Department of Financial Protection &amp; Innovation (@CaliforniaDFPI) <a href="https://twitter.com/CaliforniaDFPI/status/1648728681232347137?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Furthermore, the firms involved are accused of lying to their customers by omission, misrepresenting, or even allegedly outright falsifying their financial model.</p>
<p>Predictably, all five companies offered high-yield investments, often promising minimum returns every single day. Not only is this a red flag – since guaranteed returns on investments are pretty much impossible to achieve – the promised minimum ROIs were larger than one could reasonably hope to achieve even by betting on blue-chip opportunities.</p>
<p>The twist? According to spokespeople for these companies, the promised results could be achieved with the help of AI.</p>
<h2>Cease and Desist Orders Issued</h2>
<p>According to DFPI Commissioner Clothilde Hewitt, the <a href="https://dfpi.ca.gov/2023/04/19/dfpi-launches-sweep-of-investment-fraud-claiming-ties-to-artificial-intelligence/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">targeted</a> entities are using the recent hype around AI LLMs to entice investors into making potentially grave errors.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Today’s enforcement actions continue the DFPI’s crack down on investor fraud. Scammers are taking advantage of the recent buzz around artificial intelligence to entice investors into bogus schemes. We will continue our efforts to protect California consumers and investors by going after these unscrupulous actors.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The most brazen company to be targeted by the DFPI is Maxpread Technologies, which promised a minimum ROI of 0.6% per day. In fact, the firm appears to operate like a regular Ponzi scheme. It is also believed to be using an AI-generated <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4bp84WyjxB4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">representation</a> of a fictional CEO, although this has not yet been confirmed.</p>
<p>Up next are Harvest Keeper, Visque Capital, and QuantFund, all offering between 1% and 4.81% guaranteed APRs. The companies in question all named AI as the reason that they could offer this guarantee, as opposed to other firms that promised high-flying possible APRs.</p>
<p>The last of the companies to be targeted by the regulators is Coinbot, which is essentially just another crypto-trading bot – but this time, powered by AI. Coinbot offered investors a minimum 1.5% daily ROI, purportedly earned from trades carried out by the bot. In reality, the company simply paid older investors with funds gathered from newer investors.</p>
<p>The current buzz around AI has gathered much interest from VCs, existing blue-chip corporations, and retail investors alike. Until the hype cools down, we will likely see many more attempts to cash in on the trend, similar to the shitcoin boom of 2017.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/californian-regulator-takes-action-against-ai-based-alleged-crypto-ponzi-schemes/" rel="nofollow">Californian Regulator Takes Action Against AI-Based Alleged Crypto Ponzi Schemes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
