<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 16:00:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>FancyCrypto: Making Crypto Mining More Accessible</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fancycrypto-making-crypto-mining-more-accessible/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 01:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254522</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Mining &#8211; the process of verifying transactions and packing them in blocks to send to the blockchain &#8211; is a critical component of many networks, including the largest one &#8211; Bitcoin. It’s the foundation around the entire cryptocurrency ecosystem (for a large part) is built on, and it is absolutely paramount to the concepts of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mining &#8211; the process of verifying transactions and packing them in blocks to send to the blockchain &#8211; is a critical component of many networks, including the largest one &#8211; Bitcoin.</p>
<p>It’s the foundation around the entire cryptocurrency ecosystem (for a large part) is built on, and it is absolutely paramount to the concepts of crypto. However, it’s also very technical.</p>
<p>It’s a process that requires complex technical setups in terms of both hardware and software, sufficient electrical supply, and, if it’s made efficient &#8211; a dedicated storage space that’s being kept at the right temperature.</p>
<p>The above in itself put forward plenty of barriers to entry for many retail investors who don’t have access to significant capital. In essence, it bars retail investors from meaningfully participating in a way they can also earn a considerable profit.</p>
<p>Cloud mining comes as an attempted solution. The following explains what Cloud Mining is and looks at one of the more popular providers.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254524" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" alt="fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>What is Crypto Cloud Mining?</h2>
<p>The crux of the concept comes from the word cloud. It’s a virtual space. Cloud mining allows retail investors to put as much money as they are comfortable with and, in return, rent cloud mining space from a company that normally operates (or rents itself) data centers.</p>
<p>In essence, cloud mining is the way to mine crypto using a remote data center with shared processing power.</p>
<p>This particular type of mining allows users to mine BTC or other cryptocurrencies without having to manage hardware on their own.</p>
<p>The mining rigs themselves are housed and maintained in a facility that’s owned by a mining company. The customer simply needs to register and purchase mining contracts or shares &#8211; depending on how the agreement is framed.</p>
<p>An important consideration here is that users are strongly advised to make proper research into the cloud mining provider that they choose. Just as with a lot of other initiatives in the industry, there have been instances of fraud, so it’s important to maintain vigilance.</p>
<h2>What is FancyCrypto?</h2>
<p><a href="https://fancycrypto.pro/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">FancyCrypto</a> is a cloud mining provider, and according to its website, it has earned the trust of hundreds of thousands of users.</p>
<p>The company’s mission is to make mining more accessible to everyone, enabling access to large-scale technology and industrial data centers from virtually any device or location. The website claims that FancyCrypto operates between 2% and 10% of the world’s cloud mining hash rate.</p>
<p>FancyCrypto was founded in London in 2016. As a pioneering cloud mining company, Fancy Crypto has already carved out a reputation as being a trustworthy hash rate provider for over 360,000 users all over the world. It wants to provide access to large-scale industrial data centers aided by cutting-edge technologies to make cloud mining available to everyone.</p>
<p>The platform allows the mining of multiple cryptocurrencies, which include: Bitcoin, Litecoin, DOGE, Ethereum Classic, and others. It also offers a range of different packages that users can purchase, starting from cheaper ones for $10 and getting to as high as $5,000. The daily profits also range, depending on the contract of choice. <a href="https://fancycrypto.com/plans" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Their packages</a> include:</p>
<p><strong>Free cloud mining</strong>: Such a contract stays valid for one day and costs $10. It has a fixed return of $10.15.</p>
<p><strong>Experienced project cloud mining</strong>: It is priced at $100 and is valid within your days. Its fixed return is $105</p>
<p><strong>Ethereum project cloud mining</strong>: It is priced at 300, valid for five days, and has a fixed return of $324.</p>
<p>The platform has a range of other packages of up to $5,000, all of which you can check on the official website.</p>
<p>Some of the features of cloud mining through FancyCrypto include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed Fees</li>
</ul>
<p>There are no hidden fees or commissions &#8211; users are able to monitor every transaction in a transparent dashboard.</p>
<ul>
<li>Ease of use</li>
</ul>
<p>There’s no hassle involved, as users don’t have to set up their own mining hardware and install relevant software. The platform’s dashboard is made to be easy and comprehensible, even for people without experience.</p>
<ul>
<li>Multiple choices</li>
</ul>
<p>Many platforms only offer Bitcoin cloud mining. FancyCrypto has a more versatile range of products that users can choose between.</p>
<p><strong>Summary </strong></p>
<p>FancyCrypto has been highly impactful to the cryptocurrency cloud mining scene. It has emerged as a preferred choice for many users who seek a feature-packed, economical, and hassle-free mining experience.</p>
<p>If you want to explore further details, take a look at the official website: <a href="https://fancycrypto.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://fancycrypto.com/</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fancycrypto-making-crypto-mining-more-accessible/" rel="nofollow">FancyCrypto: Making Crypto Mining More Accessible</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Years in Prison for Arizona Entrepreneur for Offering Shadow Banking Services to Crypto Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/6-years-in-prison-for-arizona-entrepreneur-for-offering-shadow-banking-services-to-crypto-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254041</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Jail.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Jail.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Former Co-Owner of Minnesota Vikings' acquisition of a stake in the AAF, in part, led to its collapse and subsequent bankruptcy declaration, the prosecutors said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A joint investigation by the FBI’s Money Laundering Squad and Internal Revenue Service-Criminal Investigations led to a 75-month prison sentence for 64-year-old Arizona entrepreneur Reginald Fowler. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A former co-owner of the professional American football team Minnesota Vikings, Fowler has also been asked by the court to pay a forfeiture of $74.02 million and restitution of $5.31 million to the Association of American Football (AAF), a short-lived American football minor league. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The prosecution was led by the United States Attorney’s Office’s Money Laundering and Transnational Criminal Enterprises Unit. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Offering Shadow Banking Services</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Damian Williams, US Attorney’s Office, Southern District of New York (SDNY)) in a PR on June 5, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/former-co-owner-minnesota-vikings-sentenced-75-months-prison-providing-shadow-banking" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Fowler processed nearly $750 million of transactions for cryptocurrency exchanges acting as a payment processor while his company Global Trading Solution did not have a license for money transmitting business as required by the US federal laws. While doing so, he also lied to US banks.  </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“FOWLER also directed other individuals to include false information on wire transfer instructions to further deceive banks about the nature of GTS’s business. In less than ten months, FOWLER processed approximately $750 million in cryptocurrency transactions in various currencies,” the PR from Attorney’s office said.  </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Defrauding American Football League </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He was also found guilty of defrauding the Association of American Football, in which he acquired a significant stake by investing customers’ funds claiming them to be his personal wealth.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“As he did when opening bank accounts, FOWLER lied to AAF executives, telling them that the funds in the GTS bank accounts derived from real estate investments as well as government contracts and that the tens of millions of dollars in the GTS accounts were liquid assets he could use to invest in the AAF,” Williams said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In part, due to Fowler’s lies, the AAF declared bankruptcy in April 2019. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Catching Up with Crypto Crimes</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Given the rising number of cryptocurrency-related crime and fraud cases, the US Department of Justice (DoJ) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-doj-established-a-unit-of-prosecutors-to-limit-crypto-crime/" data-wpel-link="internal">formed</a> the “National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team” in September 2022. Cybersecurity prosecutor Eun Young Choi heads the team of 150 prosecutors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In May, a Russian man was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russian-man-charged-for-200-million-in-ransomware-crimes-involving-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">charged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by the DoJ with being part of three ransomware gangs that netted nearly $200 million through various ransomware attacks targeting police departments, hospitals, and schools.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/6-years-in-prison-for-arizona-entrepreneur-for-offering-shadow-banking-services-to-crypto-exchanges/" rel="nofollow">6 Years in Prison for Arizona Entrepreneur for Offering Shadow Banking Services to Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is The Market Crashing? Binance&#8217;s CZ Chips in on a Few Narratives</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-the-market-crashing-binances-cz-chips-in-on-a-few-narratives/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254697</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CZ chips in on the matter why the market is crashing, as well as touching on a few ongoing narratives. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The market took a beating over the past 24 hours, and certain altcoins performed a lot worse than others.</p>
<p>A lot of the worst-performing cryptocurrencies were also named in the lawsuit that the US Securities and Exchange Commission filed against Coinbase. The agency alleges that they are securities. These include Cardano&#8217;s ADA, Solana&#8217;s SOL, NEAR, Polygon&#8217;s MATIC, and so forth.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is down 3.4%, while Ethereum &#8211; 5.7%. Even though both of them decreased, it&#8217;s nowhere near the 20% decline that the above altcoins are charting.</p>
<p>Now, CZ &#8211; Binance&#8217;s CEO &#8211; chips in on some of the ongoing narratives.</p>
<ul>
<li>Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, chipped in on why the market is crashing. He outlined that &#8220;no one really knows&#8221; while also explaining that &#8220;there are many sellers and buyers in a market, everyone may have their own reasons.&#8221;</li>
<li>However, he also touched on a few ongoing narratives, sharing his thoughts on the matter.</li>
<li>CZ said that there&#8217;s a false narrative of Binance converting its holdings to fiat.</li>
<li>Instead, he claimed that the fiat and stablecoin reserves of Binance decreased &#8211; they are the ones used to pay for short-term salaries or expenses.</li>
<li>He also said that the crypto reserves of the exchange increased throughout the past months, weeks, and days.</li>
<li>A second narrative that he admitted to having no idea about is the matter of Robinhood and what happened to $1.3 billion worth of alts on the platform.</li>
<li>In any case, CZ explained that there are two emotions that anyone needs to manage in any market &#8211; greed and fear.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Why is the market is going up or down? No one really knows. A lot of people claim to know, and can often pin it on a single (often wrong) reason. In reality, there are many sellers and buyers in a market, everyone may have their own reasons. A few examples.</p>
<p>False narrative:… <a href="https://t.co/LQDkEOK2as" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/LQDkEOK2as</a></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1667439122137358336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-the-market-crashing-binances-cz-chips-in-on-a-few-narratives/" rel="nofollow">Why Is The Market Crashing? Binance&#8217;s CZ Chips in on a Few Narratives</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Third Canadian HODLer Lost Money in Crypto Scams (Study)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/every-third-canadian-hodler-lost-money-in-crypto-scams-study/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254544</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Canada-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Canada-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the survey, 35% of Canadian crypto owners have been conned by crypto scammers. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Research carried out by contributors of the Toronto Metropolitan University (TMU) estimated that 35% of Canadians owning digital assets had fallen victim to crypto fraud.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The study further determined that approximately 9% of the locals have purchased cryptocurrencies or NFTs, with the share being higher among individuals who graduated from universities.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Less Educated People Seem More Likely to Get Scammed</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report, conducted via a representative survey of 2,000 Canadian residents, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dais.ca/reports/risky-business-the-cyber-and-sociotechnical-security-threats-of-crypto-asset-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">showed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that fraudulent schemes related to cryptocurrencies are a serious problem in the country. Per the results, over a third of those who have invested in digital assets have been lured into some sort of scam.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">14% (the largest share) said they had been contacted by a person who presented themselves as a crypto investment manager and who later stole a fee for his &#8220;services.&#8221; 10% admitted sharing their wallet information following a request for additional information, while 7% have purchased digital currencies from a mysterious individual who then disappeared.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;When users fall prey to these cryptocurrency scams, significant financial loss can result, sometimes compromising large amounts of money from lines of credit, credit cards, and life savings. Not only are there financial losses, but also the risk of personal and financial information being stolen. The scale of these types of fraud and scams seems substantial in Canada,&#8221; the research&#8217;s authors warned.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">People from the lower income brackets and those with less education are more likely to get conned. Individuals earning over $50,000 per year and having university degrees seem more aware of the risks in the industry and are more cautious when approached by scammers. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The survey also estimated that most Canadians are wary of cryptocurrency exchanges. Nearly 50% have &#8220;low trust&#8221; in such companies, 25% are &#8220;neutral,&#8221; whereas only 9% have &#8220;high trust.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In comparison, the confidence in local banks is much higher. Just 12% do not believe in domestic banking institutions, while 46% have &#8220;high trust.&#8221;</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_254566" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254566" style="width: 784px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a style="font-weight: bold; background-color: transparent;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254566" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada.png" alt="Canadians' Trust in Crypto Exchanges" width="784" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada.png 1157w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-1024x522.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-768x392.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 784px) 100vw, 784px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254566" class="wp-caption-text">Canadians&#8217; Trust in Crypto Exchanges, Source: DAIS</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The study suggested that roughly one in 10 Canadians have hopped on the crypto bandwagon by purchasing bitcoin, ether, or another digital asset. The majority of investors are men aged between 25 and 35. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Painful Lesson Learned by a Canadian Couple</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While some scams are not that devastating and result mainly in frustration among victims, others could be crucial. One example is an elderly man and his wife from Toronto who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-a-canadian-couple-lost-nearly-300000-in-a-crypto-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">parted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with $300,000 in such a scheme. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The couple wanted to invest their life savings and were approached by an unknown individual online. After presenting themself as &#8220;professional and knowledgeable&#8221; in the investment field, they advised the family to distribute funds on a dubious cryptocurrency platform. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At first, everything seemed legit, and the duo saw their investment growing &#8220;significantly&#8221; in time. However, the problems started when they asked to withdraw some assets. The wrongdoer said they have to pay considerable fees to complete such transactions. Later, the couple saw that their entire investment had vanished, proving their fears that they had fallen victim to a crypto fraud. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fortunately for them, the Toronto Police Service recovered a &#8220;significant portion of lost funds.&#8221; The identity of the criminal who drained the money, though, remained unclear, meaning they could be located in another country.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/every-third-canadian-hodler-lost-money-in-crypto-scams-study/" rel="nofollow">Every Third Canadian HODLer Lost Money in Crypto Scams (Study)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Donates Another $100M to Fund Covid Relief Projects</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-another-100m-to-fund-covid-relief-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 12:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coronavirus (COVID-19)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254487</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Vitalik_Buterin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Vitalik_Buterin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin has pledged a further $100 million to support Covid relief projects.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a rare good news story this week, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin revealed that, along with Polygon’s Sandeep Nailwal, he has pledged another $100 million for Covid relief.</p>
<p>On June 9, Buterin said he and Sandeep “discussed and jointly concluded these and other projects are high-impact and need follow-through grants.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“Hence we decided to put $100 million more to these projects.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Last year, the pair donated a similar amount through the community-driven Crypto Relief project.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Last year <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoRelief_?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@CryptoRelief_</a> led by <a href="https://twitter.com/sandeepnailwal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@sandeepnailwal</a> allocated $100m to Covid research projects I wanted to fund</p>
<p>Sandeep and I discussed and jointly concluded these and other projects are high-impact and need follow through grants. Hence we decided to put $100m more to these projects</p>
<p>— vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1666860069273710606?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Vitalik Supporting Covid Causes</h2>
<p>He said that Crypto Relief has put in $90 million USDC from his original <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indias-cryptorelief-sends-back-100m-of-vitalik-buterins-shib-donation/" data-wpel-link="internal">SHIB donation</a>, and he is adding a further $10 million from his own funds. Vitalik donated 50 trillion SHIB tokens to the project in May 2022.</p>
<p>Crypto Relief is a project started by Buterin and Nailwal to provide long-term strategic funding for healthcare donations in India.</p>
<p>Buterin acknowledged that Covid was still a global problem along with future pandemics. “Work in India continues to be a key part of the solution,” he said before adding that we also need an integrated global approach.</p>
<p>In order to achieve public health solutions, Buterin has pledged a commitment to “insist on maximal viable open-source for anything we fund.”</p>
<h2>Crypto Use for Donations</h2>
<p>He added that another focus is on “solutions that depend not on radical behavior change, but on medical and infrastructure work.” They can be behind-the-scenes, but also need to be transparent and open to public scrutiny, he added.</p>
<p>Crypto is being used for donations for a wide array of causes and projects. These range from relief efforts in war-torn <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-3-crypto-assets-account-for-85-of-70m-crypto-donations-to-ukraine-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ukraine</a> to Turkish earthquake emergency <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-crypto-companies-to-send-aid-packages-to-earthquake-hit-turkey/" data-wpel-link="internal">donations</a> to support Canadian truckers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-donates-another-100m-to-fund-covid-relief-projects/" rel="nofollow">Vitalik Buterin Donates Another $100M to Fund Covid Relief Projects</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altcoins Crash Double Digits, Bitcoin Dominance Soars (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/altcoins-crash-double-digits-bitcoin-dominance-soars-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254680</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Red_Mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Red_Mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Major altcoins are suffering today, but Bitcoin's price is performing relatively well, boosting its dominance considerably.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past 24 hours saw the majority of altcoins crash by a considerable margin and there are no signs of slowing down.</p>
<p>However, there&#8217;s also a clear discrepancy between the price performance of certain altcoins to that of Bitcoin and Ethereum, both of which have remained relatively resilient.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Dominance Soars</h2>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance increased to around 46% (data from CoinGecko). This is a major difference. The metric tracks Bitcoin&#8217;s share relative to that of the rest of the market and is a clear indication of the dynamic between both.</p>
<p>When the BTC dominance rises, it means BTC&#8217;s price is performing better than the altcoin market.</p>
<p>Now, the major cryptocurrency is down 3.1% on the day, which is definitely not good news, but the rest of the market is performing a lot worse. This is why the dominance is increasing.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254682" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254682" style="width: 1530px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254682" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1006231" width="1530" height="972" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231.jpg 1530w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231-300x191.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231-1024x651.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231-768x488.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_price_chart_1006231-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1530px) 100vw, 1530px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254682" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Altcoins Suffering Tremendously</h2>
<p>Cardano, Solana, Polygon, and a lot of other major altcoins are trading well in the red, as seen in the following heatmap.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254683" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254683" style="width: 906px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006232.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254683" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006232.jpg" alt="crypto_heatmap_1006232" width="906" height="751" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006232.jpg 906w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006232-300x249.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006232-768x637.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006232-50x41.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 906px) 100vw, 906px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254683" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Coin360</figcaption></figure>
<p>The main reason behind the plummet seems to be the fact that the SEC has listed a lot of them as securities in their latest lawsuit against Coinbase. Another major trading platform &#8211; Robinhood, also announced plans to start delisting some altcoins in consideration of the above.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that those cryptocurrencies that haven&#8217;t been named in the SEC&#8217;s claim are performing a bit better. For instance, Ethereum&#8217;s ETH is down only about 5%, while Ripple&#8217;s XRP is down around 6%. This is still a lot, but it&#8217;s nowhere near the 20% (and more) that coins like ADA&lt; SOL, and MATIC, among others, lost today.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/altcoins-crash-double-digits-bitcoin-dominance-soars-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Altcoins Crash Double Digits, Bitcoin Dominance Soars (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SMURFS Coin: Is This Memecoin Ready to Challenge SHIB With New CEX Listing Underway?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/smurfs-coin-is-this-memecoin-ready-to-challenge-shib-with-new-cex-listing-underway/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254610</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Memecoins have taken center stage and exploded in popularity, with the likes of PEPE capturing the attention of mainstream investors. But this trend has also given birth to many new and exciting projects &#8211; just like Smurfs Coin, which is now challenging long-standing leaders like Shiba Inu (SHIB). Smurfs Coin Doing Rounds Smurfs Coin (SMURFS) [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Memecoins have taken center stage and exploded in popularity, with the likes of PEPE capturing the attention of mainstream investors.</p>
<p>But this trend has also given birth to many new and exciting projects &#8211; just like Smurfs Coin, which is now challenging long-standing leaders like Shiba Inu (SHIB).</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254614" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2.jpg" alt="smurfs_sponsored_image2" width="1200" height="600" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2.jpg 1200w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2-1024x512.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2-768x384.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image2-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></a></p>
<h2>Smurfs Coin Doing Rounds</h2>
<p><a href="https://smurfs.fun" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Smurfs Coin (SMURFS)</a> is not to be confused with SMURF (Smurf INU) on CoinMarketCap. It’s a captivating memecoin that’s making waves in the world of cryptocurrencies. The team is set in its ways to give even Shiba Inu (SHIB) a run for its money &#8211; an optimistic goal but also a motivating one.</p>
<p>What makes Smurfs Coin intriguing is its unique combination of distinct features, a thriving community, and strategic partnerships. These factors have investors eagerly preparing to hop on board the Smurfs Coin train.</p>
<p>What sets SMURFS apart is its strategic approach to building traction. The development team has cultivated a strong community of supporters and investors through well-executed social media campaigns. This dedicated following eagerly awaits every development and announcement, creating a sense of anticipation and enthusiasm.</p>
<p>The memecoin is soon to be listed on a centralized exchange (CEX) &#8211; a move that’s just around the corner. It’s building up excitement but also speculation among crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<h2>A Major Milestone for SMURFS</h2>
<p>The upcoming listing on a major cryptocurrency exchange is no doubt a significant milestone for Smurfs Coin.</p>
<p>This coveted spot on a CEX has the potential to bring numerous advantages to the memecoin and its investors. It can increase liquidity and expand trading volumes, as well as exposure to a larger pool of potential buyers.</p>
<p>Moreover, being featured on a reputable exchange is also capable of lending legitimacy to SMURFS, which, in turn, can attract other investors.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-254613" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1.jpg" alt="smurfs_sponsored_image1" width="450" height="450" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1-300x300.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1-768x768.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1-239x239.jpg 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/smurfs_sponsored_image1-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px" /></a></p>
<p>The timing is also well-thought-out for Smurfs Coin&#8217;s listing. As cryptocurrencies gain mainstream acceptance, more and more investors are looking for alternative investment opportunities beyond traditional assets.</p>
<p>Memecoins, with their entertainment value and potential for explosive moves, have caught the attention of many. With the media frenzy surrounding Shiba Inu and the rising popularity of other memecoins, the industry is getting excited.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s essential to remember that memecoins can be highly speculative and volatile, and their success hinges on various factors such as community support, market demand, and overall market conditions. As Smurfs Coin prepares for its listing on major exchange platforms within the next nine days, it has the potential to further legitimize the project.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/smurfs-coin-is-this-memecoin-ready-to-challenge-shib-with-new-cex-listing-underway/" rel="nofollow">SMURFS Coin: Is This Memecoin Ready to Challenge SHIB With New CEX Listing Underway?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bloodbath: The Reasons Behind SOL, MATIC, ADA, SAND Crash Today</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bloodbath-the-reasons-behind-sol-matic-ada-sand-crash-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254673</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bloodbath_market_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bloodbath_market_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are a few possible reasons behind today's bloodbath in the altcoin market. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The altcoin market is under fire. Major cryptocurrencies like Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), and many others &#8211; are plummeting in value.</p>
<p>The heatmap below is pretty indicative of the troubles that the market is going through. It also reveals that investors are anything but confident right now.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254674" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254674" style="width: 1167px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254674" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231.jpg" alt="crypto_heatmap_1006231" width="1167" height="758" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231.jpg 1167w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231-300x195.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231-1024x665.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231-768x499.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/crypto_heatmap_1006231-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1167px) 100vw, 1167px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254674" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Coin360</figcaption></figure>
<p>While it&#8217;s anyone&#8217;s guess why exactly that might be, two things happened in the past few days that might provide some sort of an explanation.</p>
<h2>SEC Names 13 Cryptocurrencies Securities</h2>
<p>Earlier this week, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit against Binance, its CEO, and the US arm of the firm.</p>
<p>As if that wasn&#8217;t enough, the very next day, the SEC completed the one-two punch, filing another case against the leading US-based crypto exchange &#8211; Coinbase. While both of the claims have their intricacies, the 101-page file against Coinbase seems to have had a greater impact on the broader market.</p>
<p>The main reason seems to be the fact that the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">compiled</a> a &#8220;non-exhaustive&#8221; list of 13 cryptocurrencies that it considers to fulfill the requirements of being securities.</p>
<p>As one might expect, these include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Cardano (ADA)</li>
<li>Solana (SOL)</li>
<li>Polygon (MATIC)</li>
</ul>
<p>Others on the list are SAND, AXS, FIL, ICP, NEAR, etc.</p>
<p>A broad majority of the above are also tanking in value today. But that might not be the only reason, albeit likely the primary one.</p>
<h2>Robinhood Delisting Spree</h2>
<p>Robinhood is one of the world&#8217;s largest retail trading platforms and a considerable player in the crypto industry for the past couple of years.</p>
<p>However, yesterday, reports <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/06/09/robinhood-delists-solana-sol-cardano-ada-polygon-matic-sec-lawsuits-securities/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">started</a> circling around that it will be delisting tokens for Solana, Cardano, and Polygon.</p>
<p>In light of the above, it appears that investors are starting to price in the potential for legal cases against the above.</p>
<p>Recall that in 2020, the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-the-case-so-far-and-whats-next-for-the-xrp-price/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> a lawsuit against Ripple for conducting an unregistered securities offering, essentially naming XRP &#8211; security. The cryptocurrency tumbled in response, and many exchanges started delisting it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloodbath-the-reasons-behind-sol-matic-ada-sand-crash-today/" rel="nofollow">Bloodbath: The Reasons Behind SOL, MATIC, ADA, SAND Crash Today</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Crashes 23% in a Day as Total Liquidations Near $400 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-crashes-23-in-a-day-as-total-liquidations-near-400-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254665</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cardano_crash_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cardano_crash_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cardano's ADA is taking a massive beating and it appears that the SEC's claims might be behind it.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano is taking a massive beating throughout the past few days. The cryptocurrency is down a whopping 23% in the last 24 hours alone.</p>
<p>The majority of the altcoins are also trading well in the red, triggering liquidations of close to $400 million.</p>
<ul>
<li>Cardano (ADA) and a bunch of other altcoins are plummeting today. ADA alone is down 23% in the past day as investors fear a potential clash with the SEC.</li>
<li>Data from Coinglass shows that the entire market&#8217;s liquidations have ramped up to close to $400 million for the same period.</li>
<li>As <em>CryptoPotato </em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier this week, the SEC filed a lawsuit against Coinbase. In it, the agency claims that a bunch of altcoins are essentially fitting the requirements of being securities, and ADA is among them.</li>
<li>In a recent blog post, Cardano&#8217;s Input Output Global &#8211; the firm behind Cardano&#8217;s ecosystem &#8211; released a statement dismissing the claims that ADA is security.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_254666" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254666" style="width: 1532px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254666" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231.jpg" alt="ada_price_chart_1006231" width="1532" height="975" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231.jpg 1532w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231-300x191.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231-1024x652.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231-768x489.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ada_price_chart_1006231-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1532px) 100vw, 1532px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254666" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-crashes-23-in-a-day-as-total-liquidations-near-400-million/" rel="nofollow">Cardano (ADA) Crashes 23% in a Day as Total Liquidations Near $400 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrencies Can&#8217;t Be Allowed to Undermine Public Trust in Capital Market, Gensler Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrencies-cant-be-allowed-to-undermine-public-trust-in-capital-market-gensler-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254530</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC Chair has been in the eye of a storm since his recent lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler has made his intentions clear about the digital assets class. These are securities, nothing less, he asserted in a recent interaction.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">They should be registered with the agency before being offered to investors or meet the requirements to seek exemptions, a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/08/sec-chair-gensler-says-crypto-frenzy-is-rife-with-hucksters-fraudsters-scam-artists-.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> quoted him. He added that exchanges listing cryptocurrencies must also register themselves with the regulatory agency. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Tokens are Investment Contracts</span></h2>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Congress included a long list of 30-plus items in the definition of a security, including the term &#8216;investment contract&#8217;…. the vast majority of crypto tokens meet the investment contract test. … Thus, crypto security issuers need to register the offer and sale of their investment contracts with the SEC or meet the requirements for an exemption,&#8221; Gensler said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He was speaking remotely at Piper Sandler Global Exchange and FinTech Conference in New York City on June 8. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Hucksters. Fraudsters. Scam artists. Ponzi schemes. The public left in line at the bankruptcy court.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is how the SEC Chair described the current cryptocurrency scene, calling it reminiscent of the time before the federal securities laws came into being in 1933. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stressing the role of regulators in cryptocurrency trading, Gensler asserted that the people&#8217;s trust in the capital market should not be undermined by allowing unregulated crypto securities markets. </span></p>
<blockquote><p>“The crypto securities markets should not be allowed to undermine the well-earned trust the public has in the capital markets. The crypto markets should not be allowed to harm investors,” he added.</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC chair also rejected the idea that there has been a lack of clarity about whether crypto assets are securities. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;When crypto asset market participants go on Twitter or TV and say they lacked &#8216;fair notice&#8217; that their conduct could be illegal, don&#8217;t believe it. … They may have made a calculated economic decision to take the risk of enforcement as the cost of doing business.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lawsuits Against Binance and Coinbase</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Citing irregularities, the SEC filed lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase early this week. The charges against Binance include selling unregistered securities &#8211; BNB and BUSD &#8211; and operating as an unregistered securities exchange and broker-dealer in the US. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawsuit seeks disgorgement of &#8220;ill-gotten funds&#8221; and permanently banning the firm from operating as a crypto and securities business in the US. Acting on the SEC&#8217;s legal move, the US District Court for the District of Columbia has issued a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-summoned-by-u-s-district-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">summons</a> against Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ). However, CZ has been exempted from in-person appearance. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In particular, it charged the two exchanges with the commingling of funds, broker-dealer, and clearing house functions. Binance was also accused of commingling funds. Reacting to the news, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1666129111025324035" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>, &#8220;Regarding the SEC complaint against us today, we&#8217;re proud to represent the industry in court to finally get some clarity around crypto rules.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrencies-cant-be-allowed-to-undermine-public-trust-in-capital-market-gensler-says/" rel="nofollow">Cryptocurrencies Can&#8217;t Be Allowed to Undermine Public Trust in Capital Market, Gensler Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
