<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 15:41:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Israel Could Include Crypto Into Existing Country Laws</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/israel-could-include-crypto-into-existing-country-laws/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Israel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231609</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/israeli_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/israeli_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The potential changes could come into effect in half a year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Israel Securities Authority (ISA) could amend three of its existing monetary laws to squeeze in cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The regulator&#8217;s proposals seek to grant investors maximum security when dealing with digital assets, reminding about the recent collapse of FTX and the severe losses it caused to consumers. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paying Attention to Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Israel&#8217;s financial watchdog <a href="https://www.isa.gov.il/%D7%97%D7%A7%D7%99%D7%A7%D7%94%20%D7%95%D7%90%D7%9B%D7%99%D7%A4%D7%94/Legislation/Proposed%20Legislation/Suggestions/Documents/digital.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">proposed</a> that cryptocurrencies should be included in the nation&#8217;s existing securities legislation. As such, the regulator will directly supervise operations with bitcoin and altcoins. It will also put the asset class into the category of &#8220;financial instruments,&#8221; where securities, marketing, and joint investments are also located.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The potential amendment aims to give Israeli crypto participants additional protection and to underline the sector&#8217;s technological advancement.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Cryptocurrencies are a digital representation of value used for the purpose of financial investment and can be transferred and stored electronically by using distributed ledger technology or another technology,&#8221; the ISA stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The regulator believes embracing the crypto industry could positively affect Israel&#8217;s economy because it could trigger the flow of diverse capital.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The advanced technology in these assets can lead to economic efficiency in many areas, reduce costs, save the need for intermediaries and optimize the way information is transferred between entities,&#8221; the proposal reads. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ISA added that cryptocurrencies have become a prevalent niche in the Mediterranean nation, with more than 200,000 Israelis having exposure to the market and about 150 firms operating in the field.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The proposal is open for public comments until February 12 and could go into effect after six months.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reminder About FTX and Celsius</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ISA thinks global regulators failed to impose pertinent rules on the crypto industry last year, which led to the demise of many companies, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a> and Celsius Network. It also pointed out that the latter&#8217;s Founder is Alex Mashinsky, who has Israeli origin. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celsius <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-crashes-50-as-the-platform-halts-withdrawals-due-to-extreme-market-conditions/" data-wpel-link="internal">suspended</a> withdrawals, swaps, and transfers between accounts in June last year, citing &#8220;extreme market conditions.&#8221; The company raised hopes that the move would stabilize its liquidity.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the contrary, the problems for the former crypto giant continued, and it had to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-lays-off-150-employees-as-crypto-winter-deepens-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">dismiss</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 150 of its total workforce in July. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection a week later, while CEO Mashinsky </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ceo-of-struggling-crypto-lender-celsius-tenders-resignation-letter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">resigned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> from his post in September. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company was close to inking an acquisition deal with FTX, but the latter&#8217;s doom erased those plans. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celsius recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-seeks-deadline-extension/" data-wpel-link="internal">extended</a> the deadline for customers to submit their claims until January 10 (at least). Viewed as one of the leading firms in the crypto lending space, it had 1.7 million clients at the beginning of last summer. Some of its creditors include the bankrupt Alameda Research and Pharos USD Fund SP.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/israel-could-include-crypto-into-existing-country-laws/" rel="nofollow">Israel Could Include Crypto Into Existing Country Laws</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptosat Launches Second Orbiting Satellite in Partnership With SpaceX</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptosat-launches-second-orbiting-satellite-in-partnership-with-spacex/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 22:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231642</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Satellite.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Satellite.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cryptosat sent its Crypto2 satellite into Earth's orbit via SpaceX's Falcon 9 rocket.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cryptosat &#8211; a California-based builder of satellites that power cryptographic and blockchain applications &#8211; sent into orbit another satellite called Crypto2. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company employed the services of Elon Musk&#8217;s rocket manufacturer &#8211; SpaceX.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Second Mission</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a document seen by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Cryptosat sent its second satellite into Earth&#8217;s orbit using the two-stage rocket SpaceX Falcon 9 on January 3. The spacecraft carried a total of 114 devices that could help 23 countries.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The second satellite has 30 times more computational power than the previous &#8211; Crypto1, which has been circulating around the planet since May last year. The entity&#8217;s Co-Founder &#8211; Yonatan Winetraub &#8211; commented:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The launch of Crypto2 is a milestone toward infrastructure expansion from a single satellite in 2022. The launch of Crypto2 gives us more availability and more powerful spec to support the growing portfolio of use cases in our development pipeline.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">2022 has been quite successful for Cryptosat. Apart from sending Crypto1 beyond the atmosphere, it completed a trial onboard the International Space Station.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company introduced an API tutorial in December containing a satellite trajectory simulation. The software shows developers how to interact with Cryptosat&#8217;s Low Earth Orbit (LEO) satellites when reaching space.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SpaceX and Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Elon Musk&#8217;s aerospace manufacturer has already joined the crypto bandwagon. One of the wealthiest people on the planet previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-says-spacex-will-put-dogecoin-on-the-moon-doge-price-skyrockets-35/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his firm will &#8220;put a literal Dogecoin on the literal Moon.&#8221; His announcement triggered a price jump for DOGE, which spiked by 35% in a matter of minutes.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/doge-1-mission-to-the-moon-dogecoin-payment-accepted-by-spacex/" data-wpel-link="internal">interacted</a> with the memecoin in May 2021 during its &#8220;DOGE-1 Mission to the Moon.&#8221; Back then, individuals could settle bills entirely in Dogecoin. SpaceX Vice President of Commercial Sales &#8211; Tom Ochinero &#8211; said the initiative demonstrated how cryptocurrencies could &#8220;set the foundation for interplanetary commerce.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Musk</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> doubled down</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on his support toward the memecoin in 2022, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-spikes-15-as-elon-musk-says-spacex-will-soon-accept-it-for-merch-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal">stating</a> that SpaceX will enable customers to use the asset as a payment method, similar to what Tesla did.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm&#8217;s CEO is so keen on DOGE that he referred to himself as the &#8220;DOGEFATHER&#8221; at one point. He has also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-is-better-than-bitcoin-at-handling-lots-of-transactions-elon-musk-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the first-ever memecoin is better at handling a large number of transactions than bitcoin.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptosat-launches-second-orbiting-satellite-in-partnership-with-spacex/" rel="nofollow">Cryptosat Launches Second Orbiting Satellite in Partnership With SpaceX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>RTFKT&#8217;s COO Says He Lost His NFTs in Phishing Attack</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/rtfkts-coo-says-he-lost-his-nfts-in-phishing-attack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 21:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231579</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Fishing.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Fishing.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The exec has not revealed any further details about the phishing attack.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New year or not, NFT thefts are on the rise. Nikhil Gopalani, the COO of RTFKT, has become the latest victim. The exec took to Twitter to reveal losing a significant number of NFTs from his wallet in a phishing attack.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Hey Clone X community &#8211; I was hacked by a clever Phisher (same phone # as apple ID) &amp; sold all my clone x / some other nfts&#8230; Obviously pretty upset and hurt by this and I havent really been able to move all day. Hope people who bought my clones love them (being positive).&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Phishing scams have become rampant in the crypto ecosystem, where scammers lure users to accidentally hand over the credentials to their wallets to initiate an irreversible transaction.</li>
<li>On-chain <a href="https://opensea.io/0xCBE6C780370CF501EDb74461D8Ad90037f559126" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> revealed that the attacker used <a href="https://opensea.io/0x9e913173661d8140707B34E9906daF60f0F12Abf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">two</a> wallets used to collectively drain more than $173,000 worth of NFTs from Gopalani&#8217;s wallet.</li>
<li>While one of the wallets was found empty, the other had 19 CloneX NFTs, 18 RTKFT Space Pods, 17 Loot Pods, 11 CryptoKicks, and 19 RTFKT Animus Eggs, among others.</li>
<li>Details are thin at the moment, but RTFKT&#8217;s CTO, Samuel Cardillo, said Gopalani may have provided the phishers, posing as big companies, with confidential data.</li>
<li>Many community members were not happy that the execs chose not to divulge more details on the entire incident and called their responses to be &#8220;very corporate.&#8221;</li>
<li>Cardillo, however, dismissed the accusation and hinted that a legal investigation may be underway, which could be why more information could not be shared.</li>
<li>One Twitter user <a href="https://twitter.com/1busyguy/status/1610423568659107841" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">made</a> an interesting point about stolen NFTs.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;If someone steals your bicycle, it’s generally understood that the bike is still yours. With an NFT, the “owner” is whoever has the token in their wallet. So, if someone’s ape NFT gets stolen via a phishing scam, the blockchain treats the thief as the new owner.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rtfkts-coo-says-he-lost-his-nfts-in-phishing-attack/" rel="nofollow">RTFKT&#8217;s COO Says He Lost His NFTs in Phishing Attack</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miner Core Scientific Plans to Shut Down 37,000 Celsius Rigs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-plans-to-shut-down-37000-celsius-rigs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231597</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/CoreScientificWallStreet.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/CoreScientificWallStreet.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Core had partially blamed Celsius for its financial troubles, saying its contract with the lender made it lose $28,000 daily.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Troubled Bitcoin miner Core Scientific will shut down more than 37,000 crypto mining rigs belonging to bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network as both firms finally reach an agreement in court.</p>
<p>Core Scientific, which hosts rigs for Celsius, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in December and had partially blamed the lender for its financial troubles. Both companies have a hosting deal in which the mining firm transfers some energy costs to Celsius.</p>
<h2>The Legal Fight</h2>
<p>The two parties have been in a legal battle over the contract as Core claims that Celsius has not been paying for these services since <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in July. In contrast, the lender argues that the miner supplied it with less power than required under their contract agreement.</p>
<p>Core had requested a court hearing on Jan 3, saying its contract with Celsius made it lose more than $28,000 daily.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We&#8217;re not seeking to make a dollar off of Core after today. Celsius has agreed to let Core power down the rigs and both sides are close to finalizing a deal to end their hosting relationship,&#8221; Chris Koenig, a lawyer for Celsius, <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-miner-core-scientific-to-shut-37-000-celsius-rigs-1.1865410" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said </a>in a bankruptcy hearing on Tuesday.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Celsius Owes Core Over $7.8M</h2>
<p>According to court filings, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-seeks-deadline-extension/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius Network</a>, Core&#8217;s biggest client, owes the miner approximately $7.8 million for energy costs tied to the rigs through November. This would mean that shutting down Celsius rigs could save Core thousands of dollars daily and generate more revenue if the miner gives Celsius&#8217; space to another customer.</p>
<p>Experts believe Core will likely win the case, and the verdict could serve as a legal precedent for other clients violating hosting contract agreements with the miner.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;While the legal case is still ongoing, this is a strong win for Core Scientific, who is likely facing other potential litigation from their hosting clients that had their cost increased. Partners will be less inclined to take them to court if there is precedent set for turning off the machines while the legal dispute is ongoing,&#8221; Ethan Vera, chief operations officer at crypto-mining services firm Luxor Technologies said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-plans-to-shut-down-37000-celsius-rigs/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Miner Core Scientific Plans to Shut Down 37,000 Celsius Rigs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Regulators Warn Local Banks About Risks of Dealing With Crypto After Horrific 2022</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-regulators-warn-local-banks-about-risks-of-dealing-with-crypto-after-horrific-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231578</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[American banks could become victims of fraud and scams if interacting with crypto, US regulators alerted.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">American banking watchdogs warned domestic financial institutions that delving into the world of crypto could carry various risks, such as fraud.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The warning comes as a result of a catalytic 2022, which saw the demise of multiple cryptocurrency giants, including FTX, Terraform Labs, Three Arrows Capital, Celsius Network, and more. The collapse of those firms triggered multi-billion investor losses and infused panic in the industry, resulting in a massive market decline.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Beware of the Risks</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Federal Reserve, Federal Deposit Insurance Corp., and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency issued a</span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/pressreleases/files/bcreg20230103a1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> joint statement</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, advising US banks to be utterly careful when dealing with cryptocurrencies because of the risks in the field. Monetary institutions could become victims of fraud and scams or be involved in collapsing projects, leading to severe losses:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The events of the past year have been marked by significant volatility and the exposure of vulnerabilities in the crypto-asset sector. These events highlight a number of key risks associated with crypto-assets and crypto-asset sector participants that banking organizations should be aware of.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The watchdogs claimed that the cryptocurrency industry lacks maturity and robustness, which is another prerequisite for financial damage. They also maintained that the sector is vulnerable to cyber attacks, while bitcoin and the alternative coins could facilitate illicit activities due to the absence of appropriate rules. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It is important that risks related to the crypto-asset sector that cannot be mitigated or controlled do not migrate to the banking system. The agencies are supervising banking organizations that may be exposed to risks stemming from the crypto-asset sector and carefully reviewing any proposals from banking organizations to engage in activities that involve crypto-assets,&#8221; the statement reads.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The regulators noted that last year&#8217;s numerous failing cryptocurrency projects harmed the entire industry. Given the risks of seeing another collapsing entity in the near future, the watchdogs will continue overseeing the sector and advise participants about the imminent risks. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX and Other Falling Giants</span></h2>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-valuable-lessons-from-terras-collapse-opinion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Terra&#8217;s failure</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> is one of the examples from 2022 that undermined the industry&#8217;s credibility. The project&#8217;s algorithmic stablecoin &#8211; UST &#8211; de-pegged in May and later plunged to virtually zero together with the native token LUNA. This prompted massive investor losses as sources revealed that some individuals committed suicide. </span></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-files-for-bankruptcy-as-voyager-digital-suspends-withdrawals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Three Arrows Capital (3AC)</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Celsius Network, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-suspending-withdrawals-voyager-digital-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Voyager Digital</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> felt the consequences of Terra&#8217;s debacle as they all had severe financial issues and had to file for bankruptcy. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, the most notorious collapse is arguably the one of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">. The platform, which was among the largest in its field, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for bankruptcy protection in November after facing liquidity issues and failing to honor customer withdrawal requests.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Bahamian authorities arrested Sam Bankman-Fried &#8211; the former CEO of the exchange &#8211; and sent him to Fox Hill Prison on allegations of committing fraud, money laundering, and several other crimes. He was later deported to the US and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">released</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on a $250 million bond before Christmas.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SBF (as he is commonly known) recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pleaded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> not guilty to criminal charges that he knowingly defrauded investors, while US District Judge Lewis Kaplan set his trial date for October. He currently lives at his parent&#8217;s house and has to wear an electronic monitoring device. He could spend his life in jail if found guilty in the subsequent process.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-regulators-warn-local-banks-about-risks-of-dealing-with-crypto-after-horrific-2022/" rel="nofollow">US Regulators Warn Local Banks About Risks of Dealing With Crypto After Horrific 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Inching Toward $17K, is a Breakout Imminent? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-inching-toward-17k-is-a-breakout-imminent-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 15:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231633</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As we head into 2023, the markets are beginning to show some interesting movements, and Bitcoin is no exception. Its price is currently testing a key resistance zone, and the outcome would likely determine the short-term trend for the crypto market. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart On the daily timeframe, the price seems [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we head into 2023, the markets are beginning to show some interesting movements, and Bitcoin is no exception. Its price is currently testing a key resistance zone, and the outcome would likely determine the short-term trend for the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price seems to be closing in on finally disrupting the consolidation of the last few weeks, as the 50-day moving average is being tested once more around the $16,800 mark.</p>
<p>In case of a valid bullish breakout, there would be little resistance in the way, and a rise toward the $18K resistance level would be imminent. A breakout from this significant resistance level would likely lead to a breach above the large falling wedge pattern, which could lead to a bullish market structure in the mid-term.</p>
<p>However, as the price is yet to successfully climb above the 50-day moving average, there is still a considerable chance for rejection, which could result in a drop toward the $15K support level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231634" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231634" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231634 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_040123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-4-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231634" class="wp-caption-text">Source: tradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Things appear trickier on the 4-hour timeframe, as the price action has been showing signs of rejection from the $16,800 level.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator should also be monitored closely as it is approaching the overbought zone of above 70%, a signal which could hint at rejection and a bearish reversal. In this case, the price could increase toward the $15,500 support area.</p>
<p>Still, it would be too soon to call it a bearish move, as the price is ranging near the resistance level and could showcase an impulsive break above it later in the day.</p>
<p>To summarize, the market is in a very crucial area, so the next few days, and potentially even hours, would likely decide the short-term trend based on the price&#8217;s reaction to the $16,800 area.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231635" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231635" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231635 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_040123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-4-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231635" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>The following chart consists of the Exchange to Exchange Flow (Spot to Derivatives Exchanges) metric alongside Bitcoin’s price. Evidently, derivatives markets are closely correlated with both the bullish and bearish stages of the market.</p>
<p>An increase in the metric indicates higher activity in the derivatives markets. Typically, participants use derivatives exchanges to manage their risk and exposure to the market, and a few use the leverage option to expand their profits.</p>
<p>Based on the graph, the 365-day moving average of the metric surged during the Bitcoin bull markets while, conversely, it declined during the bear markets &#8211; showing a high correlation.</p>
<p>Currently, the metric is plummeting with significant momentum. Therefore, it might be too early for Bitcoin to start a bull market, as the metric still has room to decline.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231636" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231636" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231636 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_exchangetoexchange_flow_chart_040123" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Exchange_to_Exchange_Flow_Total_Spot_Exchanges_Derivative-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231636" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-inching-toward-17k-is-a-breakout-imminent-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Inching Toward $17K, is a Breakout Imminent? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Automating Cryptocurrency Trading With Haru Invest</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/automating-cryptocurrency-trading-with-haru-invest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Danish Yasin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 15:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231655</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As people seek new ways to make money and diversify their portfolios, cryptocurrency trading has become increasingly popular in recent years. This is the main reason cryptocurrency trading volumes soared in 2021 and 2022 relative to what they were in the years before that. What is more, users have started seeking out solutions that allow [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As people seek new ways to make money and diversify their portfolios, cryptocurrency trading has become increasingly popular in recent years.</p>
<p>This is the main reason <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-report-eth-trading-volume-increased-more-than-bitcoins-in-first-half-of-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">cryptocurrency trading volumes</a> soared in 2021 and 2022 relative to what they were in the years before that. What is more, users have started seeking out solutions that allow them to automate the process and reduce the element of human error.</p>
<p>This is the main reason why there are certain crypto-automating solutions, so let’s have a closer look at their implications for traders.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-231656" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover.jpg" alt="haru_invest_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/haru_invest_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>What is Automated Crypto Trading?</h2>
<p>In automated crypto trading, the human element is reduced to a minimum, and instead, computer algorithms or programs are put to use. These systems attempt to identify profitable opportunities and execute trades based on specifically predefined criteria. Currency, stocks, options, and commodities can also be traded with them.</p>
<p>With automated trading, traders can take advantage of market movements without having to monitor the markets themselves constantly. The idea behind it is to eliminate the need for manual intervention.</p>
<h2>What are the Benefits of Automated Crypto Trading</h2>
<p><a href="https://haruinvest.com/blog/best-crypto-trading-bots/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Automated crypto trading</a> is beneficial in that it eliminates the guesswork associated with buying and selling assets. Trades can be entered or exited at optimal times with the help of automated systems that generate signals in real-time. Furthermore, these systems can reduce risk by limiting losses through stop-loss orders or other precautions.</p>
<p>Since the system does all the work, users spend less time analyzing data and worrying about market volatility, allowing them to focus on other activities.</p>
<h2>What are the Disadvantages of Automated Crypto Trading</h2>
<p>Although automated crypto trading has some advantages, it also has some disadvantages. Overtrading may result in excessive fees and losses due to failed trades if automation is used. Additionally, automated systems are not always able to correctly predict market conditions; they may not account for unforeseen events such as news announcements or political developments.</p>
<p>Additionally, while automated systems can identify profitable trades quickly and efficiently, they cannot guarantee profitability.</p>
<h2>Haru Invest: All-in-one tool for automated crypto trading</h2>
<p>With the launch of <a href="https://haruinvest.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Haru Invest</a> in 2019, the trading strategy has been driven by algorithmic trading.</p>
<p>They deploy three core algorithmic trading strategies to drive profits for investors:</p>
<ol>
<li>Arbitrage trading that leverages the price gap between crypto exchanges</li>
<li>Market neutral strategy based on the price stability mechanisms at crypto futures exchanges</li>
<li>Spread trading that focuses on the volatility of BTC/ETH futures contracts</li>
</ol>
<p>Haru Invest has paid out 4.1M+ separate earnings on time.</p>
<p>Their total transaction volume since launch exceeds $2.11B. They have more than 74,500 members from 140+ countries using Haru Invest. 87.5% of their members continue to use their platform with deposits.</p>
<p>All in all, automated crypto trading can be a valuable tool for experienced traders who understand how these systems work and have strategies in place for managing risk appropriately.</p>
<p>However, novice traders should approach these tools with caution as they do not guarantee profits nor provide any protection against losses incurred due to unexpected market movements or other factors beyond their control.</p>
<p>Therefore, it’s essential for cryptocurrency users who are considering using an automated system to do thorough research before choosing one that best suits their needs and goals. That way, they can ensure that their investments will be managed safely and responsibly while also providing them with an opportunity for growth within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/automating-cryptocurrency-trading-with-haru-invest/" rel="nofollow">Automating Cryptocurrency Trading With Haru Invest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Bonk Inu (BONK): The Dogecoin of Solana?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-bonk-inu-bonk-the-dogecoin-of-solana/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231643</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BONK is the newest kid on the block and it's driving considerable volumes on Solana. But what does it do?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Memecoins have been a part of the crypto culture for almost as long as the community existed, but 2020 and 2021 saw them soar to a whole new level.</p>
<p>It got to a point where two memecoins &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-dogecoin-doge-5-facts-about-the-crypto-that-started-as-a-joke/" data-wpel-link="internal">Dogecoin (DOGE)</a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-shiba-inu-shib/" data-wpel-link="internal">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> became frequent members of the top-10 club (the 10 largest cryptocurrencies by means of total market capitalization).</p>
<p>The bear market of 2022 has impacted most memecoins severely, but DOGE and SHIB continue to be leading coins.</p>
<p>That said, there’s a new kid on the block &#8211; one built on Solana &#8211; and is going the miles. The cryptocurrency in question is called Bonk Inu (BONK), so let’s have a closer look at what it actually does.</p>
<h2>What is Bonk Inu (BONK)?</h2>
<p>According to its official <a href="https://www.bonkcoin.com/one-pager" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">one-pager</a>, BONK is the very first Dog-themed memecoin on Solana that’s “for the people, by the people.”</p>
<p>The document states:</p>
<blockquote><p>The BONK contributors were tired of toxic “Alameda” tokenomics and wanted to make a fun memecoin where everyone gets a fair shot.</p></blockquote>
<p>50% of the total supply of the cryptocurrency was airdropped to the Solana community, while the main purpose of the team behind it is to bring back liquidity to decentralized exchanges built on Solana.</p>
<p>In fact, that’s pretty much everything the document outlines, alongside the token distribution.</p>
<h2>BONK Token Distribution Explained</h2>
<p>As mentioned above, 50% of the supply was airdropped to the Solana community, divided as it follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>20% of it went to Solana NFT collections (297K individual NFTs)</li>
<li>15% to early OpenBook traders</li>
<li>10% to Solana collectors and artists</li>
<li>5% to Solana developers</li>
</ul>
<p>The total supply is set to 100 trillion BONK tokens. The provided pie chart looks like this:</p>
<figure id="attachment_231644" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231644" style="width: 864px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_supply_distribution.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231644" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_supply_distribution.jpg" alt="bonk_inu_supply_distribution" width="864" height="519" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_supply_distribution.jpg 864w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_supply_distribution-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_supply_distribution-768x461.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_supply_distribution-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 864px) 100vw, 864px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231644" class="wp-caption-text">Source: BONK Website</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Massive BONK Burning Propelling the Price</h2>
<p>Throughout the past few days, the team behind BONK has burned a considerable number of tokens and has introduced certain capabilities that allow users to burn tokens themselves.</p>
<p>For instance, on December 4th, the team announced that the allocation that was supposed to go to the DeGods NFT project has been burned. The transaction can be found <a href="https://solscan.io/tx/3ohrMStoY3Hyr9L73efTUZH2GYQRF3AZKq2RhWfL1iuMSYiDaJyM7txpKtiTANWiwQRWtQxctJqnFGsSnRgXrYrf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">here</a>. It saw 500 billion BONK tokens wiped off the market forever.</p>
<p>This sent the price to the sky, as it was up more than 100% on that day at one point. Overall, since it was launched, the cryptocurrency has already increased by over 3000% in the past week.</p>
<p>Another reason for this is the fact that liquidity providers on popular decentralized exchanges such as Orca are yielding APIs upwards of 1000% at the time of this writing.</p>
<p>The BONK/SOL trading pair also saw a massive 24-hour volume of around $20 million.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231645" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231645" style="width: 990px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_yield_orca.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231645" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_yield_orca.jpg" alt="bonk_inu_yield_orca" width="990" height="449" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_yield_orca.jpg 990w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_yield_orca-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_yield_orca-768x348.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bonk_inu_yield_orca-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 990px) 100vw, 990px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231645" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Orca</figcaption></figure>
<p>The team, as with many memecoin projects, has remained anonymous. The website itself doesn’t contain other information but the one-pager and the rest of the links to BONK-related resources.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-bonk-inu-bonk-the-dogecoin-of-solana/" rel="nofollow">What is Bonk Inu (BONK): The Dogecoin of Solana?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic Eden Blames Unsavory Pics on Third-Party Breach</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/magic-eden-blames-unsavory-pics-on-third-party-breach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231615</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Magic_Eden.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Magic_Eden.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The NFT marketplace said the adult images displaced on its platform were from a hacked third-party image provider.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Solana&#8217;s largest non-fungible token marketplace Magic Eden recently found itself in a bizarre situation after the platform displayed pornographic images and stills from the award-winning comedy series The Big Bang Theory instead of NFT collections.</p>
<p class="p2">Shortly after the incident, users began speculating that the NFT marketplace may have been compromised. However, Magic Eden clarified that the incident was caused by a third-party image hosting provider supposedly experiencing a security breach.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Magic Eden Not Under Attack </b></h2>
<p class="p2">Sharing the news on Twitter, the Solana-based NFT platform said it had not been hacked, assuring users that their assets were unaffected by the unsavory images.</p>
<p class="p2">The announcement came after some of the company&#8217;s customers reported the incident on Twitter, asking the platform to explain what happened.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Anyone else seeing the characters from the series Big Bang Theory very quickly while loading their items on Magic Eden?</p>
<p>WTH did I just witness <a href="https://twitter.com/MagicEden?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@MagicEden</a> <a href="https://t.co/7JFccFfGv9" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/7JFccFfGv9</a></p>
<p>— Clôwn (@Yaboibeclownin) <a href="https://twitter.com/Yaboibeclownin/status/1610144133183856646?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="p2">A Twitter user said he saw stills from the Big Bang Theory before eventually seeing their digital artwork on the platform.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;Anyone else seeing the characters from the series Big Bang Theory very quickly while loading their items on Magic Eden? WTH did I just witness,&#8221; the tweet reads.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">Magic Eden explained that a hard refresh before accessing the platform would fix the issue. The glitch appears to have been fixed at press time.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hey guys our image provider, a 3rd party service we use to cache images, was compromised. Your NFTs are safe and Magic Eden has not been hacked. Unfortunately you might&#8217;ve seen some um, unsavory images. Make sure you do a hard refresh on your browser to fix it.</p>
<p>— Magic Eden <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1fa84.png" alt="🪄" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@MagicEden) <a href="https://twitter.com/MagicEden/status/1610397539685257216?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>NFT Hacks on the Rise</b></h2>
<p class="p2">While the exploit did not lead to theft or loss of assets, hackers are continuously targeting NFT users and marketplaces.</p>
<p class="p2">In 2022, the crypto industry recorded multiple attacks on NFT trading platforms. Some episodes included the OpenSea hack, which saw the platform lose millions of dollars to cybercriminals.</p>
<p class="p2">OpenSea suffered a phishing attack that affected at least 32 users. The hackers <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/1-7-million-in-eth-stolen-from-opensea-users-the-nft-marketplace-investigates/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">stole</span></a> valuable NFTs worth around $1.7 million from the exploit.</p>
<p class="p2">A month after OpenSea&#8217;s attack, another NFT marketplace, TreasureDAO, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hackes-exploit-arbitrum-based-marketplace-treasure-over-100-nfts-stolen/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">suffered</span></a> a massive security breach that saw hackers stealing over 100 NFTs from the platform.</p>
<p class="p2">According to blockchain security company Peckshield, the exploit resulted from &#8220;a bug in distinguishing ERC721 and ERC1155 in buyItem, which miscalculates the price of ERC721 as ERC1155 with the (untrusted) given 0 quantity.&#8221;</p>
<p class="p2">In July, hackers <a href="https://twitter.com/CValley_/status/1548576064351285249?t=BphEbu0ToH8MhMRFyE71AA&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">attacked</span></a> the popular NFT registration protocol Premint and made away with 320 digital artworks listed on the platform. Some stolen NFTs include expensive collections from Bored Ape Yacht Club, Otherside, Moonbirds Oddities, and Goblintown.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/magic-eden-blames-unsavory-pics-on-third-party-breach/" rel="nofollow">Magic Eden Blames Unsavory Pics on Third-Party Breach</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Ethereum Trust Discount Sinks to 60%, GBTC Down to 45%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-ethereum-trust-discount-sinks-to-60-gbtc-down-to-45/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231568</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/BitcoinEthereumGrayscale.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/BitcoinEthereumGrayscale.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The pressure is mounting on the world’s largest institutional crypto fund manager, Grayscale, and its parent company.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Grayscale Ethereum Trust (ETHE) has fallen to a record discount of -60% as fears over liquidations mount.</p>
<p>The discount to net asset value (NAV) had been between -25% and -35% up until early November when FTX collapsed. It has since plummeted to its lowest-ever level this week.</p>
<p>The Ethereum Trust is the firm’s second-largest, with $3.7 billion in assets under management (AUM). It holds around 3 million ETH, which is about 2.5% of its total market capitalization.</p>
<p>The ETHE <a href="https://grayscale.com/products/grayscale-ethereum-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">fund</a> is down 69% over the past year, according to Grayscale, but it has gained 49% since its inception in December 2017.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Every Grayscale trust and their respective premium % <a href="https://t.co/TYQf5FmeXt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/TYQf5FmeXt</a></p>
<p>— db (@tier10k) <a href="https://twitter.com/tier10k/status/1610273482016694272?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Grayscale Liquidation Fears Mount</h2>
<p>The asset manager’s flagship Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), is also in a world of pain. Its discount to NAV is currently -45%, also an all-time low according to <a href="https://ycharts.com/companies/GBTC" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Ycharts</a>.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin Trust has $10.5 billion in AUM and holds more than 630,000 BTC. It is down 65% over the past twelve months but up a whopping 10,757% since its inception in 2013. Momentum for the GBTC fund could be reignited if the SEC approves its conversion to a spot exchange-traded fund this year. However, in the current crypto and regulatory environment, that is unlikely to happen.</p>
<p>Several of Grayscale’s altcoin funds are suffering even more so. Its Ethereum Classic Trust has a discount of -77%, while the Litecoin Trust is at a -65% discount. The ETC fund holds around 8.5% of the entire Ethereum Classic market capitalization, which puts the crypto asset at risk.</p>
<p>Other altcoin funds with more than a 50% discount to NAV include Basic Attention Token (BAT), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), and Livepeer (LPT). The only two trading at a premium at the moment are the Chainlink (LINK) and Filecoin (FIL) trusts.</p>
<h2>Battling With Genesis</h2>
<p>This week, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-out-barry-silbert-on-1-675b-debt-latter-fires-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">lashed out</a> at Digital Currency Group (DCG) CEO Barry Silbert over frozen funds. The exchange lent users’ funds to Silbert’s embattled Genesis brokerage, which halted withdrawals following <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitvavo-claims-dcg-has-liquidity-issues-exchange-funds-unaffected/" data-wpel-link="internal">liquidity issues</a> after the FTX collapse.</p>
<p>DCG is Grayscale’s parent company which has raised liquidation fears. However, the assets in the Ethereum and altcoin trusts are not directly at risk yet. DCG’s position in the GBTC fund could be liquidated if the company is forced to repay its debts to Genesis creditors.</p>
<p>On Jan. 3, Three Arrows Capital (3AC) co-founder Zhu Su <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founder-zhu-su-accuses-dcg-of-being-criminally-fraudulent/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused DCG</a> of being criminally fraudulent.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-ethereum-trust-discount-sinks-to-60-gbtc-down-to-45/" rel="nofollow">Grayscale Ethereum Trust Discount Sinks to 60%, GBTC Down to 45%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
