<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 13:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Just Like Bitcoin, Binance US Drops All Ethereum-USD Trading Fees</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/just-like-bitcoin-binance-us-drops-all-ethereum-usd-trading-fees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 14:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227682</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Users can now freely trade ETH for US dollars or any of the three top stablecoins. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance US – the American branch of the world’s largest crypto exchange – has eliminated all Ether (ETH) spot trading fees just six months after doing the same for Bitcoin (BTC) pairs on the platform. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The zero-fee model will expand free trading to the platform’s </span><span style="font-weight: 400">ETH/USD, ETH/USDT, ETH/USDC, and ETH/BUSD pairs.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In a press release shared with CryptoPotato, Binance US revealed that it will be consolidating its pricing tiers into a single tier in January 2023. Tier I assets will feature the same pricing as Tier II assets, with the consolidated tier to be known as ‘Tier I’ from then onwards. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance US CEO Brian Shroder said the change is one of many at the company focused on “customer experience.” The exchange seeks to distinguish itself as one of the industry’s low-fee leaders, and to “restore trust in the greater ecosystem.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Now, more than ever, it is critical that platforms operate with users’ interests f</span><span style="font-weight: 400">irst,” stated the firm.</span></p></blockquote>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Both Binance and Binance US </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-offers-zero-trading-fees-for-bitcoin-spot-pairs/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">introduced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> zero-fee Bitcoin trading on the same USD and stablecoin pairs in June, shortly after industry competitors like Coinbase and Robinhood announced major job cuts. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Likewise, their Ethereum fee removal shortly follows the collapse of of FTX – Binance’s biggest rival from which the exchange seemingly absorbed hundreds of millions of dollars in withdrawal requests following a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/market-in-shambles-as-ftx-withdrawal-uncertainty-runs-rampant/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">bank run</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in early November. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance CEO Champeng Zhao has made numerous statements in the aftermath of FTX’s bankruptcy highlighting Binance as a more attractive alternative. These include implementing Merkle Tree proof of reserves, and </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1590058764865937409" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">re-promoting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Binance’s zero-fee Bitcoin model from June.  </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Though fees are a main source of revenue for companies like Binance, major exchanges are now taking profiting from staking services. Binance US announced ETH staking shortly before the Merge, with rates starting at 6% APY. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/just-like-bitcoin-binance-us-drops-all-ethereum-usd-trading-fees/" rel="nofollow">Just Like Bitcoin, Binance US Drops All Ethereum-USD Trading Fees</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency Advertizing ìn the US Under Scanner Over Possible Misconduct</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrency-advertizing-in-the-us-under-scanner-over-possible-misconduct/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 13:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227595</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/UnitedStates.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/UnitedStates.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The consumer watchdog is reportedly investigating several unnamed crypto firms. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Federal Trade Commission (FTC) is targeting certain crypto companies over deceptive or misleading advertising. With the latest move, the FTC appears to follow in the footsteps of the SEC as the crackdown on the ecosystem broadens.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-pressure-ratchets-up-as-ftc-probes-several-firms-over-ads-1.1855197#:~:text=Crypto%20Pressure%20Ratchets%20Up%20as%20FTC%20Probes%20Several%20Firms%20Over%20Ads,-Leah%20Nylen%20and&amp;text=(Bloomberg)%20%2D%2D%20The%20US%20Federal,misleading%2C%20the%20agency%20said%20Monday" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, FTC spokeswoman Juliana Gruenwald Henderson said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are investigating several firms for possible misconduct concerning digital assets.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Henderson, however, declined to provide further details regarding which firms were being targeted by the authorities.</li>
<li>FTC&#8217;s official website states that &#8220;under the law, claims in advertisements must be truthful, cannot be deceptive or unfair, and must be evidence-based. For some specialized products or services, additional rules may apply.&#8221;</li>
<li>The agency essentially upholds laws that require truth in advertising, including rules that individuals reveal when they have been paid for endorsements or reviews.</li>
<li>Several high-profile influencers, such as Kim Kardashian, have reportedly run afoul of the FTC&#8217;s standards in the past.</li>
<li>While the FTC has not been stringent about most cases, SEC, on the other hand, has been a warpath over anything related to the crypto-asset industry.</li>
<li>In fact, the American socialite was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-gary-gensler-break-protocol-in-the-kim-kardashian-crypto-settlement-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fined</a> $1 million by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a fraudulent crypto promotional case.</li>
<li>During the bull run of 2021, several crypto firms lavishly poured funds into advertising in a bid to capture new investors. Many featured celebrities such as Hollywood actor Matt Damon and sports star LeBron James as well as Shaquille O&#8217;Neal.</li>
<li>This summer, the Advertising Standard Council Of India (ASCI) has discovered over 400 crypto-ads to be potentially violating advertising and promotion guidelines of virtual digital assets (VDAs), and guidelines for influencer advertising.</li>
<li>The UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) also launched an investigation against companies for misleading crypto ads.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrency-advertizing-in-the-us-under-scanner-over-possible-misconduct/" rel="nofollow">Cryptocurrency Advertizing ìn the US Under Scanner Over Possible Misconduct</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>These On-Chain Indicators Suggest Bitcoin&#8217;s Bottom Draws Near</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/these-on-chain-indicators-suggest-bitcoins-bottom-draws-near/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 11:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227703</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Bitcoin_Bottom.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Bitcoin_Bottom.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A number of on-chain indicators are coming into alignment suggesting that the Bitcoin market bottom could be in.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin and crypto markets are a full year into bear territory, and it has been about that time when the cycle bottom occurs.</p>
<p>During the previous bear market, it came in December 2018, a year after the Bitcoin price peak. This time around, BTC has fallen 75% from its peak a year ago, and bottom signals are mounting up.</p>
<p>On Dec. 6, Capriole Fund founder Charles Edwards took a deep dive into the on-chain data. He discovered that there were several signals suggesting it could be the best time to buy Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Bitcoin Bottom Signal Series.</p>
<p>A thread of on-chain signals which suggest the Bitcoin bottom is in, or very close. In my opinion, these are the most important on-chain metrics today. Based on Bitcoin&#8217;s 13 year history, they are telling me this is an extraordinary opportunity. <a href="https://t.co/5io6WD2ELo" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/5io6WD2ELo</a></p>
<p>— Charles Edwards (@caprioleio) <a href="https://twitter.com/caprioleio/status/1600053321527873536?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 6, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bitcoin at The Bottom</h2>
<p>Bitcoin adoption is at an all-time high despite the FTX crypto contagion and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-capital-reset-underway-following-final-flushout-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal">market crash</a>. It is currently the highest growth rate in addresses, with more than 0.1 BTC in history. The addresses holding BTC for more than a year also represent more of the network than ever before.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there have only been four other times in network history that Bitcoin production cost has been below its electrical cost. These instances also coincided with market bottoms.</p>
<p>Edwards observed that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC price</a> is also trading at a 55% discount to Bitcoin Energy Value. The BEV is the asset&#8217;s fair value priced using pure watts of energy in the network. It is currently the largest discount since prices hit $4,000 in March 2020 and $160 on in January 2015.</p>
<p>Miner selling pressure is also at its third highest level. It only previously exceeded current levels when priced at $2 and $290. Hash ribbons have also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hash-ribbon-reversal-confirms-bitcoin-miner-capitulation-phase/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> this miner capitulation phase, as reported by <em>CryptoPotato</em>.</p>
<p>The Dynamic Range NVT or the Bitcoin PE Ratio is also flashing green which means the network is priced cheap versus the transaction value flowing through on-chain.</p>
<p>Additionally, Dormancy Flow has also been at all-time lows for the past month or so. According to the indicator creator, whenever dormancy value overtakes market capitalization at the lowest longitudinal levels, the market can be considered in full capitulation.</p>
<h2>Middle of Halving Cycle</h2>
<p>Edwards said that it was not just the data that is screaming Bitcoin is cheap, concluding:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are also situated smack-bang in the bottom zone for every prior Bitcoin halving cycle. This is where sentiment has always bottomed and the best long-term investments were made.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-on-chain-indicators-suggest-bitcoins-bottom-draws-near/" rel="nofollow">These On-Chain Indicators Suggest Bitcoin&#8217;s Bottom Draws Near</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Slips Below $17K as Altcoins Swimming in Red (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-slips-below-17k-as-altcoins-swimming-in-red-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227717</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_red_background_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_red_background_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin slips below $17K after flirting with that level for a few days, while altcoins are mainly in the red today.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After flirting with and above the $17K level for a few days, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been unsuccessful in charting any significant gains above it. Finally, the bears seem to have taken over and pushed the cryptocurrency below it.</p>
<p>This happens as the entire market capitalization lost around $20 billion in the past 24 hours, and altcoins are predominantly trading in the red.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Price Losing $17K</h2>
<p>The past 24 hours haven&#8217;t been particularly favorable throughout the entire cryptocurrency market. BTC&#8217;s price seems to have lost the $17K mark, and it&#8217;s currently trading slightly below it &#8211; around $16,800 (on Binance).</p>
<figure id="attachment_227718" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227718" style="width: 1532px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-227718" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201.png" alt="btc_price_chart_071201" width="1532" height="851" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201.png 1532w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201-300x167.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201-1024x569.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201-768x427.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_071201-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1532px) 100vw, 1532px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-227718" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Binance via TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>Bitcoin is currently down around 1.3% on the day but remains up by 2.2% on the weekly. Over the past few days, the BTC dominance &#8211; the metric that tracks its share relative to that of the entire market &#8211; has also been trending upwards. This goes to show that BTC is slightly more dominant compared to altcoins during this period.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Swimming in Red</h2>
<p>The altcoin market is also covered in red throughout the past 24 hours, with no exceptions coming from the top cryptocurrencies &#8211; as seen in the heatmap below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_227719" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227719" style="width: 1489px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-227719" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201.png" alt="altcoins_heatmap_071201" width="1489" height="799" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201.png 1489w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201-300x161.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201-1024x549.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201-768x412.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/altcoins_heatmap_071201-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1489px) 100vw, 1489px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-227719" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>Despite the current downturn, though, there are some altcoins that are performing extremely well. For example, Radix (XRD) is up a whopping 25% in the last day, making it the best performer amongst the top 100 altcoins during the past 24 hours. XRD is followed by Frax Shares (FXS), which is up 7.5%.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the coin powering the Aptos ecosystem &#8211; APT &#8211; is down 8.9%, and it&#8217;s the worst performer on that list, followed by Tokeniz Xchange&#8217;s TKX (down 8.2%).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-slips-below-17k-as-altcoins-swimming-in-red-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Slips Below $17K as Altcoins Swimming in Red (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stay Away From Everything but Bitcoin and Ether: The Wolf of Wall Street</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stay-away-from-everything-but-bitcoin-and-ether-the-wolf-of-wall-street/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 07:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227604</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/JordanBelfort.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/JordanBelfort.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BTC and ETH are the only crypto assets investors should deal with right now, Belfort said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jordan Belfort &#8211; the infamous stock broker whose story inspired Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film &#8220;The Wolf of Wall Street&#8221; &#8211; thinks the only two cryptocurrencies investors should deal with at the moment are bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH).</p>
<p>He cautioned people should invest only a small amount of their total portfolio in crypto due to the volatility and risks in the field.</p>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Disregard Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Belfort <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pSc2zpB7B8o" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">uploaded</a> a video called &#8220;My Current Crypto Update&#8221; to give his two cents on hot topics, such as the<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"> FTX fiasco</a> and whether now is the right moment to jump on the ecosystem.</p>
<p>He claimed the exchange was a scam and nothing could have protected users against the catastrophe.</p>
<p>Despite FTX&#8217;s meltdown, &#8220;the Wolf of Wall Street&#8221; does not think people should disregard bitcoin and ether. According to him, the two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization are the only ones investors should deal with during the ongoing bear market.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Outside of those two coins &#8211; I literally would not be touching crypto right now with a 10-foot pole,&#8221; he stated.</p></blockquote>
<p>Going back to bitcoin, Belfort said he hasn&#8217;t sold any of his holdings and has even purchased more. He thinks that such investment could turn profitable in the next five to ten years:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I haven&#8217;t sold even one, and I&#8217;m buying more. That&#8217;s not to say that I don&#8217;t think it&#8217;s going low because I do think it&#8217;s probably going to go a bit lower in the short term. But I believe in the long term that if you hold these coins five or ten years, I believe those two have an excellent shot of being substantially higher than what they are today.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>He recommended investors allocate a &#8220;very small&#8221; proportion of their entire portfolio when buying BTC and ETH. The best investment tools are the S&amp;P 500, or ETFs, he concluded.</p>
<h2>Belfort&#8217;s U-Turn</h2>
<p>The Wolf of Wall Street was not a big fan of bitcoin a few years ago, claiming in 2018 that it is based on the Great Fools Theory and is &#8220;going away.&#8221;</p>
<p>However, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-to-100k-says-the-wolf-of-wall-street-another-changed-heart/" data-wpel-link="internal">changed</a> his view in 2021, noting BTC&#8217;s advancement during the COVID-19 crisis. Belfort outlined its fixed maximum supply of 21 million coins ever to exist and predicted its price could skyrocket to $100,000 by the end of last year.</p>
<p>Despite not hitting the milestone, Belfort remained a proponent and kept praising the asset during 2022. He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-wolf-of-wall-street-investors-will-almost-certainly-profit-by-hodling-btc-for-3-years/" data-wpel-link="internal">advised</a> investors to view bitcoin as a long-term investment in July, forecasting that those holding it for over three years will most probably make some profits.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stay-away-from-everything-but-bitcoin-and-ether-the-wolf-of-wall-street/" rel="nofollow">Stay Away From Everything but Bitcoin and Ether: The Wolf of Wall Street</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Block Co-Leads in $2M Seed Round in East African Bitcoin Miner</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorseys-block-co-leads-in-2m-seed-round-in-east-african-bitcoin-miner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 01:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227576</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Jack-Dorsey.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Jack-Dorsey.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The latest capital infusion will be used to support the company's expansion across East African markets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gridless &#8211; a Kenyan-based Bitcoin mining company &#8211; has announced raising a $2 million seed investment round led by venture capital investor Stillmark and digital payments firm Block, Inc.</p>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://gridlesscompute.com/2022/12/06/gridless-a-bitcoin-mining-company-in-east-africa-raises-2m-in-funding-led-by-stillmark-and-block-inc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, Gridless harnesses small-scale renewable energy grids in rural Africa. The company has participated in five different project contract pilots in rural Kenya alongside an African hydroelectric company &#8211; HydroBox. Currently, three of these pilots are operational.</p>
<ul>
<li>It has also financed the construction and managing the operation of data centers in rural communities where traditional industrial or commercial customers are unavailable.</li>
<li>Commenting on the development, Gridless CEO Erik Hersman stated:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our work in supporting renewable energy mini-grid developers fills a gap, helping developers expand faster, be more sustainable, and serve thousands of households. This investment, and the high caliber of partners that are coming alongside us, means that we can accelerate our rollout knowing that we have both the capital and strategic support required.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Thomas Templeton, who happens to be the lead for bitcoin mining and wallet at Block, specified that Gridless represents a close strategic alignment with the company&#8217;s vision to ensure the network increasingly uses clean energy &#8220;in combination with bitcoin computational centers around the world.&#8221;</li>
<li>While mining operations in some parts of the world still rely on fossil fuels to power their rigs, many are turning to sustainable ways forward.</li>
<li>The conversation surrounding Bitcoin mining has gradually shifted to &#8220;green&#8221; or &#8220;clean&#8221; infrastructure.</li>
<li>In fact, a report from the Bitcoin Mining Council <a href="https://bitcoinminingcouncil.com/bitcoin-mining-council-survey-confirms-year-on-year-improvements-in-sustainable-power-mix-and-technological-efficiency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">observed</a> that the Bitcoin mining industry as a whole has increased the use of sustainable energy by 52.2% &#8211; one of the most sustainable industries in the world &#8211; as of the first quarter of 2022.</li>
<li>Over the past year, usage of sustainable energy in the space has surged by 59% as well.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorseys-block-co-leads-in-2m-seed-round-in-east-african-bitcoin-miner/" rel="nofollow">Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Block Co-Leads in $2M Seed Round in East African Bitcoin Miner</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Partners With iPhone Co-creator Tony Fadell To Launch Its New &#8216;Stax&#8221; Crypto Wallet</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-partners-with-iphone-co-creator-tony-fadell-to-launch-its-new-stax-crypto-wallet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227690</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/tinywow_FjTYptDXEAYph3s_9282896.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/tinywow_FjTYptDXEAYph3s_9282896.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The new Ledger Stax is bigger, nicer, safer, more functional, and different from any other Ledger device.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On December 6th, Ledger, the company behind the hardware wallets Ledger Nano S and Nano X, announced the launch of its new Ledger Stax wallet, which was developed in partnership with Tony Fadel, co-creator of the iPod and iPhone.</p>
<p>The new Ledger wallet has a unique and innovative design in the style of high-end Samsung cell phones. It lets users view their NFT collections even when the wallet is off.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.ledger.com/blog/ledger-stax-our-consumer-device-invented-by-ipod-creator-tony-fadell" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According to Ledger</a>, all of the improvements to the next-generation wallet were thanks to their relationship with Tony Fadell, whom they recognized as the inventor and mastermind behind Ledger Stax.</p>
<figure id="attachment_227691" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227691" style="width: 741px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ledger-Stax.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-227691" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ledger-Stax.png" alt="Ledger Stax (Render). Image: Twitter" width="741" height="838" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ledger-Stax.png 741w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ledger-Stax-265x300.png 265w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ledger-Stax-44x50.png 44w" sizes="(max-width: 741px) 100vw, 741px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-227691" class="wp-caption-text">Ledger Stax (Render). Image: Twitter</figcaption></figure>
<p>Although the wallet is not yet available for sale, interested customers can go to Ledger&#8217;s website to place reservations. The Ledger Stax will go on sale at the end of March 2023 and will cost $279.</p>
<p>Those who purchase the wallet will be eligible for various prizes, such as a &#8220;Magnet Shell&#8221; protective case and an NFT from the Art on Ledger Stax collection created by a renowned artist in the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>What Improvements Does Ledger Stax Offer?</h2>
<p>In addition to being an easy-to-carry device about the size of a credit card, it allows users to store more than <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-adds-support-for-100-cardano-native-tokens/" data-wpel-link="internal">500 cryptocurrencies</a> or NFT collections. Soon, thanks to Ledger developers, users will be able to explore Web3 applications through Ledger Live.</p>
<p>One of the most notable improvements compared to previous wallets is the curvature of its E-Ink touchscreen, which in addition to displaying NFT collections, allows all transactions to be viewed easily by new crypto users.</p>
<p>As for the battery, the company assured customers that they would be able to use the Stax for weeks or even months with a single charge. This is possible because the screen is monochromatic (works in black and white) and does not consume a lot of battery resources.</p>
<h2>A &#8220;Cool, Cute and Fun&#8221; Device For All Crypto Enthusiasts</h2>
<p>Ian Rogers, Chief Experience Officer at Ledger, noted that thanks to Tony Fadell&#8217;s uncompromising user experience-centric culture, they built an innovative and fun device while maintaining Ledger&#8217;s signature cryptographic security.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Tony Fadell has both the circuit board and the billboard in mind when he builds a product [&#8230;] With Ledger Stax we have made a device which is cool, beautiful, and fun. Together we have fused the uncompromising security and self-custody culture of Ledger, with the equally uncompromising user-experience-focused culture of Tony and his team. The result is the first true secure consumer hardware device for the revolution of value brought by blockchain technology.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Tony Fadell, the designer of Ledger Stax and director of Build Collective, said his motivation after learning about Ledger wallets was to create a &#8220;next-generation device&#8221; that was easy to use for both expert and novice users.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Digging into Ledger&#8217;s proven security technology and trying all the &#8216;best&#8217; hardware wallets out there convinced me to build a next-gen device with Pascal, Ian and the amazing Ledger team, [&#8230;] We need a user-friendly&#8230;no! A &#8216;user-delightful&#8217; tool, to bring digital asset security to the rest of us, not just the geeks.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>For his part, Pascal Gauthier, president and CEO of Ledger, indicated that the new wallet will be &#8220;secure and accessible,&#8221; after highlighting its commitment to the security of its wallets, which to date have never suffered a hack despite having sold more than 5 million units.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-partners-with-iphone-co-creator-tony-fadell-to-launch-its-new-stax-crypto-wallet/" rel="nofollow">Ledger Partners With iPhone Co-creator Tony Fadell To Launch Its New &#8216;Stax&#8221; Crypto Wallet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s Alameda&#8217;s Investment Portfolio: WSJ Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-alamedas-investment-portfolio-wsj-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 23:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227685</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Alameda_Research.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Alameda_Research.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Alameda had $67.5 million invested in an obscure token called “HOLE.”]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Financial Times (FT) published a document on Tuesday exposing where Alameda’s venture investments went days before the FTX Group filed for bankruptcy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Its hundreds of investments included high-profile companies like SpaceX, and a variety of crypto tokens like Polygon (MATIC), and NEAR. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The spreadsheet, </span><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/aaa4a42c-efcc-4c60-9dc6-ba6cccb599e6" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">dated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> early November, included Alameda’s private equity portfolio, alongside “some FTX bets mixed in.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the document provided, Alameda had over $5.4 billion spread across almost 500 “illiquid investments,” split between 10 holding companies. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Among these investments was a $1 billion+ position with Bitcoin miner Genesis Digital. Mining firms have been under massive distress over the past six months, with industry leaders like Core Scientific </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-firm-core-scientific-lost-1-7-billion-in-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">losing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> billions of dollars to increasing mining difficulty and plummeting Bitcoin prices. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, its positions with the HOLE and Polygon (MATIC) tokens amounted to $67.5 million and $50 million respectively. CoinMarketCap has no coins listed under the ticker HOLE besides an asset called “Super Black Hole,” for which no market data is available. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Alameda also appeared to have at least $200 million invested in Sequoia, $150 million invested in the now-bankrupt </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-confirms-binance-us-will-bid-again-for-voyager-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Voyager Digital</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, and another $75 million in </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-rollercoaster-apt-soars-to-100-and-drops-below-8-hours-after-listing-on-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Aptos</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – the layer 1 blockchain that had an underwhelming debut in November. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Alameda had another $50 million of equity in Yuga Labs – the company behind Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFTs which was recently </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-probes-bored-ape-creator-for-potential-unregistered-securities-sale/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">investigated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by the Securities and Exchange Commission. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Prior to FTXs insolvency, the portfolio was reportedly offered up as equity in a hasty attempt to shore up funds for FTX Group in a new credit line. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The spreadsheet appears to further blur the lines between both FTX and Alameda, with some of its listed investments (ex. Genesis) also previously appearing on FTX’s balance sheet. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-alamedas-investment-portfolio-wsj-report/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s Alameda&#8217;s Investment Portfolio: WSJ Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strike Brings Lightning-Based Remittance Payments to Africa</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/strike-brings-lightning-based-remittance-payments-to-africa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 21:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227677</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Bitcoin-Africa-e1631761292206.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Bitcoin-Africa-e1631761292206.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Americans will be able to remit value directly into African bank accounts using Strike and Bitcoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin payments platform Strike has now expanded to Africa, enabling instant and low-cost remittances to the continent by leveraging its new “Send Globally” feature.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The tool, available to all American Strike users, will offer initial coverage to Nigeria, Kenya, and Ghana. </span></p>
<h2>Bringing Bitcoin to Africa</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20221206005453/en/Strike-Launches-Lightning-Fast-Money-Transfers-to-Africa" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Strike on Tuesday, the feature was launched in partnership with the African Bitcoin company Bitnob. Within the app, U.S.-based Strike users can immediately send money to an African recipient, where the funds will be converted into their relevant local currency and deposited into their bank, mobile money, or Bitnob account. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Strike claims this feature will improve the ease of payments in Africa, where banking services are extremely limited and cross-border payment options are few and far between. Strike CEO Jack Mallers specifically pointed to the high fees and service halts from incumbent payment providers as a primary benefit. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“High fees, slow settlement, and lack of innovation in cross-border payments have negatively impacted the developing world,” said Mallers. “Strike offers an opportunity for people to transfer their US dollars easily and instantly across borders.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitnob CEO Bernard Parah added that the application will help financial institutions source USD liquidity more easily. “The current financial system isn&#8217;t set up in a way that ensures equal access for people and institutions from Africa,” he said.</span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/DocumentingBTC/status/1600136555661692928</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Africa is known for being a world leader in Bitcoin and crypto adoption given the limitations of the legacy financial system across the continent. A </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-adoption-in-nigeria-is-fueled-by-limited-access-to-financial-services-study/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">KuCoin study</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> released in April found that crypto had already reached 35% adoption in Nigeria, with over 17 million people having placed over half of their wealth in the asset class. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In June, a collection of human rights activists including Yeonmi Park </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/yeonmi-park-co-signs-letter-to-congress-explaining-bitcoins-importance-for-human-rights/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">petitioned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> congress on the importance of Bitcoin and crypto within the underdeveloped world. These countries, it argued, face issues like monetary colonialism, bank freezes, and exploitative remittance fees. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">One of the letter’s signatories – Alex Gladstein –  promoted Bitcoin again on Tuesday after the Central Bank of Africa </span><a href="https://techpoint.africa/2022/12/06/cbn-reduce-atm-withdrawal-limit?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social%20via%20ifttt&amp;utm_campaign=ifttt%20twitter%20autoshare" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that cash withdrawals at ATMs would be further reduced to just ₦20,000 per day in January 2023 – the equivalent of $45.00 USD. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/gladstein/status/1600191273691774976</p>
<h2>Strike and the Developing World</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Aside from the United States, Strike is focused on rolling out financial services to members of the global south that appear to need it most. These include remittance dependant nations like </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-launches-a-national-bitcoin-office-onbtc/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">El Salvador</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and highly inflationary environments like </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-brings-the-bitcoin-lightning-network-to-argentina/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Argentina</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The company focuses on utilizing the lightning network – Bitcoin’s off-chain scaling solution – to deliver instant global payments for both Bitcoin and fiat currencies. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-brings-lightning-based-remittance-payments-to-africa/" rel="nofollow">Strike Brings Lightning-Based Remittance Payments to Africa</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ConsenSys Clears the Air on MetaMask Privacy Policy After Community Backlash</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-clears-the-air-on-metamask-privacy-policy-after-community-backlash/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MetaMask]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227669</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/Untitled-design.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/Untitled-design.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here’s exactly what data  ConsenSys is collecting from you when you use Infura and MetaMask. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ethereum infrastructure provider ConsenSys has issued a follow-up statement to its privacy policy update that rattled the MetaMask community last month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The firm clarified that it does, in fact, collect users’ IP addresses and wallet information when they make a MetaMask transaction through Infura – but plans to reduce its retention of such data down to seven days. </span></p>
<h2>Privacy Concerns at ConsenSys</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Per the company’s </span><a href="https://consensys.net/blog/news/consensys-data-retention-update/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">statement</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, November’s policy update did not reflect a change in business practices at ConsenSys but rather served to clarify its existing practices. The </span><a href="https://consensys.net/privacy-policy/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">update</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> revealed that the company’s key products, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/metamask-founders-called-the-crypto-space-a-casino-prone-to-ponzi-schemes/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">MetaMask</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Infura, collected both users’ wallet and IP addresses, raising privacy concerns.</span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/CyphrETH/status/1595722882440642561</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We are committed to protecting the privacy of people who use our products so that they will not—and, ultimately, cannot—be betrayed by yet another centralized entity,” wrote ConsenSys.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Both MetaMask and Infura are pillars of the infrastructure that keeps Ethereum usable today. The former is the smart contract platform’s most widely used software wallet, while the latter is the API and archival node provider used by MetaMask for broadcasting transactions. Infura has also been used by various centralized exchanges like Binance and Bithumb when processing deposits and withdrawals. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As ConsenSys noted, its data collection policy comes with limits. For example, Infura does not store users’ wallet address data for ‘read’ requests, such as checking one’s account balance on MetaMask. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By contrast, wallet and IP data for “write” requests (transactions) are collected “to ensure successful transaction propagation, execution, and other important service functionality such as load balancing and DDoS protection, as provided by Infura.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Still, ConsenSys said that wallet and IP address information is stored separately so that each piece of data cannot be associated with the other within the company’s systems. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We have never and will never sell any user data we collect,” it continued.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Infura was one of the node providers to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-treasury-department-users-will-need-a-license-to-withdraw-funds-from-tornado-cash/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">limit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> access to the privacy protocol Tornado Cash following OFAC’s sanctions against it in August. </span></p>
<h2>Using Other Nodes</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">To work around the issue entirely, ConsenSys will roll out a new advanced settings page within MetaMask this week that allows wallet users to select their own RPC node provider outside of Infura. While previously possible, this new page will be seen by new users during the onboarding process, allowing them to never use Infura as their server if they so choose. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The company also plans to improve UX around the existing means for changing one’s RPC node, including making steps not to over-caution the user away from doing so. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, ConsenSys did have a certain warning about the practice of using non-default RPC nodes, including self-hosted nodes. “Alternate RPC providers have different privacy policies and data practices, and self-hosting a node may make it even easier for people to associate your Ethereum accounts with your IP address,” it said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ethereum archival nodes are </span><a href="https://ethereum.org/en/developers/docs/nodes-and-clients/#:~:text=A%20%22node%22%20is%20any%20instance,Ethereum%20software%2C%20forming%20a%20network." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">recognized</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by the Ethereum foundation for generally being difficult to run for average users. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-clears-the-air-on-metamask-privacy-policy-after-community-backlash/" rel="nofollow">ConsenSys Clears the Air on MetaMask Privacy Policy After Community Backlash</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
