<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 04:23:52 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Unleashing the Potential of Web3: MetaBlox and its User-Centric Network Revolution]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/unleashing-the-potential-of-web3-metablox-and-its-user-centric-network-revolution</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-07-21-010910.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-07-21-010910.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-07-21-010910.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/unleashing-the-potential-of-web3-metablox-and-its-user-centric-network-revolution</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) possess immense potential to reshape the future landscape of the internet, ushering in a revolutionary approach to verifying our digital identities. The path to achieving this transformation remains ambiguous as we witness the emergence of Web3, a paradigm shift from platform-centric to user-centric networking. The crucial aspect of a user-centric network lies in users defining their identities and determining the information they wish to share with others.</p>
<p>After years of unwavering dedication, the MetaBlox team has released a breakthrough protocol that uses DIDs to provide a decentralized groundwork for creating a user-centric network. The team is diligently working to build the foundation for a web3 user-centric network that can support web3 native apps.</p>
<p>The MetaBlox Network mobile app represents a major step toward this lofty goal. With this software, users may take the first necessary step toward gaining access to a Free Privacy Protected WiFi Network by registering a DID and automatically uploading it to the blockchain and, in the process, earn mPoints that can be used on the further development of the network.</p>
<p>The platform has a lot of benefits that make it stand out. First and foremost, the team believes that the most compelling aspect of MetaBlox is that it is a user-centric network supported by a rewarding system for its users and builders. MetaBlox hopes to model itself after the prosperous Web 2.0 period, during which prominent corporations gave away their services for free to demonstrate the efficacy of their monetization schemes.</p>
<p>In Web 3.0, MetaBlox seeks to replicate this prosperity with a significant distinction. Instead of profits accruing solely to private entities, MetaBlox positions itself as a decentralized solution, enabling users and network maintainers to reap the rewards. Unlike the Helium Network, which employs LORA technology, MetaBlox operates as a WiFi Network, affording the bandwidth necessary to accommodate many users, thus substantially expanding monetization opportunities for all stakeholders involved.</p>
Powering the User-Oriented Web3: MetaBlox's OpenRoaming Initiative and Decentralized Connectivity
<p>MetaBlox's decentralized OpenRoaming WiFi Network made great strides toward creating a user-oriented Web3. Several major Web3 investment businesses and organizations contributed over $2 million to the initiative. The OpenRoaming Network expanded the worldwide WiFi network by deploying hundreds of MetaBlox Miners as blockchain nodes, allowing for secure, password-free, automated connections using Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs).</p>
<p>To create an OpenRoaming network with over a million access points, MetaBlox collaborated with the Wireless Broadband Alliance (WBA). The WBA Wireless Global Congress also saw a successful demonstration of their technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Users may now create their own WiFi OpenRoaming profiles and have access to Web3 capabilities with the newly released software. Notably, MetaBlox teamed up with other initiatives such as Harmony, Caldance, Memolabs, and Deeper Network to accomplish its goals.&nbsp;</p>
MetaBlox Network's Blockchain Integration for DeFi, GameFi, and NFTs
<p>MetaBlox Network uses blockchain technology to improve the quality of its products and services significantly. Because of Blockchain technology, users' hotspot routers may double as crypto miners, earning them tokens in exchange for giving WiFi access. With this decentralized deployment approach, MetaBlox Network can steadily increase its worldwide presence and reach as an incentive for network development.</p>
<p>In addition, combining the MetaBlox Network with blockchain technology unleashes many novel possibilities. Decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms, game finance (GameFi) ecosystems, and NFT markets may all be accessed confidentially and safely by users. Individuals may make money with digital assets by participating in farming and staking activities on DeFi networks. At the same time, the system provides unhindered entry to the increasing universe of GameFi and Play-to-Earn games, with strong security provided by blockchain-held credentials in place of the more archaic passwords.</p>
<p>MetaBlox Network was developed in response to the rapidly growing NFT sector, and it provides users with simple access to NFT markets and wallets by use of their DIDs. The firm has established its collection of utility-based NFTs, seen on major platforms like OpenSea, as evidence of its dedication to the blockchain ecosystem. MetaBlox Network aims to offer a genuinely user-centric experience that adapts to the new digital environment by integrating Web3, the Metaverse, 5G rollout, DeFi, and DID-based technologies.</p>
MetaBlox's $MBLX Token and Its Role in Decentralized Network Development
<p>MetaBlox is hard at work creating a user-focused, open, and free system for anyone who wants to use it. To encourage the development of a native Web3 network, which is in accordance with this goal, the $MBLX token has been introduced.</p>
<p>Businesses that want to sell goods or provide services inside the MetaBlox ecosystem are the primary target users of the $MBLX token. These companies actively contribute to developing decentralized ownership inside the next generation of wireless networks by earning and using $MBLX tokens.</p>
<p>The $MBLX token's main benefit over competing tokens is that it was made with Web3 users' insatiable curiosity about the platform's features in mind. These customers can take advantage of all the Web3 ecosystem offers once they adopt $MBLX.</p>
MetaBlox's Founding Members and Their Remarkable Technological Achievements
<p>The first MetaBlox team mostly comprises employees from the leading organizations that make up the alliance's founding members, which are located in North America and Asia. These businesses focus on developing and implementing state-of-the-art technologies, including blockchain, IoT, Telco, AI, and financial services. The alliance members range from large, publicly traded corporations to small, innovative startups, but they all have one thing in common: a desire to build a Web3 network that puts users' wants and needs first.</p>
<p>The founding coalition has made great progress and accomplished outstanding feats during the previous four years. They collaborated with the Canadian federal government on the first blockchain program, among other pioneering endeavors. Further distinguishing themselves, they were the first group to combine blockchain technology with eSIM and Bluetooth chips.</p>
<p>It's worth noting that the alliance members are active contributors to the Decentralized ID Foundation. This shows their dedication to spreading the use of decentralized identification systems. WiGig is a broadband version of WiFi, and the alliance members are among the few businesses in the world that have access to this technology. Their proficiency with WiGig technology enables them to provide reliable and fast wireless network options.</p>
<p>Their work in the development of AI is another significant achievement of the original alliance members. They are pioneers in AI edge computing, having designed and produced one of the earliest system-on-a-chip (SOC) devices. This technological advancement provides high-performance and smart computing capabilities at the network's periphery, allowing for instantaneous data processing and analysis.</p>
<p>Members of the alliance have made significant investments in several high-profile initiatives throughout the decentralized finance (DeFi), gaming finance (GameFi), and non-fungible token (NFT) spaces, demonstrating their commitment to the development of these industries beyond just technological means. Investing in promising startups like 1inch and Axie Infinity demonstrates their dedication to fostering growth and development in the nascent blockchain industry.</p>
Final Thoughts
<p>The advent of Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) has the potential to reshape the future of the internet by revolutionizing the way we verify our digital identities. As Web3 emerges, shifting from platform-centric to user-centric networking, the MetaBlox team has made remarkable progress in developing a protocol that leverages DIDs to establish a decentralized foundation for a user-centric network. Their commitment to building a web3 native network that supports user-centric applications is evident in the MetaBlox Network mobile app.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) possess immense potential to reshape the future landscape of the internet, ushering in a revolutionary approach to verifying our digital identities. The path to achieving this transformation remains ambiguous as we witness the emergence of Web3, a paradigm shift from platform-centric to user-centric networking. The crucial aspect of a user-centric network lies in users defining their identities and determining the information they wish to share with others.</p>
<p>After years of unwavering dedication, the MetaBlox team has released a breakthrough protocol that uses DIDs to provide a decentralized groundwork for creating a user-centric network. The team is diligently working to build the foundation for a web3 user-centric network that can support web3 native apps.</p>
<p>The MetaBlox Network mobile app represents a major step toward this lofty goal. With this software, users may take the first necessary step toward gaining access to a Free Privacy Protected WiFi Network by registering a DID and automatically uploading it to the blockchain and, in the process, earn mPoints that can be used on the further development of the network.</p>
<p>The platform has a lot of benefits that make it stand out. First and foremost, the team believes that the most compelling aspect of MetaBlox is that it is a user-centric network supported by a rewarding system for its users and builders. MetaBlox hopes to model itself after the prosperous Web 2.0 period, during which prominent corporations gave away their services for free to demonstrate the efficacy of their monetization schemes.</p>
<p>In Web 3.0, MetaBlox seeks to replicate this prosperity with a significant distinction. Instead of profits accruing solely to private entities, MetaBlox positions itself as a decentralized solution, enabling users and network maintainers to reap the rewards. Unlike the Helium Network, which employs LORA technology, MetaBlox operates as a WiFi Network, affording the bandwidth necessary to accommodate many users, thus substantially expanding monetization opportunities for all stakeholders involved.</p>
Powering the User-Oriented Web3: MetaBlox's OpenRoaming Initiative and Decentralized Connectivity
<p>MetaBlox's decentralized OpenRoaming WiFi Network made great strides toward creating a user-oriented Web3. Several major Web3 investment businesses and organizations contributed over $2 million to the initiative. The OpenRoaming Network expanded the worldwide WiFi network by deploying hundreds of MetaBlox Miners as blockchain nodes, allowing for secure, password-free, automated connections using Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs).</p>
<p>To create an OpenRoaming network with over a million access points, MetaBlox collaborated with the Wireless Broadband Alliance (WBA). The WBA Wireless Global Congress also saw a successful demonstration of their technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Users may now create their own WiFi OpenRoaming profiles and have access to Web3 capabilities with the newly released software. Notably, MetaBlox teamed up with other initiatives such as Harmony, Caldance, Memolabs, and Deeper Network to accomplish its goals.&nbsp;</p>
MetaBlox Network's Blockchain Integration for DeFi, GameFi, and NFTs
<p>MetaBlox Network uses blockchain technology to improve the quality of its products and services significantly. Because of Blockchain technology, users' hotspot routers may double as crypto miners, earning them tokens in exchange for giving WiFi access. With this decentralized deployment approach, MetaBlox Network can steadily increase its worldwide presence and reach as an incentive for network development.</p>
<p>In addition, combining the MetaBlox Network with blockchain technology unleashes many novel possibilities. Decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms, game finance (GameFi) ecosystems, and NFT markets may all be accessed confidentially and safely by users. Individuals may make money with digital assets by participating in farming and staking activities on DeFi networks. At the same time, the system provides unhindered entry to the increasing universe of GameFi and Play-to-Earn games, with strong security provided by blockchain-held credentials in place of the more archaic passwords.</p>
<p>MetaBlox Network was developed in response to the rapidly growing NFT sector, and it provides users with simple access to NFT markets and wallets by use of their DIDs. The firm has established its collection of utility-based NFTs, seen on major platforms like OpenSea, as evidence of its dedication to the blockchain ecosystem. MetaBlox Network aims to offer a genuinely user-centric experience that adapts to the new digital environment by integrating Web3, the Metaverse, 5G rollout, DeFi, and DID-based technologies.</p>
MetaBlox's $MBLX Token and Its Role in Decentralized Network Development
<p>MetaBlox is hard at work creating a user-focused, open, and free system for anyone who wants to use it. To encourage the development of a native Web3 network, which is in accordance with this goal, the $MBLX token has been introduced.</p>
<p>Businesses that want to sell goods or provide services inside the MetaBlox ecosystem are the primary target users of the $MBLX token. These companies actively contribute to developing decentralized ownership inside the next generation of wireless networks by earning and using $MBLX tokens.</p>
<p>The $MBLX token's main benefit over competing tokens is that it was made with Web3 users' insatiable curiosity about the platform's features in mind. These customers can take advantage of all the Web3 ecosystem offers once they adopt $MBLX.</p>
MetaBlox's Founding Members and Their Remarkable Technological Achievements
<p>The first MetaBlox team mostly comprises employees from the leading organizations that make up the alliance's founding members, which are located in North America and Asia. These businesses focus on developing and implementing state-of-the-art technologies, including blockchain, IoT, Telco, AI, and financial services. The alliance members range from large, publicly traded corporations to small, innovative startups, but they all have one thing in common: a desire to build a Web3 network that puts users' wants and needs first.</p>
<p>The founding coalition has made great progress and accomplished outstanding feats during the previous four years. They collaborated with the Canadian federal government on the first blockchain program, among other pioneering endeavors. Further distinguishing themselves, they were the first group to combine blockchain technology with eSIM and Bluetooth chips.</p>
<p>It's worth noting that the alliance members are active contributors to the Decentralized ID Foundation. This shows their dedication to spreading the use of decentralized identification systems. WiGig is a broadband version of WiFi, and the alliance members are among the few businesses in the world that have access to this technology. Their proficiency with WiGig technology enables them to provide reliable and fast wireless network options.</p>
<p>Their work in the development of AI is another significant achievement of the original alliance members. They are pioneers in AI edge computing, having designed and produced one of the earliest system-on-a-chip (SOC) devices. This technological advancement provides high-performance and smart computing capabilities at the network's periphery, allowing for instantaneous data processing and analysis.</p>
<p>Members of the alliance have made significant investments in several high-profile initiatives throughout the decentralized finance (DeFi), gaming finance (GameFi), and non-fungible token (NFT) spaces, demonstrating their commitment to the development of these industries beyond just technological means. Investing in promising startups like 1inch and Axie Infinity demonstrates their dedication to fostering growth and development in the nascent blockchain industry.</p>
Final Thoughts
<p>The advent of Decentralized Identifiers (DIDs) has the potential to reshape the future of the internet by revolutionizing the way we verify our digital identities. As Web3 emerges, shifting from platform-centric to user-centric networking, the MetaBlox team has made remarkable progress in developing a protocol that leverages DIDs to establish a decentralized foundation for a user-centric network. Their commitment to building a web3 native network that supports user-centric applications is evident in the MetaBlox Network mobile app.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Trader Joe Goes All-In On Auto-Pools: Can this Make Joe (JOE) Match Up to the Blazing Uwerx (WERX) Presale?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/trader-joe-goes-all-in-on-auto-pools-can-this-make-joe-joe-match-up-to-the-blazing-uwerx-werx-presale</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-20-at-215023.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-20-at-215023.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-20-at-215023.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/trader-joe-goes-all-in-on-auto-pools-can-this-make-joe-joe-match-up-to-the-blazing-uwerx-werx-presale</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s4">Joe (JOE) and Uwerx are two emerging crypto platforms fastly approaching their launch date. </p>
<p class="s4">As both roll out exciting features ahead of their launch, it is crucial to understand what exactly they are and how their innovative approaches may be the revolution their respective industry needs at this time.</p>
<p class="s4">In this article, we have carefully examined these two significant potential tokens, understanding their use cases, price predictions, and how beneficial they could be for investors. </p>
Joe (JOE) Price Prediction
<p class="s4">Trader Joe is an innovative DeFi platform looking to offer an automated yield farming strategy for Liquidity Providers, consequently eliminating the traditional strenuous position management system. </p>
<p class="s4">Joe (JOE), the native token of the Trader Joe platform, is currently preparing to launch an exciting feature to augment its current value proposition, the Auto Pool. </p>
<p class="s4">Auto Pool is set to provide the best user experience and capital efficiency for DeFi users, ultimately helping the protocol generate more liquidity. This is a largely untapped area in the DeFi market, and with Joe (JOE) pioneering this aspect, you can be sure its adoption would be massive. </p>
<p class="s4">Joe&rsquo;s (JOE) first offering, The General, will be launched soon, making the token&rsquo;s future growth worth keeping an eye on. </p>
Uwerx (WERX): Championing a New Era for Freelancers
<p class="s4">Like Joe (JOE) is doing in the world of DeFi, Uwerx is also set to revolutionize the freelancing industry, serving as a threat to the progression of existing freelancing platforms. </p>
<p class="s4">While &ldquo;threat&rdquo; may sound somewhat exaggerated, it is actually the reality, considering the multiple advantages Uwerx has over these existing platforms, especially the incredibly lower transaction commission. </p>
<p class="s4">Unlike Fiverr, which charges 20%, and Upwork, which charges 10% per transaction, Uwerx will only deduct a flat fee of 1% as commission, allowing freelancers to enjoy their money while fostering a healthy client-freelancer relationship. </p>
<p class="s4">Beyond their transaction fee, the Uwerx team has also unveiled the &ldquo;Uwerx Vault,&rdquo; a central hub where users can stake (store their token for as long as they want while getting rewarded for it). </p>
<p class="s4">SolidProof and InterFi Network have audited the platform to confirm its credibility and have also been listed by CoinSniper and awaiting Uniswap listing on Tuesday, August 1, 2023. The team has also promised to renounce all contracts and reduce taxes to zero before launching the project on centralized exchanges.</p>
<p class="s4">The Uwerx platform currently boasts 1,600+ subscribers on Telegram, 1,600+ Twitter followers, and 5,500 sign-ups on the platform. </p>
Uwerx (WERX) is Enjoying an Incredible Presale Run
<p class="s4">The WERX token is enjoying an unbelievable adoption rate, with the token&rsquo;s stage 1 to stage 4 presales getting completed in record time. Although currently at stage 5 of the presale at $0.041 per token with a 15% bonus.</p>
<p class="s4">Thanks to this high demand, the Uwerx team has modified WERX token allocations and will lock liquidity before all presales end on Monday, July 31, 2023. </p>
<p class="s4">In a more recent update, the team has also disclosed their plans to send tokens to holders immediately after the end of the presale in a 6-week vesting period. This vesting period will follow a defined vesting schedule: 8% on week 1, 10% on week 2, 14% on week 3, 18% on week 4, 22% on week 5, and 28% on week 6. Similarly, after the presale ends, they also plan to host a Test Airdrop, as voted by the community. </p>
<p class="s4">Beyond the Uwerx platform enjoying a brilliant presale run, the Uwerx team has also released the first version of the Alpha platform as a PDF while waiting to transition from Alpha into Beta in the coming weeks. The published PDF features ten (10) pages, including but not limited to the Sign in Page, Log In Page, Forgot Password Page, Hiring Dashboard Page, My Activity Page, Client or Freelancer Initiation Page, etc. </p>
<p class="s4">In a bid to create an inclusive community, the team has also created a dedicated feedback email, feedback@uwerx.network, to receive comments and suggestions about the published PDF pages. </p>
<p class="s4">Tokens in the fifth stage of the presale are currently available at a favorable price of $0.05245, accompanied by an appealing 15% bonus. This creates a highly advantageous opportunity for potential participants. However, it is important to be aware that the price will rise to $0.06294 on Tuesday, February 25th, 2023, at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p class="s4">Presale: &nbsp;invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s4">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p class="s4">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s4">Joe (JOE) and Uwerx are two emerging crypto platforms fastly approaching their launch date. </p>
<p class="s4">As both roll out exciting features ahead of their launch, it is crucial to understand what exactly they are and how their innovative approaches may be the revolution their respective industry needs at this time.</p>
<p class="s4">In this article, we have carefully examined these two significant potential tokens, understanding their use cases, price predictions, and how beneficial they could be for investors. </p>
Joe (JOE) Price Prediction
<p class="s4">Trader Joe is an innovative DeFi platform looking to offer an automated yield farming strategy for Liquidity Providers, consequently eliminating the traditional strenuous position management system. </p>
<p class="s4">Joe (JOE), the native token of the Trader Joe platform, is currently preparing to launch an exciting feature to augment its current value proposition, the Auto Pool. </p>
<p class="s4">Auto Pool is set to provide the best user experience and capital efficiency for DeFi users, ultimately helping the protocol generate more liquidity. This is a largely untapped area in the DeFi market, and with Joe (JOE) pioneering this aspect, you can be sure its adoption would be massive. </p>
<p class="s4">Joe&rsquo;s (JOE) first offering, The General, will be launched soon, making the token&rsquo;s future growth worth keeping an eye on. </p>
Uwerx (WERX): Championing a New Era for Freelancers
<p class="s4">Like Joe (JOE) is doing in the world of DeFi, Uwerx is also set to revolutionize the freelancing industry, serving as a threat to the progression of existing freelancing platforms. </p>
<p class="s4">While &ldquo;threat&rdquo; may sound somewhat exaggerated, it is actually the reality, considering the multiple advantages Uwerx has over these existing platforms, especially the incredibly lower transaction commission. </p>
<p class="s4">Unlike Fiverr, which charges 20%, and Upwork, which charges 10% per transaction, Uwerx will only deduct a flat fee of 1% as commission, allowing freelancers to enjoy their money while fostering a healthy client-freelancer relationship. </p>
<p class="s4">Beyond their transaction fee, the Uwerx team has also unveiled the &ldquo;Uwerx Vault,&rdquo; a central hub where users can stake (store their token for as long as they want while getting rewarded for it). </p>
<p class="s4">SolidProof and InterFi Network have audited the platform to confirm its credibility and have also been listed by CoinSniper and awaiting Uniswap listing on Tuesday, August 1, 2023. The team has also promised to renounce all contracts and reduce taxes to zero before launching the project on centralized exchanges.</p>
<p class="s4">The Uwerx platform currently boasts 1,600+ subscribers on Telegram, 1,600+ Twitter followers, and 5,500 sign-ups on the platform. </p>
Uwerx (WERX) is Enjoying an Incredible Presale Run
<p class="s4">The WERX token is enjoying an unbelievable adoption rate, with the token&rsquo;s stage 1 to stage 4 presales getting completed in record time. Although currently at stage 5 of the presale at $0.041 per token with a 15% bonus.</p>
<p class="s4">Thanks to this high demand, the Uwerx team has modified WERX token allocations and will lock liquidity before all presales end on Monday, July 31, 2023. </p>
<p class="s4">In a more recent update, the team has also disclosed their plans to send tokens to holders immediately after the end of the presale in a 6-week vesting period. This vesting period will follow a defined vesting schedule: 8% on week 1, 10% on week 2, 14% on week 3, 18% on week 4, 22% on week 5, and 28% on week 6. Similarly, after the presale ends, they also plan to host a Test Airdrop, as voted by the community. </p>
<p class="s4">Beyond the Uwerx platform enjoying a brilliant presale run, the Uwerx team has also released the first version of the Alpha platform as a PDF while waiting to transition from Alpha into Beta in the coming weeks. The published PDF features ten (10) pages, including but not limited to the Sign in Page, Log In Page, Forgot Password Page, Hiring Dashboard Page, My Activity Page, Client or Freelancer Initiation Page, etc. </p>
<p class="s4">In a bid to create an inclusive community, the team has also created a dedicated feedback email, feedback@uwerx.network, to receive comments and suggestions about the published PDF pages. </p>
<p class="s4">Tokens in the fifth stage of the presale are currently available at a favorable price of $0.05245, accompanied by an appealing 15% bonus. This creates a highly advantageous opportunity for potential participants. However, it is important to be aware that the price will rise to $0.06294 on Tuesday, February 25th, 2023, at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p class="s4">Presale: &nbsp;invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s4">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s4">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p class="s4">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Terraform Labs Names New CEO Amid Legal Woes $LUNA]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/terraform-labs-names-new-ceo-amid-legal-woes-luna</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/terraform-labs-new-ceo-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/terraform-labs-new-ceo-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/terraform-labs-new-ceo-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/terraform-labs-names-new-ceo-amid-legal-woes-luna</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the face of legal turbulence surrounding its co-founder, Do Kwon, blockchain firm Terraform Labs has appointed a new CEO.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The change in leadership comes as Kwon, also Terraform Labs' principal shareholder, is under the threat of possible extradition to South Korea or the U.S. from Montenegro.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Steering Through the Storm</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Wall Street Journal reported that Terraform Labs has named U.S. citizen Chris Amani as its new CEO. Amani, who has been with Terraform since 2021, previously served as its chief operating officer and chief financial officer. Prior to his tenure at Terra, Amani held the CEO position at Humanity, a scheduling solution provider. His LinkedIn profile reveals that he took the reins as Terra's CEO in April 2023.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the company's past focus on stablecoins, Amani stated that the firm will not launch any more of such offerings, instead concentrating on other products.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"We have a vision for how we could salvage this, even though I think it's going to be hard and it's going to take a long time," Amani said.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">He also expressed hope that Kwon would clear himself of all charges, while affirming that Terra will continue to operate in his absence.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Legal Quagmire and Market Impact</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Terra's collapse in May 2022 set off a domino effect that rattled the crypto market. The platform's stablecoin, TerraUSD (UST), lost its peg to the U.S. dollar, inciting investigations into Kwon and co-founder Daniel Shin's suspected involvement in illicit transactions during the collapse.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In March 2023, Kwon was arrested in Montenegro for allegedly using counterfeit travel documents. Although he received a four-month prison sentence, he also faces the prospect of extradition to either the U.S. or South Korea post-sentence. South Korean prosecutors issued an arrest warrant for Kwon in 2022, accusing him of violating the country's capital market laws. He was later released on bail.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Terraform's Legal Fight</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In an additional context, Terraform Labs is striving to subpoena bankrupt FTX for relevant documents to defend its case against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The SEC had earlier sued Terraform Labs and former CEO Kwon, alleging fraudulent activities and market manipulation leading to the collapse of Terra/LUNA tokens.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The installation of a new CEO and the ongoing legal efforts highlight Terraform Labs' determination to steer its operations despite ongoing woes with its legal status.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Terraform Labs seeks the release of certain trading records from FTX to demonstrate that the destabilization of the Terra USD (UST) was triggered by a coordinated short attack by third parties. If the request is approved, the firm demands the immediate disclosure of these documents, given its trial's commencement by November 30.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the face of legal turbulence surrounding its co-founder, Do Kwon, blockchain firm Terraform Labs has appointed a new CEO.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The change in leadership comes as Kwon, also Terraform Labs' principal shareholder, is under the threat of possible extradition to South Korea or the U.S. from Montenegro.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Steering Through the Storm</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Wall Street Journal reported that Terraform Labs has named U.S. citizen Chris Amani as its new CEO. Amani, who has been with Terraform since 2021, previously served as its chief operating officer and chief financial officer. Prior to his tenure at Terra, Amani held the CEO position at Humanity, a scheduling solution provider. His LinkedIn profile reveals that he took the reins as Terra's CEO in April 2023.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the company's past focus on stablecoins, Amani stated that the firm will not launch any more of such offerings, instead concentrating on other products.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"We have a vision for how we could salvage this, even though I think it's going to be hard and it's going to take a long time," Amani said.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">He also expressed hope that Kwon would clear himself of all charges, while affirming that Terra will continue to operate in his absence.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Legal Quagmire and Market Impact</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Terra's collapse in May 2022 set off a domino effect that rattled the crypto market. The platform's stablecoin, TerraUSD (UST), lost its peg to the U.S. dollar, inciting investigations into Kwon and co-founder Daniel Shin's suspected involvement in illicit transactions during the collapse.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In March 2023, Kwon was arrested in Montenegro for allegedly using counterfeit travel documents. Although he received a four-month prison sentence, he also faces the prospect of extradition to either the U.S. or South Korea post-sentence. South Korean prosecutors issued an arrest warrant for Kwon in 2022, accusing him of violating the country's capital market laws. He was later released on bail.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Terraform's Legal Fight</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In an additional context, Terraform Labs is striving to subpoena bankrupt FTX for relevant documents to defend its case against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The SEC had earlier sued Terraform Labs and former CEO Kwon, alleging fraudulent activities and market manipulation leading to the collapse of Terra/LUNA tokens.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The installation of a new CEO and the ongoing legal efforts highlight Terraform Labs' determination to steer its operations despite ongoing woes with its legal status.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Terraform Labs seeks the release of certain trading records from FTX to demonstrate that the destabilization of the Terra USD (UST) was triggered by a coordinated short attack by third parties. If the request is approved, the firm demands the immediate disclosure of these documents, given its trial's commencement by November 30.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Myanmar's NUG Builds Crypto-Neobank To Challenge Military Rule]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/myanmar-nug-builds-crypto-neobank-to-challenge-military-rule</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/myanmar-nug-h-fixed.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/myanmar-nug-h-fixed.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/myanmar-nug-h-fixed.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/myanmar-nug-builds-crypto-neobank-to-challenge-military-rule</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Myanmar&rsquo;s National Unity Government (NUG), a shadow government opposing the current military rule, is set to launch a neobank operating on the Polygon blockchain network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This development aims to disrupt the military-controlled financial system and fund efforts to regain civilian rule.</p>
Neobank Initiative
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The NUG's neobank, known as the Spring Development Bank (SDB), plans to offer currency swap, fixed deposits, and prize-linked savings account services via a web-based app, according to a spokesperson's statement at a recent virtual press conference. The bank aims to primarily cater to supporters of the ousted leader, Aung San Suu Kyi, including the Burmese diaspora. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">By using Uniswap v3 pools and USDT stablecoins, SDB will enable users to bypass the conventional financial infrastructure controlled by the State Administration Council (SAC), the military government. Donations made through SDB will directly contribute to the revolution effort and help with the reconstruction of post-revolution Myanmar.</p>
Raising Funds for Revolution
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Since the military coup in February 2021, which triggered various sanctions from governing bodies like the U.S. and the EU, the NUG has been devising innovative methods to raise funds to challenge the military junta. These initiatives include issuing revolutionary bonds and auctioning off properties held by military leaders. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The bank, solely owned by NUG&rsquo;s Ministry of Planning, Finance, and Investment, intends to offer shares to the public in two phases. An initial coin offering (ICO) round will exclusively serve SDB account holders, followed by another ICO round targeting institutional investors. The bank also plans to raise funds through remittances, currency exchanges, loans, and other financial products. In 2021, the NUG assigned Tether as its official currency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The revolutionary government has since been recognized as the official government of Myanmar by members of the United Nations and the European Parliament, from October 2021 forward. It has been clear, however, that the U.S. has never officially disclosed any recognition of this matter.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Security Measures and User Goals</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Assuring compliance with Basel Accords and Financial Action Task Force (FATF) regulations, SDB will implement multiple layers of data and funds segregation. SDB aims to onboard 100,000 active users within six months.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the challenges facing the NUG, the launch of SDB demonstrates how blockchain technology can be leveraged to challenge established systems and foster political change. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Myanmar&rsquo;s National Unity Government (NUG), a shadow government opposing the current military rule, is set to launch a neobank operating on the Polygon blockchain network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This development aims to disrupt the military-controlled financial system and fund efforts to regain civilian rule.</p>
Neobank Initiative
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The NUG's neobank, known as the Spring Development Bank (SDB), plans to offer currency swap, fixed deposits, and prize-linked savings account services via a web-based app, according to a spokesperson's statement at a recent virtual press conference. The bank aims to primarily cater to supporters of the ousted leader, Aung San Suu Kyi, including the Burmese diaspora. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">By using Uniswap v3 pools and USDT stablecoins, SDB will enable users to bypass the conventional financial infrastructure controlled by the State Administration Council (SAC), the military government. Donations made through SDB will directly contribute to the revolution effort and help with the reconstruction of post-revolution Myanmar.</p>
Raising Funds for Revolution
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Since the military coup in February 2021, which triggered various sanctions from governing bodies like the U.S. and the EU, the NUG has been devising innovative methods to raise funds to challenge the military junta. These initiatives include issuing revolutionary bonds and auctioning off properties held by military leaders. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The bank, solely owned by NUG&rsquo;s Ministry of Planning, Finance, and Investment, intends to offer shares to the public in two phases. An initial coin offering (ICO) round will exclusively serve SDB account holders, followed by another ICO round targeting institutional investors. The bank also plans to raise funds through remittances, currency exchanges, loans, and other financial products. In 2021, the NUG assigned Tether as its official currency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The revolutionary government has since been recognized as the official government of Myanmar by members of the United Nations and the European Parliament, from October 2021 forward. It has been clear, however, that the U.S. has never officially disclosed any recognition of this matter.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Security Measures and User Goals</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Assuring compliance with Basel Accords and Financial Action Task Force (FATF) regulations, SDB will implement multiple layers of data and funds segregation. SDB aims to onboard 100,000 active users within six months.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the challenges facing the NUG, the launch of SDB demonstrates how blockchain technology can be leveraged to challenge established systems and foster political change. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[A16z Exec Touts Promise of Web3 Social Platforms]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/a16z-exec-touts-promise-of-web3-social-platforms</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/a16zcrypto-web3-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/a16zcrypto-web3-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/a16zcrypto-web3-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/a16z-exec-touts-promise-of-web3-social-platforms</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In a recent keynote speech at the Ethereum Community Conference (EthCC), Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) partner Sriram Krishnan expressed confidence that Web3 has the potential to remedy the issues plaguing current Web2-based social media platforms. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Krishnan criticized the state of modern social media, calling it &ldquo;stuck in a different era,&rdquo; and urging that it was time for a change. He proposed the construction of "large-scale crypto consumer social media marketplace applications" as the way forward.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The a16z partner highlighted key flaws in current social media platforms: a restrictive follower system, limited application programming interface support, meager economic benefits for creators, and a lack of user and creator input in platform governance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In contrast, Krishnan painted an optimistic picture of the potential that Web3 social platforms could offer, emphasizing the opportunities they present to underserved communities and high-status individuals whose voices are muted on other platforms.</p>
Social Platforms From Web3
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Krishnan also proposed an unconventional approach to developing these platforms: eschewing financial incentives at the outset. Instead of initially focusing on monetary rewards for creators, Krishnan suggested centering the early stages of a platform's life on fostering community and engagement.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Social media dynamics are weird and complicated. These are complex human dynamics, and when you introduce money, I think it gets challenging to kind of map those dynamics," Krishnan claimed.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the exec, prioritizing the monetary aspect can detract from the aim of community building and enjoyment.</p>
Handling Contradictions
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This doesn't mean the introduction of financial mechanisms should be completely foregone. According to Krishnan, once the platform has established its user base and community, creator economics and governance stakes can then be introduced. This incremental approach, he argues, could foster a more balanced and sustainable social media landscape.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On the outset, Krishnan's views hold a promising potential not only for the reinvention of social media platforms but for the broader realization of Web3's inherent capabilities. Web3 technology, built on decentralized blockchain systems, offers a level of transparency and user control not feasible within the limitations of previous Web2 environments. These traits could lend themselves well to creating a social media ecosystem more responsive to user needs and desires.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In this sense, then, the potential economic benefits offered by Web3 platforms could foster a more equitable digital environment. This is particularly significant for creators, who currently receive a minimal share of the revenue generated by their content on traditional platforms. Web3 has the potential to rectify this imbalance, offering creators a larger piece of the economic pie. The caution(s) proposed by Krishnan, to delay the introduction of financial incentives, could help ensure that these economic benefits do not overshadow the vital elements of community and engagement.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite such a potential, Krishnan's vision of the future of social media is by no means assured, though it does provide a compelling blueprint for what could be possible. By harnessing the power of Web3, the next generation of social media platforms might not only resolve the issues inherent in existing platforms, but also open up new avenues for user engagement and creator remuneration.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In a recent keynote speech at the Ethereum Community Conference (EthCC), Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) partner Sriram Krishnan expressed confidence that Web3 has the potential to remedy the issues plaguing current Web2-based social media platforms. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Krishnan criticized the state of modern social media, calling it &ldquo;stuck in a different era,&rdquo; and urging that it was time for a change. He proposed the construction of "large-scale crypto consumer social media marketplace applications" as the way forward.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The a16z partner highlighted key flaws in current social media platforms: a restrictive follower system, limited application programming interface support, meager economic benefits for creators, and a lack of user and creator input in platform governance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In contrast, Krishnan painted an optimistic picture of the potential that Web3 social platforms could offer, emphasizing the opportunities they present to underserved communities and high-status individuals whose voices are muted on other platforms.</p>
Social Platforms From Web3
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Krishnan also proposed an unconventional approach to developing these platforms: eschewing financial incentives at the outset. Instead of initially focusing on monetary rewards for creators, Krishnan suggested centering the early stages of a platform's life on fostering community and engagement.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Social media dynamics are weird and complicated. These are complex human dynamics, and when you introduce money, I think it gets challenging to kind of map those dynamics," Krishnan claimed.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the exec, prioritizing the monetary aspect can detract from the aim of community building and enjoyment.</p>
Handling Contradictions
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This doesn't mean the introduction of financial mechanisms should be completely foregone. According to Krishnan, once the platform has established its user base and community, creator economics and governance stakes can then be introduced. This incremental approach, he argues, could foster a more balanced and sustainable social media landscape.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On the outset, Krishnan's views hold a promising potential not only for the reinvention of social media platforms but for the broader realization of Web3's inherent capabilities. Web3 technology, built on decentralized blockchain systems, offers a level of transparency and user control not feasible within the limitations of previous Web2 environments. These traits could lend themselves well to creating a social media ecosystem more responsive to user needs and desires.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In this sense, then, the potential economic benefits offered by Web3 platforms could foster a more equitable digital environment. This is particularly significant for creators, who currently receive a minimal share of the revenue generated by their content on traditional platforms. Web3 has the potential to rectify this imbalance, offering creators a larger piece of the economic pie. The caution(s) proposed by Krishnan, to delay the introduction of financial incentives, could help ensure that these economic benefits do not overshadow the vital elements of community and engagement.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite such a potential, Krishnan's vision of the future of social media is by no means assured, though it does provide a compelling blueprint for what could be possible. By harnessing the power of Web3, the next generation of social media platforms might not only resolve the issues inherent in existing platforms, but also open up new avenues for user engagement and creator remuneration.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OpenEx Closes Funding Round]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/openex-closes-funding-round</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Beige_Minimalist_Rectangular_Menu_Collage_Cafe_Ins_1689852002EttCCgnBpB.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Beige_Minimalist_Rectangular_Menu_Collage_Cafe_Ins_1689852002EttCCgnBpB.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Beige_Minimalist_Rectangular_Menu_Collage_Cafe_Ins_1689852002EttCCgnBpB.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:33:34 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/openex-closes-funding-round</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, July 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>OpenEx Closed Funding Round to build an industry-unique hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, aiming to be the Hybrid,CEX+DEX, where certified partners can act as their own liquidity provider.</p><p>OpenEx today announced it has its Pre-A close for a valuation of 50 Million USD. The round includes prominent names in the Web3 space, including C&sup2; Ventures, Agallochum Capital, TKX Capital,&nbsp;and many other Web3 industry leaders. The new funding will be used to better the trading experience on the products.</p><p>The downfall of FTX reveals the chronic illness of the industry: many crypto exchanges enter the market to trade and form opposite trades with users leading to the exchange being exposed to huge price risks, rampant insider trading, and imperfect risk controls leading to user security issues such as capital safety.</p><p>By allowing certified partners to own their decentralized trading pool,&nbsp;autonomy and membership sovereignty is at the forefront. OpenEx&rsquo;s core principles are neutrality, fairness, and impartiality.&nbsp;With decentralized trading pools, OpenEx will ensure fairness and foster increased participation in the trading ecosystem.</p><p>&ldquo;OpenEx is growing at an exponential rate and we look forward to pushing out more fun and innovative products to our supporters,&rdquo; said Bob Chien, Chief Business Officer of OpenEx, &ldquo;Given the current market situation, we will soon initiate our trade mining program, where users will be rewarded as they trade.&rdquo;</p><p>&ldquo;Based on the OpenEx infrastructure and ecosystem, important links and participants of traditional financial markets, like brokers, will be able to provide more customized services to users in different regions and with different experience profiles.&rdquo;&nbsp;stated Chris Lee from TKX Capital.</p><p>When asked about the future of OpenEx, CEO Jake Stolarski, replies, &ldquo;We are here to democratize the traditional CEX model, with a focus on user empowerment and freedom, we hope that we can build a beginner-friendly platform that ensures fair transactions and personalized services.&rdquo;</p><p>OpenEx has been online for nearly 3 months and already has an active community of over 100,000 monthly active users, with 60,000+ registered users and members respectively. The daily trading volume is approximately around 100 million USD.</p><p>About OpenEx</p><p>OpenEx is building an industry-unique new-generation hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, attracting diverse market entities through diverse trading modules to maximize liquidity creation and the most efficient pricing.</p>ContactGrowth DirectorDarren GohOpenExdarren@openex.xyz]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, July 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>OpenEx Closed Funding Round to build an industry-unique hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, aiming to be the Hybrid,CEX+DEX, where certified partners can act as their own liquidity provider.</p><p>OpenEx today announced it has its Pre-A close for a valuation of 50 Million USD. The round includes prominent names in the Web3 space, including C&sup2; Ventures, Agallochum Capital, TKX Capital,&nbsp;and many other Web3 industry leaders. The new funding will be used to better the trading experience on the products.</p><p>The downfall of FTX reveals the chronic illness of the industry: many crypto exchanges enter the market to trade and form opposite trades with users leading to the exchange being exposed to huge price risks, rampant insider trading, and imperfect risk controls leading to user security issues such as capital safety.</p><p>By allowing certified partners to own their decentralized trading pool,&nbsp;autonomy and membership sovereignty is at the forefront. OpenEx&rsquo;s core principles are neutrality, fairness, and impartiality.&nbsp;With decentralized trading pools, OpenEx will ensure fairness and foster increased participation in the trading ecosystem.</p><p>&ldquo;OpenEx is growing at an exponential rate and we look forward to pushing out more fun and innovative products to our supporters,&rdquo; said Bob Chien, Chief Business Officer of OpenEx, &ldquo;Given the current market situation, we will soon initiate our trade mining program, where users will be rewarded as they trade.&rdquo;</p><p>&ldquo;Based on the OpenEx infrastructure and ecosystem, important links and participants of traditional financial markets, like brokers, will be able to provide more customized services to users in different regions and with different experience profiles.&rdquo;&nbsp;stated Chris Lee from TKX Capital.</p><p>When asked about the future of OpenEx, CEO Jake Stolarski, replies, &ldquo;We are here to democratize the traditional CEX model, with a focus on user empowerment and freedom, we hope that we can build a beginner-friendly platform that ensures fair transactions and personalized services.&rdquo;</p><p>OpenEx has been online for nearly 3 months and already has an active community of over 100,000 monthly active users, with 60,000+ registered users and members respectively. The daily trading volume is approximately around 100 million USD.</p><p>About OpenEx</p><p>OpenEx is building an industry-unique new-generation hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, attracting diverse market entities through diverse trading modules to maximize liquidity creation and the most efficient pricing.</p>ContactGrowth DirectorDarren GohOpenExdarren@openex.xyz]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Cited Below 29477 - 21 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-cited-below-29477-21-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-20-july-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-20-july-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-20-july-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-cited-below-29477-21-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Above 30354:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 21 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) sought to add to recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 30421.29 area after Stops were elected above the 30196.25 and 30354.83 areas, an upside price objective related to buying pressure that emerged around the 29757.44 area.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives related to this level include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29145, 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30369.61 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30090.97.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Above 30354:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 21 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) sought to add to recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 30421.29 area after Stops were elected above the 30196.25 and 30354.83 areas, an upside price objective related to buying pressure that emerged around the 29757.44 area.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives related to this level include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29145, 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30369.61 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30090.97.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Lists XRP, BRISE And ADA As Top Picks for Rally]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-influencer-lists-xrp-brise-and-ada-as-top-picks-for-rally</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uploads/youtube/screenshot-2023-07-20-at-152021.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uploads/youtube/screenshot-2023-07-20-at-152021.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uploads/youtube/screenshot-2023-07-20-at-152021.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-influencer-lists-xrp-brise-and-ada-as-top-picks-for-rally</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto influencer JefferyCrypt took to Twitter earlier today to share his hottest crypto picks for maximum gains in the next bull run. According to the influencer, XRP, Bitgert (BRISE) and Cardano (ADA) are likely to perform well in the near future and are poised for an upward movement in the dynamic and ever-evolving crypto space. </p>
<p>According to JefferyCrypt, Ripple&rsquo;s recent victory in the lawsuit filed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) made XRP an attractive prospect for crypto investors. The influencer told his followers on Twitter that the court victory provided much-needed legal and regulatory clarity surrounding XRP and that it had restored investors' confidence in the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap showed that XRP was trading at $0.81 at the time of writing. The crypto has gained more than 70% since the summary judgment in SEC v Ripple. The online sentiment regarding XRP is divided, with some experts anticipating a further rally while others warned of a potential decline in case the SEC decides to appeal the court&rsquo;s ruling. </p>
The JefferyCrypt&rsquo;s second pick was Bitgert&rsquo;s native token BRISE. 
<p>According to the crypto influencer, Bitgert is a rising project in the blockchain space that offers innovative solutions and a fundamental value proposition. At the time of writing, BRISE was trading at $0.00000025, with a market capitalization of $102 million and a daily trading volume of $2.5 million. </p>
<p>JefferyCrypt&rsquo;s last pick was ADA, the native token of the Cardano blockchain. The influencer cited Cardano&rsquo;s advancements in blockchain research and peer-reviewed approach as the reason for including the token in his top altcoin picks. ADA is currently trading at $0.32, up 2.9% over the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>The influencer cited the summary judgment in Ripple v SEC as a major factor for his altcoin picks. According to him, the court ruling provided regulatory clarity regarding the security status of the above-mentioned tokens, which assured investors of their regulatory compliance. </p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto influencer JefferyCrypt took to Twitter earlier today to share his hottest crypto picks for maximum gains in the next bull run. According to the influencer, XRP, Bitgert (BRISE) and Cardano (ADA) are likely to perform well in the near future and are poised for an upward movement in the dynamic and ever-evolving crypto space. </p>
<p>According to JefferyCrypt, Ripple&rsquo;s recent victory in the lawsuit filed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) made XRP an attractive prospect for crypto investors. The influencer told his followers on Twitter that the court victory provided much-needed legal and regulatory clarity surrounding XRP and that it had restored investors' confidence in the cryptocurrency. </p>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap showed that XRP was trading at $0.81 at the time of writing. The crypto has gained more than 70% since the summary judgment in SEC v Ripple. The online sentiment regarding XRP is divided, with some experts anticipating a further rally while others warned of a potential decline in case the SEC decides to appeal the court&rsquo;s ruling. </p>
The JefferyCrypt&rsquo;s second pick was Bitgert&rsquo;s native token BRISE. 
<p>According to the crypto influencer, Bitgert is a rising project in the blockchain space that offers innovative solutions and a fundamental value proposition. At the time of writing, BRISE was trading at $0.00000025, with a market capitalization of $102 million and a daily trading volume of $2.5 million. </p>
<p>JefferyCrypt&rsquo;s last pick was ADA, the native token of the Cardano blockchain. The influencer cited Cardano&rsquo;s advancements in blockchain research and peer-reviewed approach as the reason for including the token in his top altcoin picks. ADA is currently trading at $0.32, up 2.9% over the past 24 hours. </p>
<p>The influencer cited the summary judgment in Ripple v SEC as a major factor for his altcoin picks. According to him, the court ruling provided regulatory clarity regarding the security status of the above-mentioned tokens, which assured investors of their regulatory compliance. </p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US Senators Introduce DeFi Regulations]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/us-senators-introduce-defi-regulations</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/us-senate-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/us-senate-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/us-senate-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:57:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/us-senators-introduce-defi-regulations</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>A bipartisan group of United States Senators has introduced the CANSEE Act to regulate DeFi platforms in order to curb money laundering and other financial transgressions.&nbsp;</p>
Senators Against DeFi
<p>U.S. Senators are taking a strong stance against money laundering and crypto-facilitated crime by introducing new legislation aimed at regulating decentralized finance (DeFi) services. The Crypto-Asset National Security Enhancement and Enforcement (CANSEE) Act requires DeFi platforms to comply with the same anti-money laundering (AML) and economic sanctions obligations as traditional financial companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The bipartisan team of senators behind the CANSEE Act includes Jack Reed (D-RI), Mike Rounds (R-SD), Mark Warner (D-VA), and Mitt Romney (R-UT).&nbsp;</p>
DeFi To Get More Centralized
<p>The CANSEE Act will introduce tighter regulations and laws to DeFi, on par with the governance experienced by centralized institutions like banks, securities brokers, casinos, and centralized crypto trading platforms. Consequently, DeFi services will have to establish AML programs, conduct due diligence on customers, and report suspicious transactions to the Treasury Department's Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN).</p>
<p>Senator Warner noted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I believe these focused measures will help maintain the robust AML and sanctions enforcement we need to protect our national security, while allowing participants who play by the rules to continue to take advantage of the potential of distributed ledger technologies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The legislation will also extend to all individuals and entities who facilitate the use of DeFi platforms by sanctioned individuals. The regulations under the act also will hold accountable any investor putting in more than $25 million in a DeFi project without a clear in charge.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto ATMs In Trouble
<p>The CANSEE Act is also extended its reach over crypto ATMs, claiming their higher propensity to be used in money laundering activities. As a result of the legislation, operators of crypto ATMs across the country will need to conduct identity checks for all participants involved in any single transaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Senator Reed stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Our bill will also ensure that law enforcement has access to better information about cryptocurrency transactions, which they need to fight crimes like cross-border drug trafficking, weapons proliferation, and ransomware attacks.&rdquo;</p>

Industry Criticizes DeFi Bill
<p>The bill has been highly condemned by crypto Twitter, with experts deeming it an "existential threat to DeFi.&rdquo; There have also been questions about the bill&rsquo;s imposition of control responsibilities, claiming it would discourage VCs from DeFi investments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Crypto Council for Innovation stated that the proposal lacks specific guidance on how decentralized protocols can comply with Bank Secrecy Act (BSA) reporting requirements. They advocate for an alternative approach that involves distinguishing elements within the DeFi technology stack and using blockchain transparency and programmability to establish compliance measures tailored to the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A bipartisan group of United States Senators has introduced the CANSEE Act to regulate DeFi platforms in order to curb money laundering and other financial transgressions.&nbsp;</p>
Senators Against DeFi
<p>U.S. Senators are taking a strong stance against money laundering and crypto-facilitated crime by introducing new legislation aimed at regulating decentralized finance (DeFi) services. The Crypto-Asset National Security Enhancement and Enforcement (CANSEE) Act requires DeFi platforms to comply with the same anti-money laundering (AML) and economic sanctions obligations as traditional financial companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The bipartisan team of senators behind the CANSEE Act includes Jack Reed (D-RI), Mike Rounds (R-SD), Mark Warner (D-VA), and Mitt Romney (R-UT).&nbsp;</p>
DeFi To Get More Centralized
<p>The CANSEE Act will introduce tighter regulations and laws to DeFi, on par with the governance experienced by centralized institutions like banks, securities brokers, casinos, and centralized crypto trading platforms. Consequently, DeFi services will have to establish AML programs, conduct due diligence on customers, and report suspicious transactions to the Treasury Department's Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN).</p>
<p>Senator Warner noted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I believe these focused measures will help maintain the robust AML and sanctions enforcement we need to protect our national security, while allowing participants who play by the rules to continue to take advantage of the potential of distributed ledger technologies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The legislation will also extend to all individuals and entities who facilitate the use of DeFi platforms by sanctioned individuals. The regulations under the act also will hold accountable any investor putting in more than $25 million in a DeFi project without a clear in charge.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto ATMs In Trouble
<p>The CANSEE Act is also extended its reach over crypto ATMs, claiming their higher propensity to be used in money laundering activities. As a result of the legislation, operators of crypto ATMs across the country will need to conduct identity checks for all participants involved in any single transaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Senator Reed stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Our bill will also ensure that law enforcement has access to better information about cryptocurrency transactions, which they need to fight crimes like cross-border drug trafficking, weapons proliferation, and ransomware attacks.&rdquo;</p>

Industry Criticizes DeFi Bill
<p>The bill has been highly condemned by crypto Twitter, with experts deeming it an "existential threat to DeFi.&rdquo; There have also been questions about the bill&rsquo;s imposition of control responsibilities, claiming it would discourage VCs from DeFi investments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Crypto Council for Innovation stated that the proposal lacks specific guidance on how decentralized protocols can comply with Bank Secrecy Act (BSA) reporting requirements. They advocate for an alternative approach that involves distinguishing elements within the DeFi technology stack and using blockchain transparency and programmability to establish compliance measures tailored to the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Introducing ChainGPT Pad, an AI-focused Launchpad Released by ChainGPT]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/introducing-chaingpt-pad-an-ai-focused-launchpad-released-by-chaingpt</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920x1080-4.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920x1080-4.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920x1080-4.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/introducing-chaingpt-pad-an-ai-focused-launchpad-released-by-chaingpt</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>ChainGPT Pad, the IDO platform that will be enabling the next generation of startups in the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry has just been released</p>
<p>ChainGPT, the provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the digital economy has just launched the ChainGPT Pad; a platform that connects promising early-stage startups with the $CGPT community and enables a new era of initial DEX offerings.</p>
<p>Now projects of all calibers will have an environment to supercharge their social presence, bootstrap their communities, and bring their products to market with greater impact.</p>
<p>What is the ChainGPT Pad?</p>
<p>The ChainGPT Pad is an IDO platform and incubator for Web3 projects looking to bring their ideas to life and jumpstart their token ecosystems. As a means to uphold the standards of ChainGPT, the Pad conducts rigorous quality assurance tests and due diligence processes to vet incoming projects and is highly selective with who they allow to list.</p>
<p>The launchpad is coupled with the ChainGPT incubation program that provides a network of expert mentors (founders, venture capitalists, and CEOs of other successful projects) that provide support to all projects that meet a certain qualification criteria.</p>
<p>What are some of the Platform Features?</p>
<p>The ChainGPT Pad has been geared up with all of the leading innovations that contribute to successful, healthy, and effective IDO launches. Striking the perfect balance between opportunity and security the ChainGPT Pad has been carefully designed by a team of professionals with experience working on some of the industry's leading launchpads.</p>
<p>Two Round Structure&nbsp;</p>
<p>Every IDO is given two rounds for the audience to participate; starting at the guaranteed allocations for round 1 (where the upper tiers of the $CGPT community members are given exclusive access). In order to participate in the guaranteed allocation, qualifying members must register their interests (info on registration here). Moving into round 2, the FCFC (first-come-first-serve) invites members of all tiers and partners.&nbsp;</p>
Staking &amp; Point System
<p>Tithed to the $CGPT token ecosystem, the Chain GPT Pad has a simple and effective structure for establishing tiers. One $CGPT token is equal to one Point, point multipliers are based on the staking pool durations. An in-depth guide to the Staking and Point logic systems can be found here.</p>
Fair Tier System
<p></p>
<p>A model of prioritization and inclusion based on a balanced point module that leverages staking the $CGPT token to signal commitment. Composed of four distinct grade categories, Bronze, Silver, Gold, and Diamond, the tier system provides a structure for the discerning user that looks for maximal benefits. To explore the benefits of each tier and understand the detailed scope of inclusion, please refer to the official post here.</p>
Flexible Refund Policy
<p></p>
<p>As a means to provide the highest possible grade of protection to the participants of ChainGPT Pad&rsquo;s IDOs, a refund policy has been implemented that allows users up to 14 days of post-round considerations to finalize their commitments and lock in their allocations. More information about the refund policy can be found here.</p>
<p>For questions pertaining to how projects can register, how users can join, restrictions of countries, requirements to signal interest, and everything in between ChainGPT has provided a dedicated F.A.Q. for the Pad which can be accessed here.</p>
Upcoming IDOs on ChainGPT Pad
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Immediately upon launch, ChainGPT orchestrated a world-class lineup of three startups that have been going through the incubation program and have prepared to launch their IDOs in the months of July-August. With three projects already establishing their technical aptitude and social presence, here is who will be launching through the ChainGPT pad: DexCheck, TradeTomato, and Solidus AI Tech.</p>
What is DexCheck:
<p>DexCheck is an analytics platform augmenting the user experience with an AI-powered toolkit. From whale tracking and leaderboard monitoring to mirror trading and even arbitrage scanning, DexCheck is the future of on-chain intelligence.</p>
What is Tradetomato:
<p>Tradetomato is using artificial intelligence to fuel its decentralized trading platform and portfolio management ecosystem. Catering to a wide audience through modular trading algorithms, a social marketplace, unique wallet aggregators, and other elements from its stack of advanced tooling, Tradetomato is an end-to-end solution for the automation of on-chain finance.</p>
What is Solidus AI Tech:
<p>Providing AI infrastructure solutions for enterprises through its suite of SaaS, BaaS, AIaaS, AI marketplace, and HPC (high-performance computing), Solidus AI Tech is taking the Web3 industry by storm with its own 8,000-square-foot facility.&nbsp;</p>
What is the ChainGPT Incubation Program?
<p>Providing support, guidance, and accelerating excellence, the ChainGPT Incubation program is an extensive, in-depth, multi-month-long program of intense, close collaboration between ChainGPT and promising projects that are looking to launch into Web3.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Revealed in May of 2023, the incubation program aims to attract teams of innovators who have identified unique pain points of the digital economy; and equip them with the knowledge, tools, and connections to realize their visions. You can find a dedicated blog post here that provides an overview of the rationale behind the Incubation programs and an introduction to the mentorship network.</p>
About ChainGPT
<p>ChainGPT is the leading provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry. From automated smart contract generation and auditing, to autonomous community management, advanced Web3 AI chatbot, AI-powered news aggregation, and NFT generation, ChainGPT is the most sophisticated, end-to-end AI solution on the market.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ChainGPT Pad, the IDO platform that will be enabling the next generation of startups in the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry has just been released</p>
<p>ChainGPT, the provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the digital economy has just launched the ChainGPT Pad; a platform that connects promising early-stage startups with the $CGPT community and enables a new era of initial DEX offerings.</p>
<p>Now projects of all calibers will have an environment to supercharge their social presence, bootstrap their communities, and bring their products to market with greater impact.</p>
<p>What is the ChainGPT Pad?</p>
<p>The ChainGPT Pad is an IDO platform and incubator for Web3 projects looking to bring their ideas to life and jumpstart their token ecosystems. As a means to uphold the standards of ChainGPT, the Pad conducts rigorous quality assurance tests and due diligence processes to vet incoming projects and is highly selective with who they allow to list.</p>
<p>The launchpad is coupled with the ChainGPT incubation program that provides a network of expert mentors (founders, venture capitalists, and CEOs of other successful projects) that provide support to all projects that meet a certain qualification criteria.</p>
<p>What are some of the Platform Features?</p>
<p>The ChainGPT Pad has been geared up with all of the leading innovations that contribute to successful, healthy, and effective IDO launches. Striking the perfect balance between opportunity and security the ChainGPT Pad has been carefully designed by a team of professionals with experience working on some of the industry's leading launchpads.</p>
<p>Two Round Structure&nbsp;</p>
<p>Every IDO is given two rounds for the audience to participate; starting at the guaranteed allocations for round 1 (where the upper tiers of the $CGPT community members are given exclusive access). In order to participate in the guaranteed allocation, qualifying members must register their interests (info on registration here). Moving into round 2, the FCFC (first-come-first-serve) invites members of all tiers and partners.&nbsp;</p>
Staking &amp; Point System
<p>Tithed to the $CGPT token ecosystem, the Chain GPT Pad has a simple and effective structure for establishing tiers. One $CGPT token is equal to one Point, point multipliers are based on the staking pool durations. An in-depth guide to the Staking and Point logic systems can be found here.</p>
Fair Tier System
<p></p>
<p>A model of prioritization and inclusion based on a balanced point module that leverages staking the $CGPT token to signal commitment. Composed of four distinct grade categories, Bronze, Silver, Gold, and Diamond, the tier system provides a structure for the discerning user that looks for maximal benefits. To explore the benefits of each tier and understand the detailed scope of inclusion, please refer to the official post here.</p>
Flexible Refund Policy
<p></p>
<p>As a means to provide the highest possible grade of protection to the participants of ChainGPT Pad&rsquo;s IDOs, a refund policy has been implemented that allows users up to 14 days of post-round considerations to finalize their commitments and lock in their allocations. More information about the refund policy can be found here.</p>
<p>For questions pertaining to how projects can register, how users can join, restrictions of countries, requirements to signal interest, and everything in between ChainGPT has provided a dedicated F.A.Q. for the Pad which can be accessed here.</p>
Upcoming IDOs on ChainGPT Pad
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Immediately upon launch, ChainGPT orchestrated a world-class lineup of three startups that have been going through the incubation program and have prepared to launch their IDOs in the months of July-August. With three projects already establishing their technical aptitude and social presence, here is who will be launching through the ChainGPT pad: DexCheck, TradeTomato, and Solidus AI Tech.</p>
What is DexCheck:
<p>DexCheck is an analytics platform augmenting the user experience with an AI-powered toolkit. From whale tracking and leaderboard monitoring to mirror trading and even arbitrage scanning, DexCheck is the future of on-chain intelligence.</p>
What is Tradetomato:
<p>Tradetomato is using artificial intelligence to fuel its decentralized trading platform and portfolio management ecosystem. Catering to a wide audience through modular trading algorithms, a social marketplace, unique wallet aggregators, and other elements from its stack of advanced tooling, Tradetomato is an end-to-end solution for the automation of on-chain finance.</p>
What is Solidus AI Tech:
<p>Providing AI infrastructure solutions for enterprises through its suite of SaaS, BaaS, AIaaS, AI marketplace, and HPC (high-performance computing), Solidus AI Tech is taking the Web3 industry by storm with its own 8,000-square-foot facility.&nbsp;</p>
What is the ChainGPT Incubation Program?
<p>Providing support, guidance, and accelerating excellence, the ChainGPT Incubation program is an extensive, in-depth, multi-month-long program of intense, close collaboration between ChainGPT and promising projects that are looking to launch into Web3.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Revealed in May of 2023, the incubation program aims to attract teams of innovators who have identified unique pain points of the digital economy; and equip them with the knowledge, tools, and connections to realize their visions. You can find a dedicated blog post here that provides an overview of the rationale behind the Incubation programs and an introduction to the mentorship network.</p>
About ChainGPT
<p>ChainGPT is the leading provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry. From automated smart contract generation and auditing, to autonomous community management, advanced Web3 AI chatbot, AI-powered news aggregation, and NFT generation, ChainGPT is the most sophisticated, end-to-end AI solution on the market.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LFi and cLFi Tokens Make Their Debut on LYOTRADE and LBank: A Leap Forward for Decentralized Networks]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lfi-and-clfi-tokens-make-their-debut-on-lyotrade-and-lbank-a-leap-forward-for-decentralized-networks</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lfpr-1920x1080.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lfpr-1920x1080.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lfpr-1920x1080.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lfi-and-clfi-tokens-make-their-debut-on-lyotrade-and-lbank-a-leap-forward-for-decentralized-networks</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[LFi ecosystem tokens LFi and cLFi are listed with trading pair with USDT on LYOTRADE and LBank.
<p>LFi's Innovative Approach to Decentralized Networks</p>
<p>Exciting times are ahead for the LFi network, a pioneering decentralized network that is reshaping wealth creation with its trailblazing technology and DAO-driven initiatives. LFi's projects have quickly gained popularity, particularly its groundbreaking LFi One smartphone, a unique web3 android device.</p>
<p>The LFi One: More Than Just a Crypto Mobile</p>
<p>The project is getting popularity thanks to its product, the LFi One smartphone.</p>
<p>The LFi One is no ordinary smartphone. It's a smartphone for token minting crypto. Designed meticulously, it supports an application that enables you to mint crypto directly from your device. Users can leverage its unique minting app to earn rewards, essentially turning their phone into a decentralized wireless network blockchain. This feature sets the LFi One apart from its competitors - while traditional minting hardware is often bulky and requires dedicated space, the LFi One fits the power of a crypto smart phone right in your pocket.</p>
<p>Spotlight on LFi and cLFi Tokens: Revolutionizing the Decentralized Network</p>
<p>At the heart of the LFi decentralized network are two key tokens - LFi and cLFi.</p>
<p>LFi Token: This native token of the LFi ecosystem offers access to the network's resources. Users can use LFi tokens to pay for network services such as sending cryptocurrency, minting tokens, calling a smart contract, and even minting an NFT on the LFi phone.</p>
<p>cLFi Token: The cLFi is the collateral token of the LFi ecosystem. The primary purpose of this utility token is to allow users to activate the Unit license, thereby participating in the Proof of Coverage minting.</p>
<p>LFi and cLFi Tokens Now on LYOTRADE and LBank</p>
<p>LFi and cLFi tokens have now arrived on LYOTRADE and LBank, two leading cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>LYOTRADE: Founded in 2021, LYOTRADE is a centralized cryptocurrency exchange that prioritizes secure and efficient crypto trading. It offers a host of features, including staking services, crypto loans, and different types of trading. Users can buy and sell cryptocurrencies through credit cards or bank transfers.</p>
<p>https://lyotrade.com/</p>
<p>LBank: Established in 2015, LBank Exchange is a licensed cryptocurrency trading platform known for its secure and professional services. LBank supports 50+ fiat currencies and various payment methods, making digital asset trading accessible to a global audience.</p>
<p>https://www.lbank.com/</p>
<p>By listing on these platforms, LFi expands its reach, bringing the power of its tokens and the innovations of its ecosystem to a wider audience. This move marks a significant step in the growth of LFi, proving that the future of wealth creation is here, and it fits right in your pocket!</p>
<p>Website: https://lfi.io/</p>
<p>White paper: https://white-paper.lfi.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>LFi Telegram: https://t.me/lfiofficial&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[LFi ecosystem tokens LFi and cLFi are listed with trading pair with USDT on LYOTRADE and LBank.
<p>LFi's Innovative Approach to Decentralized Networks</p>
<p>Exciting times are ahead for the LFi network, a pioneering decentralized network that is reshaping wealth creation with its trailblazing technology and DAO-driven initiatives. LFi's projects have quickly gained popularity, particularly its groundbreaking LFi One smartphone, a unique web3 android device.</p>
<p>The LFi One: More Than Just a Crypto Mobile</p>
<p>The project is getting popularity thanks to its product, the LFi One smartphone.</p>
<p>The LFi One is no ordinary smartphone. It's a smartphone for token minting crypto. Designed meticulously, it supports an application that enables you to mint crypto directly from your device. Users can leverage its unique minting app to earn rewards, essentially turning their phone into a decentralized wireless network blockchain. This feature sets the LFi One apart from its competitors - while traditional minting hardware is often bulky and requires dedicated space, the LFi One fits the power of a crypto smart phone right in your pocket.</p>
<p>Spotlight on LFi and cLFi Tokens: Revolutionizing the Decentralized Network</p>
<p>At the heart of the LFi decentralized network are two key tokens - LFi and cLFi.</p>
<p>LFi Token: This native token of the LFi ecosystem offers access to the network's resources. Users can use LFi tokens to pay for network services such as sending cryptocurrency, minting tokens, calling a smart contract, and even minting an NFT on the LFi phone.</p>
<p>cLFi Token: The cLFi is the collateral token of the LFi ecosystem. The primary purpose of this utility token is to allow users to activate the Unit license, thereby participating in the Proof of Coverage minting.</p>
<p>LFi and cLFi Tokens Now on LYOTRADE and LBank</p>
<p>LFi and cLFi tokens have now arrived on LYOTRADE and LBank, two leading cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
<p>LYOTRADE: Founded in 2021, LYOTRADE is a centralized cryptocurrency exchange that prioritizes secure and efficient crypto trading. It offers a host of features, including staking services, crypto loans, and different types of trading. Users can buy and sell cryptocurrencies through credit cards or bank transfers.</p>
<p>https://lyotrade.com/</p>
<p>LBank: Established in 2015, LBank Exchange is a licensed cryptocurrency trading platform known for its secure and professional services. LBank supports 50+ fiat currencies and various payment methods, making digital asset trading accessible to a global audience.</p>
<p>https://www.lbank.com/</p>
<p>By listing on these platforms, LFi expands its reach, bringing the power of its tokens and the innovations of its ecosystem to a wider audience. This move marks a significant step in the growth of LFi, proving that the future of wealth creation is here, and it fits right in your pocket!</p>
<p>Website: https://lfi.io/</p>
<p>White paper: https://white-paper.lfi.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>LFi Telegram: https://t.me/lfiofficial&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tesla BTC Holdings Unchanged In 2023 Q2]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/tesla-btc-holdings-unchanged-in-2023-q2</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tesla-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tesla-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tesla-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/tesla-btc-holdings-unchanged-in-2023-q2</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk&rsquo;s company has continued to hodl its BTC reserves for the fourth consecutive quarter after it was forced to divest 75% of its reserves back in 2022 Q2.&nbsp;</p>
Tesla Holding On To Its BTC
<p>The electric car company, Tesla, helmed by billionaire inventor Elon Musk recently announced that it had held on to its BTC reserves for the second quarter of 2023. Tesla (TSLA) remained inactive in the Bitcoin market, refraining from any purchases or sales of the cryptocurrency for the fourth consecutive quarter. The company's earnings release, issued after the market's closing on Wednesday, confirmed this trend.</p>
Tesla&rsquo;s Digital Assets
<p>The value of Tesla's digital assets at the end of the quarter held steady at $184 million, the same figure reported for the past three quarters. During Q2, the price of Bitcoin experienced a slight increase, rising from approximately $28,500 at the end of Q1 to around $30,400.</p>
<p>However, accounting regulations restricted Tesla from adjusting the valuation of its digital assets upwards in response to rising BTC prices unless the assets were sold. Nonetheless, the valuation could be reduced in the event of price declines, even before any sales occurred.</p>
Tesla&rsquo;s BTC Investment
<p>Tesla initially acquired $1.5 billion worth of BTC in early 2021, which significantly boosted the crypto&rsquo;s demand and price tag. CEO Elon Musk had also simultaneously made the announcement back then that the company would accept BTC payments for the Tesla cars, spurring even further interest in the crypto, which soon hit its all-time highest. However, Musk soon rescinded this proposal, declaring that BTC needed to be more environmentally friendly for this to happen.&nbsp;</p>
Selling Off 75% BTC
<p>Tesla, however, had to divest a significant portion of its BTC reserves in the second quarter of 2022 over liquidity concerns. The Tesla Gigafactory in Shanghai had been shut down for over 2 months due to the Covid-19 pandemic, resulting in a serious liquidity crisis for the company. It had to sell off over 30,000 BTCs, which amounted to about 75% of its holdings at the point, raking in a whopping $936 million, leaving around 9720 BTCs in its reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In its latest report, the company revealed that since then, it had not engaged in any BTC transactions, neither selling nor buying. Even during the significant market upheaval of January 2023, the company continued to hodl its BTC, despite amassing a loss of $140 million on its net Bitcoin holdings in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
Tesla&rsquo;s Reported Earnings
<p>Regarding its financial performance, Tesla reported adjusted earnings per share of $0.91 for the second quarter. This result surpassed the consensus analyst estimate of $0.80, as reported by FactSet. Moreover, the company's revenue for the quarter amounted to $24.9 billion, exceeding analyst estimates of $24.2 billion.</p>
<p>Throughout Q2 2023, Tesla's bitcoin holdings remained constant, showcasing the company's decision to remain on the sidelines of the volatile cryptocurrency market. Despite this, Tesla's financial performance and stock price continue to exhibit strength and resilience. As the electric car industry continues to evolve, investors and analysts keep a close eye on Tesla's movements in both the traditional markets and the ever-changing world of digital assets.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk&rsquo;s company has continued to hodl its BTC reserves for the fourth consecutive quarter after it was forced to divest 75% of its reserves back in 2022 Q2.&nbsp;</p>
Tesla Holding On To Its BTC
<p>The electric car company, Tesla, helmed by billionaire inventor Elon Musk recently announced that it had held on to its BTC reserves for the second quarter of 2023. Tesla (TSLA) remained inactive in the Bitcoin market, refraining from any purchases or sales of the cryptocurrency for the fourth consecutive quarter. The company's earnings release, issued after the market's closing on Wednesday, confirmed this trend.</p>
Tesla&rsquo;s Digital Assets
<p>The value of Tesla's digital assets at the end of the quarter held steady at $184 million, the same figure reported for the past three quarters. During Q2, the price of Bitcoin experienced a slight increase, rising from approximately $28,500 at the end of Q1 to around $30,400.</p>
<p>However, accounting regulations restricted Tesla from adjusting the valuation of its digital assets upwards in response to rising BTC prices unless the assets were sold. Nonetheless, the valuation could be reduced in the event of price declines, even before any sales occurred.</p>
Tesla&rsquo;s BTC Investment
<p>Tesla initially acquired $1.5 billion worth of BTC in early 2021, which significantly boosted the crypto&rsquo;s demand and price tag. CEO Elon Musk had also simultaneously made the announcement back then that the company would accept BTC payments for the Tesla cars, spurring even further interest in the crypto, which soon hit its all-time highest. However, Musk soon rescinded this proposal, declaring that BTC needed to be more environmentally friendly for this to happen.&nbsp;</p>
Selling Off 75% BTC
<p>Tesla, however, had to divest a significant portion of its BTC reserves in the second quarter of 2022 over liquidity concerns. The Tesla Gigafactory in Shanghai had been shut down for over 2 months due to the Covid-19 pandemic, resulting in a serious liquidity crisis for the company. It had to sell off over 30,000 BTCs, which amounted to about 75% of its holdings at the point, raking in a whopping $936 million, leaving around 9720 BTCs in its reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In its latest report, the company revealed that since then, it had not engaged in any BTC transactions, neither selling nor buying. Even during the significant market upheaval of January 2023, the company continued to hodl its BTC, despite amassing a loss of $140 million on its net Bitcoin holdings in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
Tesla&rsquo;s Reported Earnings
<p>Regarding its financial performance, Tesla reported adjusted earnings per share of $0.91 for the second quarter. This result surpassed the consensus analyst estimate of $0.80, as reported by FactSet. Moreover, the company's revenue for the quarter amounted to $24.9 billion, exceeding analyst estimates of $24.2 billion.</p>
<p>Throughout Q2 2023, Tesla's bitcoin holdings remained constant, showcasing the company's decision to remain on the sidelines of the volatile cryptocurrency market. Despite this, Tesla's financial performance and stock price continue to exhibit strength and resilience. As the electric car industry continues to evolve, investors and analysts keep a close eye on Tesla's movements in both the traditional markets and the ever-changing world of digital assets.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Kuwait applies blanket ban to crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/kuwait-applies-blanket-ban-to-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kuw.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kuw.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kuw.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:07:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/kuwait-applies-blanket-ban-to-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Citing a recommendation by the Financial Assets Task Force (FATF), the Kuwaiti authorities have promulgated bans across a range of crypto activities.</p>
<p>According to the Kuwaiti Capital Markets Authority, in a circular published on Monday, it has banned all crypto-related activities by companies, it has placed an absolute ban on all digital asset mining, and, into the bargain, has prohibited that crypto be recognised as a decentralised currency.</p>
<p>The only exception to this are securities regulated by the central bank, or the Capital Markets Authority.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Securities regulated by the Central Bank of Kuwait and other securities and financial instruments regulated by the Capital Markets Authority are excluded from this prohibition,"</p>

<p>The Kuwaiti anti-crypto actions were purportedly taken in order to come into line with recommendations from the Financial Action Task Force (FATF), a global financial organisation that is obliging nation states to come into compliance for what it sees as anti money-laundering (AML) and terrorist financing threats.</p>
<p>However, according to an article on Coindesk, the FATF has not asked countries to ban crypto. Be that as it may, this regulator holds much power, and not complying with its &lsquo;recommendations&rsquo; can land a country onto the FATF blacklist.</p>
Opinion
<p>Some might argue that the FATF&rsquo;s recommendations do more harm than good from an economic perspective. There are cases where banks pull out of lending to countries in poorer regions of the world because they fear the fines they can incur from the added difficulty of being able to adequately identify customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Also, the cost of running the organisation should be measured against the costs of the illegal activity it is purportedly stopping. AML has now entered into almost every financial activity that a government can make, and the costs of compliance that all companies have to endure just to be able to go about their business can be a reason for concern.</p>
<p>In Springer Link, under &ldquo;Crime, Law and Social Change&rdquo; author Mark. T. Nance goes into a deep dive on the FATF. In the introduction he asks the question as to how there can be an increase in illicit money at the same time as the &ldquo;global governance regime&rdquo; is getting bigger to fight it.</p>
<p>He looks at the expert detractors of the FATF, and what they say makes interesting reading:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Detractors portray FATF as a faceless, unaccountable, de facto global regulatory agency run amok. On behalf of the interests of a few select states, it imposes regulations that are illegitimate and costly. For these critics, the Panama Papers are evidence that the rules are ineffective, to boot.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Banning an emerging technology in order to become compliant with an agency controlled by certain countries, with their own interests in mind is certainly a difficult call for Kuwait to make. Emerging technology has never been suppressed for long, therefore Kuwait may eventually see fit to reverse its decision.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Citing a recommendation by the Financial Assets Task Force (FATF), the Kuwaiti authorities have promulgated bans across a range of crypto activities.</p>
<p>According to the Kuwaiti Capital Markets Authority, in a circular published on Monday, it has banned all crypto-related activities by companies, it has placed an absolute ban on all digital asset mining, and, into the bargain, has prohibited that crypto be recognised as a decentralised currency.</p>
<p>The only exception to this are securities regulated by the central bank, or the Capital Markets Authority.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Securities regulated by the Central Bank of Kuwait and other securities and financial instruments regulated by the Capital Markets Authority are excluded from this prohibition,"</p>

<p>The Kuwaiti anti-crypto actions were purportedly taken in order to come into line with recommendations from the Financial Action Task Force (FATF), a global financial organisation that is obliging nation states to come into compliance for what it sees as anti money-laundering (AML) and terrorist financing threats.</p>
<p>However, according to an article on Coindesk, the FATF has not asked countries to ban crypto. Be that as it may, this regulator holds much power, and not complying with its &lsquo;recommendations&rsquo; can land a country onto the FATF blacklist.</p>
Opinion
<p>Some might argue that the FATF&rsquo;s recommendations do more harm than good from an economic perspective. There are cases where banks pull out of lending to countries in poorer regions of the world because they fear the fines they can incur from the added difficulty of being able to adequately identify customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Also, the cost of running the organisation should be measured against the costs of the illegal activity it is purportedly stopping. AML has now entered into almost every financial activity that a government can make, and the costs of compliance that all companies have to endure just to be able to go about their business can be a reason for concern.</p>
<p>In Springer Link, under &ldquo;Crime, Law and Social Change&rdquo; author Mark. T. Nance goes into a deep dive on the FATF. In the introduction he asks the question as to how there can be an increase in illicit money at the same time as the &ldquo;global governance regime&rdquo; is getting bigger to fight it.</p>
<p>He looks at the expert detractors of the FATF, and what they say makes interesting reading:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Detractors portray FATF as a faceless, unaccountable, de facto global regulatory agency run amok. On behalf of the interests of a few select states, it imposes regulations that are illegitimate and costly. For these critics, the Panama Papers are evidence that the rules are ineffective, to boot.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Banning an emerging technology in order to become compliant with an agency controlled by certain countries, with their own interests in mind is certainly a difficult call for Kuwait to make. Emerging technology has never been suppressed for long, therefore Kuwait may eventually see fit to reverse its decision.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto beats the doldrums and trends higher]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-beats-the-doldrums-and-trends-higher</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-56.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-56.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-56.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:01:11 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-beats-the-doldrums-and-trends-higher</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>After hitting the range bottom bitcoin looks to be heading higher once more. Altcoins are following suit.</p>
Bitcoin bounce?
<p>It is only a week since bitcoin made a new local high for this year and some of the altcoins made some excellent gains from the bottom. A week is a ridiculously short amount of time but it has to be remembered -&nbsp; this is crypto, and large moves up or down can often take place in days, hours, or even minutes.</p>
<p>Bitcoin did test the nerves at one point though. A wick on the daily time frame took the alpha cryptocurrency down to $29,600 at one point, but this touched a slightly upwards trendline which began on June 22, becoming the third touch of this particular support.</p>
<p>Now back over $30,000, the bulls are looking to drive bitcoin back to test the $31,000 to $32,000 major resistance once more. In order for the bull market to really be confirmed, this is the equivalent of the Pyrenees mountain range that must be crossed.</p>
Altcoins bounce better
<p>With bitcoin taking the initiative again the altcoins have also woken up and some are outdoing bitcoin quite handsomely on the day so far. The Total 3 market cap (total value of all cryptocurrencies after excluding bitcoin and ethereum) has risen $8 billion since Wednesday and is about to test the top of the down channel it has been in since mid-June of 2022.</p>
<p>A breakout of the channel potentially allows the altcoin market cap to rise to the next resistance at $407 billion, another $47 billion from here. Bitcoin Dominance is a very important factor. This experienced a sharp drop a week ago and has been forming a potential bear flag since then.&nbsp;</p>
The dollar continues to show weakness
<p>USDT Dominance is one more element to the puzzle. USDT fell through the upwards trendline it has been adhering to all the way back to November 2021. It did come back to test the line and make it resistance so it should start to decline from here. Currently at 7.10%, the next support for USDT Dominance is at 6.44%.</p>
<p>Finally, looking across at traditional markets, the Dollar Index (DXY) has been falling since September last year, as the US stock market heads in the opposite direction. If the DXY confirms 100.2 as resistance, a further decline to 94.5 would be where it will next find support.</p>
<p>It might seem as though the stars are aligning for bitcoin and the cryptocurrency sector. If the major resistance at $32,000 can finally be broken and bitcoin can hold above, blue skies until $36,000 are beckoning.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After hitting the range bottom bitcoin looks to be heading higher once more. Altcoins are following suit.</p>
Bitcoin bounce?
<p>It is only a week since bitcoin made a new local high for this year and some of the altcoins made some excellent gains from the bottom. A week is a ridiculously short amount of time but it has to be remembered -&nbsp; this is crypto, and large moves up or down can often take place in days, hours, or even minutes.</p>
<p>Bitcoin did test the nerves at one point though. A wick on the daily time frame took the alpha cryptocurrency down to $29,600 at one point, but this touched a slightly upwards trendline which began on June 22, becoming the third touch of this particular support.</p>
<p>Now back over $30,000, the bulls are looking to drive bitcoin back to test the $31,000 to $32,000 major resistance once more. In order for the bull market to really be confirmed, this is the equivalent of the Pyrenees mountain range that must be crossed.</p>
Altcoins bounce better
<p>With bitcoin taking the initiative again the altcoins have also woken up and some are outdoing bitcoin quite handsomely on the day so far. The Total 3 market cap (total value of all cryptocurrencies after excluding bitcoin and ethereum) has risen $8 billion since Wednesday and is about to test the top of the down channel it has been in since mid-June of 2022.</p>
<p>A breakout of the channel potentially allows the altcoin market cap to rise to the next resistance at $407 billion, another $47 billion from here. Bitcoin Dominance is a very important factor. This experienced a sharp drop a week ago and has been forming a potential bear flag since then.&nbsp;</p>
The dollar continues to show weakness
<p>USDT Dominance is one more element to the puzzle. USDT fell through the upwards trendline it has been adhering to all the way back to November 2021. It did come back to test the line and make it resistance so it should start to decline from here. Currently at 7.10%, the next support for USDT Dominance is at 6.44%.</p>
<p>Finally, looking across at traditional markets, the Dollar Index (DXY) has been falling since September last year, as the US stock market heads in the opposite direction. If the DXY confirms 100.2 as resistance, a further decline to 94.5 would be where it will next find support.</p>
<p>It might seem as though the stars are aligning for bitcoin and the cryptocurrency sector. If the major resistance at $32,000 can finally be broken and bitcoin can hold above, blue skies until $36,000 are beckoning.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Chinese Authorities Bust $55M USDT Money Laundering Scheme]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/chinese-authorities-bust-55m-usdt-money-laundering-scheme</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/china-arrest-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/china-arrest-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/china-arrest-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/chinese-authorities-bust-55m-usdt-money-laundering-scheme</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Enforcement authorities in China&rsquo;s northern province of Shanxi have uncovered an alleged USDT money laundering scheme amounting to over $55 million.</p>
<p>According to local news reports, the police have arrested 21 individuals in connection with the money laundering ring.</p>
A Major Bust
<p>The laundering operation came to light when authorities in Qinshui County observed that a bank account operated under the name of Mouyue Zhao had a highly erratic flow of funds. This abnormal flow of funds sparked suspicions of money laundering, leading to the police launching a thorough investigation. The investigation revealed staggering details about how an organized group of criminals had been orchestrating an over-the-counter (OTC) trading ring involving USDT since October 2021, according to a report by China&rsquo;s national broadcasting service.</p>
<p>USDT is the world&rsquo;s largest stablecoin and has its value pegged to the US Dollar. It is operated by Tether Limited Inc.</p>
Modus Operandi&nbsp;&nbsp;
<p>Investigators revealed that the accused individuals operated across four provinces, purchasing USDT at a low price and then selling it at higher prices through WeChat groups and money laundering platforms and making significant illegal profits. Authorities stated that the laundering operation had completed transactions totaling nearly $55 million over the nearly three-year period of their operations.</p>
<p>Authorities were able to track down members of the operation across six cities in the provinces of Jiangxi, Henan, Guangxi, and Anhui. Over 50 officers were dispatched to arrest the perpetrators. Along with the arrests, the police also seized over 40 mobile phones, along with 200,000 yuan ($28,000) in cash and over 1 million yuan worth of USDT ($140,000).</p>
Suspects Confess
<p>The suspects were interrogated by the authorities and, according to local news agencies, have confessed to the accusations made against them. The accusations include facilitating the conversion of the Chinese Yuan to USDT and helping criminals launder their money. However, the case is still open and remains under investigation. According to the authorities, USDT has quickly become a preferred choice for crypto money launderers thanks to the ease and anonymity that it offers.</p>
China&rsquo;s Stance On Crypto
<p>China has historically taken a tough stance against crypto. However, the country&rsquo;s stance comes as no surprise to long-time observers of the crypto space. Chinese citizens first caught wind of cryptocurrencies in 2011 thanks to the centralized exchange Bitcoin China, set up by Bobby C. Lee. Bobby C. Lee is the brother of Litecoin&rsquo;s Charlie Lee. During the early days of Bitcoin, Bitcoin China was responsible for a significant chunk of the global Bitcoin trading activity.</p>
<p>Bitcoin soon became widely accepted in China, with businesses beginning to accept it as payment. However, 2013 saw China&rsquo;s first attempt at stifling the crypto space in the country, even though Bitcoin adoption was skyrocketing, with the People&rsquo;s Bank of China prohibiting banks from holding or transacting in digital currencies. However, Chinese citizens could still buy, send, and store crypto. During the 2017 bull run, Chinese authorities put further sanctions on the crypto space, outlawing all platforms offering ICOs (Initial Coin Offerings). Additionally, authorities also forced several exchanges to shut down operations.</p>
<p>In 2021, Chinese officials banned crypto mining, effectively crippling the industry in China. The impact on the markets was severe, with Bitcoin&rsquo;s hash rate falling to 50% and its price registering a dramatic drop. Along with the ban on mining, authorities also outlawed all crypto trading and transactions. Additionally, anyone working with Chinese firms associated with the crypto space could potentially face jail time. However, despite all these hurdles, Chinese citizens can still access cryptocurrencies through proxy internet servers and decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enforcement authorities in China&rsquo;s northern province of Shanxi have uncovered an alleged USDT money laundering scheme amounting to over $55 million.</p>
<p>According to local news reports, the police have arrested 21 individuals in connection with the money laundering ring.</p>
A Major Bust
<p>The laundering operation came to light when authorities in Qinshui County observed that a bank account operated under the name of Mouyue Zhao had a highly erratic flow of funds. This abnormal flow of funds sparked suspicions of money laundering, leading to the police launching a thorough investigation. The investigation revealed staggering details about how an organized group of criminals had been orchestrating an over-the-counter (OTC) trading ring involving USDT since October 2021, according to a report by China&rsquo;s national broadcasting service.</p>
<p>USDT is the world&rsquo;s largest stablecoin and has its value pegged to the US Dollar. It is operated by Tether Limited Inc.</p>
Modus Operandi&nbsp;&nbsp;
<p>Investigators revealed that the accused individuals operated across four provinces, purchasing USDT at a low price and then selling it at higher prices through WeChat groups and money laundering platforms and making significant illegal profits. Authorities stated that the laundering operation had completed transactions totaling nearly $55 million over the nearly three-year period of their operations.</p>
<p>Authorities were able to track down members of the operation across six cities in the provinces of Jiangxi, Henan, Guangxi, and Anhui. Over 50 officers were dispatched to arrest the perpetrators. Along with the arrests, the police also seized over 40 mobile phones, along with 200,000 yuan ($28,000) in cash and over 1 million yuan worth of USDT ($140,000).</p>
Suspects Confess
<p>The suspects were interrogated by the authorities and, according to local news agencies, have confessed to the accusations made against them. The accusations include facilitating the conversion of the Chinese Yuan to USDT and helping criminals launder their money. However, the case is still open and remains under investigation. According to the authorities, USDT has quickly become a preferred choice for crypto money launderers thanks to the ease and anonymity that it offers.</p>
China&rsquo;s Stance On Crypto
<p>China has historically taken a tough stance against crypto. However, the country&rsquo;s stance comes as no surprise to long-time observers of the crypto space. Chinese citizens first caught wind of cryptocurrencies in 2011 thanks to the centralized exchange Bitcoin China, set up by Bobby C. Lee. Bobby C. Lee is the brother of Litecoin&rsquo;s Charlie Lee. During the early days of Bitcoin, Bitcoin China was responsible for a significant chunk of the global Bitcoin trading activity.</p>
<p>Bitcoin soon became widely accepted in China, with businesses beginning to accept it as payment. However, 2013 saw China&rsquo;s first attempt at stifling the crypto space in the country, even though Bitcoin adoption was skyrocketing, with the People&rsquo;s Bank of China prohibiting banks from holding or transacting in digital currencies. However, Chinese citizens could still buy, send, and store crypto. During the 2017 bull run, Chinese authorities put further sanctions on the crypto space, outlawing all platforms offering ICOs (Initial Coin Offerings). Additionally, authorities also forced several exchanges to shut down operations.</p>
<p>In 2021, Chinese officials banned crypto mining, effectively crippling the industry in China. The impact on the markets was severe, with Bitcoin&rsquo;s hash rate falling to 50% and its price registering a dramatic drop. Along with the ban on mining, authorities also outlawed all crypto trading and transactions. Additionally, anyone working with Chinese firms associated with the crypto space could potentially face jail time. However, despite all these hurdles, Chinese citizens can still access cryptocurrencies through proxy internet servers and decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Conflux And World Mobile Join Forces To Expand Blockchain-based Mobile Access]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/conflux-and-world-mobile-join-forces-to-expand-blockchain-based-mobile-access</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-07-18_124554_16896987885OpXCUZNDK.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-07-18_124554_16896987885OpXCUZNDK.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-07-18_124554_16896987885OpXCUZNDK.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:00:28 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/conflux-and-world-mobile-join-forces-to-expand-blockchain-based-mobile-access</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Toronto, Canada, July 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Conflux Network, the first regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, has today announced a new collaboration with World Mobile, the only global mobile network built on the blockchain.&nbsp;</p><p>The partnership comes on the heels of the successful launch of the Conflux BSIM card earlier this year and will see the two companies work together initially in four areas:</p><p>1) Public Bridging&nbsp;</p><p>World Mobile Token (WMT) will bridge from Cardano blockchain into the Conflux blockchain ecosystem and will be the first bridge outside the Cardano ecosystem for the mobile network&rsquo;s native token.&nbsp;</p><p>2) Tech Integration&nbsp;</p><p>World Mobile and Conflux will collaborate on the technical integration of the Conflux network into World Mobile's sidechain, AyA,&nbsp;bringing EarthNode capabilities and financial settlement to the Conflux network.</p><p>3) Asian and African Market Expansion&nbsp;</p><p>Conflux and World Mobile enjoy a strong presence in the Asian and African markets, respectively. The two businesses will work together to leverage these strengths to increase connectivity, drive user acquisition and further market penetration in key markets. Conflux&rsquo;s CFX now ranks top 3 in most popular crypto currencies in Nigeria.&nbsp;This is especially relevant as Nigeria holds nearly 67% of crypto interest in Africa. World Mobile has recently concluded successful field tests of its hybrid dynamic network in Nigeria, following a successful commercial launch in Zanzibar earlier this year.&nbsp;</p><p>4) Blockchain-based SIM card development</p><p>World Mobile and Conflux will collaborate on how the mobile network can best utilize Conflux&rsquo;s blockchain-based SIM card to increase access to digital connectivity across the world.</p>YuanJie Zhang, Co-Founder of Conflux, said of the partnership: &ldquo;Conflux Network takes its mission to push the frontier of Web3 adoption at a low cost, with fast speed and decentralized security very seriously. One important strategy is to promote collaboration with telecommunication service providers all over the world. World Mobile is the next significant partner Conflux brings on board after China Telecom. Together, affordable and applicable blockchain technology is bridged beyond Asia to the rest of the world.&rdquo;Zachary Vann, Head of Token, World Mobile Token added: &ldquo;We are excited to work with Conflux to build a more connected and inclusive future. This partnership will accelerate our market expansion in Asia and to provide connectivity globally. The Conflux network has a unique, regulatory-compliant blockchain, and the world's first blockchain-based sim cards bring many opportunities to our mobile network and our AyA chain. This is our most significant partnership to expand our network and sharing economy into the Asian markets and beyond.&rdquo;<p>About Conflux</p><p>Conflux Network is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols. Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p><p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities in the region on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Learn more: https://confluxnetwork.org/</p><p>About World Mobile</p><p>World Mobile was founded with a far-reaching goal: to connect everyone, everywhere while advocating for economic freedom and dignity. Unlike traditional mobile networks, World Mobile is based on blockchain and incentivizes people to be part of a sharing economy that taps into the trillion dollar global telecom market. Individuals and business owners around the world can operate nodes on its network and bring their community online while earning revenue.</p><p>Learn more: https://worldmobile.io/</p>ContactMelissa TireyShift6 Studiosmelissa@shift6studios.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toronto, Canada, July 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Conflux Network, the first regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, has today announced a new collaboration with World Mobile, the only global mobile network built on the blockchain.&nbsp;</p><p>The partnership comes on the heels of the successful launch of the Conflux BSIM card earlier this year and will see the two companies work together initially in four areas:</p><p>1) Public Bridging&nbsp;</p><p>World Mobile Token (WMT) will bridge from Cardano blockchain into the Conflux blockchain ecosystem and will be the first bridge outside the Cardano ecosystem for the mobile network&rsquo;s native token.&nbsp;</p><p>2) Tech Integration&nbsp;</p><p>World Mobile and Conflux will collaborate on the technical integration of the Conflux network into World Mobile's sidechain, AyA,&nbsp;bringing EarthNode capabilities and financial settlement to the Conflux network.</p><p>3) Asian and African Market Expansion&nbsp;</p><p>Conflux and World Mobile enjoy a strong presence in the Asian and African markets, respectively. The two businesses will work together to leverage these strengths to increase connectivity, drive user acquisition and further market penetration in key markets. Conflux&rsquo;s CFX now ranks top 3 in most popular crypto currencies in Nigeria.&nbsp;This is especially relevant as Nigeria holds nearly 67% of crypto interest in Africa. World Mobile has recently concluded successful field tests of its hybrid dynamic network in Nigeria, following a successful commercial launch in Zanzibar earlier this year.&nbsp;</p><p>4) Blockchain-based SIM card development</p><p>World Mobile and Conflux will collaborate on how the mobile network can best utilize Conflux&rsquo;s blockchain-based SIM card to increase access to digital connectivity across the world.</p>YuanJie Zhang, Co-Founder of Conflux, said of the partnership: &ldquo;Conflux Network takes its mission to push the frontier of Web3 adoption at a low cost, with fast speed and decentralized security very seriously. One important strategy is to promote collaboration with telecommunication service providers all over the world. World Mobile is the next significant partner Conflux brings on board after China Telecom. Together, affordable and applicable blockchain technology is bridged beyond Asia to the rest of the world.&rdquo;Zachary Vann, Head of Token, World Mobile Token added: &ldquo;We are excited to work with Conflux to build a more connected and inclusive future. This partnership will accelerate our market expansion in Asia and to provide connectivity globally. The Conflux network has a unique, regulatory-compliant blockchain, and the world's first blockchain-based sim cards bring many opportunities to our mobile network and our AyA chain. This is our most significant partnership to expand our network and sharing economy into the Asian markets and beyond.&rdquo;<p>About Conflux</p><p>Conflux Network is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols. Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p><p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities in the region on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Learn more: https://confluxnetwork.org/</p><p>About World Mobile</p><p>World Mobile was founded with a far-reaching goal: to connect everyone, everywhere while advocating for economic freedom and dignity. Unlike traditional mobile networks, World Mobile is based on blockchain and incentivizes people to be part of a sharing economy that taps into the trillion dollar global telecom market. Individuals and business owners around the world can operate nodes on its network and bring their community online while earning revenue.</p><p>Learn more: https://worldmobile.io/</p>ContactMelissa TireyShift6 Studiosmelissa@shift6studios.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Solana Rolls Out Solang Compiler, Enhances Ethereum Compatibility]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/solana-rolls-out-solang-compiler-enhances-ethereum-compatibility</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 08:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/solana-rolls-out-solang-compiler-enhances-ethereum-compatibility</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Solana Labs, the entity behind Solana, has announced the rollout of the Solang compiler. The new compiler will help Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) developers transition to the Solana ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move aligns with Solana&rsquo;s efforts to become more accessible with Solidity, the programming language used with Ethereum smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>
A New Compiler&nbsp;
<p>The launch of Solang will help developers who have worked with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) to transition into the Solana ecosystem smoothly. Solang gives developers who are familiar with Solidity, Ethereum&rsquo;s primary smart contract programming language, all the tools required to write and create apps on the Solana network. The unveiling of the new compiler comes only a day after Neon EVM released a similar tool. In a statement published on its website, Solana Labs stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Solana development is well known for using Rust or C for writing smart contracts, but Solana is evolving to become more accessible with Solidity, the primary programming language used for Ethereum smart contracts. Solana Labs is thrilled to announce that today you can now build on Solana with Solidity using Solang, a new compiler that helps bridge the gap between EVM developers and the Solana ecosystem.&rdquo;</p>

A List Of Features
<p>According to the statement, the addition of more programming languages for building on Solana will see an influx of developers with broader skill sets into the Solana ecosystem. This was witnessed with the launch of Seahorse, a community-led initiative. Seahorse enables developers to write Solana smart contracts in Python, which is arguably the world&rsquo;s most popular programming language. The Solang launch is the continuation of efforts to broaden the reach and appeal of the Solana ecosystem among developers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Solang compiler introduces an array of new features, chief among which are better compatibility with Ethereum Solidity version 0.8 and the integration of Solana SPL tokens with the Solidity language. Additionally, it also grants EVM frameworks on Solana access to the network&rsquo;s built-in functionality. Other important highlights of the new Solang compiler include the ability to call other Solana smart contracts, support for program-derived addresses, enabling development with Anchor, and native Solana smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Solana Labs has also created a beginners guide to assist developers in leveraging their existing knowledge in Solidity and tapping into Solana&rsquo;s high-speed and low-cost network. Using the guide, developers can easily set up their development environment, create and test their first smart contract, and then deploy it on Solana. Development on the Solana network has typically been around programming languages such as Rust or C, used to script smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>
Growing Efforts To Improve Ethereum-Solana Compatibility
<p>Solang&rsquo;s launch, coupled with Neon EVM&rsquo;s release, highlights the growing and continuous efforts to improve compatibility between the Solana network and Ethereum. Like Solang, Neon EVM&rsquo;s computing environment allows developers to write and create Ethereum applications on top of Solana. The implementation utilizes a smart contract built on top of Solana and deploys the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) code, which was not previously possible on the network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Apart from providing access to the Solana network, Neon EVM also looks to help Ethereum applications to take advantage of functionalities that are native to Solana, such as parallel execution of transactions. At the time of its launch, the director of the Neon Foundation, Marina Guryeva, had stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are very excited to see Neon EVM live on Solana Mainnet. Once we repeat these tests in production, we will present the figures based on real-world data.&rdquo;</p>

Solana&rsquo;s Foray Into AI&nbsp;
<p>Solana had recently made a significant announcement, officially integrating a ChatGPT plugin developed by Solana Labs and marking the official integration of AI into the network. AI has seen significant interest from big and small players in the crypto space. The Solana Foundation revealed that the integration would help users interact with the Solana network directly through ChatGPT.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This integration from Solana Labs serves as a reference for how AI can make it easier to understand Solana data and protocols or surface data about Solana&rsquo;s computing infrastructure and DeFi projects.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana Labs, the entity behind Solana, has announced the rollout of the Solang compiler. The new compiler will help Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) developers transition to the Solana ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The move aligns with Solana&rsquo;s efforts to become more accessible with Solidity, the programming language used with Ethereum smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>
A New Compiler&nbsp;
<p>The launch of Solang will help developers who have worked with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) to transition into the Solana ecosystem smoothly. Solang gives developers who are familiar with Solidity, Ethereum&rsquo;s primary smart contract programming language, all the tools required to write and create apps on the Solana network. The unveiling of the new compiler comes only a day after Neon EVM released a similar tool. In a statement published on its website, Solana Labs stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Solana development is well known for using Rust or C for writing smart contracts, but Solana is evolving to become more accessible with Solidity, the primary programming language used for Ethereum smart contracts. Solana Labs is thrilled to announce that today you can now build on Solana with Solidity using Solang, a new compiler that helps bridge the gap between EVM developers and the Solana ecosystem.&rdquo;</p>

A List Of Features
<p>According to the statement, the addition of more programming languages for building on Solana will see an influx of developers with broader skill sets into the Solana ecosystem. This was witnessed with the launch of Seahorse, a community-led initiative. Seahorse enables developers to write Solana smart contracts in Python, which is arguably the world&rsquo;s most popular programming language. The Solang launch is the continuation of efforts to broaden the reach and appeal of the Solana ecosystem among developers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Solang compiler introduces an array of new features, chief among which are better compatibility with Ethereum Solidity version 0.8 and the integration of Solana SPL tokens with the Solidity language. Additionally, it also grants EVM frameworks on Solana access to the network&rsquo;s built-in functionality. Other important highlights of the new Solang compiler include the ability to call other Solana smart contracts, support for program-derived addresses, enabling development with Anchor, and native Solana smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Solana Labs has also created a beginners guide to assist developers in leveraging their existing knowledge in Solidity and tapping into Solana&rsquo;s high-speed and low-cost network. Using the guide, developers can easily set up their development environment, create and test their first smart contract, and then deploy it on Solana. Development on the Solana network has typically been around programming languages such as Rust or C, used to script smart contracts.&nbsp;</p>
Growing Efforts To Improve Ethereum-Solana Compatibility
<p>Solang&rsquo;s launch, coupled with Neon EVM&rsquo;s release, highlights the growing and continuous efforts to improve compatibility between the Solana network and Ethereum. Like Solang, Neon EVM&rsquo;s computing environment allows developers to write and create Ethereum applications on top of Solana. The implementation utilizes a smart contract built on top of Solana and deploys the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) code, which was not previously possible on the network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Apart from providing access to the Solana network, Neon EVM also looks to help Ethereum applications to take advantage of functionalities that are native to Solana, such as parallel execution of transactions. At the time of its launch, the director of the Neon Foundation, Marina Guryeva, had stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are very excited to see Neon EVM live on Solana Mainnet. Once we repeat these tests in production, we will present the figures based on real-world data.&rdquo;</p>

Solana&rsquo;s Foray Into AI&nbsp;
<p>Solana had recently made a significant announcement, officially integrating a ChatGPT plugin developed by Solana Labs and marking the official integration of AI into the network. AI has seen significant interest from big and small players in the crypto space. The Solana Foundation revealed that the integration would help users interact with the Solana network directly through ChatGPT.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This integration from Solana Labs serves as a reference for how AI can make it easier to understand Solana data and protocols or surface data about Solana&rsquo;s computing infrastructure and DeFi projects.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Labs and Symbolic Capital Join Forces to Empower Web3 Innovation Worldwide]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lbank-labs-and-symbolic-capital-join-forces-to-empower-web3-innovation-worldwide</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1689825333udduf70XMA.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1689825333udduf70XMA.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1689825333udduf70XMA.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 06:11:54 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lbank-labs-and-symbolic-capital-join-forces-to-empower-web3-innovation-worldwide</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, July 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, at the forefront of blockchain venture funding, is delighted to share the news of its investment in Symbolic Capital. This strategic collaboration is poised to ignite innovation and provide robust support for the expansion of highly-scalable Web3 infrastructures worldwide.</p><p>LBank Labs, known for its protocol and exchange-agnostic approach, is committed to supporting projects through direct funding, acceleration, incubation, and extensive networking. With $100 million assets under management (AUM), the venture capitalist arm of global cryptocurrency exchange LBank has a strong track record of nurturing startups and helping them thrive. Besides direct investments in projects, the team aims to build a strong fund network via investing in global top funds to support portfolios from the network in both financial and resource value-add. Czhang Lin, IC board member of Labs, is also personally LPs to NGC, Blockchain Founders Fund and Lemniscap, where Eric He, Co-Founder of LBank is LP to SevenX Ventures fund I, II and FOF, and IOSG Ventures.</p><p>Symbolic Capital is a leading, thesis-driven venture capital firm co-founded by Sandeep Nailwal (founder of Polygon) and Kenzi Wang (partner at Borderless Capital). Rooted in the founders' own experiences of overcoming funding hurdles in their early days, Symbolic Capital places a special focus on identifying and accelerating the best blockchain founders. Even in the face of what some term a 'funding winter' for crypto, Symbolic Capital maintains its bullish outlook on the future of Web3, viewing it as the next evolution in the digital ecosystem.</p>Symbolic Capital&rsquo;s Co-founder Kenzi Wang expressed his enthusiasm for the firm's future collaborations, stating, "At Symbolic Capital, we are excited to collaborate with LBank Labs as we work towards our shared vision of building the future of crypto. Our partnership allows us to continue supporting innovative startups in the Web3.0 ecosystem, especially those from emerging markets, and pave the way for the mass adoption of decentralized applications."<p>As investors, LBank Labs is committed to fueling the growth of highly-scalable Web3 infrastructures and empowering innovative startups worldwide. The strategic investment in Symbolic Capital solidifies LBank Labs' dedication to building the future of crypto and supporting the mass adoption of decentralized applications.</p><p>With $100 million assets under management, LBank Labs not only boasts substantial financial resources but also possesses an expansive global network. In return, Symbolic Capital will provide LBank Labs with significant value, harnessing their expertise, strategic insights, and innovative mindset to foster mutual growth and chart a course towards resounding success.</p><p>The venture fund also aims to forge its commitment by building a comprehensive network of Fund of Funds, designed to enhance the performance and diversification of its portfolios while emphasising the inherent value of its ecosystem network. Labs&rsquo; presence in seven global regions, including San Francisco, Dubai, Paris, Denver, Singapore, Mexico, and Shanghai, positions them as a powerhouse for fostering collaboration and innovation across borders.</p><p>About LBank Labs</p><p>LBank Labs, a prominent player in the web3 space, manages a versatile $100 Million fund that extends beyond specific protocols and exchanges. With a team of experienced web3 veterans from prestigious entities, they have built an extensive network of expertise and connections. Their investment strategy includes fund-of-fund investments, direct investments in early-stage projects, and liquid projects, enabling them to explore diverse opportunities. LBank Labs actively promotes their investment thesis, &ldquo;The Other Angle,&rdquo; through engaging discussions and focuses on the PSE principles to foster sustainable growth and innovation in the web3 landscape. With a Fund of Fund network comprising 12 funds and over $1 billion in AUM, and offices in seven global regions, LBank Labs is well-positioned to expand their network and drive innovation in the web3 ecosystem, together with their partners and collaborators.</p>ContactLBank Labsjunjie.niu@lbanklabs.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, July 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, at the forefront of blockchain venture funding, is delighted to share the news of its investment in Symbolic Capital. This strategic collaboration is poised to ignite innovation and provide robust support for the expansion of highly-scalable Web3 infrastructures worldwide.</p><p>LBank Labs, known for its protocol and exchange-agnostic approach, is committed to supporting projects through direct funding, acceleration, incubation, and extensive networking. With $100 million assets under management (AUM), the venture capitalist arm of global cryptocurrency exchange LBank has a strong track record of nurturing startups and helping them thrive. Besides direct investments in projects, the team aims to build a strong fund network via investing in global top funds to support portfolios from the network in both financial and resource value-add. Czhang Lin, IC board member of Labs, is also personally LPs to NGC, Blockchain Founders Fund and Lemniscap, where Eric He, Co-Founder of LBank is LP to SevenX Ventures fund I, II and FOF, and IOSG Ventures.</p><p>Symbolic Capital is a leading, thesis-driven venture capital firm co-founded by Sandeep Nailwal (founder of Polygon) and Kenzi Wang (partner at Borderless Capital). Rooted in the founders' own experiences of overcoming funding hurdles in their early days, Symbolic Capital places a special focus on identifying and accelerating the best blockchain founders. Even in the face of what some term a 'funding winter' for crypto, Symbolic Capital maintains its bullish outlook on the future of Web3, viewing it as the next evolution in the digital ecosystem.</p>Symbolic Capital&rsquo;s Co-founder Kenzi Wang expressed his enthusiasm for the firm's future collaborations, stating, "At Symbolic Capital, we are excited to collaborate with LBank Labs as we work towards our shared vision of building the future of crypto. Our partnership allows us to continue supporting innovative startups in the Web3.0 ecosystem, especially those from emerging markets, and pave the way for the mass adoption of decentralized applications."<p>As investors, LBank Labs is committed to fueling the growth of highly-scalable Web3 infrastructures and empowering innovative startups worldwide. The strategic investment in Symbolic Capital solidifies LBank Labs' dedication to building the future of crypto and supporting the mass adoption of decentralized applications.</p><p>With $100 million assets under management, LBank Labs not only boasts substantial financial resources but also possesses an expansive global network. In return, Symbolic Capital will provide LBank Labs with significant value, harnessing their expertise, strategic insights, and innovative mindset to foster mutual growth and chart a course towards resounding success.</p><p>The venture fund also aims to forge its commitment by building a comprehensive network of Fund of Funds, designed to enhance the performance and diversification of its portfolios while emphasising the inherent value of its ecosystem network. Labs&rsquo; presence in seven global regions, including San Francisco, Dubai, Paris, Denver, Singapore, Mexico, and Shanghai, positions them as a powerhouse for fostering collaboration and innovation across borders.</p><p>About LBank Labs</p><p>LBank Labs, a prominent player in the web3 space, manages a versatile $100 Million fund that extends beyond specific protocols and exchanges. With a team of experienced web3 veterans from prestigious entities, they have built an extensive network of expertise and connections. Their investment strategy includes fund-of-fund investments, direct investments in early-stage projects, and liquid projects, enabling them to explore diverse opportunities. LBank Labs actively promotes their investment thesis, &ldquo;The Other Angle,&rdquo; through engaging discussions and focuses on the PSE principles to foster sustainable growth and innovation in the web3 landscape. With a Fund of Fund network comprising 12 funds and over $1 billion in AUM, and offices in seven global regions, LBank Labs is well-positioned to expand their network and drive innovation in the web3 ecosystem, together with their partners and collaborators.</p>ContactLBank Labsjunjie.niu@lbanklabs.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Starknet Introduces Appchains Framework $STRK]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/starknet-introduces-appchains-framework-strk</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/starknet-appchains-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/starknet-appchains-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/starknet-appchains-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/starknet-introduces-appchains-framework-strk</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet, an Ethereum Layer 2, has disclosed the initiation of "appchains," a framework designed to enable developers to construct several application-specific blockchains within the Starknet ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The innovative project is in alignment with the growing trend of modular networks in the Layer 2 ecosystem, spearheaded by projects like Optimism, Polygon, zkSync, and Arbitrum. </p>
A New Era For Application-Specific Chains
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Developers can harness Starknet Stack, the native developer toolkit of Starknet's ecosystem, to create these appchains, using STARK proofs to boost security. Central to this toolkit is Cairo, a programming language developed by the StarkWare team, bearing similarities to Rust.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent blog post, Starknet revealed that the use of appchains could offer developers an enhanced performance, a claim further supported by Starknet's recent v0.12.0 upgrade on the mainnet, which reportedly amplified network performance. </p>
Advancing Customization For Devs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A unique aspect of appchains lies in their capability to support features currently not present on Starknet's main network. This includes features like custom fee market logic and consernsus mechanisms, among others. This flexibility can potentially grant developers the ability to customize their application's configurations and functionalities, thus offering a greater degree of control over their projects.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Starknet Appchains are the bespoke environment where applications can tailor an instance of Starknet to achieve better control over the specs, lower cost, greater scale, and opt-in privacy," the firm shared.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The team underscored the escalating interest in application-specific blockchains, tailored to meet customized requirements. They stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"The need for appchains has been apparent for several years and is now getting renewed attention."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet's introduction of appchains represents a significant milestone in the blockchain landscape, enhancing developers' capacity for customization, and making the ecosystem more versatile and adaptable to specific application requirements. Such a move signals a key step towards a more decerntralized, diversified, and performance-oriented blockchain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet, an Ethereum Layer 2, has disclosed the initiation of "appchains," a framework designed to enable developers to construct several application-specific blockchains within the Starknet ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The innovative project is in alignment with the growing trend of modular networks in the Layer 2 ecosystem, spearheaded by projects like Optimism, Polygon, zkSync, and Arbitrum. </p>
A New Era For Application-Specific Chains
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Developers can harness Starknet Stack, the native developer toolkit of Starknet's ecosystem, to create these appchains, using STARK proofs to boost security. Central to this toolkit is Cairo, a programming language developed by the StarkWare team, bearing similarities to Rust.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent blog post, Starknet revealed that the use of appchains could offer developers an enhanced performance, a claim further supported by Starknet's recent v0.12.0 upgrade on the mainnet, which reportedly amplified network performance. </p>
Advancing Customization For Devs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A unique aspect of appchains lies in their capability to support features currently not present on Starknet's main network. This includes features like custom fee market logic and consernsus mechanisms, among others. This flexibility can potentially grant developers the ability to customize their application's configurations and functionalities, thus offering a greater degree of control over their projects.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Starknet Appchains are the bespoke environment where applications can tailor an instance of Starknet to achieve better control over the specs, lower cost, greater scale, and opt-in privacy," the firm shared.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The team underscored the escalating interest in application-specific blockchains, tailored to meet customized requirements. They stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"The need for appchains has been apparent for several years and is now getting renewed attention."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet's introduction of appchains represents a significant milestone in the blockchain landscape, enhancing developers' capacity for customization, and making the ecosystem more versatile and adaptable to specific application requirements. Such a move signals a key step towards a more decerntralized, diversified, and performance-oriented blockchain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Spectrum Finance To Integrate With Cardano $SPF $ADA]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/spectrum-finance-to-integrate-with-cardano-spf-ada</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/spectrum-finance-x-cardano-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/spectrum-finance-x-cardano-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/spectrum-finance-x-cardano-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/spectrum-finance-to-integrate-with-cardano-spf-ada</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance, a distinguished name in the decentralized exchange (DEX) landscape, renowned for fostering trustless, cross-chain programmable messaging, has revealed its strategic collaboration with Cardano, the innovative smart contract platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership is intended to extend Spectrum's capabilities into the Cardano ecosystem, enabling new opportunities for seamless blockchain interoperability.</p>
Amplified Capacities
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance has garnered recognition in the crypto industry by offering various functionalities tailored to user-specific needs, providing access to the Spectrum Network, a cross-chain smart contract platform for facilitating the creation of dApps that operate natively in a cross-chain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Its standout feature is its ability to interact seamlessly with native currencies and tokens across different blockchains simultaneously. This negates the need for wrapped or synthetic assets when conducting transactions between blockchains, allowing actions such as swapping native ETH from the Ethereum mainnet to native ADA on the Cardano mainnet with ease.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For Cardano, a platform built on peer-reviewed research and high-assurance development, the partnership with Spectrum Finance signals a significant enhancement. It will enable Cardano to offer its users a broader range of cross-chain functionality, capitalizing on Spectrum's interoperability capabilities. The integration with Spectrum sets the stage for the creation of innovative dApps leveraging the combined potential of Cardano's sophisticated smart contract capabilities and Spectrum's cross-chain abilities. This synergy is expected to yield dApps with unprecedented reach and functionality, harnessing the best features from both platforms.</p>
Challenges For Interoperability
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Blockchain interoperability has been a central challenge inhibiting wider adoption of the technology. It ensures seamless transactions across various blockchain networks without the need for intermediaries, reducing the fragmentation of the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, interoperability protocol implementation is complex, as different blockchains have distinct security solutions, consensus algorithms, and programming languages.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Solutions such as the Spectrum Protocol, which offers a truly decentralized, secure, and scalable cross-chain interoperability solution, are vital to overcoming this hurdle. The integration of Spectrum and Cardano represents a critical step towards both transforming and effectively pushing forward blockchain interoperability, with the promise and potential of unlocking new possibilities for the crypto industry, bringing users closer to an interconnected and seamless blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance, a distinguished name in the decentralized exchange (DEX) landscape, renowned for fostering trustless, cross-chain programmable messaging, has revealed its strategic collaboration with Cardano, the innovative smart contract platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership is intended to extend Spectrum's capabilities into the Cardano ecosystem, enabling new opportunities for seamless blockchain interoperability.</p>
Amplified Capacities
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance has garnered recognition in the crypto industry by offering various functionalities tailored to user-specific needs, providing access to the Spectrum Network, a cross-chain smart contract platform for facilitating the creation of dApps that operate natively in a cross-chain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Its standout feature is its ability to interact seamlessly with native currencies and tokens across different blockchains simultaneously. This negates the need for wrapped or synthetic assets when conducting transactions between blockchains, allowing actions such as swapping native ETH from the Ethereum mainnet to native ADA on the Cardano mainnet with ease.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For Cardano, a platform built on peer-reviewed research and high-assurance development, the partnership with Spectrum Finance signals a significant enhancement. It will enable Cardano to offer its users a broader range of cross-chain functionality, capitalizing on Spectrum's interoperability capabilities. The integration with Spectrum sets the stage for the creation of innovative dApps leveraging the combined potential of Cardano's sophisticated smart contract capabilities and Spectrum's cross-chain abilities. This synergy is expected to yield dApps with unprecedented reach and functionality, harnessing the best features from both platforms.</p>
Challenges For Interoperability
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Blockchain interoperability has been a central challenge inhibiting wider adoption of the technology. It ensures seamless transactions across various blockchain networks without the need for intermediaries, reducing the fragmentation of the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, interoperability protocol implementation is complex, as different blockchains have distinct security solutions, consensus algorithms, and programming languages.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Solutions such as the Spectrum Protocol, which offers a truly decentralized, secure, and scalable cross-chain interoperability solution, are vital to overcoming this hurdle. The integration of Spectrum and Cardano represents a critical step towards both transforming and effectively pushing forward blockchain interoperability, with the promise and potential of unlocking new possibilities for the crypto industry, bringing users closer to an interconnected and seamless blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
