<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:56:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XRP Price Dips Below $0.6 As Investors Lose Hope in Ripple &#8211; Could $LPX Token Be An Alternative?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-dips-below-0-6-as-investors-lose-hope-in-ripple-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267144</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/launchpad_xrp_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/launchpad_xrp_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies are registering steep losses as a perfect storm led by worsening inflation levels, SEC’s hawkish stance and struggling equities has turned the market sentiment distinctly bearish. The global crypto market cap plummeted by 2% over the past day, with even Bitcoin showing strong volatility as it fell to the $28,600 price level. XRP [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Major cryptocurrencies are registering steep losses as a perfect storm led by worsening inflation levels, SEC’s hawkish stance and struggling equities has turned the market sentiment distinctly bearish.</p>
<p>The global crypto market cap plummeted by 2% over the past day, with even Bitcoin showing strong volatility as it fell to the $28,600 price level.</p>
<p>XRP is also seeing a major sell-off as the token has fallen below the $0.6 price mark. Investors believe that the token will continue to retrace its post-win bull rally, especially with the SEC seeking to appeal Ripple’s landmark victory.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the demand for high-utility presale tokens is on the rise. The Launchpad XYZ ($LPX) token is emerging as an alternative investment to XRP, having already raised $1.3 million in its presale.</p>
<h2><strong>XRP Plummets Despite Ripple’s Strong Opposition Against An SEC Appeal</strong></h2>
<p>The XRP market capitalization has fallen below the $31 billion mark after the token corrected over 2% in the daily time frame, bringing its cumulative loss to over 6% over the past week.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-26.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267147" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-26.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="309" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-26.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-26-300x154.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-26-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a>XRP saw a remarkable, bullish surge after it was granted a non-security status in Ripple’s watershed victory against the SEC. District Judge Analisa Torres ruled that the programmatic and individual sales of XRP tokens did not meet the Howey criteria and thus did not violate the Securities Act.</p>
<p>Following the historic win, the token traded as high as $0.85, with a market capitalization of over $43 billion.</p>
<p>However, with the ruling now in danger of an SEC appeal, the token has plunged over 21% in the past month to trade at just $0.58.</p>
<p>Last week, the SEC requested an interlocutory appeal against Torres’ ruling and asked for a stay on all court proceedings. In response, <a href="https://twitter.com/FilanLaw/status/1691912544976515511?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ripple lawyers have filed a strong opposition</a> to any such appeal, stating that the SEC has no substantial ground for such a request.</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse and co-founder Chris Larsen, who are individual defendants in the case, have also separately <a href="https://twitter.com/FilanLaw/status/1691921878137401705?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">filed their opposition</a>.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, investor confidence in XRP appears to have shaken, especially since another District Judge Jed Rakoff sided with the SEC and rejected Torres’ Howey analysis in regards to XRP.</p>
<p><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/symbols/XRPUSD/technicals/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">TradingView</a> reflects this pessimistic view of investors, giving it a Sell signal in the daily time frame. The token is underperforming most of the important moving average indicators and is at risk of falling below its 100-day Exponential Moving Average at $0.577.</p>
<p>XRP is also bearing the brunt of the worsening macroeconomic outlook. The FOMC minutes released by the US Fed on Wednesday highlighted the need for more interest rate hikes, a scenario that could be extremely bearish for the crypto market.</p>
<p>In response to this news, equities like S&amp;P 500 and NASDAQ-100 turned red, which led to further selling pressure on the crypto market and altcoins like XRP.</p>
<p>However, while XRP and other major altcoins struggle, some new tokens continue to grow despite the bearish market conditions. One example is the Launchpad XYZ project, which is currently offering its $LPX token on presale and has gained a lot of attention from investors.</p>
<h2><strong>Launchpad XYZ Sees Surging Demand Despite Bear Market &#8211; $LPX Token Presale Nears $1.5 Million</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=xrp-price-dips-below-0-6-as-investors-lose-hope-in-ripple-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ</a> is a comprehensive all-in-one platform designed to meet the diverse needs of crypto traders and investors, empowering them for resounding success within the Web3 landscape.</p>
<p>The platform is offering a suite of powerful products that will help its users navigate the complexities of the market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-25.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267146" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-25.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="387" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-25.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-25-300x193.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-25-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>For example, investors are often unaware of high-potential gems like Pepe and FLOKI until it&#8217;s too late. To help solve this issue, the Launchpad Quotient ranks a diverse set of crypto assets across 400 data points, ensuring that investors do not miss out on the next big coin.</p>
<p>Traders can also gain a competitive advantage through Launchpad’s Trading Edge platform. Similar to leading investment analysis platforms like <a href="https://altindex.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">AltIndex</a>, it helps traders make real-time informed decisions with the help of sentiment analysis, the latest news and important market insights.</p>
<p>However, unlike other platforms, Launchpad XYZ also offers its own Terminal trading engine, so pro traders can execute their trades at a blazing-fast speed.</p>
<p>This all-in-one portal claims to bring “all of Web3 in one place”, offering its own Web3 wallet, a decentralized exchange, an NFT marketplace, fractionalized assets, etc.</p>
<p>Investors have been quick to recognize the potential of this project, as its native $LPX token has already raised over $1.3 million in the presale. There’s now just $200,000 to go before the next stage price increase.</p>
<p><a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=xrp-price-dips-below-0-6-as-investors-lose-hope-in-ripple-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-dips-below-0-6-as-investors-lose-hope-in-ripple-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative/" rel="nofollow">XRP Price Dips Below $0.6 As Investors Lose Hope in Ripple &#8211; Could $LPX Token Be An Alternative?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Brandt Warns of Bitcoin Bear Trap as BTC Dumps $1K Daily</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/peter-brandt-warns-of-bitcoin-bear-trap-as-btc-dumps-1k-daily/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267061</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls are currently struggling to regain momentum. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is currently undergoing a period of record low volatility. However, the asset appears to be a &#8220;challenging multi-contact point trendline&#8221; that can be traced to its lowest point in 2023.</p>
<p>This could offer insights into the future direction of the leading crypto-asset, according to renowned veteran trader Peter Brandt, who said the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization could drop further.</p>
<p>The prediction comes as BTC finally broke off from its narrow range and dived to a two-month low of $28.3k.</p>
<ul>
<li>In his latest <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterLBrandt/status/1691853244677644560" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweet</a>, Brandt speculated that if bitcoin moves south of the trendline that is located below $28,000, it would indicate the continuation of a bearish trend or a bear trap.</li>
<li>The founder and CEO of proprietary trading firm Factor LLC further added that the trendline violation negates the bullish narrative.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As a swing trader I would respect the violation of the trendline. So, my positions would be either short or flat. Only if a bear trap is actually &#8220;sprung&#8221; would I consider it a bullish development. I strongly prefer horizontal chart construction.</p>
<p>— Peter Brandt (@PeterLBrandt) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterLBrandt/status/1691853244677644560?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin&#8217;s price action has been dull for the most part, especially after declining slowly since its July peak.</li>
<li>The latest downward price action extended its monthly losses to nearly 6%.</li>
<li>However, Fundstrat <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fundstrat-predicts-150k-bitcoin-price-but-btc-drops-to-8-week-low/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">analyst</a> Tom Lee remains a major Bitcoin bull. He recently predicted an influx in demand for bitcoin if a spot BTC ETF gets approved in the US.</li>
<li>The company&#8217;s crypto strategists even forecasted a price range of $150,000 to $180,000, but only if such a product sees the light of day.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-brandt-warns-of-bitcoin-bear-trap-as-btc-dumps-1k-daily/" rel="nofollow">Peter Brandt Warns of Bitcoin Bear Trap as BTC Dumps $1K Daily</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Lead Dev: All is Well, No Bridge Issue, This Caused the Shibarium Problems</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-lead-dev-all-is-well-no-bridge-issue-this-caused-the-shibarium-issues/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267109</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_lead_dev_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_lead_dev_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu lead developer Shytoshi Kusama addresses the recent turmoil.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s lead developer Shytoshi Kusama addressed the recent turmoil within the cryptocurrency community regarding the issues that Shibarium&#8217;s launch faced.</p>
<ul>
<li>As <em>CryptoPotato </em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier, the Shibarium launch was faced with some issues, including stuck transactions.</li>
<li>Reports started circling around that Shytoshi Kusama acknowledged the problems, also saying that there&#8217;s a huge number of ETH stuck in the Shibarium bridge that can&#8217;t be recovered.</li>
<li>In a blog post published just now, Kusama <a href="https://blog.shib.io/shibarium-insane-influx/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">addressed</a> the above, saying that all is well.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>Let&#8217;s deal with the fud. There is no bridge issue, any screenshot you see of me saying any issue is false and your funds are safu.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The post goes on to explain the issues that caused delays in processing transactions.</li>
<li>Kusama revealed that they saw an &#8220;insane level of traffic,&#8221; providing the following visualization to exemplify the difference of the normal load as opposed to what the network faced in reality.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_267120" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267120" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267120" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units.jpg" alt="Compute Units" width="1280" height="817" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units.jpg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units-300x191.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units-1024x654.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units-768x490.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Compute-Units-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267120" class="wp-caption-text">Source: shib.io</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-lead-dev-all-is-well-no-bridge-issue-this-caused-the-shibarium-issues/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu Lead Dev: All is Well, No Bridge Issue, This Caused the Shibarium Problems</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huge Wave of Money to Flow Into XRP Under These Circumstances: Wall Street Veteran</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/huge-wave-of-money-to-flow-into-xrp-under-these-circumstances-wall-street-veteran/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267099</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_wave_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_wave_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A well-known Wall Street veteran believes that there's a huge wave of money waiting to flow in XRP. But when?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s XRP has been at the forefront of experts&#8217; discussions for quite a while now, especially in 2023.</p>
<p>The main reason for this seems to be the ongoing <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-opposes-secs-request-for-interlocutory-appeal-in-ongoing-legal-spat/" data-wpel-link="internal">spat</a> between Ripple Labs and the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to many analysts and XRP proponents, the price of the token has been heavily suppressed by the ongoing legal feud between the US SEC and Ripple.</li>
<li>After all, the top financial watchdog of the world&#8217;s strongest economy is alleging that sales of XRP, be it primary or secondary, constitute an investment contract, essentially claiming that XRP is a security.</li>
<li>If that&#8217;s found to be the case, Ripple would have conducted an unregistered securities offering worth over $1 billion.</li>
<li>More importantly, though, it would legitimize the claim that XRP is a security, which would put the asset under the scrutiny and purview of the Securities and Exchange Commission.</li>
<li>That said, Wall Street veteran Linda Jones thinks that the XRP price will eventually be pushed higher by none other but institutions.</li>
<li>She thinks that they need more legal clarity.</li>
<li>More recently, Judge Analisa Torres, who&#8217;s presiding over the Ripple case, ruled partially in favor of the company, concluding that secondary sales of XRP do not constitute an investment contract.</li>
<li>Yet, the case still has a long way to go.</li>
<li>Jones also <a href="https://twitter.com/LindaPJones/status/1691810186736922776" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">believes</a> that congressional lawmaking is also needed for XRP&#8217;s price to increase.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>It&#8217;s institutional money that will drive XRP&#8217;s price higher, imo. Institutions need legal clarity and framework. The lawsuit was one important piece of that. More Congressional lawmaking is needed, but it will happen. After that, the money will flow in a huge wave. They are preparing.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/huge-wave-of-money-to-flow-into-xrp-under-these-circumstances-wall-street-veteran/" rel="nofollow">Huge Wave of Money to Flow Into XRP Under These Circumstances: Wall Street Veteran</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How This Early Pepe Trader Became a Millionaire – Which New Meme Coins Are Investors Backing Now?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-this-early-pepe-trader-became-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-are-investors-backing-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267078</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/wsm_sonik_pepe_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/wsm_sonik_pepe_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The massive gains scored by early investors in meme coins like Pepe ($PEPE) have shown the sector’s explosive potential. One anonymous trader became an overnight millionaire after purchasing trillions of $PEPE tokens right after launch, setting themselves up for life-changing wealth. With new meme coins constantly emerging, investors are keen to identify the next potential [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The massive gains scored by early investors in meme coins like Pepe ($PEPE) have shown the sector’s explosive potential.</p>
<p>One anonymous trader became an overnight millionaire after purchasing trillions of $PEPE tokens right after launch, setting themselves up for life-changing wealth.</p>
<p>With new meme coins constantly emerging, investors are keen to identify the next potential winners in the space – hoping to become the next &#8220;crypto millionaires.&#8221;</p>
<h2>$PEPE’s Rollercoaster Ride Highlights Meme Coin Potential</h2>
<p>$PEPE has dominated crypto conversations in recent months following its incredible launch and price rise.</p>
<p>The token debuted on Uniswap in mid-April when meme coin momentum was exceedingly low.</p>
<p>However, through viral social media marketing and enthusiastic community support, $PEPE gained traction and saw its price explode in May.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-23.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267088" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-23.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="249" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-23.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-23-300x124.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-23-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, $PEPE hit an all-time high of $0.000001265 on May 5 – over 3,500% higher than its launch price.</p>
<p>Unfortunately for $PEPE bulls, this peak was fleeting, and the price has gradually fallen in recent months, now trading 72% below May&#8217;s high.</p>
<h2>How One Trader Scored Millions Off a $27 Pepe Coin Investment</h2>
<p>One trader turned a negligible $27 investment into nearly $4 million thanks to their timely $PEPE entry.</p>
<p>As highlighted in a <a href="https://twitter.com/DexGemsReal/status/1648575669641543681?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter post from lyx.eth</a> back in April, a wallet beginning with 0xaf23 had purchased 2.5 trillion $PEPE tokens right after launch for a total of $27.</p>
<p>As the hype around the new meme coin took off, the value of those tokens exploded.</p>
<p>Within weeks, the wallet’s holdings were worth close to $1 million as the buying frenzy around $PEPE reached fever pitch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-25.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267087" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-25.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="253" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-25.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-25-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-25-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>At the peak of Pepe mania in early May, when the project&#8217;s market cap hit $1.8 billion, these tokens would have been worth close to $10 million.</p>
<p>Though $PEPE subsequently declined from its highs, the trader continues holding their tokens, according to <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xaf2358e98683265cbd3a48509123d390ddf54534#tokentxns" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data from Etherscan.io</a>.</p>
<p>The trader’s holdings are now worth just over $3 million, and while they missed the chance to cash out at $PEPE’s peak, they remain a multimillionaire off of a tiny $27 investment on an unknown meme coin.</p>
<p>Stories like this have fueled the meme coin craze, with investors hoping to replicate this success through early identification and support of new meme coins.</p>
<h2>Which Other Meme Coins Are Investors Backing?</h2>
<p>With new meme coins constantly launching, investors are always searching for the next breakout stars.</p>
<p>Two projects that have quickly gained backing are Sonik Coin and Wall Street Memes, thanks to their strong branding and unique tokenomics structures.</p>
<h2>Sonik Coin Presale Surges Past $50k Thanks to Early Investor Buzz &#8211; Could it 10x?</h2>
<p>One new meme coin gaining significant traction is <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/box_3bb03a9e65107f306e2760608ad07313?referrer=how-this-early-pepe-trader-became-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-are-investors-backing-now" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sonik Coin ($SONIK)</a>, which has built momentum through its limited-time presale phase.</p>
<p>Tapping into the popularity of Sonic the Hedgehog, $SONIK has raised over $57,000 so far in its presale, with investors able to participate for only $0.000014 per token.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s staking functionality is a major draw, which allocates 40% of the total token supply to rewards for $SONIK holders.</p>
<p>By locking up their tokens, stakers can earn yields as high as 1,027% annually, according to the <a href="https://www.sonikcoin.com/en/dashboard" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sonik Coin dashboard</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267086" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-24.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="292" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-24.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-24-300x146.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-24-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>$SONIK&#8217;s presale has a hard cap of just $2 million, and due to the strength of the early investor demand, there&#8217;s a growing belief it could be hit soon.</p>
<p>This could prime the token for subsequent growth once $SONIK lists on Uniswap shortly after.</p>
<p>The combination of an accessible presale, strong meme appeal, and staking rewards has caught the attention of several influencers, with <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9doZ8g7S8bA&amp;pp=ygURamFjb2IgY3J5cHRvIGJ1cnk%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">YouTuber Jacob Bury</a> stating it’s one of his top five cryptocurrencies to buy in August.</p>
<p>While meme coins are undoubtedly risky, Sonik Coin’s clever formula could make it one to monitor in the coming weeks.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/box_3bb03a9e65107f306e2760608ad07313?referrer=how-this-early-pepe-trader-became-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-are-investors-backing-now" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Sonik Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Presale Crosses $24m Ahead of Major Exchange Listings</h2>
<p>Another meme coin grabbing attention is <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=how-this-early-pepe-trader-became-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-are-investors-backing-now" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a>, which taps into the viral retail trading movement popularized on Reddit.</p>
<p>The $WSM presale is now nearing its conclusion, raising an incredible $24.5 million across 29 stages, each with its own price point.</p>
<p>With the presale now in its second-last stage, the window is closing for investors to purchase $WSM tokens at the discounted price of $0.0334.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267085" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-18.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="297" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-18.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-18-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-18-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The token’s creators have hinted at plans to launch $WSM on major exchanges immediately after the presale ends, so anticipation is rapidly building.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes&#8217; huge social media presence has driven presale demand, with the brand boasting over 1.1 million followers worldwide.</p>
<p>Several influencers have also endorsed the project, including <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=skW4VvqOUa4&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Joe Parys Crypto</a>, who has over 380,000 subscribers on YouTube.</p>
<p>As the final stage of the presale approaches, Wall Street Memes looks poised to transition to an exchange listing with massive momentum behind it – priming it to potentially become the next breakout star in the meme coin space.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=how-this-early-pepe-trader-became-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-are-investors-backing-now" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-this-early-pepe-trader-became-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-are-investors-backing-now/" rel="nofollow">How This Early Pepe Trader Became a Millionaire – Which New Meme Coins Are Investors Backing Now?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price During Next Bull Market: 3 Things to Keep an Eye Out For</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-during-next-bull-market-3-things-to-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267063</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are three important considerations that might shape XRP's price during the next bull market. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the crypto market continues evolving, investors eagerly anticipate the next bull market. Among the coins poised to make a significant impact is XRP, the digital asset associated with Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>Given its distinctive attributes and significant potential for widespread adoption, it is crucial to monitor three key factors when assessing XRP&#8217;s price trajectory in the upcoming bull market.</p>
<h2>Regulatory Developments</h2>
<p>Having regulatory clarity regarding crypto, especially XRP could greatly impact its price. Ripple Labs is currently engaged in a legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding the classification of XRP as a security.</p>
<p>A favorable resolution to this dispute could propel XRP&#8217;s value upward. Conversely, an adverse ruling could <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-tumbles-in-anticipation-of-major-development-in-ripple-v-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">dampen</a> investor sentiment and potential price gains. In a recent statement, John Reed Stark, a former SEC official, <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1690707913789112320?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1690707913789112320%7Ctwgr%5E5d408781b80e3b6af5e2f930bb02eefd55e035f3%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcryptopotato.com%2Fhow-high-can-ripple-xrp-go-during-the-next-bull-market%2F" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">hinted</a> at the possibility of more crypto-friendly policies and increased regulatory clarity in the event of a Republican victory in the upcoming U.S. presidential elections.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267071" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover.jpg" alt="xrp_bull_rocket_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_bull_rocket_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Technological Advancements</h2>
<p>Technological advancements within the Ripple ecosystem will also shape XRP&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-high-can-ripple-xrp-go-during-the-next-bull-market/" data-wpel-link="internal">price</a> during the next bull market.</p>
<p>The integration of new features, such as the implementation of the Flare Network for smart contracts and interoperability with other blockchains, could significantly enhance XRP&#8217;s utility and demand.</p>
<p>These improvements could position XRP as more than just a cryptocurrency, appealing to a broader user base and contributing to price growth.</p>
<h2>Market Sentiment and Adoption</h2>
<p>The sentiment surrounding the broader cryptocurrency market and XRP&#8217;s adoption rate will be pivotal in determining its price trajectory during the next bull market.</p>
<p>Positive sentiment and increasing adoption by financial institutions can drive demand for XRP. Furthermore, partnerships and collaborations with established players in the financial sector can instill confidence in XRP&#8217;s use case and potential, positively impacting its price.</p>
<p>Monitoring these key factors will provide investors with valuable insights into the potential direction of XRP&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>None of the above should be considered as financial advice, and readers are strongly advised to carry out their own research or consult a professional before making any investments.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-during-next-bull-market-3-things-to-keep-an-eye-out-for/" rel="nofollow">XRP Price During Next Bull Market: 3 Things to Keep an Eye Out For</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Opposes SEC’s Request for Interlocutory Appeal in Ongoing Legal Spat</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-opposes-secs-request-for-interlocutory-appeal-in-ongoing-legal-spat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267060</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple argued that there is no extraordinary circumstance justifying a departure from the rule that requires all issues to be resolved before an appeal.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple Labs has opposed the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) request for an interlocutory appeal against Judge Analisa Torres’ decision on the sale of XRP constituting securities.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1691917112019960288?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> by Ripple Labs chief legal officer Stuart Alderoty, the court should reject the SEC’s request because there is no extraordinary circumstance justifying a departure from the rule that requires all issues to be resolved before an appeal.</p>
<h2>Ripple Opposes SEC’s Appeal Request</h2>
<p>In mid-July, Judge Torres <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/history-in-the-making-with-ripple-scoring-massive-win-in-court-in-xrp-security-case-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">passed</a> a landmark decision in the legal case between the SEC and Ripple. She ruled that the sale of XRP to retail investors on exchanges did not qualify as securities because they followed a blind bid process. In contrast, the opposite is the case when the same assets are sold to institutional investors.</p>
<p>The judge’s ruling dealt a massive blow to the SEC because its lawsuit against Ripple was based on accusations that the company conducted an unregistered sale of securities even in secondary markets.</p>
<p>Subsequently, the SEC signaled its intent to appeal the ruling and, on August 9, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-institutional-interest-skyrockets-despite-secs-intention-to-appeal-judges-decision-in-ripple-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> an interlocutory brief to that effect. The agency cited a recent incident where a presiding judge in its case against Terraform Labs and its founder, Do Kwon, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-rejects-terraforms-attempt-to-capitalize-on-ripple-precedent-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">dismissed</a> the XRP ruling.</p>
<p>An interlocutory appeal occurs when a decision by a trial court is challenged while other aspects of the case are still proceeding. Such requests are usually allowed under rare or specific circumstances.</p>
<p>In Ripple’s <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.889.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">opposition</a>, the company insisted that the SEC be allowed to appeal Judge Torres’ decision in the normal course after a final judgment is passed.</p>
<h2>Ripple Will Prove SEC Wrong Again: Garlinghouse</h2>
<p>Ripple’s opposition to the SEC’s motion was based on three reasons, with the first being that the judge’s ruling was not a “pure question of law.” The company also argued that the Commission’s disagreement with the decision did not show a substantial ground for a difference of opinion.</p>
<p>Lastly, an immediate appeal of the ruling would not lead to the termination of the legal case, according to Ripple.</p>
<p>Commenting on Ripple’s opposition, the company’s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1691927226009235666?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> that even if the appeal is granted, it will not change the fact that XRP is not a security.</p>
<p>The Ripple chief added that the SEC’s claims that he and his partner Chris Larsen acted recklessly in believing the crypto asset is not a security is “utter nonsense,” stating that they look forward to proving the agency wrong again.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-opposes-secs-request-for-interlocutory-appeal-in-ongoing-legal-spat/" rel="nofollow">Ripple Opposes SEC’s Request for Interlocutory Appeal in Ongoing Legal Spat</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON DAO Ventures Invests $2 Million in CRV and Curve to Launch on TRON and BTTC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tron-dao-ventures-invests-2-million-in-crv-and-curve-to-launch-on-tron-and-bttc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267028</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/46c45ae6-5a58-4053-9878-db127a03acb5_1692259989D7hFvsQULj.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/46c45ae6-5a58-4053-9878-db127a03acb5_1692259989D7hFvsQULj.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 17th, 2023] TRON DAO Ventures, the investment arm of TRON DAO, has recently bought $2 million worth of CRV tokens. As part of this strategic partnership, Curve will launch on both the TRON and the BTTC networks. Curve is a decentralized exchange acclaimed for its automated market makers (AMMs) [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 17th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>TRON DAO Ventures, the investment arm of <a href="http://trondao.org" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">TRON DAO</a>, has recently bought $2 million worth of CRV tokens. As part of this strategic partnership, Curve will launch on both the TRON and the BTTC networks.</p>
<p>Curve is a decentralized exchange acclaimed for its automated market makers (AMMs) tailored for stablecoin trading. Having experienced an exponential surge in the latter half of 2020, it once established itself as the epitome of DeFi platforms. Currently, Curve ranks as the world&#8217;s second-largest decentralized exchange (DEX) and the largest DEX for stablecoin trading.</p>
<p>The recent hack targeting the platform has led to a chain reaction in the DeFi space. TRON founder Justin Sun promptly expressed his support for Curve after the incident, stating, &#8220;Curve is an essential DeFi infrastructure for the blockchain industry. Our thoughts are with the team and the users affected. As a community, let&#8217;s support and strengthen the security measures to protect our decentralized ecosystem.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amidst the volatile market on August 1, TRON forged a partnership with Curve, introducing a stUSDT pool on the platform. stUSDT, the world&#8217;s first rebase real-world asset (RWA) protocol on the TRON blockchain, is hailed as the Web3 world&#8217;s version of Yu&#8217;E Bao (once China’s largest money market fund). According to <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/stusdt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Defillama</a>, the TVL on stUSDT has already exceeded $700 million.</p>
<p>Following that, TRON DAO Ventures announced its investment in Curve, underscoring TRON&#8217;s ecosystem support not only through collaboration but also through financial backing. Meanwhile, Curve will integrate with the TRON and the BTTC networks as part of the partnership.</p>
<p>The collaboration among TRON, BTTC, and Curve is set to generate crucial synergies for the industry. Curve, a foundation infrastructure in the DeFi domain, offers significant advantages in terms of reduced financial costs and time inefficiencies while also supporting prominent public blockchains like Ethereum, Arbitrum, and Avalanche. This collaboration is poised to help further develop TRON&#8217;s DeFi ecosystem. Meanwhile, as a major driver of DeFi innovation, TRON will share its most secure and cutting-edge products with Curve.</p>
<p>The integration between Curve and BTTC will also fuel the growth of DeFi ecosystems, especially DEX platforms. As the industry&#8217;s first heterogeneous cross-chain interoperability protocol, BTTC has supported cross-chain functionality between TRON, Ethereum, and BNB Chain upon its release. It will also introduce zero-knowledge (ZK) proof technology later this year, which enables users to build dApps seamlessly across different blockchains, promoting an inclusive ecosystem open to everyone.</p>
<p>With the backing of TRON and BTTC, Curve anticipates a rapid rebound, and users are bound to witness a more vibrant DeFi ecosystem in the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>About TRON DAO</h2>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of August 2023, it has over 179.07 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 6.26 billion total transactions, and over $13.01 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN.</p>
<p>In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which marks the first time a major public blockchain partnered with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government’s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (“DMC”), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica’s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens &#8211; TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<h2>About Curve</h2>
<p>Founded by Michael Egorov and launched in January 2020, Curve Finance positions itself as a DEX built on an AMM model. It focuses on the trading of stablecoins (USDT, USDC, DAI), synthetic assets/derivatives/staking assets (wBTC, renBTC, stETH), etc. In addition to its stronghold Ethereum, Curve also extended its presence across other chains such as Fantom, Polygon, Avalanche, Arbitrum, and Optimism.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-dao-ventures-invests-2-million-in-crv-and-curve-to-launch-on-tron-and-bttc/" rel="nofollow">TRON DAO Ventures Invests $2 Million in CRV and Curve to Launch on TRON and BTTC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Experiences Major Issues on Day 1: Details</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267015</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shiba_inu_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shiba_inu_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shibarium's launch causes stir as community slams "non-functional" RPC, "awful" blockchain explorer, and an overall "sloppy" experience.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The highly awaited Shibarium finally made its debut this week. The spotlight was firmly fixed at layer-2 primarily because it aimed to elevate the meme coin&#8217;s status in the industry into a more substantial contender. The launch, however, did not meet the expectation as SHIB, BONE, LEASH, and TREAT are experiencing declines in the aftermath.</p>
<p>Transactions stuck on the Shibarium in a pending state is to blame. The community has also pointed to issues plaguing the remote procedure call system, also known as the RPC.</p>
<h2>Shibarium&#8217;s &#8216;Sloppy&#8217; Start</h2>
<p>According to the blockchain security platform Beosin, there are currently $1.7 million in funds <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1692003409602445743" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">locked</a> in Shibarium. It advised users to temporarily stop using the blockchain. The figure was further confirmed by another blockchain security expert, PeckShied, which revealed that 956 ETH was stuck on the Shibarium bridge.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">In case yall were wondering how Shibarium is going <a href="https://t.co/S5vjTxoMDk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/S5vjTxoMDk</a></p>
<p>— ʎppɐꓷ ɯooɹɥS (@shroom_daddy) <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953231289528683?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Shibarium is a layer-2 solution for the Shiba Inu blockchain that was designed to reduce gas fees and ramp up transactions.</p>
<p>However, a screenshot allegedly depicting an internal conversation on Telegram between Shiba Inu’s lead developer, who goes by the pseudonym Shytoshi Kusama, and other members of the team indicates the failure to retrieve assets bridged to the Shibarium network.</p>
<p>An additional <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953687994757292" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">screenshot</a> has been going around that purportedly displayed a Shibarium user encountering a technical issue with the block scanner. They mentioned being unable to retrieve their bridged balance through the RPC query. Meanwhile, the Shibarium RPC website remains inaccessible as well.</p>
<p>Prominent crypto sleuth ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1691962886585815081" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">described</a> the launch as a &#8220;sloppy&#8221; one. Shibarium&#8217;s blockchain explorer, which has faced <a href="https://twitter.com/Boo_Koo_Bucks/status/1691963193147674918" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">criticism</a> for being subpar, <a href="https://www.shibariumscan.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">indicates</a> that the most recent block was added three hours ago.</p>
<h2>Shib Inu Tokens Suffer Losses</h2>
<p>The botched launch has had a negative impact on the price of all the tokens associated with the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The SHIB meme coin, for one, lost almost 10% in the last 24 hours. However, it is the Shibarium’s governance tokens &#8211; BONE and LEASH &#8211; that suffered the most, recording approximately 15% and 24% drawdowns during the same period. Meanwhile, TREAT was also down by more than 22%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Experiences Major Issues on Day 1: Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Shiba Inu (SHIB) Crashing Despite Shibarium Launch? 2 Possible Reasons</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-shiba-inu-shib-crashing-despite-shibarium-launch-2-possible-reasons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267041</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) is crashing. Here's why.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu is going through major developments throughout the past few days that the community has been long looking forward to.</p>
<p>As <em>CryptoPotato </em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-team-announces-launch-of-shibarium-mainnet/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> yesterday, Shiba Inu developers appeared on stage at the Blockchain Futurist Conference in Toronto to announce the launch of the Shibarium mainnet.</p>
<p>The price, however, hasn&#8217;t perceived the news positively and is, in turn, crashing during the past 24 hours. But why?</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267043" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" alt="shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Shibarium Launched Not Without Problems</h2>
<p>First of all, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-shibarium/" data-wpel-link="internal">Shibarium</a> &#8211; Shiba Inu&#8217;s much-anticipated layer 2 blockchain &#8211; launched its mainnet yesterday but not without its issues.</p>
<p>Data from Shibarium&#8217;s blockchain scanner reveals that transactions on the protocol had been stalling for no less than many hours.</p>
<p>In addition, the Shib Mainnet RPC, which should be accessible via <a href="https://www.shibrpc.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">this website</a>, is also not functioning properly.</p>
<p>There are also reports circling, which indicate that bridging to Shibarium is also impossible.</p>
<p>The underwhelming launch of the much-anticipated Shibarium network might as well be one of the main reasons, if not the main one, for the price&#8217;s decline throughout the past 24 hours.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267044" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267044" style="width: 810px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267044" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231.jpg" alt="shib_chart_1708231" width="810" height="543" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231.jpg 810w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231-300x201.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231-768x515.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 810px) 100vw, 810px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267044" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sell The News</h2>
<p>Shibarium had been announced for quite a while now, and many were already speculating that yesterday was going to be its official launch date.</p>
<p>Events of this kind, which are highly anticipated and present a considerable shift in the development of a cryptocurrency&#8217;s ecosystem, oftentimes turn out to be &#8220;sell the news&#8221;  events.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s a common investment saying which goes like this:</p>
<blockquote><p>Buy the rumor, sell the news.</p></blockquote>
<p>In essence, this entails that investors in the know will bet on an upcoming event, buying when there&#8217;s no certainty in anticipation of a considerable increase once the event gets to see the light of day. Then, once the rest who failed to chip in earlier start buying, those who bought would take advantage of the liquidity and sell at profit.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-shiba-inu-shib-crashing-despite-shibarium-launch-2-possible-reasons/" rel="nofollow">Why is Shiba Inu (SHIB) Crashing Despite Shibarium Launch? 2 Possible Reasons</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
