<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Voyager Digital Customers Will Recover 35% of Their Crypto Deposits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-digital-customers-will-recover-35-of-their-crypto-deposits.htm</link><description>Bankruptcy crypto lender Voyager Digital said customers will soon recover 35 percent of their cryptocurrency deposits, following a rocky road over the past few months of multiple failed buyouts. &lt;br /&gt;
US Bankruptcy Judge Michael Wiles approved Voyager’s liquidation plan on Wednesday, which will allow the firm to return about $1.33 billion in crypto assets to its customers, according to a report from Reuters. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-digital-customers-will-recover-35-of-their-crypto-deposits.htm"&gt;Read More: Voyager Digital Customers Will Recover 35% of Their Crypto Deposits&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Voyager Digital</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><category>FTX</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-digital-customers-will-recover-35-of-their-crypto-deposits.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114218/276083/hammer-g1f7d675f0-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="176811"/></item><item><title>South Korean Lawmakers ‘Must Declare’ Crypto Holdings – ‘Coin Gate’ Fallout Continues</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-lawmakers-must-declare-crypto-holdings-coin-gate-fallout-continues.htm</link><description>South Korean lawmakers will likely be “obliged” to declare their crypto holdings following a national outcry over alleged “insider trading.” &lt;br /&gt;
The National Assembly’s Political Affairs Committee has co-created a resolution that would create a “voluntary” system whereby they are requested to report their cryptoasset holdings. &lt;br /&gt;
But any such system is likely to become a de facto mandatory protocol, South Korean media outlets have claimed....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-lawmakers-must-declare-crypto-holdings-coin-gate-fallout-continues.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Lawmakers ‘Must Declare’ Crypto Holdings – ‘Coin Gate’ Fallout Continues&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Politics</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-lawmakers-must-declare-crypto-holdings-coin-gate-fallout-continues.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114115/275941/s-korea-natl-assmbly.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="696622"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 17 May – Conflux, Render, Litecoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-17-may-conflux-render-litecoin.htm</link><description>Tether, the largest stablecoin issuer and one of the most controversial companies in crypto, announced a new investment strategy today: the company will allocate up to 15% of its reserves to buy and hold Bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
The strategy moves away from Tether's long-held conservative investment approach and shows that the company believes that Bitcoin is the future and offers more upside than any other cryptocurrencies. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this new development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-17-may-conflux-render-litecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 17 May – Conflux, Render, Litecoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>CFX</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>RNDR</category><category>YPRED</category><category>LTC</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Conflux</category><category>Render Token</category><category>yPredictm Litecoin</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-17-may-conflux-render-litecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114217/276081/best-crypto-17.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="232756"/></item><item><title>This Metric of Bitcoin (BTC) Price Momentum Just Fell to its Lowest Since March – Is Now a Good Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/metric-of-bitcoin-btc-price-momentum-just-fell-its-lowest-since-march-now-good-time-buy.htm</link><description>A key metric that measures momentum in the Bitcoin price just fell to its weakest level since March. &lt;br /&gt;
Last week, Bitcoin’s Z-score to its 200-Day Moving Average fell under 1.0, where it has remained more or less ever since. &lt;br /&gt;
That means that the current Bitcoin price is only just under one standard deviation above its average daily closing price over the past 200 days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/metric-of-bitcoin-btc-price-momentum-just-fell-its-lowest-since-march-now-good-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: This Metric of Bitcoin (BTC) Price Momentum Just Fell to its Lowest Since March – Is Now a Good Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Metric</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/metric-of-bitcoin-btc-price-momentum-just-fell-its-lowest-since-march-now-good-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114214/276076/btc-9.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="108800"/></item><item><title>US SEC Says Filecoin Is a Security in Comment Letter to Grayscale</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-says-filecoin-security-comment-letter-grayscale.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission determined that Filecoin is a security, according to a statement released by asset manager Grayscale Investments. &lt;br /&gt;
In a press release sent on Wednesday afternoon, the digital currency asset manager said it had received a comment letter from SEC staff stating that view. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-says-filecoin-security-comment-letter-grayscale.htm"&gt;Read More: US SEC Says Filecoin Is a Security in Comment Letter to Grayscale&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Filecoin</category><category>Filecoin Price</category><category>Grayscale</category><category>Grayscale Investments</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-says-filecoin-security-comment-letter-grayscale.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114212/276068/gavel-g152d4497b-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="108210"/></item><item><title>Citadel Securities Suing Two Former Employees After They Left To Form a Crypto Firm</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/citadel-securities-suing-two-former-employees-after-they-left-form-crypto-firm.htm</link><description>Citadel Securities is suing two former employees after they left to form a cryptocurrency market-making firm.  &lt;br /&gt;
One of the world’s largest market makers claims that Leonard Lancia and Alex Casimo started raising capital and building the trading firm Portofino Technologies, while still working at Citadel, with access to proprietary information, according to Bloomberg News....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/citadel-securities-suing-two-former-employees-after-they-left-form-crypto-firm.htm"&gt;Read More: Citadel Securities Suing Two Former Employees After They Left To Form a Crypto Firm&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Citadel</category><category>Bloomberg</category><category>Market Maker</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/citadel-securities-suing-two-former-employees-after-they-left-form-crypto-firm.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114204/276055/pexels-ekaterina-bolovtso.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="109177"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Spikes Up 4% From Recent Bottom – Where is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-spikes-up-4-from-recent-bottom-where-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, has experienced a significant spike of 4% from its recent bottom. &lt;br /&gt;
This upward movement has sparked curiosity among investors and traders who are now eager to know where Bitcoin's price is heading next.  &lt;br /&gt;
As market participants closely monitor the ongoing price action, they seek insights and predictions to identify potential target levels for Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-spikes-up-4-from-recent-bottom-where-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Spikes Up 4% From Recent Bottom – Where is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-spikes-up-4-from-recent-bottom-where-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114203/276046/17-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480491"/></item><item><title>Ledger Hardware Wallet Addresses Criticism, Stands by New Wallet Recovery Service – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ledger-hardware-wallet-addresses-criticism-stands-by-new-wallet-recovery-service-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The popular hardware wallet maker Ledger has addressed some of the concerns from the community, after it introduced a new and controversial wallet recovery service. &lt;br /&gt;
In a video posted on Tuesday, Ledger’s chief technology officer Charles Guillemet stressed that although the new wallet recovery feature may be convenient for some users, it will be completely optional to use it....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ledger-hardware-wallet-addresses-criticism-stands-by-new-wallet-recovery-service-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Ledger Hardware Wallet Addresses Criticism, Stands by New Wallet Recovery Service – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ledger</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ledger-hardware-wallet-addresses-criticism-stands-by-new-wallet-recovery-service-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114176/275996/ledger.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="160914"/></item><item><title>Berenberg Investment Firm Analyst Sees MicroStrategy as Safer Bet than Coinbase Due to SEC Risk</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/berenberg-investment-firm-analyst-sees-microstrategy-as-safer-bet-than-coinbase-due-sec-risk.htm</link><description>An analyst at Berenberg investment firm believes MicroStrategy is now a safer bet compared to Coinbase due to the exchange's regulatory issues.  &lt;br /&gt;
Mark Palmer, an equity research analyst at Berenberg Capital Markets, said the US Securities and Exchange Commission will likely file an enforcement action against Coinbase as the commission increases its scrutiny of the crypto sector. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/berenberg-investment-firm-analyst-sees-microstrategy-as-safer-bet-than-coinbase-due-sec-risk.htm"&gt;Read More: Berenberg Investment Firm Analyst Sees MicroStrategy as Safer Bet than Coinbase Due to SEC Risk&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><category>Berenberg</category><category>MicroStrategy</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/berenberg-investment-firm-analyst-sees-microstrategy-as-safer-bet-than-coinbase-due-sec-risk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114189/276022/adobestock-photo-gonzo-1-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="33858"/></item><item><title>Rep. Maxine Waters Ushers In Stablecoin Bill Ahead of Thursday House Hearing</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rep-maxine-waters-ushers-stablecoin-bill-ahead-of-thursday-house-hearing.htm</link><description>Rep. Maxine Waters is ushering in a draft bill to regulate stablecoins ahead of a House hearing this week. &lt;br /&gt;
The California Democrat’s draft bill would “provide requirements for payment stablecoin issuers, research on a digital dollar, and for other purposes,” according to a committee memo for Thursday’s hearing.  &lt;br /&gt;
The bill would also require payment stablecoin issuers to be approved by the Federal Reserve or possibly a state regulator....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rep-maxine-waters-ushers-stablecoin-bill-ahead-of-thursday-house-hearing.htm"&gt;Read More: Rep. Maxine Waters Ushers In Stablecoin Bill Ahead of Thursday House Hearing&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rep-maxine-waters-ushers-stablecoin-bill-ahead-of-thursday-house-hearing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114201/276041/united-states-capitol-g4d.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="270933"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Justin Sun Accuses Huobi Founder's Brother of Illegally Profiting from Tokens – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-accuses-huobi-founders-brother-of-illegally-profiting-from-tokens-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Precocious billionaire tech and crypto entrepreneur Justin Sun just accused the brother founder of the world’s 13th largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volumes Huobi of having illegally profited from HT token sales. &lt;br /&gt;
HT is the native utility token of the Huobi exchange and its holders can receive substantial trading fee discounts....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-accuses-huobi-founders-brother-of-illegally-profiting-from-tokens-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Justin Sun Accuses Huobi Founder's Brother of Illegally Profiting from Tokens – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Huobi Global</category><category>HT</category><category>Justin Sun</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-accuses-huobi-founders-brother-of-illegally-profiting-from-tokens-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114200/276040/huobi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2148826"/></item><item><title>US Secret Service Reveals Crypto Holdings, Blockchain Fascination and NFT Collection in Reddit AMA</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-secret-service-reveals-crypto-holdings-blockchain-fascination-nft-collection-reddit-ama.htm</link><description>The US Secret Service has revealed that they are “definitely holders of crypto,” that they have a collection of non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and claimed that crypto has made it easier than before to track flows of illicit money....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-secret-service-reveals-crypto-holdings-blockchain-fascination-nft-collection-reddit-ama.htm"&gt;Read More: US Secret Service Reveals Crypto Holdings, Blockchain Fascination and NFT Collection in Reddit AMA&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Crime</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-secret-service-reveals-crypto-holdings-blockchain-fascination-nft-collection-reddit-ama.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114199/276038/vault.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="134808"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Prediction as SOL Blockchain Sees Huge Surge in New Users Following Spike in ETH Gas Fees – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-blockchain-sees-huge-surge-new-users-following-spike-eth-gas-fees-time-buy.htm</link><description>The Solana network, a layer-1 smart-contract-enabled blockchain protocol famed for its high transaction throughput and low gas fees, has seen a spike in daily users in recent weeks. &lt;br /&gt;
As per data presented by Token Terminal, the number of daily active users on the blockchain recently spiked to its highest in nearly 12 months at nearly 400,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-blockchain-sees-huge-surge-new-users-following-spike-eth-gas-fees-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Prediction as SOL Blockchain Sees Huge Surge in New Users Following Spike in ETH Gas Fees – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-blockchain-sees-huge-surge-new-users-following-spike-eth-gas-fees-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114193/276025/sol-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="668218"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Startup River Raises $35 Million in Funding Round Supported by Billionaire Peter Thiel</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-startup-river-raises-35-million-funding-round-supported-by-billionaire-peter-thiel.htm</link><description>Amid the dwindling venture capital investing in the crypto and blockchain industry, Bitcoin start-up firm, River, has secured a $35 million Series B funding.  &lt;br /&gt;
River took to Twitter to share its excitement about the development. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the announcement, a notable venture capitalist firm, Kingsway Capital, led the Series B funding round. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-startup-river-raises-35-million-funding-round-supported-by-billionaire-peter-thiel.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Startup River Raises $35 Million in Funding Round Supported by Billionaire Peter Thiel&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-startup-river-raises-35-million-funding-round-supported-by-billionaire-peter-thiel.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114186/276016/pexels-karolina-grabowska.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="141913"/></item><item><title>Elon Musk Net Worth and Crypto Holdings Revealed – Richest Man in The World?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/elon-musk-net-worth-crypto-holdings-revealed-richest-man-world.htm</link><description>Billionaire Elon Musk is widely regarded as one of the world’s most successful entrepreneurs and businessmen in the world.  &lt;br /&gt;
He is the founder and CEO of SpaceX, angel investor and CEO of Tesla, owner and CEO of Twitter, founder of The Boring Company and co-founder of Neuralink and OpenAI....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/elon-musk-net-worth-crypto-holdings-revealed-richest-man-world.htm"&gt;Read More: Elon Musk Net Worth and Crypto Holdings Revealed – Richest Man in The World?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>People In Crypto</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Net Worth</category><category>Tesla</category><category>SpaceX</category><category>Twitter</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/elon-musk-net-worth-crypto-holdings-revealed-richest-man-world.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/107675/275994/screenshot-2023-05-17-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="285836"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Ripple Acquires Metaco, Tether to Buy BTC Monthly Using Realized Profits, WazirX Claims Binance Controls WRX</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ripple-acquires-metaco-tether-to-buy-btc-monthly-using-realized-profits-wazirx-claims-binance-controls-wrx.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ripple-acquires-metaco-tether-to-buy-btc-monthly-using-realized-profits-wazirx-claims-binance-controls-wrx.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Ripple Acquires Metaco, Tether to Buy BTC Monthly Using Realized Profits, WazirX Claims Binance Controls WRX&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>China</category><category>NFT</category><category>USA</category><category>France</category><category>Europe</category><category>Investment</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Latin America</category><category>Asia</category><category>Axie Infinity</category><category>Apple</category><category>WazirX</category><category>Binance</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Staking</category><category>USDC</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Compound</category><category>Arbitrum</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Tether</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ripple-acquires-metaco-tether-to-buy-btc-monthly-using-realized-profits-wazirx-claims-binance-controls-wrx.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114144/275986/dbb88c2476-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="131868"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Shiba Inu? SHIB Price Keeps Falling But SpongeBob is Rallying Higher – 100x Potential in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-shib-price-keeps-falling-but-spongebob-rallying-higher-100x-potential-2023.htm</link><description>The SHIB Army is in disarray after 28 days of downside price action for the beloved SHIB token. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite the explosive 2023 meme coin season, SHIB has been sidelined by lucrative returns from prominent moon shots like Pepe coin and Wojak. &lt;br /&gt;
Currently trading at $0.0000086 (a 24-hour change of -1.25%), SHIB bulls have worked to form a strong consolidation foothold above lower trendline support....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-shib-price-keeps-falling-but-spongebob-rallying-higher-100x-potential-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Shiba Inu? SHIB Price Keeps Falling But SpongeBob is Rallying Higher – 100x Potential in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-shib-price-keeps-falling-but-spongebob-rallying-higher-100x-potential-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114171/276007/americana-gc26b413a3-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="224483"/></item><item><title>VC Funding Boost for Web3 Marketplace Following Success with Rihanna's Music Rights</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/vc-funding-boost-for-web3-marketplace-following-success-with-rihannas-music-rights.htm</link><description>The advent of tokenized music assets and NFTs allowed investors to acquire rights to their favorite music, a feat that was nearly impossible a few years back.  &lt;br /&gt;
This use case has increased investor interest in Web3 and blockchain technology recently. &lt;br /&gt;
In a new development, Web3 marketplace AnotherBlock has secured a new round of VC funding after successfully selling Rihanna's music rights on the platform. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/vc-funding-boost-for-web3-marketplace-following-success-with-rihannas-music-rights.htm"&gt;Read More: VC Funding Boost for Web3 Marketplace Following Success with Rihanna's Music Rights&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/vc-funding-boost-for-web3-marketplace-following-success-with-rihannas-music-rights.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114182/276004/pexels-pixabay-534229.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="257761"/></item><item><title>Tether Plans 15% of Its Net Profits Into Bitcoin in Move of Confidence</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-plans-15-of-its-net-profits-into-bitcoin-move-of-confidence.htm</link><description>Tether, the world’s largest stablecoin issuer by market capitalization, said it is planning to invest 15 percent of its net profits into bitcoin to strengthen its reserves.  &lt;br /&gt;
Tether said it expects the move to “strengthen and diversify” its reserves of its $1 pegged stablecoin, in a statement released on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-plans-15-of-its-net-profits-into-bitcoin-move-of-confidence.htm"&gt;Read More: Tether Plans 15% of Its Net Profits Into Bitcoin in Move of Confidence&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Tether</category><category>Legislation</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-plans-15-of-its-net-profits-into-bitcoin-move-of-confidence.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114178/276001/pexels-alesia-kozik-6765371.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="139508"/></item><item><title>Serial Scammer Uses Advanced Laundering Techniques to Clean Stolen Crypto Worth $15 Million – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/serial-scammer-uses-advanced-laundering-techniques-clean-stolen-crypto-worth-15-million-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>A scammer or group of scammers have used a fake phishing version of the crypto exchange HitBTC’s website to steal some $15 million worth of crypto. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a Twitter thread from crypto compliance firm MistTrack, the phishing website that was used looked almost identical to HitBTC’s real website, except for a minor difference in the URL, which was hitbt2c[.]lol instead of hitbtc[.]com....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/serial-scammer-uses-advanced-laundering-techniques-clean-stolen-crypto-worth-15-million-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Serial Scammer Uses Advanced Laundering Techniques to Clean Stolen Crypto Worth $15 Million – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Scam</category><category>HitBTC</category><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/serial-scammer-uses-advanced-laundering-techniques-clean-stolen-crypto-worth-15-million-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114163/275989/adobestock-568027794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="584960"/></item></channel></rss>
