<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:36:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Finblox Token (FBX) Listed on Major Exchanges After a Sold out Launchpad</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/finblox-token-fbx-listed-on-major-exchanges-after-a-sold-out-launchpad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251451</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Finblox, a leading crypto superapp backed and supported by behemoths like Dragonfly and Sequoia, is delighted to announce the remarkable success of its recent token launch, defying current market conditions and generating a trading volume exceeding 2 million USD in the first 12 trading hours. Preparation for the ICO [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>Finblox, a leading crypto superapp backed and supported by behemoths like Dragonfly and Sequoia, is delighted to announce the remarkable success of its recent token launch, defying current market conditions and generating a trading volume exceeding 2 million USD in the first 12 trading hours.</p>
<h2>Preparation for the ICO</h2>
<p>Leading up to the listing, Finblox witnessed impressive participation from the crypto community across various partner launchpads, with more than 3,000 unique addresses who purchased FBX during the pre-sale period from PoolZ, Decubate, Spores, and from Finblox’s own launchpad: FinLaunch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251455" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3.jpg" alt="finblox3" width="624" height="416" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>As part of its comprehensive community strategy, Finblox conducted a series of compelling online and offline activities, including social media campaigns, learn-and-earn activities, and interactive ask-me-anything sessions.</p>
<p>The culmination of these efforts took shape in the form of highly successful offline meetups called Finblox Summit held in Manila, Philippines, and Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam last May 8 and 16, respectively, which brought together power users, partners, and media from the local communities.</p>
<p>FBX has further achieved a significant milestone by being listed on major exchanges, including Gate.io, MEXC Global, BTSE, starting May 18, 2023. The token&#8217;s all-time high during the ICO peaked at an astounding 500% above the listing price, demonstrating the market&#8217;s strong support for Finblox despite the volatility.</p>
<h2>Building a Sustainable Roadmap</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251456" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2.jpg" alt="Finblox2" width="624" height="351" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>To further fortify the utility of Finblox Tokens, the superapp has <a href="https://help.finblox.com/en/articles/7912800-party-to-30-30-apy-for-your-finblox-tokens?utm_source=hs_email&amp;&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;&amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz--MNmsh5keOgC-gZbc-IbWU2ZAdbXdxLujQ8zhXo_oyPfwXQbAK4pVZghFGQjzpbcKmP-7A" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">announced</a> a promotion of 30% APY for users who deposit their fresh FBX tokens into their Finblox Wallets between May 18 and July 18, 2023. This limited-time offer allows token holders to actively engage in the Finblox ecosystem while earning substantial rewards.</p>
<p>Finblox invites all token holders to take advantage of this exclusive offer by transferring their Finblox Tokens to their Finblox Wallets and embarking on a journey of earning rewards. By participating in this initiative, users become a part of the Finblox community while maximizing their potential within the platform.</p>
<p>Finblox has initiated a token burn in a strategic move to ensure fair value of the remaining tokens in circulation. As of May 19, 2023, 437 million tokens, valued at $3.07 million, representing 4.37% of the total supply, have been burnt.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our users can now be a part of the growth and development of the Finblox ecosystem. With the roadmap ahead, we invite the community to join us in the journey of democratising finance with Web3”, said Peter Hoang, CEO and Founder of Finblox.</p></blockquote>
<p>Users are encouraged to check out Finblox’s <a href="https://help.finblox.com/en/articles/7919428-introducing-the-1st-fbx-burn-event" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">blog</a> to learn more about the token-burning activity. For more information on how you can accumulate more FBX tokens through the promotion, check out Finblox’s article <a href="https://help.finblox.com/en/articles/7912800-party-to-30-30-apy-for-your-finblox-tokens" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<h2>About Finblox</h2>
<p>Finblox is a crypto superapp backed by top-tier VCs like Sequoia Capital, Dragonfly, and Saison Capital. Users can earn up to 100x rewards by participating in the ecosystem of products, including trading, staking, and AI games.</p>
<p>Finblox Token (FBX) is the utility token native to the Finblox ecosystem. With FBX, users can enjoy perks that can be used across our entire suite of products &#8211; and shape the future direction of the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/finblox-token-fbx-listed-on-major-exchanges-after-a-sold-out-launchpad/" rel="nofollow">Finblox Token (FBX) Listed on Major Exchanges After a Sold out Launchpad</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hyperspace and Mysten Labs Partner to Bring Web3 Gaming and NFT Trading to Sui Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/hyperspace-and-mysten-labs-partner-to-bring-web3-gaming-and-nft-trading-to-sui-blockchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251419</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Press_Release_3_1684451756BsEtlTcN9w.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Press_Release_3_1684451756BsEtlTcN9w.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, United States, May 19th, 2023] Hyperspace, the pioneering NFT marketplace, and launchpad, today announced a partnership with Mysten Labs, a web3 infrastructure company and original contributor to Sui, a Layer 1 blockchain, to help bring Hyperspace onto the protocol. As one of the leading open web marketplaces for NFTs, Hyperspace [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, United States, May 19th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://hyperspace.xyz" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Hyperspace</a>, the pioneering NFT marketplace, and launchpad, today announced a partnership with <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fmystenlabs.com%2F&amp;esheet=53325938&amp;newsitemid=20230214005897&amp;lan=en-US&amp;anchor=Mysten+Labs&amp;index=2&amp;md5=c13f15c66585ebc2ac0ed7d270e6defe" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Mysten Labs</a>, a web3 infrastructure company and original contributor to <a href="https://sui.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Sui</a>, a Layer 1 blockchain, to help bring Hyperspace onto the protocol.</p>
<p>As one of the leading open web marketplaces for NFTs, Hyperspace drives openness and composability in web3 through its full suite of user-friendly NFT products, allowing users to discover, trade and mint NFTs and enjoy new, immersive web3 games. Through this strategic partnership with Mysten Labs and expansion onto the Sui blockchain, Hyperspace is set to revolutionize the world of web3 gaming and NFT trading, enabling unparalleled experiences for users.</p>
<p>At the core of this new capability is Sui’s robust horizontal scalability and object-based model, which enables an easy-to-use developer experience and allows for efficient handling of dynamic NFTs. This breakthrough feature will serve as a catalyst for the creation of immersive web3 games, in which players can truly own and interact with their in-game assets like never before.</p>
<p>While Hyperspace originally launched on the Solana blockchain, and remains unwaveringly committed to supporting Solana, expanding onto Sui will enable the company to broaden its reach and empower even more developers and creators across the web3 ecosystem. Today, Hyperspace also provides NFT indexing and marketplace infrastructure to hundreds of developers on Solana and plans to provide similar services and infrastructure on Sui in an easy-to-use SDK for developers.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to partner with the talented Mysten Labs team,&#8221; said Kamil Mafoud, Co-founder at Hyperspace. &#8220;This collaboration represents a significant milestone in our journey towards reshaping the web3 landscape. By harnessing the power of Sui&#8217;s horizontally scalable infrastructure, we can unlock the true potential of dynamic NFTs, enabling unparalleled experiences for gamers, creators and enthusiasts. We want to continue pushing the boundaries of what is achievable in NFT trading and utilization.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>“The integration of Hyperspace on Sui will unlock a new era of gaming experiences, characterized by unprecedented interactivity and player-driven economies,” said Evan Cheng, co-founder and Chief Executive Officer of Mysten Labs. “Hyperspace recognizes the value of building for the future of NFT trading and utilization, and we are excited that the team will be leveraging the unique technology that Sui provides for seamless developer and user experiences and rapid transaction speeds. The expansion onto Sui is a testament to Hyperspace&#8217;s dedication to exploring innovative solutions for NFT enthusiasts, and we can’t wait to support them as they continue to create new opportunities for NFT developers and collectors.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>“A truly immersive decentralized platform for managing digital assets and gaming where the user experience is on par with or exceeds those in traditional venues has the potential to bring the benefits of web3 to an entirely new, far broader set of users,” said Greg Siourounis, Managing Director of the Sui Foundation. “We are truly excited to see the Hyperspace team, which has already accomplished so much, joining the Sui community and leveraging Sui’s groundbreaking, highly scalable and performant technology to build the next level experience for gamers and NFT collectors.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As Hyperspace embraces Sui and its game-changing capabilities, the team reaffirms its dedication to fostering innovation and revolutionizing the NFT space. By expanding its reach and continuously pushing the boundaries of what is possible, Hyperspace is leading the charge in creating a vibrant and immersive web3 gaming future, providing users with unparalleled opportunities for engagement and ownership.</p>
<h2>About Hyperspace</h2>
<p>Hyperspace is a multi-chain NFT marketplace, launchpad and developer platform dedicated to driving the mass adoption of digital assets. It is backed by Dragonfly, Pantera, Coinbase Ventures, and other notable funds. Hyperspace provides an intuitive and seamless platform for creators, developers, collectors, and gamers to trade and interact with NFTs. With a strong focus on innovation and user experience, Hyperspace is committed to shaping the future of NFT trading and utilization. Learn more: https://sui.hyperspace.xyz/ and https://hyperspace.xyz</p>
<h2>About Mysten Labs</h2>
<p>Mysten Labs is a team of leading distributed systems, programming languages, and cryptography experts whose founders were senior executives of Meta’s Novi Research and include lead architects of the Diem blockchain and Move programming language. The mission of Mysten Labs is to create foundational infrastructure for web3. Learn more: https://mystenlabs.com</p>
<h2>About Sui</h2>
<p>Sui is a first-of-its-kind Layer 1 blockchain and smart contract platform designed from the bottom up to make digital asset ownership fast, private, secure, and accessible to everyone. Its object-centric model, based on the Move programming language, enables parallel execution, sub-second finality, and rich on-chain assets. With horizontally scalable processing and storage, Sui supports a wide range of applications with unrivaled speed at a low cost. Sui is a step-function advancement in blockchain and a platform on which creators and developers can build amazing, user-friendly experiences. Learn more: https://sui.io</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hyperspace-and-mysten-labs-partner-to-bring-web3-gaming-and-nft-trading-to-sui-blockchain/" rel="nofollow">Hyperspace and Mysten Labs Partner to Bring Web3 Gaming and NFT Trading to Sui Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is XRP 9% Up Weekly and Will Ripple&#8217;s Surge Continue?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-xrp-9-up-weekly-and-will-ripples-surge-continue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251339</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Ripple.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Ripple.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple is this week's market frontrunner. Here are a couple of possible reasons why. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple (XRP) is this week&#8217;s frontrunner as the rest of the market continues to either consolidate or trade in a ruthless chop. The cryptocurrency has defied expectations and is trending upwards with little signs of slowing down.</p>
<p>Here are a few possible reasons why and whether this rally could go any further.</p>
<h2>Case Against SEC Tilts in Ripple&#8217;s Favor</h2>
<p>It seems that the major reason for the increase in XRP&#8217;s price is that investors seem to be leaning bullish on Ripple winning the case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<p>Recall that the SEC filed a lawsuit alleging that Ripple conducted an unregistered sale of securities, essentially claiming that XRP is a security.</p>
<p>This week, Judge Analisa Torres <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-judge-denies-the-sealing-of-hinmans-speech-once-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">denied</a> the Commission&#8217;s request to seal documents pertaining to a speech by Bill Hinman &#8211; the director of the agency&#8217;s corporate finance division. This is the third time this specific request has been denied, so the question is &#8211; why is it so important for the SEC to seal these records? Well, it&#8217;s pretty straightforward.</p>
<p>William Hinman is a former director of the SEC&#8217;s Division of Corporation Finance. The speech in question refers to when he indicated that the agency didn&#8217;t consider ETH security at the time, and Ripple layers have fought to find out more about how he came to that conclusion. They hope it could impact XRP&#8217;s own classification.</p>
<p>Judge Torres says the documents should be accessible based on the common law principle of public access to judicial documents:</p>
<blockquote><p>Documents are considered &#8220;judicial documents&#8221; if they are &#8220;relevant to the performance of the judicial function and useful in the judicial process. [&#8230;] The relevance of a specific document does not depend on which way the court ultimately rules or whether the document ultimately in fact influences the court’s decision. Rather, what is important is whether a document “would reasonably have the tendency to influence a district court’s ruling on a motion.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>$250M Metaco Deal Finalized</h2>
<p>Another positive development for Ripple, and thereby &#8211; XRP, is that the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-enters-a-250-million-deal-to-acquire-metaco/" data-wpel-link="internal">entered</a> into a $250 million deal to acquire Metaco. The latter is a cryptocurrency custody provider based in Switzerland.</p>
<p>The deal aims to expand Ripple&#8217;s position in the world of crypto by also expanding its services toward crypto custody.</p>
<p>Speaking on the deal, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Metaco is a proven leader in institutional digital asset custody with an exceptional executive bench and a truly unmatched customer track record. Through the strength of our balance sheet and financial position, Ripple will continue pressing our advantage in the areas critical to crypto infrastructure. Bringing on Metaco is monumental for our growing product suite and expanding global footprint.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The above can finally explain XRP&#8217;s price surge in the past few days, but the question is &#8211; will it continue? This is a question that only time can answer, but if the positive developments surrounding the case against the SEC continue, then this might also have a somewhat positive impact on the price. After all, crypto is known for being news-driven, where announcements, be it good or bad, tend to influence the price.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-xrp-9-up-weekly-and-will-ripples-surge-continue/" rel="nofollow">Why is XRP 9% Up Weekly and Will Ripple&#8217;s Surge Continue?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis May-19: ETH, XRP, ADA, OP, and PEPE</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-19-eth-xrp-ada-op-and-pepe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimism (OP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251349</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/friday_post_1205231-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/friday_post_1205231-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Optimism, and Pepe. Ethereum (ETH) The market leaders turned flat this past week, and ETH booked a modest 2.6% price increase. The volatility has remained low, and the price continues to sit below the key resistance at $1,820. The PA and momentum indicators show [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Optimism, and Pepe.</p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>The market leaders turned flat this past week, and ETH booked a modest 2.6% price increase. The volatility has remained low, and the price continues to sit below the key resistance at $1,820.</p>
<p>The PA and momentum indicators show indecision from market participants. With decreasing volume, both bulls and bears seem absent from the market. There is no conviction on either side, and the price failed to move in a decisive manner. The current support is $1,660.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, it seems that this consolidation under the key resistance could continue. It seems unlikely that sellers will attempt to test the key support level since the market is waiting for a trigger to bring back volatility.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251355" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251355" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251355" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43.png" alt="ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43" width="1813" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43-768x365.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-19_16-18-43-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251355" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>XRP rallied by 8.5% in the past week, and the price has now arrived at the 47 cents resistance. This impressive rally is atypical, considering that ETH and BTC failed to rally this week.</p>
<p>Thanks to this renewed interest from buyers, the momentum indicators for this cryptocurrency have turned bullish. With decent volume on the way up and five consecutive daily candles closing in green, bulls dominate at this time.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, sellers may make a stand at the key resistance and stop this uptrend, at least for a while. If a pullback happens, then XRP has good support at 44 cents which could be tested before the next leg up.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251354" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251354" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251354" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19" width="1813" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19-1024x454.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-19-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251354" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>This past week, ADA failed to break above the key resistance at 38 cents but still managed to book a modest 2.8% price increase. At the time of this post, the price appears to be compressing between 36 and 38 cents, and a decisive move could happen soon.</p>
<p>The most significant level of support is found at 34 cents. It is unlikely for this level to be tested, considering that buyers appeared eager to buy this cryptocurrency whenever it had a pullback. Despite this, bulls were unable to break the key resistance to date.</p>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking ahead</span></span>, Cardano could be positioning for a major breakout similar to XRP, which could see the 38 cents resistance quickly falls but it remains to be seen if this would be the case.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251353" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251353" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251353" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44" width="1813" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44-1024x454.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-19_16-19-44-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251353" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Optimism (OP)</span></p>
<p>Optimism had a volatile week and managed to book a price increase of almost 10%, which took it to the key resistance at $1.8. This performance came after bulls found good support at $1.6.</p>
<p>Since touching the key resistance, the price has entered into a pullback. This could see OP retest the key support if buyers are not eager to return soon. Nevertheless, this price action has put a stop to a major downtrend that started in April.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Optimism seems well-positioned to attempt a breakout above $1.8 and seek a higher valuation. If successful, then the next major target will be found at $2, which is also a key psychological level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251352" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251352" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251352" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06.png" alt="OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06" width="1813" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06-768x365.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OPUSDT_2023-05-19_16-22-06-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251352" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Pepe (PEPE) </span></p>
<p>After finding good support at $0.0000011, PEPE managed to rally hard in a short amount of time and booked a 24% price increase compared to last Friday. However, the price is now correcting, and buyers are showing a lack of interest.</p>
<p>The momentum on the 4-hour timeframe appears bearish at the time of this post, with the MACD having completed a bearish cross. This indicates that the price may continue to fall in the short term until buyers return.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, PEPE continues to draw a lot of volatility not seen in many altcoins. This attracts traders that are likely to become active whenever the price reaches a critical level, like the key support. The current resistance is at $0.0000018.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251351" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251351" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251351" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12" width="1813" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12-768x365.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-19_16-23-12-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251351" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-19-eth-xrp-ada-op-and-pepe/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis May-19: ETH, XRP, ADA, OP, and PEPE</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traders Are Backing These Crypto Presales to Outperform This Year</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/traders-are-backing-these-crypto-presales-to-outperform-this-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251379</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Traders-Backing-CryptoPotato-2.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Traders-Backing-CryptoPotato-2.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With the ever-evolving crypto market capturing the attention of global investors, a remarkable trend has emerged in recent times: crypto presales. These exclusive offerings, often shrouded in anticipation, have garnered significant traction as traders seek the potential to generate market-beating returns. This article delves into the captivating realm of crypto presales, shedding light on five [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the ever-evolving crypto market capturing the attention of global investors, a remarkable trend has emerged in recent times: crypto presales.</p>
<p>These exclusive offerings, often shrouded in anticipation, have garnered significant traction as traders seek the potential to generate market-beating returns.</p>
<p>This article delves into the captivating realm of crypto presales, shedding light on five eagerly-awaited coins poised to soar when they debut on major exchanges in the coming months.</p>
<h2>AiDoge (AI) – Revolutionizing the Meme Coin Niche Using the Power of AI, Over $9m Raised</h2>
<p>AiDoge breaks new ground as it uniquely fuses the viral appeal of memes with the rapidly expanding sphere of artificial intelligence</p>
<p>Using AiDoge&#8217;s &#8220;meme generator,&#8221; users can instantly create memes without having to come up with a caption or have any prior photo-editing experience – making it easy to upload hilarious images to sites like Reddit and Twitter.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251382" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1.png" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="204" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1-300x102.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-1-50x17.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Users can also earn AI, AiDoge&#8217;s native token, by posting their memes on the &#8220;public wall.&#8221; The memes that garner the most votes each month will earn their creators additional AI tokens.</p>
<p>AI has been attracting attention from the broader crypto community – leading to over $9.1 million being raised through the ongoing presale phase.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251383" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1.png" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="156" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1-300x78.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-1-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>AiDoge’s remarkable early success has caught the eye of several prominent crypto influencers. My Financial Friend, who boasts over 236,000 subscribers on YouTube, recently released a<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pp9j_aKKfAU&amp;ab_channel=MyFinancialFriend" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> video</a> speculating that AiDoge could be &#8220;the new king of meme coins.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ultimately, AiDoge’s blend of memes and AI technology, along with its recognition from prominent crypto influencers, positions it as a promising contender in the presale market.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>yPredict (YPRED) – Pioneering Crypto Analytics Platform with AI Integration</h2>
<p>Another crypto presale that is gaining traction is yPredict. yPredict ambitiously positions itself as the future of AI-driven crypto analytics, creating a comprehensive &#8216;all-in-one&#8217; ecosystem catering to traders, developers, quants, and analysts.</p>
<p>Using yPredict, individuals can gain access to state-of-the-art predictive models that provide an edge in the market. The yPredict platform is built on the Polygon network, meaning it’s fully decentralized and part of the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251384" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1.png" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="421" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1-300x210.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-1-50x35.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>yPredict&#8217;s suite of features includes real-time sentiment analytics, advanced technical indicators, automatic pattern recognition tools, and AI-powered price forecasts.</p>
<p>yPredict users can even &#8220;subscribe&#8221; to financial models developed by industry-leading AI and machine learning (ML) experts.</p>
<p>Given the usefulness of these features, yPredict’s presale has been an instant success, raising over $1.2 million in funding thus far.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251385" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1.png" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="161" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1-300x80.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture4-1-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Crypto YouTuber Michael Wrubel, who has over 310,000 subscribers, highlighted in a recent<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KwoCQl5h4qE&amp;ab_channel=MichaelWrubel" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> video</a> that he’s incredibly bullish on yPredict – a sentiment that has ignited considerable excitement within the investment community.</p>
<p>To sum up, the project looks primed and ready to blast off once listed on centralized exchanges (CEXs) as the demand for objective crypto analytics becomes more significant than ever.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Ecoterra (ECOTERRA) – New Blockchain Project Championing Sustainability</h2>
<p>Harnessing the power of the blockchain, Ecoterra sets a new standard by rewarding eco-friendly behaviors and taking a proactive stance towards environmental preservation.</p>
<p>The ecosystem’s main feature is its Recycle2Earn app that rewards users with ECOTERRA, the project’s native token, whenever they recycle used materials. Ecoterra also offers a marketplace for recycled materials and carbon offsets, providing an easy-to-use solution for sustainability-focused companies.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251386" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5.png" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="267" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture5-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Ecoterra even has a trackable &#8220;Impact Profile,&#8221; which allows individuals and businesses to easily track their positive environmental actions and practices.</p>
<p>Like the projects noted above, Ecoterra has captured the market’s attention through its presale phase, raising over $3.9 million – and counting.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251387" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6.png" alt="Picture6" width="602" height="160" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-300x80.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Crypto influencer Jacob Bury even suggested in his<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lcZZg3Z2O7A&amp;pp=ygUPZWNvdGVycmEgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> video analysis</a> of the project that the ECOTERRA token could potentially 10x in value once it’s listed on CEXs in Q3 2023.</p>
<p>Ultimately, by incentivizing recycling and providing a transparent marketplace for used materials and carbon offsets, Ecoterra is positioning itself as one of the go-to crypto projects for those looking to make an impact in the fight against climate change.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>DeeLance (DLANCE) – Ethereum-Based Platform Empowering Freelancers Through Decentralization</h2>
<p>DeeLance is another presale crypto project making waves due to its innovative approach to freelancing and recruitment.</p>
<p>This decentralized platform revolutionizes how freelancers connect with potential clients by leveraging the incredible power of blockchain technology.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251388" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7.png" alt="Picture7" width="602" height="384" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7-300x191.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>DeeLance’s ecosystem includes a freelancing platform, a custom-built metaverse for all users, and even an NFT marketplace where freelancers can show off their work.</p>
<p>One standout feature of DeeLance is its low fees; freelancers pay only a 2% commission on their jobs, a figure significantly below the industry average.</p>
<p>In addition, all payments are settled using DLANCE, DeeLance’s native token, which eradicates payment disputes and ensures a fair and transparent environment for all parties.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture10.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251389" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture10.png" alt="Picture10" width="602" height="161" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture10.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture10-300x80.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture10-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Popular finance YouTuber Crypto Gains, who has over 105,000 subscribers, released a<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-9i_pUVuVxc&amp;ab_channel=CryptoGains" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> video breakdown</a> of the DeeLance project. He speculated that the DLANCE token could provide 100x returns for those who invest through the presale.</p>
<p>Given its unique blend of services and its commitment to decentralization, there’s certainly scope for this to happen – making it one to watch in the blockchain space.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_3bcb6414.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit DeeLance Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Launchpad XYZ (LPX) – Web3-Powered Ecosystem Streamlining the Crypto &amp; NFT Investing Process</h2>
<p>Launchpad XYZ is a comprehensive portal designed to equip users with the tools they need to thrive in the Web3 environment.</p>
<p>The Launchpad XYZ ecosystem offers a range of services, including trading insights, an NFT marketplace, and a metaverse experience library, all aimed at streamlining the investment experience for market participants.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture8.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251390" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture8.png" alt="Picture8" width="602" height="336" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture8.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture8-300x167.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture8-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ will also have a super-fast trading terminal, allowing investors to execute trades at the optimal time – ideal for those interested in day trading or scalping.</p>
<p>Users will even be able to benefit from in-depth analytics, news, and market sentiment indicators – helping them identify which projects could be the “next big thing” in the digital assets marketplace.</p>
<p>This holistic approach has got investors excited, with Launchpad XYZ’s presale raising over $500,000 ahead of the CEX listings planned for the coming months.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture9.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251391" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture9.png" alt="Picture9" width="602" height="159" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture9.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture9-300x79.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture9-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Social media trendsetter Crypto ZEUS also had his say on Launchpad XYZ’s prospects, highlighting in a<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vFXGO033v7s&amp;ab_channel=CryptoZEUS" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> YouTube video</a> that LPX, the project’s native token, could “get big” soon.</p>
<p>This statement will be music to the ears of early investors, who have put themselves in line to make significant returns if Crypto ZEUS&#8217; estimations turn out to be true.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_596f215c.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/traders-are-backing-these-crypto-presales-to-outperform-this-year/" rel="nofollow">Traders Are Backing These Crypto Presales to Outperform This Year</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT Hits Apple&#8217;s App Store in US But What About Android Users?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/openais-chatgpt-hits-apples-app-store-in-us-but-what-about-android-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251333</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ChatGPT_Apple.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ChatGPT_Apple.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[OpenAI also provided more details concerning Android users. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American artificial intelligence research laboratory OpenAI announced the launch of an iOS app for ChatGPT. Similar to the original web model of the chatbot that was released around six months ago, the app is also a free-to-use version that is built on GPT-3.5.</p>
<p>The existing subscribers of ChatGPT Plus will be able to have exclusive access to GPT-4&#8217;s capabilities, early access to features as well faster response times on iOS.</p>
<h2>ChatGPT on App Store</h2>
<p>OpenAI revealed in a <a href="https://openai.com/blog/introducing-the-chatgpt-app-for-ios" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a> that the new mobile app will sync the user history of chats with its bot across devices. It also features voice input, supported by the company&#8217;s open-source speech recognition model Whisper.</p>
<p>At the launch, the app will be available only in the US and will expand to other countries &#8220;in the coming weeks.&#8221; Next up in its roadmap for OpenAI is Android device expansion.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the ChatGPT app for iOS, we’re taking another step towards our mission by transforming state-of-the-art research into useful tools that empower people, while continuously making them more accessible.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Although the company failed to provide a precise date, it said Android users will be next in line.</p>
<h2>Rise to Prominence</h2>
<p>While OpenAI did not hint at a new mobile incarnation, the move is not surprising since ChatGPT&#8217;s popularity has skyrocketed in a very short span of time. The popular artificial intelligence chatbot <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/feb/02/chatgpt-100-million-users-open-ai-fastest-growing-app" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">attracted</a> 100 million users just two months after launching. In January, it had nearly 590 million visits.</p>
<p>OpenAI, which is a private company backed by Microsoft, made it available to the public for free last November, just 5 days after which ChatGPT acquired a million users. To put things into perspective, it took Instagram nearly 2.5 months to reach a million downloads. Whereas popular streaming service Netflix had to wait more than 3 years to reach one million users.</p>
<p>Recently, ChatGPT also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-8-things-that-will-happen-to-crypto-by-2033/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">came up</a> with several scenarios on what could happen in the digital asset space within the next decade.</p>
<p>The roaring success of ChatGPT has ignited a frantic rush to release new AI products to market. This hysteria has consumed some of the biggest tech behemoths and startups as they fight for space in the burgeoning sector.</p>
<p>Google, for one, is working on its own AI chatbot, Bard, which has so far failed to woo investors after giving an <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-ai-chatbot-bard-offers-inaccurate-information-company-ad-2023-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">incorrect</a> answer in a promotional video. Chinese tech giant Baidu has also doubled down on plans to integrate its AI chatbot Ernie into its search engine services this year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/openais-chatgpt-hits-apples-app-store-in-us-but-what-about-android-users/" rel="nofollow">OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT Hits Apple&#8217;s App Store in US But What About Android Users?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Defies Market Sentiment With 3% Increase, BTC Drops Below $27K (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-defies-market-sentiment-with-3-increase-btc-drops-below-27k-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251337</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Ripple.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Ripple.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[XRP is the only larger-cap alt in the green today. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin dropped by over a grand in the past 24 hours and registered its lowest price tag in about a week earlier today.</p>
<p>The altcoins are also slightly in the red now, with LDO dumping the most (over 6%).</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Slips Under $27K</h2>
<p>Last week&#8217;s unfavorable market conditions culminated on Friday when BTC slumped to a two-month low at $25,800. However, the asset bounced off during the weekend, and spent most of it at around $27,000.</p>
<p>Monday began on a more positive note as BTC jumped to $27,600. However, it failed there and quickly lost all daily gains. Another <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-pushes-past-27k-render-rndr-explodes-20-daily-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">leg up came</a> on Wednesday, but the bears intercepted the move once again, and BTC was unable to challenge $27,500.</p>
<p>The subsequent rejection was a lot more violent than the previous one. It took bitcoin south by a grand, and it plummeted to a weekly low of $26,400. Despite regaining several hundred dollars since then, bitcoin still trades under $27,000 as it&#8217;s 2% down on the day.</p>
<p>As a result, its market capitalization has slumped back down to $520 billion, while its dominance over the altcoins sits tight at 46.3%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251340" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251340" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251340" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-18-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251340" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>XRP Defies Market Sentiment</h2>
<p>Most of the altcoins have also followed suit with minor daily declines. Ethereum, for one, has retraced by around 1% and is close to breaking below $1,800 once again. Binance Coin is back below $310 after a similar daily decline.</p>
<p>Cardano, Solana, Litecoin, Polkadot, Shiba Inu, and Avalanche have produced drops of around 1-2%. More daily losses come from the likes of Chainlink, ATOM, and TONCOIN &#8211; all of which are down by around 3%.</p>
<p>Lido DAO&#8217;s native token has dropped the most from the larger-cap alts with a 6% nosedive. Yet, LDO still trades above $2.1.</p>
<p>Ripple is the only top 10 alt with a minor daily increase. XRP, perhaps fueled by the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-judge-denies-the-sealing-of-hinmans-speech-once-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">positive developments</a> around the blockchain company&#8217;s legal case against the SEC, is up by around 3% and trades above $0.45.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap erased yesterday&#8217;s gains and is down to $1.120 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251341" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251341" style="width: 1880px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251341" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4.png" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1880" height="881" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4.png 1880w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-300x141.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-1024x480.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-768x360.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-1536x720.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1880px) 100vw, 1880px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251341" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-defies-market-sentiment-with-3-increase-btc-drops-below-27k-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">XRP Defies Market Sentiment With 3% Increase, BTC Drops Below $27K (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Launches Zero-Fee Trading, But There Are Catches</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launches-zero-fee-trading-but-there-are-catches/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 06:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251322</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[America’s largest crypto exchange is trying to increase its customer base with the lure of zero-fee trading but all is not what it seems.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On May 18, the company announced upgrades to Coinbase One, a membership account that offers zero trading fees, boosted staking rewards, and priority support.</p>
<p>However, the catch is that users will have to stump up $30 a month for the privilege.</p>
<p>Coinbase has often been criticized for having some of the highest trading fees in the industry. It makes the lion’s share of its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-posts-79m-net-loss-but-beats-expectations/" data-wpel-link="internal">profits</a> from these often extortionate fees, so the model obviously works.</p>
<p>Paying a monthly fee to eliminate these fees would only be of benefit to whales and heavy traders. Furthermore, those that do trade a lot are unlikely to trade on Coinbase and would favor a decentralized exchange (DEX) where the fees are a fraction.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">2/ The best of Coinbase just got <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />better<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Unlock zero trading fees, a dedicated support team, boosted staking rewards, and exclusive benefits from partners with Coinbase One — all for $29.99/month.</p>
<p>Claim your 30-day free trial → <a href="https://t.co/agCecP7lsp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/agCecP7lsp</a></p>
<p>— Coinbase <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6e1.png" alt="🛡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@coinbase) <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase/status/1659230867963650048?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Coinbase One Catches</h2>
<p>Coinbase is offering a 30-day free trial for its new service, which includes priority support. Aside from its hefty fees, the firm has also been heavily criticized for its lack of customer support.</p>
<p>It appears that Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-decentralization-claim-draws-fury-from-its-customers/" data-wpel-link="internal">customers</a> now have to pay to get a timely response through support channels. Members will also be able to receive support with crypto tax filing, it <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/new-updates-to-coinbase-one-zero-trading-fees-boosted-staking-rewards-and" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">added</a>.</p>
<p>The firm stated it was expanding access to Coinbase One in the United Kingdom, Germany, and Ireland in addition to the United States.</p>
<p>Moreover, the firm is offering perks with partners, including Messari, CoinTracker, and Lemonade.</p>
<p>Coinbase already offers premium accounts and stated that the zero trading fee offer does not apply to Advanced Trade, Coinbase Pro, or Coinbase Prime.</p>
<p>The crypto community&#8217;s reaction was mixed with a fair bit of skepticism over the service. “Nebraskangooner” said to his 300,000 followers:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Your support team told me to cancel my membership because the zero trading fees is misleading and only for up to $10,000 worth of trading a month and you still take advantage of people with slippage on basic trading anyway.”</p></blockquote>
<p>COIN shares slipped 1.28% on the day in a fall to $60.35 in after-hours trading.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Crypto markets dropped 1.5% on the day, with total capitalization falling to $1.16 trillion.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin</a> lost 2% in a fall to $26,782, while <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum</a> dipped 1.3% to just below $1,800 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Markets have remained sideways for the past couple of months and are still cooling from their mid-April high for the year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launches-zero-fee-trading-but-there-are-catches/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Launches Zero-Fee Trading, But There Are Catches</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple (XRP) Enters a $250 Million Deal to Acquire Metaco</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-enters-a-250-million-deal-to-acquire-metaco/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 23:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251079</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/RipplePublic.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/RipplePublic.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Followinng today's transaction, Ripple will become the sole shareholder of Metaco.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple announced the acquisition of Swiss-based crypto custody provider Metaco, marking the blockchain firm&#8217;s expansion across the growing institutional crypto custody market.</p>
<p>The deal, worth $250 million, surfaces as Ripple continues to defend against the long-drawn lawsuit from the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<h2>Ripple Acquires Metaco</h2>
<p>Ripple is expected to ramp up its enterprise offerings providing customers the technology to custody, issue, and settle any type of tokenized asset. At the heart of the deal, the two companies look to tap the growing institutional crypto custody market, which is forecasted to reach $10 trillion by 2030.</p>
<p>Metaco, on the other hand, will be able to leverage the San Francisco-based company&#8217;s established base of hundreds of customers and capital to address new demand and resources for its banking and institutional clients.</p>
<p>According to the official press <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230514005055/en/Leading-Enterprise-Crypto-Company-Ripple-Acquires-Custody-Provider-Metaco-for-250M" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">release</a>, Metaco will continue to operate as an independent brand and business unit, while its founder and CEO, Adrien Treccani, will lead its operations.</p>
<p>Commenting on the development, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Metaco is a proven leader in institutional digital asset custody with an exceptional executive bench and a truly unmatched customer track record. Through the strength of our balance sheet and financial position, Ripple will continue pressing our advantage in the areas critical to crypto infrastructure. Bringing on Metaco is monumental for our growing product suite and expanding global footprint.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Reports also suggest that Ripple <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/17/ripple-buys-swiss-startup-metaco-as-sec-lawsuit-conclusion-looms.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">invested</a> $250 million of cash off its own balance sheet to fund the acquisition, despite challenging market conditions as a result of higher interest rates and tighter funding conditions to mass layoffs and falling company valuations.</p>
<p>In a call to CNBC, Garlinghouse said the deal would help Ripple increase its presence overseas at a time when the SEC is taking stringent actions against major players in the digital asset industry.</p>
<h2>Ripple Vs. SEC: Another Breakthrough</h2>
<p>The lawsuit contested by Ripple has been dragging on for years. But in a significant development, a federal judge <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-judge-denies-the-sealing-of-hinmans-speech-once-again/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ruled</a> that the SEC cannot seal documents connected to former official William Hinman&#8217;s 2018 speech on crypto and securities.</p>
<p>The documents in question consist of drafts and emails that indicated the agency did not consider Ether a security at the time. The lawyers representing Ripple have been fighting to learn more about how Hinman came to the conclusion a claim could impact XRP&#8217;s own classification.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-enters-a-250-million-deal-to-acquire-metaco/" rel="nofollow">Ripple (XRP) Enters a $250 Million Deal to Acquire Metaco</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Seeks to Claw Back $250M From SBF and Execs in New Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-seeks-to-claw-back-250m-from-sbf-and-execs-in-new-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251251</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX_Judge.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/FTX_Judge.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FTX is accusing its former management team of conducting no due diligence before acquiring Embed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt cryptocurrency entities FTX, FTX.US, and Alameda Research have filed a lawsuit against former executives Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), Nishad Singh, and Gary Wang for lavishly spending FTX Group’s assets on the acquisition of stock clearing firm Embed Financial Technologies.</p>
<p>The move is the first formal action from FTX CEO John Ray against the company’s former management. The lawsuit, <a href="https://t.co/U4nXh9qhVu" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed</a> in the United States Bankruptcy Court for the District of Delaware, seeks to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-attempts-3-9-billion-clawback-from-genesis/" data-wpel-link="internal">claw back</a> the funds spent during the acquisition.</p>
<h2>FTX Sues SBF and His Inner Circle</h2>
<p>According to the court document, the plaintiffs accused the former management of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-us-discovers-another-90-million-missing/" data-wpel-link="internal">taking advantage</a> of FTX Group’s lack of controls and recordkeeping to inflate the valuation of Embed and deliberately purchasing the platform for more than it was worth.</p>
<p>The defendants, addressed as FTX Insiders, performed little to no due diligence on Embed, as they prioritized speed above everything else in the transaction. They accepted all the terms proposed during the negotiation by Michael Giles, Embed’s founder and CEO, who was also the sole representative.</p>
<p>Giles walked away from the deal with roughly $157 million and an “extravagant and unwarranted retention bonus” as an incentive to quickly complete the sale.</p>
<p>FTX began the acquisition negotiation with Giles at the end of March 2022. By mid-April of the same year, the parties had signed the “Memorandum of Terms,” which ascribed a $220 million enterprise value to Embed with a $75 million retention bonus to the platform’s employees, including $55 million to Giles.</p>
<p>However, when the deal was finalized in September – a few weeks before FTX Group went bankrupt – the FTX Insiders spent more than $248 million to acquire Embed. The plaintiffs allege that while the deal took about six months, the essential terms were negotiated and agreed upon within two weeks.</p>
<h2>FTX Seeks to Recover $250M</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the plaintiffs accused SBF, Singh, and Wang of causing the bankrupt entity to issue Simple Agreements for Future Equity (SAFEs), which could be converted into common stock in the event of a Chapter 11 bankruptcy filing.</p>
<p>Through his lawyers, Ray <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/john-ray-says-reviving-ftx-is-on-the-table-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">seeks</a> to revoke the SAFEs and recover the funds spent during the acquisition of Embed. The plaintiffs have also asked the court to order the defendants to bear the legal costs of the lawsuit.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the plaintiffs also <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MTUwNDgyOQ==&amp;id2=-1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed</a> an adversary lawsuit against Giles, the employees, and former equity holders of Embed. Some former equity holders include Silicon Valley venture capital firms like Y Combinator, Bain Capital Ventures, and 9Yards.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-seeks-to-claw-back-250m-from-sbf-and-execs-in-new-lawsuit/" rel="nofollow">FTX Seeks to Claw Back $250M From SBF and Execs in New Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
