<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 01:15:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tesla Remained a Bitcoin Hodler During Q2 of 2022</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tesla-remained-a-bitcoin-hodler-during-q2-of-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 01:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234933</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/BitcoinTeslaLSD.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/BitcoinTeslaLSD.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tesla sold 75% of its Bitcoin stash, but it kept the remaining 25% of its coins during the darkest of times.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tesla, the electric car company led by Elon Musk, did not sell the remaining of its Bitcoin stash, as it was supposed to do during the 4th quarter of 2022, according to a filing published by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>Tesla&#8217;s BTC holdings should be priced at around $245 million, which would be the last 25% of all the Bitcoin purchased by the company during the Crypto Bullrun of 2021.</p>
<p>Despite the crypto market crash of the following year and the negative news that darkened the crypto ecosystem, such as the bankruptcy of major firms in the industry, Tesla kept &#8220;hodling&#8221; part of its crypto fortune, according to its <a href="https://tesla-cdn.thron.com/static/GZR0GS_TSLA_Q4_2022_Update_PVPJAG.pdf?xseo=&amp;response-content-disposition=inline%3Bfilename%3D%22b7871185-dd6a-4d79-9c3b-19b497227f2a.pdf%22" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Q4 and FY 2022 Update</a>.</p>
<h2>Musk Invests in Opportunities</h2>
<p>During the first quarter of 2021, Tesla purchased 43,200 BTC for $1.5 billion. The company held onto its bitcoins for more than a year despite the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, which caused massive layoffs and the closure of multiple US companies.</p>
<p>In July 2022, Tesla CEO Elon Musk announced that the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tesla-sold-936-million-of-its-bitcoin-holdings-in-q2/" data-wpel-link="internal">had to sell 75% of its Bitcoin</a> for $936 million due to the rise in the company&#8217;s production costs in China, which had soared to unprecedented levels in the wake of the coronavirus.</p>
<p>However, Musk clarified that the company was &#8220;open to increasing bitcoin holdings in the future&#8221; and that they had nothing against BTC. He stated that the reason for the sale was due to uncertainty surrounding the COVID lockdowns in China and the need to maximize the company&#8217;s cash position.</p>
<p>Musk also reported in March 2022 that he was still holding his personal bitcoins and had no intention of selling them.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As a general principle, for those looking for advice from this thread, it is generally better to own physical things like a home or stock in companies you think make good products, than dollars when inflation is high.</p>
<p>I still own &amp; won’t sell my Bitcoin, Ethereum or Doge fwiw.</p>
<p>— Mr. Tweet (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1503222294277197829?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">March 14, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<h2>Tesla and its Bitcoin Trust Issues</h2>
<p>Tesla was one of the first companies to invest large amounts of money in bitcoin, and its first purchase fueled BTC&#8217;s bullish rally, driving it from approximately $20,000 to nearly $70,000. However, it started to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-energy-concerns-are-lobbyist-propaganda-says-michael-saylor/" data-wpel-link="internal">lose confidence</a> in its investment due to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-company-vows-to-be-carbon-neutral-following-teslas-recent-statement/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin&#8217;s energy consumption</a>, causing Tesla to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tesla-stops-accepting-bitcoin-price-slumps-3000-in-response/" data-wpel-link="internal">stop accepting Bitcoin</a> payments for the purchase of its cars in May 2021. Bitcoin crashed shortly after that, going from $55K to $52K in hours.</p>
<p>In September 2022, Michael Saylor, founder of Microstrategy, spoke out in defense of the Bitcoin mining industry, arguing that reports of increased carbon emissions from Bitcoin mining were &#8220;wrong.&#8221; He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-energy-concerns-are-lobbyist-propaganda-says-michael-saylor/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that &#8220;99.92% of the world&#8217;s carbon emissions are due to industrial energy uses other than bitcoin mining.&#8221;</p>
<p>Despite this, Tesla has not since spoken out on bitcoin mining. It&#8217;s unclear if the company is planning to embrace Bitcoin again in the future. However, Tesla&#8217;s retention of 25% of its Bitcoin stash, despite the market crash and negative news in the crypto ecosystem, could indicate a renewed interest in the digital currency.</p>
<p>Moreover, Musk has always been vocal about his support for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies —<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-doge-broke-all-time-high-above-0-7-following-elon-musks-recent-tweets/" data-wpel-link="internal">especially Dogecoin</a>. The company may be waiting for the right time to make a move, but it&#8217;s also possible they&#8217;re simply holding on to their Bitcoin stash as a long-term investment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tesla-remained-a-bitcoin-hodler-during-q2-of-2022/" rel="nofollow">Tesla Remained a Bitcoin Hodler During Q2 of 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Miner Core Scientific Raises $500M From BlackRock, Ibex Investors (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-miner-core-scientific-raises-500m-from-blackrock-ibex-investors-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234773</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/CoreScientificWallStreet.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/CoreScientificWallStreet.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BlackRock lent Core Scientific approximately $38 million by purchasing its secured convertible notes.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US-based bitcoin miner &#8211; Core Scientific &#8211; reportedly secured a $500 million fundraiser led by leading finance players, such as BlackRock, Apollo Capital, Kensico Capital, Ibex Investors, and others.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company filed for bankruptcy protection at the end of last year but continued mining BTC to repay debtholders.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Traditional Finance Firms Flocking to Help</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a court filing seen by </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/blackrock-apollo-among-creditors-lending-500-million-to-core-scientific-1.1874321" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bloomberg</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, BlackRock and several other high-profile investors lent approximately $500 million to Core Scientific by purchasing its secured convertible notes. Ibex Investors was the largest contributor to the financing, lending nearly $100 million.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BlackRock loaned $38 million through note purchases, while Apollo Capital Management bought $22.6 million and $11 million in April and August, respectively.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Both asset managers gave away $23 million in total to Core Scientific&#8217;s debtor-in-possession loan so it could continue mining bitcoin despite its problems. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The prolonged bear market and the plummeting price of the primary digital asset significantly harmed the crypto miner, which </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection a few days before Christmas. Despite that, the entity saw the price of its shares rise in the following weeks. Currently, CORZQ trades at around $0.11, compared to the $0.05 marked nearly a month ago.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, its market capitalization of around $41 million stands far from the $4.3 billion reached at the beginning of 2022 (upon getting listed on Nasdaq).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mining Remains Unfazed</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Regardless of its multi-billion losses registered in 2022, the dismissed employees, and the bankruptcy filing, Core Scientific <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/core-scientific-mined-over-1400-btc-in-december-despite-bankruptcy-filing/" data-wpel-link="internal">mined</a> 1,435 BTC in December. In comparison, the November production was 1,356 BTC. It also increased its self-mining hashrate from 15.4 EH/s to 15.7 EH/s.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, the organization provided data center colocation services and operating support for 91,000 customer-owned ASIC servers (in November) and 80,500 (in December), representing approximately 37% and 34% of the functioning mining fleet in those months. Those servers produced 795 BTC in November and 931 BTC in the following month.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The results came in spite of the numerous closures of data centers, which represented 5,828 and 17,179 megawatt hours (in November and December, respectively). Core revealed it has teamed up with utility companies to ensure power grid stability.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Its main facilities remain distributed in Texas, Kentucky, Georgia, North Dakota, and North Carolina. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-miner-core-scientific-raises-500m-from-blackrock-ibex-investors-report/" rel="nofollow">BTC Miner Core Scientific Raises $500M From BlackRock, Ibex Investors (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>dYdX Extends 156 Million Token Lock-up Period by 10 Months</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-extends-156-million-token-lock-up-period-by-10-months/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234923</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/dydx.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/dydx.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Depending on the math used, the end of the lockup could have released $300 million worth of DYDX back onto the market]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Decentralized cryptocurrency exchange dYdX has postponed plans to unlock nearly $300 million worth of dYdX tokens for investors, extending the lockup period from February until December. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Since the news broke, DYDX has surged by 24% on the day. </span></p>
<h2>Extending the Lock-up Period</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://dydx.foundation/blog/lock-up-extension" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by dYdX on Wednesday, the dYdX foundation, dYdX trading, and parties to the warrants for purchasing DYDX tokens signed an amendment to extend the transfer restriction schedule of said tokens. This included postponing their initial release date from February 3 to December 1.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The warrant amendment mentioned above does not alter the staggered unlock that occurs after the initial unlock date,” the foundation clarified.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The dYdX foundation is a Swiss non-profit formed to bolster the growth of dYdX’s protocol ecosystem and communities. The protocol itself is governed by holders of DYDX – a governance token that simultaneously offers rewards to holders through token staking and trading fee discounts. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At present, only about 15% of DYDX’s total 1 billion token supply has entered circulation. The token’s initial allocation in August 2021 was partially reserved for investors in dYdX Trading, as well as the company’s present/future employees, founders, and consultants.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Going forward, the next token unlock will include a 30% unlock on December 1, followed by a 40% unlock spread between the first 6 months of 2024. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The first day of each month for the following 12 months will cumulatively unlock another 20% of tokens, while the next 12 months unlock the final 10% of tokens. That means all dYdX unlocks will be complete by June 1, 2026. </span></p>
<h2>dYdX Pump</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">dYdX began trading at $1.56 on Wednesday, before rocketing to over $2.00 at 11:25 ET. It is now trading at $1.93, up roughly 25% on the day. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The initially planned release, scheduled for next week, would have unlocked 156 million dYdX tokens. Cumulatively, that&#8217;s $243 million worth of tokens based on Wednesday’s starting price, and $301 million based on its current price. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">dYDX was one of the few tokens to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-could-be-among-largest-beneficiaries-from-ftx-collapse-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">benefit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from FTX’s downfall in November, surging 50% within a week after it filed for bankruptcy. The exchange prides itself on being non-custodial, thus eliminating the counterparty risk associated with similar centralized exchange failures. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, those behind the protocol have confessed to blocking addresses linked to the Ethereum privacy tool Tornado Cash, at the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-confirms-blocking-accounts-linked-to-tornado-cash/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">request</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> of the Treasury Department. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-extends-156-million-token-lock-up-period-by-10-months/" rel="nofollow">dYdX Extends 156 Million Token Lock-up Period by 10 Months</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bithumb&#8217;s &#8220;Real&#8221; Owner Faces Arrest Warrant on Embezzlement Charges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bithumbs-real-owner-faces-arrest-warrant-on-embezzlement-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 22:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234918</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Bithumb-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Bithumb-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Kang siblings are charged with embezzlement, breach of trust, and market manipulation. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Multiple executives at the South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb are now beleaguered by charges of embezzlement and market manipulation, according to the South Korean financial outlet InfoMax. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Under these charges, an arrest warrant has been issued for Kang Jong-hyeon, who is thought to be the “actual owner of Bithumb. </span></p>
<h2>Bithumb Executives Under Fire</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On Wednesday, members of the legal community </span><a href="https://news.einfomax.co.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=4251784" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">confirmed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Kang and two of Bithumb’s executives have been sentenced by the Seoul Southern District Prosecutor’s Office on embezzlement and breach of trust charges. They’ve also been charged with fraudulent illegal transactions under the Capital Markets Act.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Kang’s younger sister, Kang Ji-yeon, runs Bithumb affiliates including Inbiogen and Bucket Studio – a footwear firm and distribution company respectively. The former is believed to have artificially inflated the share price of both companies by issuing convertible bonds.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Prosecutors seized the circumstances in which Mr. Kang stole company money or manipulated stock prices, and in October of last year, they seized and searched Bithumb affiliates, such as Vident, Inbiogen, and Bucket Studio,” stated InfoMax.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Each company’s shares were tied up with one another: Vidente is the single largest shareholder of Bithumb, Inbiogen is the largest shareholder of Vidente, and Bucket Studio is the largest shareholder of Inbiogen. </span></p>
<h2>Bithumb’s Many Troubles</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bithumb was under investigation by the prosecutors’ office for months for an alleged $70 million fraud carried out by former chairman Lee Jung-hoon. After being </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumb-ex-chair-faces-8-years-in-prison-for-alleged-70m-crypto-fraud-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">charged</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in October, Jung-hoon was found </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumbs-owner-found-not-guilty-on-charges-of-fraud-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">not guilty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> earlier this month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Two weeks ago, the prosecutors’ office launched a renewed investigation into Bithumb on whether Kang had violated domestic taxation laws – including a look into his sibling’s activities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Vidente’s vice president Park Mo’s body was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vp-of-bithumb-linked-company-found-dead-in-seoul-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">found</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> dead in Seoul late last month, with reports suggesting the death may have been suicide. Park was rumored to be overseeing accounting for the Kang siblings during his time as VP of Vidente. Suspicions that the Kang siblings had framed Park for embezzlement and market manipulation were circulating at the time. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumbs-real-owner-faces-arrest-warrant-on-embezzlement-charges/" rel="nofollow">Bithumb&#8217;s &#8220;Real&#8221; Owner Faces Arrest Warrant on Embezzlement Charges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Visa CEO Says There&#8217;s a &#8220;Meaningful&#8221; Future for Stablecoins and CBDCs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/visa-ceo-says-theres-a-meaningful-future-for-stablecoins-and-cbdcs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 20:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234912</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Visa.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Visa.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies pose both complementary opportunities and competitive threats to Visa, per the company’s annual shareholder report. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The CEO of the world’s largest credit card company told shareholders on Tuesday that stablecoins and central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) will play a “meaningful role” in the payments space going forward. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The company also published its 2022 annual report, in which it wrote about its simultaneously complementary and competitive relationship with cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<h2>Visa’s Crypto Outlook</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As explained by CEO Alfred Kelly during a </span><a href="https://annualreport.visa.com/annual-meeting/default.aspx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">conference call</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Visa already has “multiple initiatives” underway in the blockchain space, and has invested many crypto funds and companies already. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“It’s very early days, but we continue to believe that stablecoins and central bank digital currencies have the potential to play a meaningful role in the payments space,” said Kelly.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Stablecoins combine the peer-to-peer nature of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin with the relative price stability of another currency or asset – frequently the U.S. dollar. This solves for the price instability problem that critics – including </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-and-ethereum-are-not-currencies-states-swedish-central-bank/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">central banks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – claim prevents Bitcoin from being a legitimate currency.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tether (USDT), which is the largest stablecoin by market cap, has a higher daily transaction volume than any other crypto. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, CBDCs are a government-issued currency in digital form, built upon blockchain rails. Federal Reserve vice chair Lael Brainard has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fed-vice-chair-presses-for-cbdc-in-us-amidst-market-stress/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">shown support</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for launching a CBDC in the United States by providing a “safe central bank liability in the digital financial ecosystem.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Last year, Visa </span><a href="http://t" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">formed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a partnership with ConsenSys to onramp CBDCs to existing payment networks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In its report, Visa said it is “developing or participating in alternative payments systems or products,” that could potentially disintermediate its role, some of which include “stablecoin-based payments initiatives.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a section titled “Competition,” Visa named “Digital Wallet Providers” and Alternative Payments Providers” among them, the latter of which included “cryptocurrency platforms.” While these venues are primarily focused on e-commerce and mobile payments right now, the company expects them to “expand their offerings to the physical point of sale.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Technology and innovation are shifting consumer habits and driving growth opportunities in ecommerce, mobile payments, blockchain technology and digital currencies,” the company stated, adding that crypto payment platforms “can be both a partner and a competitor to Visa.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Reputational Harm</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Cryptocurrencies pose not only technological threats and opportunities for Visa, but reputational ones too. The company’s report claimed its brand could be negatively impacted when its services are used for “legal, but controversial” products like cryptocurrencies, equating them to “adult content” and “gambling” in this regard.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A month before FTX went bankrupt, Visa </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftt-spiked-to-3-week-high-as-visa-ftx-revealed-crypto-debit-card/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">planned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a partnership with the exchange to provide a crypto debit card in 40 countries. The program was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/visa-terminates-ftx-debit-card-program/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">terminated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shortly after the collapse. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/visa-ceo-says-theres-a-meaningful-future-for-stablecoins-and-cbdcs/" rel="nofollow">Visa CEO Says There&#8217;s a &#8220;Meaningful&#8221; Future for Stablecoins and CBDCs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Bull Market to Start Once US Inflation Drops to 4-5%: Scaramucci</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bull-market-to-start-once-us-inflation-drops-to-4-5-scaramucci/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 18:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234824</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/scaramucci.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/scaramucci.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Scaramucci said the Fed might stop lifting interest rates when inflation decreases to 4-5%, sparking a price expansion for the digital assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Anthony Scaramucci &#8211; the Founder of SkyBridge Capital and former White House official &#8211; believes cryptocurrencies will revive once the Federal Reserve stops raising interest rates.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He thinks this will happen once inflation in the United States dropped back down to 4-5%.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Surge Could be on the Horizon</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The financier <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/scaramucci-sees-risk-asset-crypto-resurgence-on-fed-pause-1.1874404" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">thinks</a> the US central bank will halt the interest rate hikes before reaching the 2% inflation goal and, thus, stimulate a price expansion for risk assets, such as cryptocurrencies:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I do believe that the Fed declares victory at 4% to 5% inflation. If I&#8217;m right, there will be a resurgence in the market. There&#8217;ll be a lot of short covering in crypto, and there&#8217;ll be a rebirth of risk assets.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_95964" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-95964" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-95964" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min.jpg" alt="Anthony Scaramucci. Source: CNBC" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AnthonyScaramucci-min-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-95964" class="wp-caption-text">Anthony Scaramucci. Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p>Recall that January&#8217;s CPI numbers <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/enhanced-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-cpi-numbers-clock-in-at-6-5/" data-wpel-link="internal">showed</a> the inflation in the USA in December stood at 6.5%, while the peak was marked in June last year when the rate reached a 40-year high of 9.1%.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scaramucci&#8217;s investment management firm &#8211; SkyBridge Capital &#8211; has around 10% exposure to bitcoin through the SkyBridge Multi-Adviser Hedge Fund Portfolios Series G fund. He said the company might focus on other assets if the primary cryptocurrency starts a bull run.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American, who briefly served as the White House Director of Communications, is among the most prominent bitcoin advocates and kept his faith throughout the continuous market decline. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, he has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-can-become-the-global-reserve-currency-says-skybridges-anthony-scaramucci/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">advised</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> people to properly scale their BTC investments and allocate not more than 5% of their total savings. Thus, they could enjoy solid profits if the asset skyrockets in the future, while potential losses would be insignificant in case of a price shrink (which he doubts). </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;I got Burned by Sam&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scaramucci, who once had a close relationship with the former CEO of FTX &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried &#8211; and members of his family, shed more light on the losses that the exchange&#8217;s collapse triggered for his company.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SkyBridge accepted $45 million in funding from SBF shortly before the demise of the platform and used the cash to purchase $10 million worth of FTT tokens. The firm later sold the stash at a loss of $9.6 million.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I don&#8217;t shy away from it. I think it&#8217;s important for people who believe in capitalism and important for people that are risk-takers to understand what happened. I&#8217;m not going to be the person that takes no more risk in the future because I got burned by Sam,&#8221; Scaramucci stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/anthony-scaramucci-calls-sam-bankman-fried-the-bernie-madoff-of-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">compared</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> SBF to &#8220;the Bernie Madoff of crypto,&#8221; saying &#8220;the ninth circle of Hell&#8221; is reserved for people like him. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bull-market-to-start-once-us-inflation-drops-to-4-5-scaramucci/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Bull Market to Start Once US Inflation Drops to 4-5%: Scaramucci</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DCG Subsidiary Luno Lays Off 35% of Employees (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-subsidiary-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234865</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Luno_Dismiss.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Luno_Dismiss.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto platform Luno will supposedly slash its headcount by more than 330 people.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The London-based cryptocurrency platform &#8211; Luno &#8211; will reportedly trim the size of its team by over 330 people.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It adds its name to the growing list of industry players dismissing staff due to the bear market, including Coinbase, Crypto.com, Bybit, Huobi, Gemini, and more.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/25/dcg-owned-crypto-exchange-luno-axes-35percent-of-staff.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">coverage</a>, Luno will reduce its headcount from 960 to around 630.</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;2022 has been an incredibly tough year for the broader tech industry and, in particular, the crypto market. Luno, unfortunately, hasn&#8217;t been immune to this turbulence, which has affected our overall growth and revenue numbers,&#8221; a spokesperson of the trading venue stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Several other cryptocurrency exchanges have already enforced redundancies. </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-dismisses-950-people-citing-current-economic-climate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> dismissed 18% last year and additional 950 people earlier this month. </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-to-lay-off-30-of-workforce-amid-colder-crypto-winter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bybit</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> (30%), </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-to-reportedly-lay-off-at-least-30-of-staff-citing-sharp-revenue-drop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Huobi</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> (30%), </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitmex-to-dismiss-30-of-its-workforce-shortly-after-ceo-replacement-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BitMEX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> (30%), and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-respite-from-layoffs-crypto-com-cuts-20-workforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto.com</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> are part of that club, too.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Luno is under the umbrella of the distressed Digital Currency Group. While headquartered in London, it has offices across Europe, Africa, and South East Asia.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DCG &#8211; one of the numerous cryptocurrency entities caught up in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-wide-does-ftx-contagion-spread-the-affected-companies-so-far/" data-wpel-link="internal">the FTX domino effect</a> &#8211; has to cope with multiple issues.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It dismissed 10% of its staff last year and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-wealth-management-division-shuts-down-hours-after-genesis-announced-layoffs-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">closed</a> its wealth-management division. One of its subsidiaries &#8211; Genesis &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcgs-subsidiary-genesis-global-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for bankruptcy protection, following which Gemini&#8217;s Co-Founder &#8211; Cameron Winklevoss &#8211; threatened to sue CEO Barry Silbert:</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Unless Barry and DCG come to their senses and make a fair offer to creditors, we will be filing a lawsuit against Barry and DCG imminently,&#8221; he stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Winklevoss previously claimed that Digital Currency Group owes Genesis over $1.6 billion, accusing Silbert of causing that &#8220;mess.&#8221; He also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-for-the-removal-of-dcg-ceo-barry-silbert/" data-wpel-link="internal">urged</a> the Board of DCG to remove him immediately.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-subsidiary-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees-report/" rel="nofollow">DCG Subsidiary Luno Lays Off 35% of Employees (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Pulls Back But Are Bulls Staging a Rally to $24K? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-pulls-back-but-are-bulls-staging-a-rally-to-24k-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234873</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s recent uptrend has paused temporarily upon arriving at the major swing level of roughly $22.8K. Although there are some bullish signs based on the on-chain analysis, there is a significant resistance region ahead in Bitcoin’s path. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart The market appears to be looking for direction as the price [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin’s recent uptrend has paused temporarily upon arriving at the major swing level of roughly $22.8K. Although there are some bullish signs based on the on-chain analysis, there is a significant resistance region ahead in Bitcoin’s path.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The market appears to be looking for direction as the price has now reached a critical resistance zone. The descending trendline had been supporting the price until Bitcoin experienced a sudden cascade and dropped below it in late June 2022. This trendline then turned into a substantial resistance level and has rejected the price ever since.</p>
<p>However, Bitcoin has initiated a surge and currently aims to surpass the trendline, which presently stands at approximately $24.5K. A valid breakout should facilitate the uptrend and result in an impulsive bullish move.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also worth mentioning that the 50-day moving average is about to claim the 100-day moving average, a well-known bullish indication for the market structure, implying that a new bull run might occur soon.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234876" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234876" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234876 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2501231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234876" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Bitcoin’s price is currently consolidating at a vital resistance zone of $22.5K, which also aligns with a prior major swing at $22.8K. In case of a breakout, the market may attain adequate demand and could expect another short run towards the $25K crucial resistance level.</p>
<p>However, by comparing the price and the RSI indicator’s behavior, a significant bearish divergence can be identified in the 4-hour timeframe, which could potentially result in a reversal.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, considering the bearish divergence, the more probable scenario is a short-term consolidation correction phase followed by another impulsive uptrend toward higher price levels.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234875" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234875" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234875 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2501232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234875" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">On-chain Analysis</span></p>
<p>The MVRV metric measures the ratio of coins’ Market Cap to their Realized Cap, indicating whether the price is overvalued. Historically, Values over &#8216;3.7&#8217; pointed to price tops, while values below &#8216;1&#8217; marked price bottoms.</p>
<p>The following chart demonstrates the MVRV metric and Bitcoin’s price. During the last stage of the 2018 bear market, the metric dropped below 1 and, after a mid-term consolidation, spiked and surpassed 1. At the same time, Bitcoin found its bottom and started an uptrend marking the 2019 bull market.</p>
<p>The same behavior can be seen in MVRV’s recent move. The metric has lately surged and reached 1.14 due to Bitcoin’s impulsive uptrend. This can be interpreted as a bullish sign that Bitcoin is about to initiate a significant growing trend.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234874" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234874" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234874 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-scaled.jpg" alt="bitcoin_mvrv_ratio_250123" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234874" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-pulls-back-but-are-bulls-staging-a-rally-to-24k-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Pulls Back But Are Bulls Staging a Rally to $24K? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Long Will the Ethereum LSD Narrative Last? Talking 2023 Trends with Nansen&#8217;s Martin Lee</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-long-will-the-ethereum-lsd-narrative-last-talking-2023-trends-with-nansens-martin-lee/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234794</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CPT-Podcast-Design-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CPT-Podcast-Design-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum Liquid Staking Derivative coins are the hottest topic of 2023 so far, but what other trends are taking shape according to on-chain data?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ethereum Liquid Staking tokens are going through the roof. Lido is up 150% in a month, similarly Frax Shares, while other protocols, such as Rocket Pool, are also catching up. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But that&#8217;s not all. NFTs are also seeing massive volumes for multiple consecutive weeks, showing little signs of slowing down.</span></p>
<p>The question now is for how long this positive trend will sustain &#8211; is it a dead cat bounce or the beginning of a much-awaited recovery?</p>
<p>To help us crunch the numbers and interpret some of the on-chain data is <a href="https://twitter.com/themlpx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Martin Lee</a> &#8211; a Data Journalist from the popular cryptocurrency analytics firm <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Nansen</a>.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="How Long Will the Ethereum LSD Narrative Last? Talking 2023 Trends with Nansen's Martin Lee" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pODdACRccK0" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p>
<h2>Liquid Staking Coins Trend Upwards, but for How Long?</h2>
<p>Ethereum LSD, or liquid staking derivative coins, have been the hottest story of 2023 so far, with many of the protocols seeing tremendous growth in the value locked and, by extension &#8211; popularity.</p>
<p><em>To those unfamiliar with the concept, we have a comprehensive guide on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-ethereum-liquid-staking/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum liquid staking</a>. </em></p>
<p>As opposed to staking directly into the Beacon depositor contract, LSD protocols allow users to stake their ETH and receive a synthetic version of it &#8211; a new token, per se &#8211; that can then be used across various DeFi applications to trade, farm, provide liquidity, and so forth.</p>
<p>Speaking on the matter, Lee outlined two major advantages that, according to him, are part of the reasons why the narrative has grown so strong. For instance, h outlined that staking ETH directly into the smart contract is &#8220;really capital inefficient&#8221; because of a few things. First, the capital requirement is quite considerable (32 ETH), and the lockup period used to be unknown.</p>
<p>Therefore:</p>
<blockquote><p>The natural solution to this would be liquid staking. You get a liquid token in exchange for whatever you&#8217;ve staked (in this case ETH). For example, if you stake ETH with Lido, you get stETH, which is fully liquid and you can interact with various DeFi protocols.</p></blockquote>
<p>Liquid staking solves both the problems of the staked ETH being illiquid and the high capital requirement to participate in ETH staking.</p>
<p>Native tokens of LSD protocols, such as Lido&#8217;s LDO, for instance, have been on the run lately. LDO itself is up close to 150% in the past month, similar to other protocols of the kind like Rocket Pool and others.</p>
<p>The catalyst for this seems to have been the recent announcement that Ethereum&#8217;s Shanghai upgrade will hit the public testnet in February and the mainnet in 2023. This is a pivotal moment for the Ethereum community because it will allow validators to unlock the 32 ETH they&#8217;ve staked in the Beacon contract for the first time. The consensus seems to be that this would increase the demand for liquid staking alternatives, which is the predominant reason for the current popularity and increase in their valuations.</p>
<p>On when the narrative will inevitably die out, Lee says that most trends like this typically slow down on the date of the event that prompted their emergence in the first place &#8211; in this case, the Shanghai upgrade.</p>
<blockquote><p>Typically, the trend dies out on the date of the event itself. For example, the ETH Merge was such a huge topic, but on the Merge date itself, people completely stopped talking about it.</p></blockquote>
<h2>NFT Volumes Also Pop</h2>
<p>At the time of our recording, NFT trading volume was going through the roof, and even though there was a certain decline in the past couple of days, the market saw a considerable rebound.</p>
<p>In fact, by January 17th, ETH NFTs saw five consecutive weeks of up-only volumes.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234864" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234864" style="width: 2119px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234864" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes.jpg" alt="img1_nft_volumes" width="2119" height="1174" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes.jpg 2119w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes-300x166.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes-1024x567.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes-768x425.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes-1536x851.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes-2048x1135.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/img1_nft_volumes-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2119px) 100vw, 2119px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234864" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Nansen</figcaption></figure>
<p>Commenting on the matter, Lee said that it&#8217;s more or less this is in line with what we&#8217;ve seen in past cycles.</p>
<blockquote><p>Whenever we have long periods of very boring action, where there&#8217;s basically no movements, prices are extremely stable, NFTs tend to go on their own mini-run whenever that happens.</p>
<p>In the past 2-3 months, the price action across the board was extremely stagnant. Then, NFTs kind of went on their own mini-run, with some projects doing better than others.</p></blockquote>
<p>To find out what Lee thinks the trends of this year will look like, as well as whether or not the Shanghai upgrade will cause a lot of selling pressure on ETH&#8217;s price, don&#8217;t hesitate to watch the full video above.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-long-will-the-ethereum-lsd-narrative-last-talking-2023-trends-with-nansens-martin-lee/" rel="nofollow">How Long Will the Ethereum LSD Narrative Last? Talking 2023 Trends with Nansen&#8217;s Martin Lee</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pantera, Kraken, and Others Join Consortium for Injective Labs&#8217; $150M Fund</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pantera-kraken-and-others-join-consortium-for-injective-labs-150m-fund/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmos (ATOM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234774</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Injective.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Injective.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The initiative's consortium will help with technical development, research, marketing, and community growth.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The digital asset markets have been shaky in the past year, but the blockchain sector continues to scale as demand intensifies from both crypto-native as well as traditional institutions eyeing to leverage the space.</p>
<p>Decentralized smart contracts platform Injective is the latest to announce a new $150 million ecosystem initiative to spur the adoption of interoperable infrastructure and DeFi.</p>
<p>Leading the charge is a consortium of prominent Web3 players such as Pantera Capital, Kraken Ventures, Jump Crypto, Kucoin Ventures, Delphi Labs, Flow Traders, Gate Labs, and IDG Capital, among others. Injective has assembled the largest consortium to date within the broader Cosmos ecosystem for the purpose.</p>
<h2>$150M Fund</h2>
<p>The members will focus on backing promising projects building within a diverse array of sectors encompassing interoperability, decentralized finance, trading, Proof-of-Stake (PoS) infrastructure, and scalability solutions.</p>
<p>Aside from a bespoke token, the consortium will also support via equity investments, alongside mentorship in technical development, cryptographic research, business development, marketing, community growth, etc.</p>
<p>According to the official press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the focus will also be on founders building within Injective and the broader Cosmos ecosystem. Commenting on the initiative, Eric Chen, co-founder, and CEO of Injective Labs, the firm behind the layer-1 blockchain, stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We&#8217;re thrilled to see some of the largest names in the industry joining Injective&#8217;s mission to create a more democratized financial system through decentralization. Developer activity on Injective is rapidly increasing with major projects and this new ecosystem fund will provide unmatched opportunities for new builders entering Web3 and the Cosmos ecosystem overall.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Funding Round</h2>
<p>Amid a brutal crypto winter, Injective Protocol <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/injective-raises-40m-from-jump-crypto-and-bh-digital-to-accelerate-growth-301602848.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">raised</a> $40 million in a round led by Jump Crypto last summer. Other participants leading the funding round included Brevan Howard Digital, the crypto arm of British billionaire hedge fund manager Alan Howard.</p>
<p>The fresh capital infusion was set to be used to support incoming developers. Building critical toolkits, support software, and core upgrades to expand the Injective ecosystem were some of the other key areas alongside increasing utility for its native token, INJ&#8217;s, and providing liquidity and support to dApps on its blockchain.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pantera-kraken-and-others-join-consortium-for-injective-labs-150m-fund/" rel="nofollow">Pantera, Kraken, and Others Join Consortium for Injective Labs&#8217; $150M Fund</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
