<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Metaverse Gaming is the Theme of 2023 and This Crypto Project Will Shake Things Up</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/metaverse-gaming-theme-of-2023-crypto-project-will-shake-things-up.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/metaverse-gaming-theme-of-2023-crypto-project-will-shake-things-up.htm"&gt;Read More: Metaverse Gaming is the Theme of 2023 and This Crypto Project Will Shake Things Up&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Metaverse Gaming</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Web3 Games</category><category>Web3 Gaming</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Taro</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/metaverse-gaming-theme-of-2023-crypto-project-will-shake-things-up.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100962/249414/robotera-land.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="367990"/></item><item><title>Mark Cuban Wants to Buy More Bitcoin and Thinks Gold Buyers Are Dumb</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mark-cuban-wants-buy-more-bitcoin-thinks-gold-buyers-are-dumb.htm</link><description>Billionaire investor and TV personality Mark Cuban is looking to buy more bitcoin (BTC) despite the asset being down 75% from its peak. &lt;br /&gt;
“I want Bitcoin to go down a lot further so I can buy some more,” Cuban said in a recent podcast interview with talk show host Bill Maher. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin is down to around $17,400 at the time of writing, after trading at an all-time high of $69,000 back in November of 2021....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mark-cuban-wants-buy-more-bitcoin-thinks-gold-buyers-are-dumb.htm"&gt;Read More: Mark Cuban Wants to Buy More Bitcoin and Thinks Gold Buyers Are Dumb&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Mark Cuban</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mark-cuban-wants-buy-more-bitcoin-thinks-gold-buyers-are-dumb.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100902/249246/mark-cuban.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="37298"/></item><item><title>Hurry To Invest in Kucoin Supported Calvaria Battle Cards Fantasy Game Before Red Hot Presale Ends Soon</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hurry-invest-kucoin-supported-calvaria-battle-cards-fantasy-game-before-red-hot-presale-ends-soon.htm</link><description>The play to earn gaming space is one of the most significant in the entirety of the cryptocurrency industry, and has been exploding in popularity recently.  &lt;br /&gt;
One of the main reasons for this is the fact that the play to earn sector has a wider appeal for retail users, who may not usually be so inclined to participate in the crypto industry thanks to the relatively high barrier to entry. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hurry-invest-kucoin-supported-calvaria-battle-cards-fantasy-game-before-red-hot-presale-ends-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Hurry To Invest in Kucoin Supported Calvaria Battle Cards Fantasy Game Before Red Hot Presale Ends Soon&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hurry-invest-kucoin-supported-calvaria-battle-cards-fantasy-game-before-red-hot-presale-ends-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100927/249326/97a142731923824017576ad7503b8e92-1.webp" type="image/webp" length="237920"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Coinbase to Close Down Most Japanese Operations, Voyager Granted Initial Approval to Sell Assets to Binance.US, Ledger Integrates 'Cometh Battle' Card Game</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-coinbase-to-close-down-most-japanese-operations-voyager-granted-initial-approval-to-sell-assets-to-binanceus-ledger-integrates-cometh-battle-card-game.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-coinbase-to-close-down-most-japanese-operations-voyager-granted-initial-approval-to-sell-assets-to-binanceus-ledger-integrates-cometh-battle-card-game.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Coinbase to Close Down Most Japanese Operations, Voyager Granted Initial Approval to Sell Assets to Binance.US, Ledger Integrates 'Cometh Battle' Card Game&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Japan</category><category>Huobi</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>Genesis</category><category>WazirX</category><category>Binance</category><category>Binance.us</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Investment</category><category>Legal</category><category>Voyager</category><category>Gaming</category><category>Ledger</category><category>Dai</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-coinbase-to-close-down-most-japanese-operations-voyager-granted-initial-approval-to-sell-assets-to-binanceus-ledger-integrates-cometh-battle-card-game.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100895/249238/adobestock-24k-production-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="430117"/></item><item><title>Gala Games Price is Giving Back Some Gains So Maybe It's Time to Consider This Crypto Web3 Game Alternative</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-games-price-giving-back-some-gains-so-maybe-its-time-consider-crypto-web3-game-alternative.htm</link><description>In recent days, GALA's price has been on the rise, thanks in part to a highly-publicized partnership with Hollywood stars Mark Wahlberg and Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson. This partnership helped push the price of Gala Games's crypto Web3 game token up by an impressive 150% in the first 10 days of January alone....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-games-price-giving-back-some-gains-so-maybe-its-time-consider-crypto-web3-game-alternative.htm"&gt;Read More: Gala Games Price is Giving Back Some Gains So Maybe It's Time to Consider This Crypto Web3 Game Alternative&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-games-price-giving-back-some-gains-so-maybe-its-time-consider-crypto-web3-game-alternative.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100929/249311/gala.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="667445"/></item><item><title>WazirX Releases Proof of Reserves, Around 20% of Holdings are in Shiba Inu</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wazirx-releases-proof-of-reserves-around-20-of-holdings-are-shiba-inu.htm</link><description>Indian crypto exchange WazirX has released its Proof of Reserves (PoR), sharing wallet addresses and digital asset holdings. Notably, Shiba Inu accounts for the largest proportion of assets on the exchange as over 19% of its holdings are in the form of the meme coin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wazirx-releases-proof-of-reserves-around-20-of-holdings-are-shiba-inu.htm"&gt;Read More: WazirX Releases Proof of Reserves, Around 20% of Holdings are in Shiba Inu&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>WazirX</category><category>Binance</category><category>Proof of Reserves</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wazirx-releases-proof-of-reserves-around-20-of-holdings-are-shiba-inu.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100926/249300/adobestock-453185424-editorial-media-library-original-1225-817.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="151333"/></item><item><title>Newly Listed Coins to Buy Today - Dash 2 Trade (D2T), Proxy Swap (PROXY), Genius (GENI), Meta Masters Guild (MEMAG), Calvaria (RIA)</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/newly-listed-coins-to-buy-today-dash-2-trade-d2t-proxy-swap-proxy-medal-of-honor-moh-meta-masters-guild-memag-calvaria-ria.htm</link><description>Broader cryptocurrency markets have been rallying in recent days, but with bitcoin volatility at historic lows, traders looking for choppier price action to take advantage of might instead prefer to take a look at some popular newly listed cryptocurrencies. Recently listed tokens are typically highly volatile and often respond well to short-term technical breakouts. Here a few big names that began changing hands on exchanges in the last few days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/newly-listed-coins-to-buy-today-dash-2-trade-d2t-proxy-swap-proxy-medal-of-honor-moh-meta-masters-guild-memag-calvaria-ria.htm"&gt;Read More: Newly Listed Coins to Buy Today - Dash 2 Trade (D2T), Proxy Swap (PROXY), Genius (GENI), Meta Masters Guild (MEMAG), Calvaria (RIA)&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>Genius</category><category>Proxy Swap</category><category>Meta Masters Guild</category><category>Calvaria</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/newly-listed-coins-to-buy-today-dash-2-trade-d2t-proxy-swap-proxy-medal-of-honor-moh-meta-masters-guild-memag-calvaria-ria.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100907/249261/newly-listed-coins-jan11.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="381303"/></item><item><title>Group One “Beneficially” Owns 13% of MicroStrategy in Big Bitcoin Bet - Is the BTC Bottom In?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/group-one-beneficially-owns-13-of-microstrategy-in-big-bitcoin-bet-is-the-btc-bottom-in.htm</link><description>Chicago-based trading firm Group One Trading has taken a massive bet on bitcoin (BTC) by taking a “beneficial” position representing 13% of bitcoin bull Michael Saylor’s company MicroStrategy. &lt;br /&gt;
The bet on MicroStrategy’s stock included bullish options that gives the trading firm the right to buy more than 1.3 million shares of MicroStrategy, according to an SEC filing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/group-one-beneficially-owns-13-of-microstrategy-in-big-bitcoin-bet-is-the-btc-bottom-in.htm"&gt;Read More: Group One “Beneficially” Owns 13% of MicroStrategy in Big Bitcoin Bet - Is the BTC Bottom In?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>MicroStrategy</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/group-one-beneficially-owns-13-of-microstrategy-in-big-bitcoin-bet-is-the-btc-bottom-in.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100870/249205/microstrategy.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="33858"/></item><item><title>Digital Yuan Pilot Expands into Wealth Management, Securities &amp; Education</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-yuan-pilot-expands-into-wealth-management-securities-education.htm</link><description>The central People’s Bank of China (PBoC)’s digital yuan is set to expand into the world of wealth management – and has also broken new ground in the field of education. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Shanghai Securities News, the Hong Kong Stock Exchange-listed brokerage and investment bank China Galaxy Securities will allow digital yuan-paying customers access to over-the-counter wealth management products....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-yuan-pilot-expands-into-wealth-management-securities-education.htm"&gt;Read More: Digital Yuan Pilot Expands into Wealth Management, Securities &amp; Education&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-yuan-pilot-expands-into-wealth-management-securities-education.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100861/249196/adobestock-365305673-editorial-use-only.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2218677"/></item><item><title>Move-to-Earn Crypto Is Coming to Gyms and Fitness With the Help of Combat Athlete Stars - Where to Invest Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/move-earn-crypto-is-coming-to-gyms-and-fitness-with-the-help-of-combat-athlete-stars-where-to-invest-today.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
According to Statista, the health fitness industry is currently worth $96 billion. However, the healthcare sector is stalling due to a lack of radical technology breaking new ground, and Fight Out, appears to be the solution, as it is revolutionizing the fitness and health industry and providing massive value to users and investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/move-earn-crypto-is-coming-to-gyms-and-fitness-with-the-help-of-combat-athlete-stars-where-to-invest-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Move-to-Earn Crypto Is Coming to Gyms and Fitness With the Help of Combat Athlete Stars - Where to Invest Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/move-earn-crypto-is-coming-to-gyms-and-fitness-with-the-help-of-combat-athlete-stars-where-to-invest-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100891/249229/fightout-1024x467.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="404689"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction - Can This Meme Coin Deliver for Crypto Bulls in 2023 as Price Edges Higher?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-can-this-meme-coin-deliver-for-crypto-bulls-in-2023-as-price-edges-higher.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu price continues to outshine its peers in the market, with its value increasing 9.9% in seven days and 9.4% in two weeks. However, the second-largest meme coin has lost 2.4% of its value to exchange hands at $0.00000895 at the time of writing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-can-this-meme-coin-deliver-for-crypto-bulls-in-2023-as-price-edges-higher.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction - Can This Meme Coin Deliver for Crypto Bulls in 2023 as Price Edges Higher?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-can-this-meme-coin-deliver-for-crypto-bulls-in-2023-as-price-edges-higher.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100890/249228/shibusd-2023-01-11-14-45-07.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="446944"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 11th January – MEMAG, XRP,  FGHT, SHIB, CCHG, BNB, RIA, MATIC, D2T</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-11th-january-memag-xrp-fght-shib-cchg-bnb-ria-matic-d2t.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has crept up by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, reaching a total cap of $894 billion. This means it has risen by around 6.5% in the past week, although it's mostly unchanged in the past month and still significantly down compared to this time last year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-11th-january-memag-xrp-fght-shib-cchg-bnb-ria-matic-d2t.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 11th January – MEMAG, XRP,  FGHT, SHIB, CCHG, BNB, RIA, MATIC, D2T&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-11th-january-memag-xrp-fght-shib-cchg-bnb-ria-matic-d2t.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100856/249219/best-crypto-11th-jan.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="402390"/></item><item><title>Did Sam Bankman-Fried in Effect Pay VC Firms Like Paradigm to Invest in FTX in a Circular Funding Arrangement?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/did-sam-bankman-fried-in-effect-pay-vc-firms-like-paradigm-to-invest-in-ftx-in-a-circular-funding-arrangement.htm</link><description>New revelations indicate that there were some close links between Sam Bankman-Fried, the disgraced founder of collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX, and some of his major backers. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a new report by the Financial Times, Bankman-Fried invested $20 million in a fund managed by crypto venture capital firm Paradigm in late 2021. The same fund later invested in FTX and FTX US exchanges....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/did-sam-bankman-fried-in-effect-pay-vc-firms-like-paradigm-to-invest-in-ftx-in-a-circular-funding-arrangement.htm"&gt;Read More: Did Sam Bankman-Fried in Effect Pay VC Firms Like Paradigm to Invest in FTX in a Circular Funding Arrangement?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>Paradigm</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/did-sam-bankman-fried-in-effect-pay-vc-firms-like-paradigm-to-invest-in-ftx-in-a-circular-funding-arrangement.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100866/249204/sam-bankman-fried-media-library-original-1200-766.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="61980"/></item><item><title>This is Why Crypto Prices Could Be Set For a Sustained Rally in 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/why-crypto-prices-could-set-for-sustained-rally-2023.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has posted a 1% gain in the past 24 hours, with its total cap reaching $894 billion. This represents a 6.5% increase in the last two weeks,  signalling a hope that the market may have turned a corner after a difficult 2022. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/why-crypto-prices-could-set-for-sustained-rally-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: This is Why Crypto Prices Could Be Set For a Sustained Rally in 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/why-crypto-prices-could-set-for-sustained-rally-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100835/249191/why-crypto-prices-could-be-set-for-a-sustained-rally-in-2023.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="146408"/></item><item><title>US Investors Drop Terraform Labs Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-investors-drop-terraform-labs-lawsuit.htm</link><description>The American investment firm Albright Capital has pulled out of a class action lawsuit against Terraform Labs, the firm behind the Terra protocol and the Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) coin. &lt;br /&gt;
Per court documents, Albright – along with its fellow claimants, the legal firms Scott &amp; Scott and Bragar Eagel &amp; Squire – voluntarily retracted its claims “without prejudice and without costs against the defendant(s)” at a branch of the New York Southern District Court....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-investors-drop-terraform-labs-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: US Investors Drop Terraform Labs Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra</category><category>Legal</category><category>Do Kwon</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-investors-drop-terraform-labs-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100852/249187/adobestock-10089072.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2679133"/></item><item><title>Crypto Boss Mike Novogratz Says Its Time to Cut Costs and Survive This ‘Transition period’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-boss-mike-novogratz-says-its-time-to-cut-costs-and-survive-this-transition-period.htm</link><description>Michael Novogratz, the founder of the US-based crypto financial services firm Galaxy Digital Holdings, argued that the events of 2022 have 'cleansed' the industry and that it is now time to survive the "transition period".  &lt;br /&gt;
Talking to CNBC on Tuesday, Novogratz said that 2022 was a "grand washout" for the crypto industry, explaining that everything that had high costs and shrinking revenues "got hammered."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-boss-mike-novogratz-says-its-time-to-cut-costs-and-survive-this-transition-period.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Boss Mike Novogratz Says Its Time to Cut Costs and Survive This ‘Transition period’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Mike Novogratz</category><category>Market</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Genesis</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-boss-mike-novogratz-says-its-time-to-cut-costs-and-survive-this-transition-period.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100826/249159/snapshot-media-library-original-912-608.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="45052"/></item></channel></rss>
