<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 09:41:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>21Shares&#8217; New ETP Provides Exposure to PoS Cryptocurrencies But No ETH</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/21shares-new-etp-provides-exposure-to-pos-cryptocurrencies-but-no-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 23:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake (PoS)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233813</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/21Shares.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/21Shares.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Zug-based crypto firm is now eyeing to list the new product on Xetra Deutsche Boerse.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>21Shares announced the launch of first-of-its-kind crypto staking index ETP focused on proof-of-stake-based coins.</p>
<p>Dubbed 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP (STAKE), the product will essentially provide exposure to staking rewards while tracking the performance of underlying staked coins via a single ETP.</p>
<h2>World&#8217;s First Crypto Staking Index ETP</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/21shares-unveils-worlds-first-crypto-staking-index-etp-301723801.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, the index will track ten crypto-assets, including Binance Coin (BNB), Cardano (ADA), Cosmos (ATOM), Polkadot (DOT), Solana (SOL), and Tezos (XTZ).</p>
<p>It is expected to address demands from both retail and institutional investors across the world.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that STAKE is designed to track PoS-based coins, the product, however, does not include Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p>In a statement, the company further revealed that the index will rebalance in March and September on a semi-annual basis to demonstrate shifts in the crypto market.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s parent firm, 21.co&#8217;s Director of ETP Product, <span class="xn-person">Arthur Krause highlighted the increased investor demand for &#8220;diversified, crypto-native return streams,&#8221; especially amid the bear market. Staking, for one, was touted as one of the most attractive of them all. </span></p>
<p>He went on to add,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In particular, we&#8217;ve heard demand for a reliable and safe way to access staking, one of the most attractive potential return streams available in the crypto ecosystem. The 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP does just that, and will be an attractive addition to many portfolios.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP, which was made available on for trading on January 18th on the BX Swiss exchange, was developed in collaboration with Swedish index provider Vinter.</p>
<p>Its CEO, Jacob Lindberg, said the two firms will continue to work on launching more investment products that &#8220;build bridges into the crypto world.&#8221;</p>
<h2>21Shares&#8217; Expansion and More</h2>
<p>With the latest launch, 21Shares and it&#8217;s parent firm listed more than 40 products across 12 exchanges in 8 countries.</p>
<p>Last October, the Swiss fintech company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/21shares-focuses-on-the-middle-east-by-rolling-out-a-bitcoin-etp-on-nasdaq-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> Bitcoin exchange-traded product on Nasdaq Dubai. This marked the first physically-backed BTC ETP in the Middle East.</p>
<p>21.co, on the other hand, fetched $25 million in a funding round in September. The move catapulted its valuation to $2 billion, and made it &#8220;Switzerland’s largest crypto unicorn.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/21shares-new-etp-provides-exposure-to-pos-cryptocurrencies-but-no-eth/" rel="nofollow">21Shares&#8217; New ETP Provides Exposure to PoS Cryptocurrencies But No ETH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum on the Verge of Huge Milestone Following Bullish Start of 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-on-the-verge-of-huge-milestone-following-bullish-start-of-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 20:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233820</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETH_addresses_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETH_addresses_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ETH's price is not the only thing going up during the latest rally.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ETH&#8217;s price is rallying throughout the past couple of weeks. But that&#8217;s not the only news adding to Ethereum&#8217;s bullish momentum this month. The decentralized computer network is closing in on 100 million Ethereum addresses.</p>
<p>Crypto prices continue to swell with capital inflows as we enter the second half of January. Positive macroeconomic data continues to work its magic on asset valuations across the board.</p>
<p>The S&amp;P 500 Index and NASDAQ Composite have continued their new year rally with crypto prices in tow. The strengthening <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stocks-correlation-surges-after-decoupling-from-wall-st-amid-ftx-drama/" data-wpel-link="internal">correlation between crypto prices and stock prices</a> indicates crypto&#8217;s maturity and adoption at this stage.</p>
<p>But the reviving Ethereum price action is not the only long-term bullish indicator materializing at the moment. Activity and usage of the Ethereum network keep sailing to new all-time highs.</p>
<h2>A Major Milestone</h2>
<p>The number of Ethereum addresses with a nonzero balance keeps running higher. It reached a record high of 92.5 million addresses this week, according to fresh data from Glassnode.</p>
<p>Active addresses on Ethereum <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/metrics?a=ETH&amp;amp%3Bamp=1&amp;amp%3Bm=distribution.BalanceExchanges&amp;m=addresses.ActiveCount" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">are also on the rise</a>, with a heavy spike in recent activity.</p>
<p>Active addresses are a measure of the number of unique addresses that are transacted as a sender or receiver. Only those that successfully completed a transaction are counted.</p>
<p>So, Ethereum users aren&#8217;t just holding their Ether. They&#8217;re using it to run programs on the network. Even though the crypto price winter took out some crypto exchanges and custodians, it has not paused demand for new addresses and transactions.</p>
<p>While the drama and scandal of these crypto startup failures make for some wild headlines, it doesn&#8217;t paint a true picture of the progress the crypto ecosystem is making in development, adoption, and usage.</p>
<p>At its current rate of growth, Ethereum addresses could hit the 100 million mark by Q2 2023.</p>
<h2>The Ethereum Network Lives</h2>
<p>The number of unique Ethereum addresses is seen as a good proxy indicator of the overall level of adoption. It shows Ethereum adoption is on the march.</p>
<p>Day traders aren&#8217;t just pushing the line for the Ethereum price up and down on a candlestick chart. People are actually adopting and using decentralized finance applications and paying ETH for gas fees to run them.</p>
<p>Here are some interesting ways <a href="https://consensys.net/blog/news/90-ethereum-apps-you-can-use-right-now/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">people are using Ethereum</a> in a list made by Consensys.</p>
<p>Over at NPR&#8217;s Business Desk, David Gura <a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/01/18/1149002158/cryptocurrencies-ftx-bitcoin-sam-bankman-fried-sec-collapse" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wrote Wednesday</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The fallout from the catastrophic collapse of crypto exchange FTX is spreading, and a so-called &#8220;crypto winter,&#8221; which has dragged on for months, shows no signs of letting up.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-on-the-verge-of-huge-milestone-following-bullish-start-of-2023/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum on the Verge of Huge Milestone Following Bullish Start of 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>60% of North Americans Invest in Crypto Without Doing Due Diligence: Study</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/60-of-north-americans-invest-in-crypto-without-doing-due-diligence-study/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 17:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233950</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/AmericaCrypto.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/AmericaCrypto.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[15% of North Americans don't do any research before investing in crypto, while 49% spend less than two hours.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a study by Bybit and Toluna, 64% of North Americans spend less than two hours or don&#8217;t research at all before investing in cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Boomers (those aged 56-64) tend to be more cautious, focusing on technical factors and inspecting the market a few days before diving into it.</p>
<h2>Jumping on the Bandwagon Without Proper Analysis</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Bybit &#8211; and the consumer intelligence platform &#8211; Toluna &#8211; <a href="https://www.bybit.com/common-static/fhs/BybitxTolunaJointResearchReport-5e44e7cf355184e247d67e63009d20c5.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">surveyed</a> over 10,000 individuals to determine whether they follow appropriate due diligence procedures prior to allocating funds in digital currencies.</p>
<p>Nearly 50% of the North American respondents admitted becoming HODLers after evaluating the pros and cons for just a couple of hours, while 15% said they rely entirely on social media and advice from friends.</p>
<p>Younger generations are more likely to neglect the due diligence process than the older. 33% of Gen X and 47% of Boomers spend at least a few days before investing in a cryptocurrency project.</p>
<p>The study further revealed that over 1,700 of the participants have already bought digital assets. 50% don&#8217;t view stricter regulatory standards as a concern, while 25% would support enhanced supervision on centralized exchanges to get additional protection.</p>
<p>Know Your Customer verification seems to have little effect on users when choosing a platform, with 50% saying they don&#8217;t have any preference on the type of requirements. On the other hand, 21% would pick a trading venue that does not impose such validation.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In an ideal world, it is understandable why some might oppose KYC verifications. However, in reality, the abuse of the system by malicious individuals needs to be prevented. Thus giving rise to the need for such forms of protection, not just for the exchanges but for the users,&#8221; the report explained.</p></blockquote>
<p>Bybit and Toluna also outlined that KYC requirements are useful tools that could prevent cybercrime and hacks, which &#8220;ultimately contribute largely to the safety and security of the ecosystem.&#8221;</p>
<h2>CEXs Are More Trusted Than Banks</h2>
<p>The analysis showed that cryptocurrency investors have more faith in centralized exchanges than traditional banks, Internet providers, local governments, and NFTs. It is worth noting that even DeFi believers put high trust scores on CEXs.</p>
<p>Such platforms have been in the spotlight after<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the collapse of FTX</a>. Many presented proof-of-reserves to customers to display they have no liquidity issues. Despite that, a significant number of investors transferred their holdings to self-custody wallets or cashed out in the weeks after the infamous crash.</p>
<p>The world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange &#8211; Binance &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-processes-close-to-8-billion-in-daily-withdrawals-cz-says-it-wasnt-a-even-top-5/" data-wpel-link="internal">processed</a> over $8 billion in daily withdrawals in mid-December. CEO Changpeng Zhao seemed unconcerned, viewing it as a &#8220;stress test&#8221; that could show the trading venue could honor a large number of requests at any time.</p>
<p>He <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1602905590384181248" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">argued</a> that the withdrawal wave resulted from a FUD, saying users should feel free to store their crypto holdings in cold wallets if they have concerns. &#8220;Otherwise, we are here,&#8221; he assured.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/60-of-north-americans-invest-in-crypto-without-doing-due-diligence-study/" rel="nofollow">60% of North Americans Invest in Crypto Without Doing Due Diligence: Study</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Became Greener and More Efficient in 2022</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-became-greener-and-more-efficient-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 14:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234091</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/bitcoing_green_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/bitcoing_green_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s sustainable energy mix is roughly 58.9% sustainable as of Q4 2022. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite much turmoil in 2022, the Bitcoin mining industry’s hashing technology only continued to grow more efficient throughout the year, according to a new survey from the Bitcoin Mining Council (BMC). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The industry also grew marginally greener, retaining a sustainable energy mix of over 58%.</span></p>
<h2>Bitcoin is Green, Says BMC</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a </span><a href="https://bitcoinminingcouncil.com/bitcoin-mining-council-survey-confirms-year-on-year-improvements-in-sustainable-power-mix-and-technological-efficiency-in-q4-2022/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">press release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on Thursday, the BMC confirmed that its members’ hashrate has increased from 95 exahashes from its inception in Q1 2022 to 119 exahashes by Q4 2022. An exahash is equal to 1 quintillion hashes – answers to a complex math problem produced by miners in a race to create Bitcoin’s next block. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BMC represents 48.4% of Bitcoin’s global hash rate, meaning its collective increase in hashrate has implications for the entire network. A higher hashrate forces Bitcoin’s difficulty to adjust higher, increasing the network’s security and settlement assurance. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Powering those computers costs a lot of electricity, but the BMC argues that its electricity sources are primarily clean – and its use is highly efficient.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“The results of this survey show that the members of the BMC and participants in the survey are currently utilizing electricity with a 63.8% sustainable power mix,” read the group’s statement. “Based on this data, the global bitcoin mining industry’s sustainable electricity mix has improved marginally to 58.9% and remains one of the most sustainable industries globally.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin’s proof of work mechanism is often derided for incentivizing network users to consume vast amounts of electricity. According to the Cambridge Bitcoin Electricity Consumption Index, the network currently consumes roughly 102.91 TWh per year – more than all of Finland. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mining proponents, however, contend that this mix is </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/norway-is-producing-1-of-btc-hash-rate-using-renewable-energy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">largely renewable</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – and set to become cleaner over time as miners seek out the world’s cheapest energy sources. Furthermore, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-in-texas-halt-operations-due-to-a-severe-heat-wave/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">curtailment programs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can effectively prevent the mining industry from draining energy from those who need it most in times of peak demand. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“In Q4 2022, we also saw a significant increase in curtailment, with 14 BMC members reporting 2.5 GW worth of Bitcoin mining operations participating in curtailment programs and 1,280 GWh of energy released back to local grids during times of peak demand,” said Ben Gagnon, Chief Mining Officer of Bitfarms.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Year over year, the mining network’s technological efficiency also grew by 16%, “from 19.3 EH per gigawatt (GW) in Q4 2021 to 22.4 EH per GW in Q4 2022.”</span></p>
<h2>Is Proof of Stake Better?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To virtually do away with Bitcoin’s energy consumption, some figures have spoken in favor of transitioning it to a proof of stake consensus mechanism. Such people include Commodities and Futures Trading Commission chairman Rostin Benham and Ripple co-founder </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-co-founder-donates-5m-to-environmental-campaign-against-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chris Larsen</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Proof of Stake lets users stake their cryptocurrency holdings to provide financial security for the network rather than energy. Ethereum adopted this technology last September, reducing its total energy consumption by 99.9%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoiners, however, are largely opposed to the move. The Bitcoin Mining Council and other community figureheads issued a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-community-sends-letter-to-epa-debunking-proof-of-work-fud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">letter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to the Environmental Protection Agency in May, arguing that proof of stake is unsuited to “govern a global, apolitical monetary system.”</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-became-greener-and-more-efficient-in-2022/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Mining Became Greener and More Efficient in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Feds Confiscate Nearly $700M of Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Assets: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-feds-confiscate-nearly-700m-of-sam-bankman-frieds-assets-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 12:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234290</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Sam-Bankman-Fried-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Sam-Bankman-Fried-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The court filings have, so far, disclosed only the accounts and the Robinhood shares. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Federal prosecutors have confiscated nearly $700 million in cash and assets connected to Sam Bankman-Fried, the disgraced founder of FTX.</p>
<p>At the heart of the seizure are the 55 million Robinhood shares owned by Bankman-Fried and Gary Wang, valued at over $455 million. The ownership of the shares has been disputed even by BlockFi and FTX creditor Yonathan Ben Shimon who laid claims over them. The Feds, for one, believe they were purchased using allegedly stolen funds of FTX customers.</p>
<h2>Assets Seized</h2>
<p>The CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/01/20/feds-seize-almost-700-million-of-sam-bankman-frieds-assets-in-cash-and-equity.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> identified three accounts by FTX Digital Markets on Silvergate Bank, which held over $6 million. These assets were seized around January 11. A rural Washington state bank, Moonstone Bank, also had ties to FTX management and held nearly $50 million, which is now in the custody of the US government.</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230119005836/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, the bank said that it will be exiting the crypto space and will instead return to its &#8220;original mission&#8221; as a community bank.</p>
<p>Assets were seized from one Binance and two Binance.US account numbers, but the Feds have been tight-lipped about the values. Over $20 million held under Emergent Fidelity Technologies was also subjected to forfeiture.</p>
<p>FTX’s chief restructuring officer, John J. Ray III, along with its new management, has tracked down billions of dollars of assets linked to the Bankman-Fried&#8217;s crypto empire as part of bankruptcy proceedings. The former CEO pleaded not guilty to eight criminal <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-closer-look-at-what-sam-bankman-fried-is-accused-of-exactly/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">charges</a>, including wire fraud and violations of campaign finance laws, after his extradition to the United States from the Bahamas.</p>
<h2>Aftermath SBF&#8217;s Bail</h2>
<p>Following his bail, new details <a href="https://www.businessinsider.in/tech/news/sam-bankman-frieds-2-mysterious-bail-sponsors-ponied-up-a-total-of-700000-to-get-the-alleged-fraudster-out-of-jail/articleshow/97183821.cms" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">surfaced</a> regarding two anonymous persons, in addition to his parents, that co-sponsored a total of $700,000 on bond for Bankman-Fried&#8217;s bail. One individual poured in $500,000, while the other put $200,000 to help get him out of jail. However, their names were redacted by the court after lawyers representing the FTX founder raised concerns about their safety.</p>
<p>The former crypto mogul previously argued that his family became a target of &#8220;intense media scrutiny, harassment, received threats of physical harm&#8221; after the exchange slid into bankruptcy, trapping billions of investor funds.</p>
<p>More recently, in a filing with the Manhattan federal court, SBF lawyers <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-us-president-shares-what-destroyed-his-relationship-with-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">claimed</a> that three men drove their vehicle into a metal barricade outside his parent’s house in California and even threatened the security officer stationed there.</p>
<p>The 30-year-old was granted bail on a $250 million bond accompanied by several conditions. His criminal trial is scheduled to begin in October this year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-feds-confiscate-nearly-700m-of-sam-bankman-frieds-assets-report/" rel="nofollow">US Feds Confiscate Nearly $700M of Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s Assets: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Market Cap Reclaims $1T as SOL, OKB, APT Explode by Double Digits: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-reclaims-1t-as-sol-okb-apt-explode-by-double-digits-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234304</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOL_OKB_APT_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOL_OKB_APT_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto market cap is above $1 trillion following the latest 2023 rally. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin soared by roughly $2,000 in the past several, charting its highest price position since mid-September.</p>
<p>The altcoins are well in the green as well, with some, such as SOL and OKB, posting massive double-digit price increases.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Sees 18-Week High</h2>
<p>The latest bitcoin surge came amid <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-on-chain-factors-suggest-bitcoins-bull-run-could-have-started-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">five bullish on-chain factors</a> provided by CryptoQuant earlier this week. The asset had calmed after touching $21,600 and had retraced to just under $21,000.</p>
<p>The bulls had a battle that continued for a few days seems to be won, at least for now, as BTC went through one of its most impressive overnight price surges in a while. It took it from below $21,000 to inches away from $23,000.</p>
<p>Although it has still been unable to tap that level as of now, touching $22,800 is the highest price tag bitcoin has seen in 18 weeks. Somewhat expectedly, this price surge caused losses <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/300m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-soars-to-18-week-high/" data-wpel-link="internal">worth millions of dollars</a> for over-leveraged traders, with the majority being short positions.</p>
<p>The price pump has helped BTC&#8217;s market cap to increase to almost $440 billion. Its dominance over the altcoins is also on the rise and is up to 42%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234305" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234305" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234305" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-21-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234305" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>APT, SOL, OKB Skyrocket</h2>
<p>Although BTC&#8217;s market dominance is increasing, several altcoins are actually outperforming the largest digital asset on a daily scale. Among those, Aptos&#8217; native token has taken the main stage with a mind-blowing 57% surge. As a result, APT has marked a multi-month high above $12.</p>
<p>Next in line from the larger-cap altcoins are Solana, OKB, MANA, SAND, ICP, VET, HBAR, NEAR, and ATOM. All of those have skyrocketed by between 10% and 20% overnight.</p>
<p>Ethereum is at $1,650 after a 6.5% increase. Binance Coin has reclaimed $300 following a 5.5% jump.</p>
<p>All of these price jumps have helped the crypto market cap to surge above $1 trillion on CoinMarketCap as well.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234306" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234306" style="width: 1855px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234306" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1855" height="732" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14.jpg 1855w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14-300x118.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14-1024x404.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14-768x303.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14-1536x606.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-14-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1855px) 100vw, 1855px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234306" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-reclaims-1t-as-sol-okb-apt-explode-by-double-digits-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Market Cap Reclaims $1T as SOL, OKB, APT Explode by Double Digits: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>$300M Shorts Liquidated as Bitcoin Soars to 18-Week High</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/300m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-soars-to-18-week-high/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 06:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234294</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinRocket.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinRocket.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin and most altcoins have exploded for a second consecutive Saturday.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a few days of trading sideways and even slipping below $21,000, the bitcoin bulls returned on Saturday morning to push the asset to its highest price tag since September 13.</p>
<p>With most altcoins well in the green as well, the number of liquidated short traders has soared.</p>
<ul>
<li>The start of 2023 continues to bring good news for the bitcoin bulls, which were quite dishearted following the painful 2022. However, BTC had added over $5,000 in the first few weeks of the new year and had tapped $21,500 to mark a multi-month high a few days ago.</li>
<li>The end of last week was significantly calmer, with bitcoin sitting around $21,000 and the bulls <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bulls-fight-for-21k-nexo-explodes-12-daily-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">having to fight</a> for that level, despite the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-on-chain-factors-suggest-bitcoins-bull-run-could-have-started-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">numerous positive signs</a> suggesting the end of the bear market.</li>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/600m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-skyrockets-to-21k/" data-wpel-link="internal">Similar</a> to last Saturday morning, though, they seem to be getting the upper hand in this battle as they pushed bitcoin not only beyond $21,000 but also above $22,000. In fact, BTC tapped an intraday high of just under $22,800. This is the highest it has been in over three months.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_234295" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234295" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234295" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-20-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234295" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li>Most altcoins have followed suit. Ethereum has skyrocketed above $1,600 following a 6.5% daily increase. Solana and OKB have taken the lead with massive double-digit price pumps. Consequently, SOL sits close to $25, while OKB is at $35.</li>
<li>The crypto market cap has also reclaimed the coveted $1 trillion mark even on CoinMarketCap. Naturally, these explosive moves have harmed short traders.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">total value of liquidated positions</a> in the past 24 hours is just under $300 million, $245 million of which are from short traders.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/300m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-soars-to-18-week-high/" rel="nofollow">$300M Shorts Liquidated as Bitcoin Soars to 18-Week High</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CleanSpark Kicksoff 50MW Bitcoin Mining Expansion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cleanspark-kicksoff-50mw-bitcoin-mining-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 05:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234049</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CleanSpark had acquired the site last summer for $16.2 million. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin mining company &#8211; CleanSpark &#8211; has started the construction of the second phase on a site in Washington, Georgia, that is set to accommodate 16,000 miners. This move is expected to increase its hash rate total to as high as 8.7 EH/s, thereby contributing an additional 2.2 EH/s.</p>
<p>In the new phase, the mining machine fleet will include &#8211; Antminer S19j Pro and Antminer S19 XP &#8211; which are considered to be the latest and most power-efficient models of such machines currently available.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Mining Expansion</h2>
<p>Based on the final number of each model in the mix, the total computing power that will be added to CleanSpark’s bitcoin mining capacity will range from 25% to 34% increase from its current hash rate of 6.5 EH/s. Zach Bradford, CleanSpark&#8217;s Chief Executive Officer, said the company was fairly confident about expanding quickly after purchasing the site and adding this 50MW to the existing 36MW of infrastructure.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/01/19/2591858/0/en/CleanSpark-Breaks-Ground-on-50-Megawatt-Bitcoin-Mining-Expansion.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, the exec said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This second phase more than doubles the size of the existing operation. We are looking forward to expanding our relationship with the Washington City community and to be able to support the construction jobs that will come with this expansion.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The construction of the second phase is projected to be completed by late spring.</p>
<h2>CleanSpark&#8217;s Focus on Low-Carbon Sources of Energy</h2>
<p>The announcement comes amidst a struggling market with several mining companies filing for bankruptcy, while more casualties are expected this year. CleanSpark, for one, claims to have ramped up its hash rate from 2.1 EH/s, in January 2022, to 6.2 EH/s, in December 2022, despite a downturn. It did so by selling a major portion of its mined BTC to reinvest in growth by following a &#8220;capital management strategy.&#8221;</p>
<p>CleanSpark also claims to mine mainly with renewable or low-carbon sources of energy. In fact, the company&#8217;s first phase of the site primarily uses low-carbon sources of power. As noted by Scott Garrison, Vice President of Business Development, the Georgia site also employs the newest generation technology and is among the most power-efficient and sustainable Bitcoin mining operations.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Georgia has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/georgia-becomes-an-attractive-area-for-american-bitcoin-miners-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">attracted</a> several miners over the past couple of years with its relatively low energy prices. It also offers a considerable amount of nuclear and solar power, enabling entities to brand themselves as &#8220;sustainable and green-oriented.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cleanspark-kicksoff-50mw-bitcoin-mining-expansion/" rel="nofollow">CleanSpark Kicksoff 50MW Bitcoin Mining Expansion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Car Crashed Into the Barricade of SBF&#8217;s Current Home, Lawyers Said</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/a-car-crashed-into-the-barricade-of-sbfs-current-home-lawyers-said/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 01:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234158</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["You won't be able to keep us out," the three men threatened before leaving the scene.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawyers of Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) цлаимед that three men drove their vehicle into a metal barricade outside his parents&#8217; house in California. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The family of FTX&#8217;s former CEO recently admitted becoming a target of &#8220;intense media scrutiny, harassment,&#8221; and even physical threats.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Security Incident</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The gigantic crash of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> caused multi-billion investor losses and turned SBF into one of the most infamous figures in the cryptocurrency space. The US authorities </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-closer-look-at-what-sam-bankman-fried-is-accused-of-exactly/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the 30-year-old of being the main culprit behind the collapse, committing several crimes such as money laundering and fraud.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Somewhat expectedly, the wave of criticism spread across affected investors, many of whom also blamed him for the event.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His attorneys recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/car-drove-into-barricade-outside-bankman-frieds-home-lawyers-say-2023-01-20/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that three individuals crashed their car into the barricade of his current home and told a security officer:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;You won&#8217;t be able to keep us out.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Then they got back in the vehicle and drove away without being recognized. The man guarding the home in Palo Alto could not record the car&#8217;s license plate.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The incident happened nearly a month after a New York federal judge </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">allowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> SBF to live at his parents&#8217; house on a record $250 million bond. Prior to that, he spent a week in the Bahamian Fox Hill Prison, while the trial on October 2, 2023, will rule whether he played a role in the FTX demise and determine his final sentence. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawyers </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/bankman-frieds-parents-have-been-physically-threatened-his-lawyers-say-2023-01-03/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">disclosed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this month that his mother &#8211; Barbara Fried &#8211; and father &#8211; Joseph Bankman &#8211; have received &#8220;a steady stream of threatening correspondence, including communications expressing a desire that they suffer physical harm.&#8221; </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Who Allowed the Bond?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The $250 million bond that enabled SBF to await his trial at his parents&#8217; house sparked significant controversy in the crypto community. As such, leading media outlets, including Bloomberg, CNBC, The Financial Times, The Washington Post, and others, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/major-media-want-know-who-guaranteed-sam-bankman-frieds-250-million-bond-2023-01-12/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">urged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the judge overseeing the case to reveal the names of the people who allowed it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SBF&#8217;s lawyers declined to provide details on the request, explaining there was a high chance those sureties suffer similar harassment like Ms. Fried and Mr. Bankman should their profiles become publicly known: </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Given the notoriety of this case and the extraordinary media attention it is receiving, it is reasonable to assume that the non-parent sureties will face significant privacy and safety concerns if their identities are disclosed.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prosecutors have not yet taken any steps to honor the appeal of the media outlets. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-car-crashed-into-the-barricade-of-sbfs-current-home-lawyers-said/" rel="nofollow">A Car Crashed Into the Barricade of SBF&#8217;s Current Home, Lawyers Said</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Has $226 Million in Claims Against FTX</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-has-226-million-in-claims-against-ftx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234273</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Bankruptcy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Bankruptcy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Genesis Global Capital is FTX’s largest unsecured creditor, according to the exchange’s latest filings. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Genesis – a top crypto lending unit that filed for bankruptcy on Thursday – was listed as FTX’s top unsecured creditor within the exchange’s own bankruptcy documents.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The firm has an unliquidated claim against FTX worth $226 million. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Per FTX’s Thursday </span><a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DocketInfo" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, the defunct exchange has ten customers to whom it owes over $100 million each. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">While an earlier version of the filing already showed claims from FTX’s top 50 creditors, the revised version has revealed the names of those appointed by the U.S. Trustee in the case to the Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors. One of those appointed was Genesis – FTX’s top creditor. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Some of the few other names that are no longer redacted include the Hong Kong-based crypto trading firm Pulsar Global, individual creditor Larry Qian, and crypto market maker </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-maker-wintermute-hackers-drain-160m-profanity-bug-suspected/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Wintermute</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. Each party is owed $92.9 million, $91.1 million, and $33 million respectively. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Genesis itself </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcgs-subsidiary-genesis-global-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">filed for bankruptcy</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Thursday after failing to raise fresh capital in the aftermath of FTX’s collapse. The company claimed to have $5.1 billion in liabilities. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In November, Genesis claimed to have $175 million trapped inside of FTX.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-has-226-million-in-claims-against-ftx/" rel="nofollow">Genesis Has $226 Million in Claims Against FTX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
