<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 16:35:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US SEC Charges 8 People and Businesses Linked to a $45 Million Crypto Scam</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-charges-8-people-and-businesses-linked-to-a-45-million-crypto-scam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 23:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231818</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/US_SEC4.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/US_SEC4.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC accused eight individuals and organizations of stealing $45 million from investors via their CoinDeal crypto project.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) charged Neil Chandran and seven other individuals and entities for orchestrating the fraudulent cryptocurrency investment scheme called CoinDeal. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The suspects allegedly defrauded investors with around $45 million over the years and used the money to buy real estate, cars, and a boat.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Halting the Crime</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Neil Chandran, Michael Glaspie, Garry Davidson, Linda Knott, Amy Mossel, AEO Publishing Inc, Banner Co-Op, Inc, and BannersGo, LLC of embezzling $45 million from consumers through their fraudulent entity CoinDeal. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The individuals promised to sell the blockchain-based project to a group of prominent buyers which would guarantee great returns for investors. They also deceived them about CoinDeal&#8217;s valuation and the companies involved in the potential acquisition deal.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The defendants ran their scheme between January 2019 and 2022. CoinDeal&#8217;s sale never happened, and investors did not receive any distributions for their involvement in the project. The SEC further maintained that Chandran, Glaspie, Davidson, Knott, and Mossel used the amassed $45 million to purchase cars, properties, and a boat. Daniel Gregus &#8211; Director of the SEC&#8217;s Chicago Regional Office &#8211; commented:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We allege the defendants falsely claimed access to valuable blockchain technology and that the imminent sale of the technology would generate investment returns of more than 500,000 times for investors.</span></p>
<p>As alleged in our complaint, in reality, this was all just an elaborate scheme where the defendants enriched themselves while defrauding tens of thousands of retail investors.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Department of Justice previously arrested Chandran for offenses related to wire fraud and engaging in illicit money transactions while being part of CoinDeal.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Commission seeks to impose penalties and permanent injunctions against all defendants. At the same time, it insists that Chandran should be a subject of a conduct-based injunction. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC&#8217;s Previous Hunt</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-sues-owner-of-alleged-ponzi-like-cryptocurrency-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> another investigation against two advisory companies and their owner &#8211; Gabriel Edelman &#8211; for running a Ponzi-like cryptocurrency scheme in September last year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organizations supposedly operated between February 2017 and May 2021, raising nearly $4.4 million from investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Edelman promised he would invest the capital in cryptocurrencies purchased at discounted rates. However, he funneled &#8220;only a small portion of investor funds in digital assets,&#8221; using the rest to buy personal items and send money to family members. The SEC explained in detail how Edelman&#8217;s Ponzi scheme worked:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;For example, one Investor initially invested $50,000. Edelman returned $75,000 within a few months, and the Investor subsequently invested an additional $600,000. Edelman then returned $720,000 a few months later. After that, the Investor invested $1,000,000–based on purported past performance and Edelman&#8217;s promise that the Investor would receive a 15% return. Thereafter, Edelman did not return any funds to that Investor.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-charges-8-people-and-businesses-linked-to-a-45-million-crypto-scam/" rel="nofollow">US SEC Charges 8 People and Businesses Linked to a $45 Million Crypto Scam</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>$3.8B of Cumulative Volume Moved Overseas Since Indian Crypto Taxes Kicked In</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3-8b-of-cumulative-volume-moved-overseas-since-indian-crypto-taxes-kicked-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231600</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/india-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/india-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[India introduced two new taxes on crypto transactions - 30% capital gains tax and 1% transaction tax as TDS - effective April 1, 2022.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Indian crypto exchanges lost a significant portion of their trading volume after new taxes for the sector came into force, the losses, so far, were referred to in percentage terms, with most estimates quoting them to be above 90%, compared to the previous year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Now, a new study has quantified the value of cumulative trading that shifted from Indian to foreign crypto exchanges after the new taxes kicked in.</span></p>
<p><em>CryptoPotato</em> reported earlier that Indian traders are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/traders-flock-to-binance-as-new-taxes-send-indian-exchanges-out-of-business-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">flocking</a> to foreign exchanges after the tax and regulatory environment in the country has become &#8220;<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-has-no-big-plans-for-india-due-to-high-taxation-says-cz/" data-wpel-link="internal">unviable</a>.&#8221;</p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">$3.8 Billion Moved</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Esya Centre, an Indian think tank on technology policy matters, in a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.esyacentre.org/documents/2022/12/12/virtual-digital-asset-tax-architecture-in-india-a-critical-examination" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> published on January 3, said that Rs. 32,000 crores ($3.85 billion) of cumulative trade volume shifted from Indian crypto exchanges to foreign competitors between February and October 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report, titled &#8220;Virtual Digital Asset Tax Architecture in India: A Critical Examination,&#8221; examines how the new taxes for the domestic crypto market proposed in the Union budget 2022-23 on February 1 impacted the overall business in this sector.  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It said Rs. 25,300 crores ($3.05 billion) of cumulative trading moved out of Indian crypto exchanges in the six months to October 2022, that is, since the new taxes became effective on April 1. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Taking peer-to-peer trade into account, the total contribution of trade volume from India to foreign exchanges is to the tune of Rs. 80,000 crores ($9.67 billion), the Esya Centre report said.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;India’s tax treatment of VDAs is regressive in comparison to other countries with high VDA adoption rates, such as the USA, UK, South Africa, Vietnam, Philippines, and Brazil,&#8221; it claimed.  </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fall in Volume </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decline in trading volume came in a phased manner, the report said, with the initial onslaught claiming 15% of the trading volume coming in the first two months since the tax amendment made by Indian Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her budget speech on February 1, 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another 14% was lost in the three months since April 2022, when the 30% tax on crypto gains became effective. The steep taxation was implemented without the provision to set off losses against profits.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The third and final blow arrived when a 1% transaction tax came into force on July 1, 2022, which eroded up to 81% of the trading volume from the Indian exchanges, the report said.     </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Many Indian VDA users seem to be switching from domestic centralised VDA exchanges to foreign counterparts (an estimated 17 lakh users switched in the period analysed), a trend visible starting Feb 2022 (i.e. following from the Union Budget announcement),&#8221; the report claimed. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-8b-of-cumulative-volume-moved-overseas-since-indian-crypto-taxes-kicked-in/" rel="nofollow">$3.8B of Cumulative Volume Moved Overseas Since Indian Crypto Taxes Kicked In</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Despite SEC Battle, XRP Investment Products Saw Record Inflows in 2022: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/despite-sec-battle-xrp-investment-products-saw-record-inflows-in-2022-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231640</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple_XRP.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ripple_XRP.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the incessant tepid price action, market players choosing to invest are tactically adding to positions during price weakness.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 saw many crypto-assets lose value, prompting investors to pull their money from the market. During turbulent times, inflows plummeted massively.</p>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-112-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-e00679d7fea6" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by CoinShares, the digital asset inflow was recorded at $433 million, the lowest in four years. The last time figures were hovering near the current level was in 2018, when inflows stood at $233 million.</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin saw the third-worst year for inflows with $287 million after declining by well over 60% this year.</li>
<li>Multi-asset investment products recorded inflows of just $209 million.</li>
<li>The Merge was the biggest highlight in the Ethereum ecosystem. But investor concerns over a successful transition to proof of stake (PoS) translated into outflows of $402 million.</li>
<li>The figure was in a sharp reversal compared to the previous two years when Ethereum saw massive inflows of more than $1.8 billion and $920 million, respectively.</li>
<li>Other altcoins that bore the brunt of the tumultuous year were Binance Coin (BNB) with $24 million and Tron (TRX) with $3 million outflows.</li>
<li>On the other hand, Litecoin (LTC) and Polygon (MATIC) oriented products registered inflows of $2 million and $1 million, respectively.</li>
<li>While the washout of crypto exchange FTX severely affected the Solana network, it wrapped up the year on a positive note with $121 million.</li>
<li>XRP remained unfazed by the twists and turns of the battle between crypto firm Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In fact, XRP-related investment products clocked in $32 million in inflows, the second highest in the last five years.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, short-investment products came to the fore with inflows worth $108 million for the whole of 2022.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-sec-battle-xrp-investment-products-saw-record-inflows-in-2022-report/" rel="nofollow">Despite SEC Battle, XRP Investment Products Saw Record Inflows in 2022: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Testing $17K But is Another Crash Imminent? (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-testing-17k-but-is-another-crash-imminent-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 16:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232096</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price has broken above a significant moving average which has been acting as a resistance over recent weeks. The market seems ready to rise higher in the coming week if the remaining negative factors do not hinder the forming momentum. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, the price has [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has broken above a significant moving average which has been acting as a resistance over recent weeks. The market seems ready to rise higher in the coming week if the remaining negative factors do not hinder the forming momentum.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price has closed above the 50-day moving average to the upside at last, after failing to do so and getting rejected multiple times over the last few weeks.</p>
<p>This breakout has seemingly paved the way for a rally toward the $18K resistance level and perhaps even higher. A break above the wedge pattern would likely lead to bullish price action in the mid-term, as it is considered a reversal pattern in a bear market.</p>
<p>However, if the price drops back below the 50-day moving average, the chance of declining toward the $15K support zone will increase accordingly.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232100" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232100" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232100 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_070123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-7-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232100" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour chart, the fake breakout and bearish scenario seem more probable, as the price is yet to break above the $17K resistance area to maintain the formed bullish momentum.</p>
<p>Moreover, the RSI indicator shows a clear bearish divergence signal, which further strengthens the likelihood of a reversal in the short term.</p>
<p>An impulsive rejection from the current price level would likely lead to a drop toward the $15,500 support level, which would be the bulls&#8217; last resort.</p>
<p>All in all, things are getting interesting from a technical point of view, as BTC&#8217;s behavior around the $17K mark in the next few days would likely determine the mid-term trend of the crypto market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232099" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232099" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232099 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_070123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-7-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232099" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>The following chart includes the Realized Price metric, one of the most valuable indicators to determine whether Bitcoin is under or over-valued. Typically, the price stays above the realized price during bullish market cycles. Conversely, during the last capitulation phase of a bear market, the price drops below the realized price, bringing significant fear and uncertainty. During this period, market participants are under much stress and distribute their assets to avoid additional losses and control their exposure to further market fluctuations.</p>
<p>Considering the previous cycles, the beginning of a bull market is anticipated once the market price surpasses the realized price. This has not happened yet, as the cryptocurrency has failed to break above the realized price, followed by a short leg down.</p>
<p>Consequently, the sustainability of any positive price action is questionable unless Bitcoin surpasses the realized price ($19.7K).</p>
<figure id="attachment_232101" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232101" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232101 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_realized_price_chart_070123" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Realized-Price-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232101" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-testing-17k-but-is-another-crash-imminent-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Testing $17K But is Another Crash Imminent? (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemini-DCG Fiasco May Shape to Be &#8216;Market Bottom Event&#8217; in 2023: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-dcg-fiasco-may-shape-to-be-market-bottom-event-in-2023-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231995</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Gemini_DCG.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Gemini_DCG.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After a hectic year, the focus in 2022 will be accumulation and building exposure]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to the latest edition of Arcane Research, the entire market appears to be stabilizing even though there&#8217;s still some uncertainty left.</p>
<p>Having said that, all eyes are on DCG&#8217;s next steps, which can further intensify downward price action.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Volatility Nearing 30-Months Low</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s current price action was defined as stale as its volatility slumbered toward rare lows. Data suggested that the largest coin&#8217;s 7-day volatility reached lows not seen for two and half years as it plunged to 0.7%.</p>
<p>The current numbers were only visited once since February 2019 &#8211; during the stagnant markets of July 2020.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the 30-day volatility also follows a similar trend as it currently hovered near 1.4% and coincided with levels that were briefly touched before the FTX collapse in early November. In fact, the figure has only been lower on seven occasions since February 2019. Arcane suggested that these periods of low volatility rarely last for long. As such, volatility compression periods tend to be followed by sharp moves, even during dull markets.</p>
<p>In addition to the dwindling lack of price movements, Bitcoin&#8217;s spot volumes are also drying up. The futures market, on the other hand, was observed to be reigning in a flat regime.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The entire market is generally stabilizing, accompanied by apathetic market participation. Closed US markets are likely the core reason behind the dull price action of late, but it’s also been exaggerated by a general exodus of active retail participation and few important news catalysts.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Gemini-DCG Fiasco</h2>
<p>Going forward, 2023 will be shaped by low volatility and stagnant market trend. But the Gemini-DCG fiasco poses a significant threat to the market.</p>
<p>The co-founder of crypto exchange Cameron Winklevoss <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-out-barry-silbert-on-1-675b-debt-latter-fires-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">gave a soft ultimatum</a> to Digital Currency Group (DCG) CEO Barry Silbert to collaborate on repaying Genesis by January 8.</p>
<p>For context,  Gemini used to offer 8% interest to investors on certain cryptocurrencies under its Earn program, whose contributor was &#8211; Genesis. But with FTX&#8217;s collapse, the latter came under severe financial stress. The cash crunch forced the platform to halt withdrawals from Gemini for nearly two months now. Genesis owes Gemini users a total of $900 million.</p>
<p>According to Arcane, a &#8220;natural and less liquidity-constrained route&#8221; to this sale could be to initiate a Reg M, thereby enabling traders to redeem shares at NAV. This would narrow the discounts, and its impact will be felt in crypto markets.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Currently, GBTC trade at a 45% discount to its NAV, while ETHE trades at a 59% discount to its NAV. GBTC holds 3.3% of the circulating BTC supply and 2.5% of the ETH supply. A Reg M would cause a massive arbitrage strategy of selling crypto spot versus buying Grayscale Trust shares.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>If this scenario transpires, the downside will be inevitable. In the long term, however, the market would finally get eliminate &#8220;the major burden that the Grayscale widow maker trade has generated&#8221; and is shaping up to become a &#8220;potential market bottom event.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-dcg-fiasco-may-shape-to-be-market-bottom-event-in-2023-report/" rel="nofollow">Gemini-DCG Fiasco May Shape to Be &#8216;Market Bottom Event&#8217; in 2023: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mt. Gox Extends Repayment Registration Deadline to March 30</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mt-gox-extends-repayment-registration-deadline-to-march-30/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt. Gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232022</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MT_GOX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MT_GOX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The extension also affected the distribution deadline as Mt. Gox creditors now have to wait until September 30 to receive compensation. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Creditors of the defunct cryptocurrency exchange Mt. Gox have received more time to select and register how they wish to receive compensation from the company.</p>
<p class="p2">According to a <a href="https://www.mtgox.com/img/pdf/20230106_announcement_en.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">document</a> from the exchange&#8217;s trustee Nobuaki Kobayashi, the registration deadline, which was previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mt-gox-creditors-have-until-january-2023-to-select-a-repayment-method/" data-wpel-link="internal">set</a> as January 10, 2023, has been extended to March 10 (Japan time) after receiving approval from the court.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;The deadline for the Selection and Registration was January 10, 2023 (Japan time) but having obtained the permission of the court, the Rehabilitation Trustee has changed the deadline to March 10, 2023 (Japan time), considering various circumstances such as the progress by rehabilitation creditors in respect of the Selection and Registration,&#8221; the trustee wrote.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p2">Gox Moves Compensation Deadline to September 30</h2>
<p class="p2">Kobayashi urged creditors to complete the registration process before the new deadline, adding that those who failed to complete their selection would not receive compensation or might have to submit additional documents to the company&#8217;s head office.</p>
<p class="p2">The trustee noted that those who have already registered their selections do not have to do it again. Although they can change their selection before the new deadline, the update discouraged creditors from doing so to make the confirmation process smooth.</p>
<p class="p2">Furthermore, the extension affected the distribution deadline as creditors would have to wait longer to receive compensation. The repayment deadline was postponed from July 31 to September 30, 2023.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;Having obtained the permission of the court, the Rehabilitation Trustee has also changed the Base Repayment Deadline, Early Lump-Sum Repayment Deadline, and Intermediate Repayment Deadline from July 31, 2023 (Japan time) to September 30, 2023 (Japan time) following the change of the deadline for the Selection and Registration.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Mt. Gox Creditors to Receive Billions</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, Mt. Gox became insolvent in 2014 after losing 850,000 bitcoins to hackers. Since then, the company has been working on how to repay affected customers.</p>
<p class="p2">The value of BTC stolen from the exchange was worth $473 million at the time of the incident, but the assets are worth over $14 billion at current prices. However, the trustee will not pay 850,000 BTC to creditors since the exchange could not recover the stolen assets.</p>
<p class="p2">Nonetheless, creditors are expected to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mt-gox-creditors-could-receive-billions-in-btc-as-latest-rehabilitation-plan-gets-approval/" data-wpel-link="internal">receive</a> more than 140,000 BTC, worth around $2.3 billion.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mt-gox-extends-repayment-registration-deadline-to-march-30/" rel="nofollow">Mt. Gox Extends Repayment Registration Deadline to March 30</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weekend Watch: Lido DAO Soars to 2-Month High, BTC Touched $17K</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-lido-dao-soars-to-2-month-high-btc-touched-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 09:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232075</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_LIDO.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_LIDO.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[LDO is up by double digits weekly, even though MakerDAO took back its DeFi throne. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After failing to challenge $17,000 for several straight days, bitcoin finally touched that level, marking a multi-week high.</p>
<p>The altcoins also turned green on Saturday, with impressive gains from Ethereum Classic and Lido DAO.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Touches $17K</h2>
<p>The end of 2022 was quite calm for the primary cryptocurrency, and the first day of the new year didn&#8217;t bring any more excitement either, as it remained at around $16,500. The situation started to change on Monday with a minor push from the bulls to $16,700.</p>
<p>BTC tried to come closer to $17,000 in the next few days but ultimately failed to tap that line. The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-up-12-weekly-bitcoin-stopped-at-17k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">latest rejection</a> from yesterday even pushed the asset south by a few hundred dollars.</p>
<p>However, bitcoin indeed touched $17,000 a few hours ago, doing so for the first time since December 20. It has lost some ground as of now and stands just under it, but it&#8217;s still around 1% up on the day.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization has increased to north of $325 billion, but its dominance over the alts is back down to 39.6%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232076" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232076" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-232076" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-6-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232076" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LDO, ETC on the Run</h2>
<p><em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-protocol-lido-reaches-5-9b-in-tvl-dethroning-makerdao/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier this week when Lido DAO became a leader in terms of Total Value Locked, surpassing MakerDAO. Although the latter reclaimed its first position, the former&#8217;s native cryptocurrency has continued to rise higher.</p>
<p>The latest push came earlier today, as LDO skyrocketed by double digits and reached $1.5. This became its highest price tag in about two months.</p>
<p>Ethereum Classic is another notable performer on a daily scale. ETC is up by 10% and trades at just over $20.</p>
<p>Litecoin and Polygon have jumped the most from the top 15 largest cryptocurrencies, with gains of up to 4%.</p>
<p>Ethereum, Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, OKB, and Polkadot have increased by between 1-2% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency market cap has regained all losses from yesterday and is back above $820 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232077" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232077" style="width: 1846px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-232077" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1846" height="652" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss.jpg 1846w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss-300x106.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss-1024x362.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss-768x271.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss-1536x543.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoinss-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1846px) 100vw, 1846px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232077" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-lido-dao-soars-to-2-month-high-btc-touched-17k/" rel="nofollow">Weekend Watch: Lido DAO Soars to 2-Month High, BTC Touched $17K</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bank of France Governor Thinks Crypto Companies Should Abide by Stricter Rules</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bank-of-france-governor-thinks-crypto-companies-should-abide-by-stricter-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 00:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[France]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231895</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bank_De_France.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bank_De_France.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The "disruption" in the crypto sector is the main reason for more stringent rules, Villeroy stated.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Francois Villeroy de Galhau &#8211; Governor of Banque de France &#8211; believes cryptocurrency firms should obtain tougher regulatory licenses to continue providing their services.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also stated France should introduce stricter rules for domestic digital asset entities as soon as it is ready with its legislation instead of waiting for other European countries. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Villeroy&#8217;s Latest Recommendation</span></h2>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.banque-france.fr/en/intervention/new-year-wishes-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to the central banker, cryptocurrency entities should secure more stringent authorization from watchdogs than the existing ones due to the current &#8220;unstable environment.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Around 60 organizations, including Binance, have received registration from The Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF) to offer their products and services in the European nation. However, none have the license Villeroy urges for. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Governor maintained that the recent chaos in the world of crypto, which saw numerous bankruptcies, investor interest outflow, and a market decline, is the main reason why France should speed up with such amendments:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The disruption seen in 2022 is nourishing one basic conviction: France should switch as soon as possible to the compulsory authorization of DASPs (digital asset service providers) rather than simply requiring their registration. And this needs to happen well before MiCA enters into force to create the necessary framework of trust.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_127063" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-127063" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-127063" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau.jpg" alt="François Villeroy de Galhau" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/Francois-Villeroy-de-Galhau-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-127063" class="wp-caption-text">François Villeroy de Galhau, Source: Bloomberg</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The European Union (EU) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/eu-greenlights-mica-major-turning-point-for-europes-crypto-landscape-and-bitcoin-kyc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">approved</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation in October last year. The upcoming bill could establish a pertinent licensing regime for exchanges and other businesses that will apply to all 27 members of the bloc. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It will specifically focus on combating tax evasion and money laundering and could go into effect in 2024. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Not Much Time Left</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Villeroy has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/europe-needs-to-regulate-crypto-as-quickly-as-possible-says-banque-de-france-governor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">urged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the European authorities to build a cryptocurrency regulatory framework as soon as possible because otherwise, the Old Continent could lose its financial dominance while the euro could suffer a drawback:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Whether it is digital currencies or payments, we in Europe must be ready to act as quickly as necessary or take the risk of an erosion of our monetary sovereignty.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also said the EU has one or two years to introduce such legislation, or the continent could &#8220;lose its momentum.&#8221; Villeroy aired his thoughts in the summer of 2021, meaning that the potential bill might occur in the following months (assuming European watchdogs consider his recommendation).</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bank-of-france-governor-thinks-crypto-companies-should-abide-by-stricter-rules/" rel="nofollow">Bank of France Governor Thinks Crypto Companies Should Abide by Stricter Rules</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senator Stabenow Who Designed &#8216;SBF Crypto Bill&#8217; Will not Seek Re-Election</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/senator-stabenow-who-designed-sbf-crypto-bill-will-not-seek-re-election/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231937</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Debbie-Stabenow.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Debbie-Stabenow.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Senator Debbie Stabenow, who received a significant donation from SBF, will vacate her post on January 2025.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Michigan Senator Debbie Stabenow announced she will abandon her post in January 2025.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The politician was one of the creators of cryptocurrency legislation that could empower the CFTC with exclusive jurisdiction when overseeing the market. Interestingly, the former CEO of FTX &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried &#8211; was a vocal supporter of the bill, which received the nickname: &#8220;the SBF crypto bill.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Passing the Torch</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Senator Stabenow &#8211; the first woman from Michigan elected to the United States Senate &#8211; will </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.stabenow.senate.gov/news/senator-stabenow-announces-she-will-not-seek-re-election-in-2024" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">leave</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> her position in the Northern state:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Inspired by a new generation of leaders, I have decided to pass the torch in the US Senate. I am announcing today that I will not seek re-election and will leave the US Senate at the end of my term on January 3, 2025.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_231960" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231960" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231960" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator.jpg" alt="Senator Debbie Stabenow" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator.jpg 2000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator-768x512.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator-1536x1025.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Senator-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231960" class="wp-caption-text">Senator Debbie Stabenow, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">She said her main focus throughout the next two years will be the well-being of the locals and creating job opportunities in the urban and rural communities. The politician vowed to continue serving Michigan even outside Senate while spending more time with her family.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">She cooperated with Senators John Boozman, Cory Booker, and John Thune in August last year to submit the Digital Commodities Consumer Protection Act. The potential bill aims to give the CFTC greater authority when monitoring the cryptocurrency sector and thus protect consumers from fraud. However, critics warned that it could negatively affect decentralized finance (DeFi).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the outspoken proponents of the legislation was Sam Bankman-Fried. He also reportedly </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.michigancapitolconfidential.com/news/stabenow-took-nearly-56k-of-donations-from-ftx-then-took-lead-role-on-crypto-bill" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">donated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> over $56,000 to Senator Stabenow and funds related to her. The Michigan politician received contributions from other former FTX executives, such as Ryne Miller, Mark Wetjen, and Zachary Dexter.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SBF&#8217;s Donations</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 30-year-old, who faces several charges because of his firm&#8217;s collapse in November 2022, donated significant sums to US politicians over the past years. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/its-a-close-race-for-ceo-support-too-11603913772" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">gifted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Joe Biden&#8217;s presidential campaign in 2020 over $5 million, while subsequent sources </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2022/11/29/sam-bankman-fried-political-donations-democrats-republicans-dark-money/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">indicated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that he gave away millions to Republicans, too.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other lawmakers who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://time.com/6241262/sam-bankman-fried-political-donations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> funds from the former crypto mogul include the likes of Senators Kirsten Gillibrand of New York, Cory Booker of New York, Maggie Hassan of New Hampshire, Susan Collins of Maine, and Lisa Murkowski of Alaska. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other reports hinted that SBF was also bribing media outlets so they could portray him as a humble person who managed an entirely legal entity. Tesla&#8217;s CEO was among those who believed that thesis, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-believes-sbf-is-better-at-bribing-media-outlets-than-running-ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">saying</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in December:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If SBF was as good at running a crypto exchange as he was at bribing media, FTX would still be solvent!&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-stabenow-who-designed-sbf-crypto-bill-will-not-seek-re-election/" rel="nofollow">Senator Stabenow Who Designed &#8216;SBF Crypto Bill&#8217; Will not Seek Re-Election</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DCG Wealth Management Division Shuts Down Hours After Genesis Announced Layoffs: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-wealth-management-division-shuts-down-hours-after-genesis-announced-layoffs-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231938</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Digital_Currency_Group.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Digital_Currency_Group.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The DCG Group, who are reportedly having trouble staying afloat, seem to be cutting off ballast wherever they can.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, the DCG Group – a conglomerate that manages Genesis, Grayscale, and wealth management service HQ – announced a 30% workforce reduction as the shadow of bankruptcy looms over the battered crypto broker.</p>
<p>DCG has been in trouble for a while now, with partnered services <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitvavo-claims-dcg-has-liquidity-issues-exchange-funds-unaffected/" data-wpel-link="internal">distancing</a> themselves from any possible fallout.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, it seems that problems are piling up at DCG as one division after another begins to fold.</p>
<h2>Closed for Winter</h2>
<p>The concerning <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/dcg-shuts-down-wealth-management-031136907.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcement</a> regarding Genesis’s workforce reduction and possible bankruptcy was soon followed by another one regarding sister company “HQ.”</p>
<p>According to a spokesperson for the company, HQ will be halting all activity as of January 31, although it will consider re-opening the branch in the future.</p>
<p>The shutdown of HQ is blamed on the broader financial situation – and, naturally, on the ongoing crypto winter.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Due to the state of the broader economic environment and prolonged crypto winter presenting significant headwinds to the industry, we made the decision to wind down HQ, effective January 31, 2023. We’re proud of the work that the team has done and look forward to potentially revisiting the project in the future.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The first cracks started to show in November when DCG CEO Barry Silbert advised investors that 2022 revenues will be lower than expected. At the time, Genesis – who had already laid off 20% of their workforce in August – owed about $575 million to parent company DCG.</p>
<p>To further compound the terrible financial position Genesis and DCG were in, Bitvavo alone claimed to be owed about $300 million by DCG, who allegedly shunted the blame onto Genesis alone.</p>
<h2>Investors and Partners Left Perplexed</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/genesis-parent-company-dcg-shutters-its-wealth-management-division" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by The Information, HQ was still managing about $3.5 billion worth of assets as recently as December, in spite of the crypto winter. As a result, partners and investors were allegedly stunned by the decision, claiming it came completely out of the left field.</p>
<p>Although the DCG group hints at the implosion of 3AC and FTX as culprits for its own woes – claiming that its assets were lost when withdrawals from the two defunct crypto platforms were stopped – the responsibility for liquidity issues should never be passed on to someone else. Had proper due diligence been carried out, the situation at DCG would probably be very different.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-wealth-management-division-shuts-down-hours-after-genesis-announced-layoffs-report/" rel="nofollow">DCG Wealth Management Division Shuts Down Hours After Genesis Announced Layoffs: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
