<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 03:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Head of French Central Bank Pushes for Crypto Licensing]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/head-of-french-central-bank-pushes-for-crypto-licensing</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/france-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/france-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/france-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/head-of-french-central-bank-pushes-for-crypto-licensing</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France given the recent turmoil in the market. The head of the central bank said France should not wait for the upcoming MiCA regulation to enact obligatory licensing for local digital asset service providers (DASPs). </p>
<p>Francois Villeroy de Galhau, governor of the Bank of France, said during a speech in Paris on January 5, that the recent chaos in the crypto markets necessitates that France moves ahead with a mandatory licensing scheme for crypto firms &ldquo;as soon as possible,&rdquo; according to reports by Bloomberg. The governor said that France should not wait for the upcoming EU crypto laws &ndash; the Markets in Crypto Assets bill (MiCA), to come into effect before enacting mandatory licensing for DASPs.</p>
France Needs to Act Before MiCA Comes into Force
<p>Villeroy addressed France&rsquo;s financial industry in his speech, saying:</p>

<p>All the disorder in 2022 feeds a simple belief: it is desirable for France to move to an obligatory licensing of DASP as soon as possible, rather than just registration.</p>

<p>The European Parliament&rsquo;s MiCA is expected to potentially come into force in 2024 and will provide a crypto licensing regime for the European Union.</p>
<p>As it stands in France, the Financial Markets Authority (AMF), the nation&rsquo;s market regulator, requires &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from cryptocurrency firms offering trading and custody services. A DASP license is currently voluntary per Bloomberg, and none of the service providers hold one. The less strict &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from the AMF is held by about 60 businesses.</p>
<p>Villeroy&rsquo;s calls come after Herv&eacute; Maurey, a member of the Senate Finance Commission, in December 2022 proposed an amendment that would do away with the provision allowing businesses to operate without a license.</p>
<p>In December reports were circulating that France is considering an obligation for crypto firms to obtain a full license before they can operate. The government then already expressed concern over the lack of regulation and oversight in the crypto space in the wake of the recent bankruptcy of FTX.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France given the recent turmoil in the market. The head of the central bank said France should not wait for the upcoming MiCA regulation to enact obligatory licensing for local digital asset service providers (DASPs). </p>
<p>Francois Villeroy de Galhau, governor of the Bank of France, said during a speech in Paris on January 5, that the recent chaos in the crypto markets necessitates that France moves ahead with a mandatory licensing scheme for crypto firms &ldquo;as soon as possible,&rdquo; according to reports by Bloomberg. The governor said that France should not wait for the upcoming EU crypto laws &ndash; the Markets in Crypto Assets bill (MiCA), to come into effect before enacting mandatory licensing for DASPs.</p>
France Needs to Act Before MiCA Comes into Force
<p>Villeroy addressed France&rsquo;s financial industry in his speech, saying:</p>

<p>All the disorder in 2022 feeds a simple belief: it is desirable for France to move to an obligatory licensing of DASP as soon as possible, rather than just registration.</p>

<p>The European Parliament&rsquo;s MiCA is expected to potentially come into force in 2024 and will provide a crypto licensing regime for the European Union.</p>
<p>As it stands in France, the Financial Markets Authority (AMF), the nation&rsquo;s market regulator, requires &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from cryptocurrency firms offering trading and custody services. A DASP license is currently voluntary per Bloomberg, and none of the service providers hold one. The less strict &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from the AMF is held by about 60 businesses.</p>
<p>Villeroy&rsquo;s calls come after Herv&eacute; Maurey, a member of the Senate Finance Commission, in December 2022 proposed an amendment that would do away with the provision allowing businesses to operate without a license.</p>
<p>In December reports were circulating that France is considering an obligation for crypto firms to obtain a full license before they can operate. The government then already expressed concern over the lack of regulation and oversight in the crypto space in the wake of the recent bankruptcy of FTX.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Heralds Major Blockchain Adoption in Turkey]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/lbank-heralds-major-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-01-06_60547_1672999558OlDkfDzMFz.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-01-06_60547_1672999558OlDkfDzMFz.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-01-06_60547_1672999558OlDkfDzMFz.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/lbank-heralds-major-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, 6th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank, the licensed European cryptocurrency exchange, has applauded measures taken by the Turkish government to utilize blockchain technology. LBank CEO Allen Wei has highlighted a number of positive developments in Turkey including CBDC trials and regional blockchain projects.</p>
<p>The Central Bank of Turkey (CBRT) completed CBDC tests in December 2022 and the government is currently planning to use blockchain technology for online public services. Both signal an even stronger embrace of blockchain technology in 2023.</p>
"Turkey is an exciting market that ranks among the top 10 in crypto adoption globally,&rdquo; said Allen Wei, Co-Founder and CEO of LBank Exchange. &ldquo;Efforts such as these show Turkey&rsquo;s determination to push for wider blockchain integration in the country. It&rsquo;s a boost for the digital Turkish lira and a positive step from the forward-looking government.&rdquo;
<p>Since the Turkish government unveiled its plan for a national blockchain infrastructure in 2019, Turkey has had many ambitious blockchain-based goals. However, besides specific project announcements, there have been few deliverables. This looks set to change in 2023, with several promising projects at an advanced stage of development.</p>
<p>A recent statement from the CBRT revealed that &ldquo;the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network were executed successfully.&rdquo; It said that further advanced-stage tests will be run in the first quarter of 2023, and selected banks and financial technology companies will be chosen to be included in the expansion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The official announcement for a CBDC came in September of 2021. Initially, the CBRT did not commit to a digital Turkish lira. However, the most recent statement mentions that &ldquo;the CBRT will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Testing and successful completion of the digital Turkish lira is seen as a big step towards rolling out a digital lira,&rdquo; said Adem &Ouml;zkan &Ouml;zdil, LBank Community Manager for Turkey. Beyond Turkey&rsquo;s CBDC, the government has made other commitments, such as testing and integrating blockchain technology in public services.</p>
<p>Amid the news about the digital Turkish lira, the Vice President of Turkey, Fuat Oktay, announced plans for a blockchain-based digital identity application during the Digital Turkey 2023 event. Many public services, including residential matters and military services, will be integrated into the E-Devlet portal, which will use a blockchain-based digital identity and login system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Turkey first shared its vision to utilize blockchain technology in public services in 2019. In its Strategy 2023 presentation, Turkey&rsquo;s Ministry of Industry and Technology put blockchain and distributed ledger technology (DLT) as one of the priorities of 2020.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, the city of Konya, one of the most important cultural centers of Turkey, revealed in 2020 that it was planning to develop a &ldquo;city coin&rdquo; and use blockchain technology to fund social programs. Konya served as an initial test to see how blockchain technology works with public services on a large scale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About LBank
LBank, founded in 2015, is an innovative global trading platform for various crypto assets. The exchange provides its users with safe crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. It has become one of the most popular and trusted crypto trading platforms, with over 7 million users from more than 210 regions around the world.
&nbsp;</p>
<p>Start Trading Now</p>
<p>Community &amp; Social Media:
Telegram l Twitter l Facebook l LinkedIn l Instagram l YouTube</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, 6th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank, the licensed European cryptocurrency exchange, has applauded measures taken by the Turkish government to utilize blockchain technology. LBank CEO Allen Wei has highlighted a number of positive developments in Turkey including CBDC trials and regional blockchain projects.</p>
<p>The Central Bank of Turkey (CBRT) completed CBDC tests in December 2022 and the government is currently planning to use blockchain technology for online public services. Both signal an even stronger embrace of blockchain technology in 2023.</p>
"Turkey is an exciting market that ranks among the top 10 in crypto adoption globally,&rdquo; said Allen Wei, Co-Founder and CEO of LBank Exchange. &ldquo;Efforts such as these show Turkey&rsquo;s determination to push for wider blockchain integration in the country. It&rsquo;s a boost for the digital Turkish lira and a positive step from the forward-looking government.&rdquo;
<p>Since the Turkish government unveiled its plan for a national blockchain infrastructure in 2019, Turkey has had many ambitious blockchain-based goals. However, besides specific project announcements, there have been few deliverables. This looks set to change in 2023, with several promising projects at an advanced stage of development.</p>
<p>A recent statement from the CBRT revealed that &ldquo;the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network were executed successfully.&rdquo; It said that further advanced-stage tests will be run in the first quarter of 2023, and selected banks and financial technology companies will be chosen to be included in the expansion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The official announcement for a CBDC came in September of 2021. Initially, the CBRT did not commit to a digital Turkish lira. However, the most recent statement mentions that &ldquo;the CBRT will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Testing and successful completion of the digital Turkish lira is seen as a big step towards rolling out a digital lira,&rdquo; said Adem &Ouml;zkan &Ouml;zdil, LBank Community Manager for Turkey. Beyond Turkey&rsquo;s CBDC, the government has made other commitments, such as testing and integrating blockchain technology in public services.</p>
<p>Amid the news about the digital Turkish lira, the Vice President of Turkey, Fuat Oktay, announced plans for a blockchain-based digital identity application during the Digital Turkey 2023 event. Many public services, including residential matters and military services, will be integrated into the E-Devlet portal, which will use a blockchain-based digital identity and login system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Turkey first shared its vision to utilize blockchain technology in public services in 2019. In its Strategy 2023 presentation, Turkey&rsquo;s Ministry of Industry and Technology put blockchain and distributed ledger technology (DLT) as one of the priorities of 2020.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, the city of Konya, one of the most important cultural centers of Turkey, revealed in 2020 that it was planning to develop a &ldquo;city coin&rdquo; and use blockchain technology to fund social programs. Konya served as an initial test to see how blockchain technology works with public services on a large scale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About LBank
LBank, founded in 2015, is an innovative global trading platform for various crypto assets. The exchange provides its users with safe crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. It has become one of the most popular and trusted crypto trading platforms, with over 7 million users from more than 210 regions around the world.
&nbsp;</p>
<p>Start Trading Now</p>
<p>Community &amp; Social Media:
Telegram l Twitter l Facebook l LinkedIn l Instagram l YouTube</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi Plans Staff Layoffs, Rumors of Insolvency Hang in the Air]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/huobi-plans-staff-layoffs-rumors-of-insolvency-hang-in-the-air</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/huobi-plans-staff-layoffs-rumors-of-insolvency-hang-in-the-air</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX. </p>
<p>In the latest round of all-over cost-cutting across the crypto industry, crypto exchange Huobi today confirmed to Reuters that the firm plans to lay off about 20% of its staff. Huobi said in a statement to the news agency:</p>

<p>The planned layoff ratio is about 20%, but it is not implemented now. With the current state of the bear market, a very lean team will be maintained going forward.</p>

<p>The statement to Reuters confirms an earlier message from Tron founder Justin Sun, who said that a &ldquo;structural adjustment&rdquo; is to start in Huobi soon. Sun, who is a member of Huobi&rsquo;s global advisory board, said in an internal memo to company staff that the firm has been like &ldquo;a fire in the crypto winter&rdquo; despite the worsening macro environment. Huobi is based in Seychelles and has offices in Hong Kong, the United States, Japan, and in South Korea. The company is publicly listed on the Stock Exchange of Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Along with the layoffs, which rumours of have been running wild on Twitter, Sun has also had to address rumours of insolvency. He said in a January 5 Tweet, that business development of the exchange was &ldquo;good&rdquo; and the &ldquo;security of users&rsquo; assets will always be fully protected.&rdquo; Earlier in January, crypto journalist, Colin Wu, reported that Sun had changed employee salaries from being paid in fiat to being either paid in Tether or USD Coin. The journalist also claimed that staff who disagreed with the new payment systems faced being laid off. Sun dismissed these claims saying that Huobi will &ldquo;fully respect the legal demands of local employees.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Justin Sun's HR is communicating with all Huobi employees to change the salary form from fiat currency to USDT/USDC; employees who cannot accept it may be dismissed. The move sparked protests from some employees. Exclusive https://t.co/QB4sjDyHc7</p>
&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) January 4, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Wu also cited insiders and reported that in December Huobi cancelled end-of-year bonuses and was preparing to cut up to half of its staff.</p>
Crypto Firms Off to a Rocky Start in 2023
<p>Huobi&rsquo;s announcement does not come as the first for 2023. In the first couple of days of the year, crypto firm Genesis cut 30% of its workforce in a second round of layoffs in less than six months. Silvergate Capital Corp, a crypto-focused bank, cut its workforce by 40% and has been forced to abandon some of its projects.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX. </p>
<p>In the latest round of all-over cost-cutting across the crypto industry, crypto exchange Huobi today confirmed to Reuters that the firm plans to lay off about 20% of its staff. Huobi said in a statement to the news agency:</p>

<p>The planned layoff ratio is about 20%, but it is not implemented now. With the current state of the bear market, a very lean team will be maintained going forward.</p>

<p>The statement to Reuters confirms an earlier message from Tron founder Justin Sun, who said that a &ldquo;structural adjustment&rdquo; is to start in Huobi soon. Sun, who is a member of Huobi&rsquo;s global advisory board, said in an internal memo to company staff that the firm has been like &ldquo;a fire in the crypto winter&rdquo; despite the worsening macro environment. Huobi is based in Seychelles and has offices in Hong Kong, the United States, Japan, and in South Korea. The company is publicly listed on the Stock Exchange of Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Along with the layoffs, which rumours of have been running wild on Twitter, Sun has also had to address rumours of insolvency. He said in a January 5 Tweet, that business development of the exchange was &ldquo;good&rdquo; and the &ldquo;security of users&rsquo; assets will always be fully protected.&rdquo; Earlier in January, crypto journalist, Colin Wu, reported that Sun had changed employee salaries from being paid in fiat to being either paid in Tether or USD Coin. The journalist also claimed that staff who disagreed with the new payment systems faced being laid off. Sun dismissed these claims saying that Huobi will &ldquo;fully respect the legal demands of local employees.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Justin Sun's HR is communicating with all Huobi employees to change the salary form from fiat currency to USDT/USDC; employees who cannot accept it may be dismissed. The move sparked protests from some employees. Exclusive https://t.co/QB4sjDyHc7</p>
&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) January 4, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Wu also cited insiders and reported that in December Huobi cancelled end-of-year bonuses and was preparing to cut up to half of its staff.</p>
Crypto Firms Off to a Rocky Start in 2023
<p>Huobi&rsquo;s announcement does not come as the first for 2023. In the first couple of days of the year, crypto firm Genesis cut 30% of its workforce in a second round of layoffs in less than six months. Silvergate Capital Corp, a crypto-focused bank, cut its workforce by 40% and has been forced to abandon some of its projects.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[$100 million in stablecoins transferred to Huobi by Justin Sun]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/100-million-in-stablecoins-transferred-to-huobi-by-justin-sun</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/100-million-in-stablecoins-transferred-to-huobi-by-justin-sun</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Recently, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In an article posted by The Block earlier today, security analysts at PeckShield reported that two transactions of $50 million each of USDC and USDT were conducted at 11:10 a.m. UTC. The wallet, which can be linked to Sun through the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan, also holds $16.5 million worth of decentralised usd (USDD), a stablecoin from the Tron blockchain, and closely connected to Sun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It has been noted that the majority of the funds in the recent transactions originated from Just Lend, a Tron-based lending platform, and were transferred to the wallet through Binance before ultimately reaching Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the transactions to Huobi, some exchange users noticed the creation of a $1 million buy wall for $HT, indicating that someone was willing to purchase $1 million worth of the token at a specific price, which is possibly a strategy used to keep the token price from crashing.</p>
<p>The news comes at a time when Huobi is in the public eye, with rumours circulating about layoffs and a mandate for employees to be paid in stablecoins rather than fiat currency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, there have been unconfirmed reports of internal communication platforms being shut down, which caused the price of Huobi's token ($HT) to drop to a low of $4.30 from $5.20 over the past 48 hours. $HT has since recovered to $4.64 at time of going to press.</p>
<p>In response to these rumours, Huobi's Global Head of Sales, James Hume, posted on LinkedIn that "most if not all" of them were "totally false or inaccurate." Hume went on to clarify that the exchange's internal communication platform was functioning normally and that it was "business as usual."</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In an article posted by The Block earlier today, security analysts at PeckShield reported that two transactions of $50 million each of USDC and USDT were conducted at 11:10 a.m. UTC. The wallet, which can be linked to Sun through the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan, also holds $16.5 million worth of decentralised usd (USDD), a stablecoin from the Tron blockchain, and closely connected to Sun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It has been noted that the majority of the funds in the recent transactions originated from Just Lend, a Tron-based lending platform, and were transferred to the wallet through Binance before ultimately reaching Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the transactions to Huobi, some exchange users noticed the creation of a $1 million buy wall for $HT, indicating that someone was willing to purchase $1 million worth of the token at a specific price, which is possibly a strategy used to keep the token price from crashing.</p>
<p>The news comes at a time when Huobi is in the public eye, with rumours circulating about layoffs and a mandate for employees to be paid in stablecoins rather than fiat currency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, there have been unconfirmed reports of internal communication platforms being shut down, which caused the price of Huobi's token ($HT) to drop to a low of $4.30 from $5.20 over the past 48 hours. $HT has since recovered to $4.64 at time of going to press.</p>
<p>In response to these rumours, Huobi's Global Head of Sales, James Hume, posted on LinkedIn that "most if not all" of them were "totally false or inaccurate." Hume went on to clarify that the exchange's internal communication platform was functioning normally and that it was "business as usual."</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Given Below 16880 - 7 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-below-16880-7-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-below-16880-7-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Given Below 16880:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 7 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered additional volatility early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 17000 figure after recently peaking around the 16988 level, its strongest print since 20 December.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders lifted BTC/USD higher to the 16809.30 level, representing a test of the 50-hour simple moving average, and then BTC/USD retreated lower to the 16670.82 area, representing a test of the 200-hour simple moving average.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 1.4% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16725.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16711.39.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Given Below 16880:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 7 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered additional volatility early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 17000 figure after recently peaking around the 16988 level, its strongest print since 20 December.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders lifted BTC/USD higher to the 16809.30 level, representing a test of the 50-hour simple moving average, and then BTC/USD retreated lower to the 16670.82 area, representing a test of the 200-hour simple moving average.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 1.4% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16725.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16711.39.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Genesis Lays Off 30% Of Workforce]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/genesis-lays-off-30-percent-of-workforce</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gns-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gns-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gns-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/genesis-lays-off-30-percent-of-workforce</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis On The Verge Of Bankruptcy?
<p>Less than six months after its first round of layoffs, Genesis, has been forced to cut loose around 30% of its workforce. Moreover, the word around the blockchain is that the lending platform is considering filing for bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Genesis has confirmed the news, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"As we continue to navigate unprecedented industry challenges, Genesis has made the difficult decision to reduce our headcount globally."&nbsp;</p>

<p>According to other sources, the company is working with investment bank Moelis &amp; Co to evaluate its options.&nbsp;</p>
FTX Contagion Spreads&nbsp;
<p>The biggest blow to the industry this year was the utter destruction of the FTX ecosystem. Not only did the major crypto exchange crash down dramatically, but it also took with it several significant institutions and crypto firms. For example, crypto-focused bank Silvergate Capital was also affected heavily by the FTX crash and has announced that it will slash its headcount by 40%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the year crypto has had, Genesis would not be the first crypto firm to go down the bankruptcy route. Crypto lender BlockFi was the first to follow FTX into Chapter 11 bankruptcy filing. The market downturn has forced the hands of many crypto executives to cut costs in their respective firms by trimming the workforce fat. In many cases, declaring bankruptcy is the only option left.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis In Trouble
<p>Genesis has been treading troubled waters lately, thanks to its association with the FTX ecosystem. The company&rsquo;s interim CEO, Derar Islim, penned a client letter in which he wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We believe we can arrive at a solution. As a key element in this process, we have made significant progress in refining our business plans for Genesis&rsquo; client offerings. This includes reducing costs and driving efficiencies in all our business lines.'</p>

<p>In November 2022, the company closed down withdrawals. Just a week before this, it was seeking a billion-dollar emergency loan. Both these events have led to the most recent skirmish with one of the founders of the Gemini crypto exchange, Cameron Winklevoss. The latter has accused Genesis and the Digital Currency Group (DCG) of acting in bad faith. Winklevoss penned an open letter to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, claiming that the latter has been evading all attempts at consensual resolution since Genesis owes members of Gemini Earn around $900 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis On The Verge Of Bankruptcy?
<p>Less than six months after its first round of layoffs, Genesis, has been forced to cut loose around 30% of its workforce. Moreover, the word around the blockchain is that the lending platform is considering filing for bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Genesis has confirmed the news, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"As we continue to navigate unprecedented industry challenges, Genesis has made the difficult decision to reduce our headcount globally."&nbsp;</p>

<p>According to other sources, the company is working with investment bank Moelis &amp; Co to evaluate its options.&nbsp;</p>
FTX Contagion Spreads&nbsp;
<p>The biggest blow to the industry this year was the utter destruction of the FTX ecosystem. Not only did the major crypto exchange crash down dramatically, but it also took with it several significant institutions and crypto firms. For example, crypto-focused bank Silvergate Capital was also affected heavily by the FTX crash and has announced that it will slash its headcount by 40%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the year crypto has had, Genesis would not be the first crypto firm to go down the bankruptcy route. Crypto lender BlockFi was the first to follow FTX into Chapter 11 bankruptcy filing. The market downturn has forced the hands of many crypto executives to cut costs in their respective firms by trimming the workforce fat. In many cases, declaring bankruptcy is the only option left.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis In Trouble
<p>Genesis has been treading troubled waters lately, thanks to its association with the FTX ecosystem. The company&rsquo;s interim CEO, Derar Islim, penned a client letter in which he wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We believe we can arrive at a solution. As a key element in this process, we have made significant progress in refining our business plans for Genesis&rsquo; client offerings. This includes reducing costs and driving efficiencies in all our business lines.'</p>

<p>In November 2022, the company closed down withdrawals. Just a week before this, it was seeking a billion-dollar emergency loan. Both these events have led to the most recent skirmish with one of the founders of the Gemini crypto exchange, Cameron Winklevoss. The latter has accused Genesis and the Digital Currency Group (DCG) of acting in bad faith. Winklevoss penned an open letter to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, claiming that the latter has been evading all attempts at consensual resolution since Genesis owes members of Gemini Earn around $900 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Analysts’ Top Picks: Polygon (MATIC), Solana (SOL), Polkadot (DOT) and Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Are the Best Long Term Crypto Holds]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/analysts-top-picks-polygon-matic-solana-sol-polkadot-dot-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-are-the-best-long-term-crypto-holds</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-06-at-145939.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-06-at-145939.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-06-at-145939.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/analysts-top-picks-polygon-matic-solana-sol-polkadot-dot-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-are-the-best-long-term-crypto-holds</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Speculative investors in the cryptocurrency market are putting in long hours trying to predict which coins will have the greatest price appreciation in 2023 and beyond. </p>
<p>Analysts, however, anticipate that Polygon (MATIC), Solana (SOL), Polkadot (DOT), and Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) will all see tremendous price increases in the near futureand are hence excellent long-term investments. </p>
<p>For instance, the presale for Orbeon Protocol is still in phase 3 but industry experts project a 60x&nbsp;increase in value within the next few weeks. Let&rsquo;s see why these cryptos are good long-term investments. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) Seeing Even More Mainstream Acceptance</p>
<p>The Polygon ecosystem, including its native coin MATIC, appears to be a promising investment option at the present time. </p>
<p>Meta, Instagram's parent company, has even&nbsp;named Polygon (MATIC) as its inaugural partner for NFT tools, letting its users mint, display, and trade NFTs&nbsp;on&nbsp;Instagram. These partnerships have boosted the Polygon (MATIC) system&rsquo;s popularity over the past few years.</p>
<p>On top of that, JPMorgan used Polygon to execute a $70,000+ live deal on the public blockchain. This is a monumental development on the road to the mainstream acceptance of the cryptocurrency. Polygon (MATIC), therefore, appears to be a promising future technology, and if Polygon (MATIC) continues along this trajectory, it is bound for significant positive price movement. As such, analysts predict Polygon (MATIC) could surpass its ATH this &nbsp;year.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Solana (SOL) Still Surviving the Odds</p>
<p>Solana (SOL) gives out such a solid vibe in the cryptocurrency market. Despite facing challenges that might have derailed less resilient tokens, Solana (SOL) has managed to keep moving ahead. </p>
<p>Since its 2020 launch, Solana (SOL) has been plagued by outages and even become the target of hacking assaults that have resulted in the loss of millions of dollars&rsquo; worth of cryptocurrency. Moreover, there are talks of filing a class action lawsuit against the platform.</p>
<p>Solana (SOL), though, is unmoved by the odds stacked against it. They respond by continually developing cutting-edge innovations. As a result, Solana (SOL) overcame all odds to become one of the most promising crypto assets on the market, and the Solana (SOL) blockchain remains a vibrant and active marketplace for NFTs and dApps.</p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT): The Future of Web 3</p>
<p>When compared to Charles Hoskinson's Cardano (ADA), Polkadot (DOT) is sometimes seen as a more formidable rival. </p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT) &nbsp;is built on a network of parachains which are specialized blockchains that prioritize multichain capabilities. The Polkadot (DOT) group considers their setup to be Web3's inevitable future. </p>
<p>The price of Polkadot (DOT) has dropped from its all-time high of $55 to less than $6 now. In other words, investors stand to gain from the price differential. </p>
<p>But like Solana (SOL), Polkadot's price is very volatile and subject to market forces. However, Polkadot (DOT)&nbsp;is still a good option to hold on to for&nbsp;long-term gains - analysts forecast Polkadot (DOT) to increase further as time goes on, with many suggesting it will increase past its all-time high in 2023.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is Giving Investors Massive ROI in Presale </p>
<p>A lot of people are talking about Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) in the crowdfunding and venture capital communities. </p>
<p>So, what&rsquo;s Orbeon and how is it changing the crowdfunding industry?</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is a blockchain-based investment platform. It gives everyday investors an opportunity to invest in promising startups while offering new businesses a Web3 platform to engage with their community and simultaneously raise capital.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol creates fractionalized NFTs representing the equity of promising startups. Then, for as low as a dollar, anyone can buy the fractionalized NFTs as investments in promising new businesses at an affordable rate. This advantage provides investors with unparalleled accessibility to the venture capital market.</p>
<p>ORBN is the Orbeon Protocol's token, and it's what makes everything work on the network. Holders of the token can participate in governance and staking, among other features like exclusive investor groups. </p>
<p>There are a total of 888,000,000 tokens available. Experts estimate an enormous 6000% increase in the price of ORBN to $0.24 by the beginning of 2023 from its initial price of $0.004. The token has already seen a marked increase in price to its current $0.0362 in a matter of weeks, signaling that it has following this trend.</p>
<p class="s11">Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s14">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s14">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Speculative investors in the cryptocurrency market are putting in long hours trying to predict which coins will have the greatest price appreciation in 2023 and beyond. </p>
<p>Analysts, however, anticipate that Polygon (MATIC), Solana (SOL), Polkadot (DOT), and Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) will all see tremendous price increases in the near futureand are hence excellent long-term investments. </p>
<p>For instance, the presale for Orbeon Protocol is still in phase 3 but industry experts project a 60x&nbsp;increase in value within the next few weeks. Let&rsquo;s see why these cryptos are good long-term investments. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) Seeing Even More Mainstream Acceptance</p>
<p>The Polygon ecosystem, including its native coin MATIC, appears to be a promising investment option at the present time. </p>
<p>Meta, Instagram's parent company, has even&nbsp;named Polygon (MATIC) as its inaugural partner for NFT tools, letting its users mint, display, and trade NFTs&nbsp;on&nbsp;Instagram. These partnerships have boosted the Polygon (MATIC) system&rsquo;s popularity over the past few years.</p>
<p>On top of that, JPMorgan used Polygon to execute a $70,000+ live deal on the public blockchain. This is a monumental development on the road to the mainstream acceptance of the cryptocurrency. Polygon (MATIC), therefore, appears to be a promising future technology, and if Polygon (MATIC) continues along this trajectory, it is bound for significant positive price movement. As such, analysts predict Polygon (MATIC) could surpass its ATH this &nbsp;year.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Solana (SOL) Still Surviving the Odds</p>
<p>Solana (SOL) gives out such a solid vibe in the cryptocurrency market. Despite facing challenges that might have derailed less resilient tokens, Solana (SOL) has managed to keep moving ahead. </p>
<p>Since its 2020 launch, Solana (SOL) has been plagued by outages and even become the target of hacking assaults that have resulted in the loss of millions of dollars&rsquo; worth of cryptocurrency. Moreover, there are talks of filing a class action lawsuit against the platform.</p>
<p>Solana (SOL), though, is unmoved by the odds stacked against it. They respond by continually developing cutting-edge innovations. As a result, Solana (SOL) overcame all odds to become one of the most promising crypto assets on the market, and the Solana (SOL) blockchain remains a vibrant and active marketplace for NFTs and dApps.</p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT): The Future of Web 3</p>
<p>When compared to Charles Hoskinson's Cardano (ADA), Polkadot (DOT) is sometimes seen as a more formidable rival. </p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT) &nbsp;is built on a network of parachains which are specialized blockchains that prioritize multichain capabilities. The Polkadot (DOT) group considers their setup to be Web3's inevitable future. </p>
<p>The price of Polkadot (DOT) has dropped from its all-time high of $55 to less than $6 now. In other words, investors stand to gain from the price differential. </p>
<p>But like Solana (SOL), Polkadot's price is very volatile and subject to market forces. However, Polkadot (DOT)&nbsp;is still a good option to hold on to for&nbsp;long-term gains - analysts forecast Polkadot (DOT) to increase further as time goes on, with many suggesting it will increase past its all-time high in 2023.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is Giving Investors Massive ROI in Presale </p>
<p>A lot of people are talking about Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) in the crowdfunding and venture capital communities. </p>
<p>So, what&rsquo;s Orbeon and how is it changing the crowdfunding industry?</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is a blockchain-based investment platform. It gives everyday investors an opportunity to invest in promising startups while offering new businesses a Web3 platform to engage with their community and simultaneously raise capital.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol creates fractionalized NFTs representing the equity of promising startups. Then, for as low as a dollar, anyone can buy the fractionalized NFTs as investments in promising new businesses at an affordable rate. This advantage provides investors with unparalleled accessibility to the venture capital market.</p>
<p>ORBN is the Orbeon Protocol's token, and it's what makes everything work on the network. Holders of the token can participate in governance and staking, among other features like exclusive investor groups. </p>
<p>There are a total of 888,000,000 tokens available. Experts estimate an enormous 6000% increase in the price of ORBN to $0.24 by the beginning of 2023 from its initial price of $0.004. The token has already seen a marked increase in price to its current $0.0362 in a matter of weeks, signaling that it has following this trend.</p>
<p class="s11">Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s14">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s14">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto and Carbon Reduction - Climate Tech Company YES WORLD is carving out a niche to solve the Global Warming Crisis. Launches Energy Efficient Glass Product Range]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-and-carbon-reduction-climate-tech-company-yes-world-is-carving-out-a-niche-to-solve-the-global-warming-crisis-launches-energy-efficient-glass-product-range</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yes-world-1200-720.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yes-world-1200-720.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yes-world-1200-720.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-and-carbon-reduction-climate-tech-company-yes-world-is-carving-out-a-niche-to-solve-the-global-warming-crisis-launches-energy-efficient-glass-product-range</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain based climate tech company - YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd launches world&rsquo;s first Energy Efficient Windows Solution for home and commercial buildings. This new product line of specialized glass is part of company SAVE EARTH MISSION to reduce the carbon footprint from the atmosphere.</p>
<p>The specialized glass solution includes double pane glass and sandwich glass which has a layer of patented material that reflects the 85% solar radiant heat as well as blocks 92% of UV rays from entering the building. The energy efficient glass is a see-through windows solution that blocks the majority of solar heat from entering the building and significantly reduces the energy consumption in terms of HVAC load.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>The energy efficient glass product line by YES WORLD not only reduces the radiant heat, thereby reducing the greenhouse effect in the building, but also reflects 92% of the damaging UV rays back out through the window, reducing fading and sun damage.&nbsp; It also provides daytime privacy through its unique one way vision design, as well as control glare issues for sensitive eyes.</p>
<p>As a climate tech company, YES WORLD is on the world's biggest mission to SAVE EARTH, working towards a solution for the biggest problem faced by mankind - Global Warming. YES WORLD is among a very few companies that have tangible offerings towards the solution of the global warming crisis. In addition to the energy efficient windows solution, YES WORLD is also working on Carbon emission data analytics as well as tokenization service for carbon offsets. &nbsp;</p>
<p>YES WORLD TOKEN is the native token for YES WORLD's Save Earth mission. YES WORLD has taken a community driven approach to generate awareness around climate change and global warming and YES is a powerful mechanism to create a strong community working towards meaningful carbon emission reduction activities while getting advantages of holding best in class utility Token in the form of $YES.</p>
<p>Launched in April 2022, YES WORLD Token is getting a lot of interest from global crypto audiences and buying interest seen across all exchanges. Based on CoinMarketCap data, it has already generated three digit returns for early adopters. YES WORLD announced launch of global utilities portal which is available in 80 countries worldwide</p>
<p>YES is a leading utility token with token&nbsp; usability available across several verticals - Gaming, Travel, NFT Marketplace, Health &amp; Fitness, Financial services as well as wide acceptance among e-commerce and brick-and-mortar stores. YES WORLD plans to onboard 10 million merchants worldwide by the global launch event scheduled in April 2024.</p>
<p></p>
<p>YES WORLD Token offers several utility services to investors and enables them to not just hold a token for price appreciation, but also to use it for various usability and utility services available in their countries. Users can make the payment by scanning the bar-code presented at the checkout on the POS Terminal using the token.</p>
<p>YES WORLD Token is trading on several leading centralized exchanges including XT.com and Coinsbit.io, as well as on decentralized exchange - PancakeSwap. YES WORLD plans to be listed on over 50 leading crypto exchanges before its global launch.</p>
<p>Just last week YES WORLD announced that it crossed an important milestone of 1.5 million transactions and 100k holders on explorer - BSCScan.</p>
<p>YES WORLD is inceptualized and promoted by Save Earth activist Dr Sandeep Choudhary, who has constantly been working to generate awareness of global warming and climate change impacts. Under Dr. Choudhary's vision and leadership, YES WORLD has championed a noble cause of reducing carbon footprint and bringing forth the issue of global warming and climate change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Important links -</p>
<p>Twitter - https://twitter.com/yesworld24</p>
<p>CMC - https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yes-world-token/</p>
<p>Website - www.yesworld.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain based climate tech company - YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd launches world&rsquo;s first Energy Efficient Windows Solution for home and commercial buildings. This new product line of specialized glass is part of company SAVE EARTH MISSION to reduce the carbon footprint from the atmosphere.</p>
<p>The specialized glass solution includes double pane glass and sandwich glass which has a layer of patented material that reflects the 85% solar radiant heat as well as blocks 92% of UV rays from entering the building. The energy efficient glass is a see-through windows solution that blocks the majority of solar heat from entering the building and significantly reduces the energy consumption in terms of HVAC load.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>The energy efficient glass product line by YES WORLD not only reduces the radiant heat, thereby reducing the greenhouse effect in the building, but also reflects 92% of the damaging UV rays back out through the window, reducing fading and sun damage.&nbsp; It also provides daytime privacy through its unique one way vision design, as well as control glare issues for sensitive eyes.</p>
<p>As a climate tech company, YES WORLD is on the world's biggest mission to SAVE EARTH, working towards a solution for the biggest problem faced by mankind - Global Warming. YES WORLD is among a very few companies that have tangible offerings towards the solution of the global warming crisis. In addition to the energy efficient windows solution, YES WORLD is also working on Carbon emission data analytics as well as tokenization service for carbon offsets. &nbsp;</p>
<p>YES WORLD TOKEN is the native token for YES WORLD's Save Earth mission. YES WORLD has taken a community driven approach to generate awareness around climate change and global warming and YES is a powerful mechanism to create a strong community working towards meaningful carbon emission reduction activities while getting advantages of holding best in class utility Token in the form of $YES.</p>
<p>Launched in April 2022, YES WORLD Token is getting a lot of interest from global crypto audiences and buying interest seen across all exchanges. Based on CoinMarketCap data, it has already generated three digit returns for early adopters. YES WORLD announced launch of global utilities portal which is available in 80 countries worldwide</p>
<p>YES is a leading utility token with token&nbsp; usability available across several verticals - Gaming, Travel, NFT Marketplace, Health &amp; Fitness, Financial services as well as wide acceptance among e-commerce and brick-and-mortar stores. YES WORLD plans to onboard 10 million merchants worldwide by the global launch event scheduled in April 2024.</p>
<p></p>
<p>YES WORLD Token offers several utility services to investors and enables them to not just hold a token for price appreciation, but also to use it for various usability and utility services available in their countries. Users can make the payment by scanning the bar-code presented at the checkout on the POS Terminal using the token.</p>
<p>YES WORLD Token is trading on several leading centralized exchanges including XT.com and Coinsbit.io, as well as on decentralized exchange - PancakeSwap. YES WORLD plans to be listed on over 50 leading crypto exchanges before its global launch.</p>
<p>Just last week YES WORLD announced that it crossed an important milestone of 1.5 million transactions and 100k holders on explorer - BSCScan.</p>
<p>YES WORLD is inceptualized and promoted by Save Earth activist Dr Sandeep Choudhary, who has constantly been working to generate awareness of global warming and climate change impacts. Under Dr. Choudhary's vision and leadership, YES WORLD has championed a noble cause of reducing carbon footprint and bringing forth the issue of global warming and climate change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Important links -</p>
<p>Twitter - https://twitter.com/yesworld24</p>
<p>CMC - https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yes-world-token/</p>
<p>Website - www.yesworld.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto bank Silvergate sees two thirds of clients withdraw assets]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-bank-silvergate-sees-two-thirds-of-clients-withdraw-assets</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/silv-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/silv-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/silv-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 13:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-bank-silvergate-sees-two-thirds-of-clients-withdraw-assets</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Customers of US bank Silvergate, which provides cryptocurrency services, have withdrawn over $8bn (&pound;6.7bn) of their crypto-linked deposits.&nbsp;</p>
Customers pull deposits
<p>Around two-thirds of the bank's customers pulled their deposits in the final three months of 2022, leading the bank to sell $5.2bn in assets to cover the cost and remain liquid.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The mass withdrawals came after three US agencies warned banks that issuing or holding crypto was "likely to be inconsistent with safe and sound banking practices," as well as the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange and the subsequent bankruptcy filing of Alameda Research, owned by former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried The case has had ripple effects throughout the crypto industry, leading to declines in value and bankruptcy filings at other firms.</p>
<p>According to an article recently published by the BBC, lan Lane, chief executive of Silvergate, said the bank was selling assets to cover the withdrawals by customers "in response to the rapid changes in the digital asset industry."&nbsp;</p>
A stunning fall
<p>Silvergate is the latest victim of the so-called "crypto winter" that has been affecting the industry since last spring. The bank, which is listed on the New York Stock Exchange and regulated within the financial sector, occupied a unique position as a bank for cryptocurrency companies that struggled to get banking services from traditional sources.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Before entering the world of cryptocurrency, Silvergate was a small US bank that went public in November 2019. At the peak of the market in 2021, its shares had grown by more than 1,500% due to the massive growth of crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The mass withdrawals have caused the bank to lose $718m, a total higher than its profit since 2013, leading the bank to reduce its staff by 40%, or around 200 people.&nbsp;</p>
Failed stablecoin project
<p>Silvergate also attempted to launch its own stablecoin and spent $182m to acquire the technology behind Meta's proposed Diem (formerly Libra) stablecoin, which never saw the light of day.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In a filing to the US Securities and Exchange Commission, the bank revealed it had sold debt to cover the withdrawals and had written off the Diem purchase, no longer counting it as an asset.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Customers of US bank Silvergate, which provides cryptocurrency services, have withdrawn over $8bn (&pound;6.7bn) of their crypto-linked deposits.&nbsp;</p>
Customers pull deposits
<p>Around two-thirds of the bank's customers pulled their deposits in the final three months of 2022, leading the bank to sell $5.2bn in assets to cover the cost and remain liquid.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The mass withdrawals came after three US agencies warned banks that issuing or holding crypto was "likely to be inconsistent with safe and sound banking practices," as well as the collapse of the FTX crypto exchange and the subsequent bankruptcy filing of Alameda Research, owned by former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried The case has had ripple effects throughout the crypto industry, leading to declines in value and bankruptcy filings at other firms.</p>
<p>According to an article recently published by the BBC, lan Lane, chief executive of Silvergate, said the bank was selling assets to cover the withdrawals by customers "in response to the rapid changes in the digital asset industry."&nbsp;</p>
A stunning fall
<p>Silvergate is the latest victim of the so-called "crypto winter" that has been affecting the industry since last spring. The bank, which is listed on the New York Stock Exchange and regulated within the financial sector, occupied a unique position as a bank for cryptocurrency companies that struggled to get banking services from traditional sources.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Before entering the world of cryptocurrency, Silvergate was a small US bank that went public in November 2019. At the peak of the market in 2021, its shares had grown by more than 1,500% due to the massive growth of crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The mass withdrawals have caused the bank to lose $718m, a total higher than its profit since 2013, leading the bank to reduce its staff by 40%, or around 200 people.&nbsp;</p>
Failed stablecoin project
<p>Silvergate also attempted to launch its own stablecoin and spent $182m to acquire the technology behind Meta's proposed Diem (formerly Libra) stablecoin, which never saw the light of day.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In a filing to the US Securities and Exchange Commission, the bank revealed it had sold debt to cover the withdrawals and had written off the Diem purchase, no longer counting it as an asset.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA['Earn' Assets Belong To Celsius, Crypto Daily TV 6/1/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/earn-assets-belong-to-celsius-crypto-daily-tv-6-1-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-celsius.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-celsius.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-celsius.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/earn-assets-belong-to-celsius-crypto-daily-tv-6-1-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Celsius 'Earn' assets belong to bankrupt crypto lender.</p>
<p>The chief U.S. bankruptcy judge in the Southern District of New York said in a court order that Celsius's terms of service made it clear it took possession of crypto assets deposited into its Earn product, dealing a blow to some customers hoping to recoup their funds from the company.</p>
<p>Hong Kong crypto mogul aims to raise $1 billion.</p>
<p>Animoca Brands Corp. is looking to raise about $1 billion this quarter for its new Web3 and metaverse investment fund, sharply scaling back its ambitions during the current crypto industry meltdown.</p>
<p>Fanatics selling its stake in NFT firm Candy Digital.</p>
<p>Sports apparel and memorabilia firm Fanatics is selling its 60% stake in sports-focused NFT company Candy Digital to a group led by Galaxy Digital, according to a report, citing an internal email obtained by the network.</p>
BTC/USD traded sideways in the last session
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair traded sideways in the last session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 16518.6667 and resistance at 17172.6667.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
ETH dropped 0.3% against USD in the last session
<p>The last session saw the Ethereum fall 0.3% against the Dollar. The MACD's positive signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 1191.511 and resistance at 1299.671.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 1.7% in the last session
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dove 1.7% in the last session. The RSI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 0.3369 and resistance at 0.3574.</p>
<p>The RSI is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD plummeted 1.1% in the last session
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dove 1.1% in the last session. The RSI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 72.5767 and resistance at 79.2567.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP Jibun Bank Services PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) captures the business conditions in the services sector. The services PMI is an important indicator of the overall economic conditions. Japan's Jibun Bank Services PMI will be released at 00:30 GMT, the Eurozone's Business Climate at 10:00 GMT, the UK's CFTC GBP NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Business Climate</p>
<p>The Business Climate indicator is based on monthly surveys and is designed to deliver a clear and timely assessment of the cyclical situation within the local economy.</p>
<p>UK CFTC GBP NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>JP CFTC JPY NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions. Japan's CFTC JPY NC Net Positions will be released at 20:30 GMT, the US ISM Services PMI at 15:00 GMT, and the US Nonfarm Payrolls at 13:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US ISM Services PMI</p>
<p>The ISM Services PMI shows the business conditions outside of the manufacturing sector, taking into account expectations for future production, new orders, inventories, employment, and deliveries.</p>
<p>US Nonfarm Payrolls</p>
<p>The Nonfarm Payrolls presents the number of new jobs created during the previous month, excluding the agricultural sector.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Celsius 'Earn' assets belong to bankrupt crypto lender.</p>
<p>The chief U.S. bankruptcy judge in the Southern District of New York said in a court order that Celsius's terms of service made it clear it took possession of crypto assets deposited into its Earn product, dealing a blow to some customers hoping to recoup their funds from the company.</p>
<p>Hong Kong crypto mogul aims to raise $1 billion.</p>
<p>Animoca Brands Corp. is looking to raise about $1 billion this quarter for its new Web3 and metaverse investment fund, sharply scaling back its ambitions during the current crypto industry meltdown.</p>
<p>Fanatics selling its stake in NFT firm Candy Digital.</p>
<p>Sports apparel and memorabilia firm Fanatics is selling its 60% stake in sports-focused NFT company Candy Digital to a group led by Galaxy Digital, according to a report, citing an internal email obtained by the network.</p>
BTC/USD traded sideways in the last session
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair traded sideways in the last session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 16518.6667 and resistance at 17172.6667.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
ETH dropped 0.3% against USD in the last session
<p>The last session saw the Ethereum fall 0.3% against the Dollar. The MACD's positive signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 1191.511 and resistance at 1299.671.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 1.7% in the last session
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dove 1.7% in the last session. The RSI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 0.3369 and resistance at 0.3574.</p>
<p>The RSI is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD plummeted 1.1% in the last session
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dove 1.1% in the last session. The RSI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 72.5767 and resistance at 79.2567.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP Jibun Bank Services PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) captures the business conditions in the services sector. The services PMI is an important indicator of the overall economic conditions. Japan's Jibun Bank Services PMI will be released at 00:30 GMT, the Eurozone's Business Climate at 10:00 GMT, the UK's CFTC GBP NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Business Climate</p>
<p>The Business Climate indicator is based on monthly surveys and is designed to deliver a clear and timely assessment of the cyclical situation within the local economy.</p>
<p>UK CFTC GBP NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>JP CFTC JPY NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions. Japan's CFTC JPY NC Net Positions will be released at 20:30 GMT, the US ISM Services PMI at 15:00 GMT, and the US Nonfarm Payrolls at 13:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US ISM Services PMI</p>
<p>The ISM Services PMI shows the business conditions outside of the manufacturing sector, taking into account expectations for future production, new orders, inventories, employment, and deliveries.</p>
<p>US Nonfarm Payrolls</p>
<p>The Nonfarm Payrolls presents the number of new jobs created during the previous month, excluding the agricultural sector.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mt Gox repayments moved back to September 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/mt-gox-repayments-moved-back-to-september-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mt-gox.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mt-gox.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mt-gox.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 12:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/mt-gox-repayments-moved-back-to-september-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a Mt Gox announcement, base, and intermediate payments will be moved back from July to September 2023.</p>
<p>After many years of waiting for their funds, creditors can now see a light at the end of the tunnel, albeit a slightly extended one. Creditors that were expecting to receive their first repayments in July, will now have to wait until September.</p>
<p>Creditors will first receive a base payment, and then also a lump sum payment. Another available option is to wait a further period, and then accept what could potentially be a larger sum. Payments are to be made in cryptocurrency, a bank deposit, or a combination of both.</p>
<p>According to a report by The Block, speculation has it that the recent change of date for crypto payments may be related to Kraken's decision to exit the Japanese market. Creditors had the option to choose from several exchanges to receive their payments, with Kraken being one of them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the exchange announced that it will be leaving Japan in January, causing some creditors to face difficulties in getting their exchange details verified in time for the previous deadline.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Many creditors have registered with multiple exchanges as a backup, but some are still waiting for their KYC to be completed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Kraken's exit may not impact the majority of creditors, it could create issues for Japanese users looking to exchange their crypto for fiat currency and withdraw to their local bank accounts.</p>
<p>The Mt Gox bankruptcy, following a hack, goes all the way back to 2014. The current day FTX debacle might be argued to pale in comparison, given that 740,000 bitcoins were stolen from customers, along with 100,000 bitcoins belonging to Mt Gox itself.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to a Mt Gox announcement, base, and intermediate payments will be moved back from July to September 2023.</p>
<p>After many years of waiting for their funds, creditors can now see a light at the end of the tunnel, albeit a slightly extended one. Creditors that were expecting to receive their first repayments in July, will now have to wait until September.</p>
<p>Creditors will first receive a base payment, and then also a lump sum payment. Another available option is to wait a further period, and then accept what could potentially be a larger sum. Payments are to be made in cryptocurrency, a bank deposit, or a combination of both.</p>
<p>According to a report by The Block, speculation has it that the recent change of date for crypto payments may be related to Kraken's decision to exit the Japanese market. Creditors had the option to choose from several exchanges to receive their payments, with Kraken being one of them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the exchange announced that it will be leaving Japan in January, causing some creditors to face difficulties in getting their exchange details verified in time for the previous deadline.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Many creditors have registered with multiple exchanges as a backup, but some are still waiting for their KYC to be completed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Kraken's exit may not impact the majority of creditors, it could create issues for Japanese users looking to exchange their crypto for fiat currency and withdraw to their local bank accounts.</p>
<p>The Mt Gox bankruptcy, following a hack, goes all the way back to 2014. The current day FTX debacle might be argued to pale in comparison, given that 740,000 bitcoins were stolen from customers, along with 100,000 bitcoins belonging to Mt Gox itself.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners return energy to distressed Texas grid]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-miners-return-energy-to-distressed-texas-grid</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/snow.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/snow.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/snow.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-miners-return-energy-to-distressed-texas-grid</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of the devastating winter storm in Texas in December 2022, Bitcoin miners returned up to 1,500 megawatts of energy to the grid, enough to power over 1.5 million small homes.</p>
<p>This impressive feat was made possible due to the flexibility of mining operations and the ancillary services provided by state authorities. In the days leading up to Christmas, a "bomb cyclone" unleashed extreme temperatures across the United States, leaving millions without electricity and claiming dozens of lives.</p>
<p>According to a report first published today by Cointelegraph, the global Bitcoin mining hashrate saw a significant drop of 30% on Dec. 24-25, 2022. However, miners in Texas proved to be model participants in the state's ancillary services, which encourage customers to reduce their consumption during peak demand in order to stabilise the grid.</p>
<p>Software providers have also been working with miners to ensure they have the necessary tools to properly enable grid balancing. Back in March 2022, the Electric Reliability Council of Texas established an interim process to facilitate the connection of new large loads, including Bitcoin miners, to the ERCOT grid.</p>
<p>With a 14% share in Bitcoin hashrate, Texas is one of the top states for Bitcoin mining in the United States, along with New York (19.9%), Kentucky (18.7%), and Georgia (17.3%). The efforts of Bitcoin miners during the winter storm demonstrate the potential for the industry to not only drive economic growth, but also to provide valuable assistance in times of crisis.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the wake of the devastating winter storm in Texas in December 2022, Bitcoin miners returned up to 1,500 megawatts of energy to the grid, enough to power over 1.5 million small homes.</p>
<p>This impressive feat was made possible due to the flexibility of mining operations and the ancillary services provided by state authorities. In the days leading up to Christmas, a "bomb cyclone" unleashed extreme temperatures across the United States, leaving millions without electricity and claiming dozens of lives.</p>
<p>According to a report first published today by Cointelegraph, the global Bitcoin mining hashrate saw a significant drop of 30% on Dec. 24-25, 2022. However, miners in Texas proved to be model participants in the state's ancillary services, which encourage customers to reduce their consumption during peak demand in order to stabilise the grid.</p>
<p>Software providers have also been working with miners to ensure they have the necessary tools to properly enable grid balancing. Back in March 2022, the Electric Reliability Council of Texas established an interim process to facilitate the connection of new large loads, including Bitcoin miners, to the ERCOT grid.</p>
<p>With a 14% share in Bitcoin hashrate, Texas is one of the top states for Bitcoin mining in the United States, along with New York (19.9%), Kentucky (18.7%), and Georgia (17.3%). The efforts of Bitcoin miners during the winter storm demonstrate the potential for the industry to not only drive economic growth, but also to provide valuable assistance in times of crisis.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital Founders Issued Subpoena Via Twitter]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/three-arrows-capital-founders-issued-subpoena-via-twitter</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/3ac-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/3ac-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/3ac-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/three-arrows-capital-founders-issued-subpoena-via-twitter</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Liquidators found a unique way to subpoena Three Arrows Capital co-founders Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, issuing them a copy of the subpoena via Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This comes after both founders have been notoriously difficult to get hold of, despite being extremely active on Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
A Twitter Subpoena&nbsp;
<p>Zhu Su and Kyle Davies, the co-founders of Three Arrows Capital (3AC), were served with a subpoena through Twitter on the 5th of January. Liquidators were granted permission to serve the subpoena from the Singaporean authorities following a United States bankruptcy court order. Lawyers have repeatedly tried and failed to engage with Su and Davies, who failed to adhere to a stipulated communications protocol. According to a presentation held on the 2nd of December,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A communication protocol was agreed between the liquidators and founders but has not yielded satisfactory cooperation.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The official Twitter account of the court-appointed Joint Liquidators of Three Arrows Capital uploaded the subpoenas.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;@zhusu and @KyleLDavies jpg copies of orders made by the Supreme Court of Singapore against Mr. Zhu, Mr. Davies, and Three Arrows Capital Pte. Ltd. are attached to this tweet by way of service. An unredacted copy of the order was served via email and can be provided upon request.&rdquo;</p>

Key Information Sought&nbsp;
<p>With the subpoena&rsquo;s help, the liquidators hope to access important information such as account information, seed phrases, and private keys of Three Arrows Capital&rsquo;s fiat and digital assets. It also seeks to obtain information about securities, unregistered shares, any accounts held on other centralized and decentralized exchanges, and other tangible and intangible assets.</p>
<p>The subpoena also directed Su and Davies to furnish all documents that were available with them.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Furnish all documents available to you regardless of whether this information is possessed directly by you, your agents, representatives, employees, or investigators, or by any other legal or non-legal entities controlled by or in any manner presently or precisely affiliated with you.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Furthermore, if the co-founders did not have possession of certain documents, the subpoena directed them to disclose the date and nature of the documents in question and explain why it was not available with them.&nbsp;</p>
Founders Nowhere To Be Found
<p>Liquidators had announced back in December 2022 that they were planning to subpoena the founders via Twitter. This is because Three Arrows Capital&rsquo;s bankruptcy process has been facing considerable hurdles due to the whereabouts of its founders. Liquidators have speculated that the duo was somewhere in Indonesia and the United Arab Emirates (UAE), where it is highly difficult to enforce court orders. Furthermore, the court has also called into question the citizenship of the founders of 3AC, which could potentially impact the court&rsquo;s ability to exercise jurisdiction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>3AC was ordered to liquidate in June following speculation it had endured heavy losses due to the Terra collapse. It was later revealed that the company had lost $200 million on its TerraUSD position, and creditors margin called the company, meaning they had to stump up more capital. The final blow came when Voyager Digital, itself undergoing bankruptcy proceedings, issued the company a default notice of $600 million. By July, reports revealed that 3AC&rsquo;s Singapore office had been abandoned, with the founders nowhere to be found. Around the same time, Zhu tweeted, criticizing liquidators for missing a deadline to claim StarkWare tokens, before going dark on social media.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Sadly, our good faith to cooperate with the Liquidators was met with baiting. Hope that they did exercise good faith wrt the StarkWare token warrants.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Liquidators found a unique way to subpoena Three Arrows Capital co-founders Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, issuing them a copy of the subpoena via Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This comes after both founders have been notoriously difficult to get hold of, despite being extremely active on Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
A Twitter Subpoena&nbsp;
<p>Zhu Su and Kyle Davies, the co-founders of Three Arrows Capital (3AC), were served with a subpoena through Twitter on the 5th of January. Liquidators were granted permission to serve the subpoena from the Singaporean authorities following a United States bankruptcy court order. Lawyers have repeatedly tried and failed to engage with Su and Davies, who failed to adhere to a stipulated communications protocol. According to a presentation held on the 2nd of December,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A communication protocol was agreed between the liquidators and founders but has not yielded satisfactory cooperation.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The official Twitter account of the court-appointed Joint Liquidators of Three Arrows Capital uploaded the subpoenas.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;@zhusu and @KyleLDavies jpg copies of orders made by the Supreme Court of Singapore against Mr. Zhu, Mr. Davies, and Three Arrows Capital Pte. Ltd. are attached to this tweet by way of service. An unredacted copy of the order was served via email and can be provided upon request.&rdquo;</p>

Key Information Sought&nbsp;
<p>With the subpoena&rsquo;s help, the liquidators hope to access important information such as account information, seed phrases, and private keys of Three Arrows Capital&rsquo;s fiat and digital assets. It also seeks to obtain information about securities, unregistered shares, any accounts held on other centralized and decentralized exchanges, and other tangible and intangible assets.</p>
<p>The subpoena also directed Su and Davies to furnish all documents that were available with them.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Furnish all documents available to you regardless of whether this information is possessed directly by you, your agents, representatives, employees, or investigators, or by any other legal or non-legal entities controlled by or in any manner presently or precisely affiliated with you.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Furthermore, if the co-founders did not have possession of certain documents, the subpoena directed them to disclose the date and nature of the documents in question and explain why it was not available with them.&nbsp;</p>
Founders Nowhere To Be Found
<p>Liquidators had announced back in December 2022 that they were planning to subpoena the founders via Twitter. This is because Three Arrows Capital&rsquo;s bankruptcy process has been facing considerable hurdles due to the whereabouts of its founders. Liquidators have speculated that the duo was somewhere in Indonesia and the United Arab Emirates (UAE), where it is highly difficult to enforce court orders. Furthermore, the court has also called into question the citizenship of the founders of 3AC, which could potentially impact the court&rsquo;s ability to exercise jurisdiction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>3AC was ordered to liquidate in June following speculation it had endured heavy losses due to the Terra collapse. It was later revealed that the company had lost $200 million on its TerraUSD position, and creditors margin called the company, meaning they had to stump up more capital. The final blow came when Voyager Digital, itself undergoing bankruptcy proceedings, issued the company a default notice of $600 million. By July, reports revealed that 3AC&rsquo;s Singapore office had been abandoned, with the founders nowhere to be found. Around the same time, Zhu tweeted, criticizing liquidators for missing a deadline to claim StarkWare tokens, before going dark on social media.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Sadly, our good faith to cooperate with the Liquidators was met with baiting. Hope that they did exercise good faith wrt the StarkWare token warrants.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky Sued By New York Attorney General]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky-sued-by-new-york-attorney-general</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1450-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1450-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1450-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky-sued-by-new-york-attorney-general</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>New York Attorney General Letitia James has sued the founder and former CEO of collapsed crypto bank Celsius, Alex Mashinsky.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the AG, Mashinsky misrepresented the financial condition of Celsius to investors, causing them significant losses.&nbsp;</p>
New York AG Sues Mashinsky&nbsp;
<p>Letitia James, Attorney General of New York, has filed a lawsuit against the founder and former CEO of Celsius, Alex Mashinsky. James alleged that Mashinsky had deliberately made several &ldquo;false and misleading&rdquo; statements, leading investors, including 26,000 New Yorkers, to lose billions. The lawsuit also alleged that Mashinsky lied to investors, hid the true extent of Celsius&rsquo;s financial problems, and also failed to meet state law registration requirements. James released a statement on Twitter, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m suing the former CEO of cryptocurrency platform @CelsiusNetwork for defrauding investors out of billions of dollars. Alex Mashinsky lied to people about the risks of investing in Celsius, hid its deteriorating financial condition, and failed to register in New York.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Attorney General further added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As the former CEO of Celsius, Alex Mashinsky promised to lead investors to financial freedom but led them down a path of financial ruin. The law is clear that making false and unsubstantiated promises and misleading investors is illegal. Today, we are taking action on behalf of thousands of New Yorkers who were defrauded by Mr. Mashinsky to recoup their losses.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The action comes against the backdrop of similar suits against crypto lender Nexo.&nbsp;</p>
Pushing A False Narrative&nbsp;
<p>James also accused Mashinsky of pushing a false narrative through various appearances at conferences, in interviews, and on social media. She further added that customers of Celsius did not have access to the same protections as those available to customers of traditional financial institutions because Celsius was not subject to regulatory norms and requirements. The lawsuit aims to ban Mashinsky from doing any business in New York in the future and pay damages, restitution, and disgorgement to Celsius users impacted by the collapse.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Mashinsky repeatedly claimed that Celsius made safe, low-risk investments and only lent assets to credible and reputable entities. However, investors&rsquo; assets were routinely exposed to high-risk counterparties and strategies, many of which resulted in losses that Mashinsky concealed from investors.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The lawsuit stated that Mashinsky, on several occasions, made statements contrary to the company&rsquo;s risk management hygiene. It cited a 13th April interview, where Mashinsky stated that Celsius did not offer non-collateralized loans. However, it increased its exposure to uncollateralized loans between 2020 and 2022, offering the riskier loans to counterparties, including Three Arrows Capital and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
The Celsius Collapse&nbsp;
<p>Celsius froze customer withdrawals at the beginning of June as its business model began unraveling. The company then filed for bankruptcy protection at the beginning of July. This left a sizable number of users with assets locked on Celsius, along with a significant gap in the company&rsquo;s balance sheet. In September, Mashinsky resigned as the CEO of the company, stating his role was an &ldquo;increasing distraction&rdquo; with users facing incredibly difficult financial circumstances.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the time of filing for bankruptcy, Celsius had 600,000 accounts in its Earn program, which had a market value of $4.2 billion as of 10th July 2022. This figure also included $23 million in pegged stablecoins. Furthermore, Celsius reported a $1.2 billion gap between assets and liabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Attorney General Letitia James has sued the founder and former CEO of collapsed crypto bank Celsius, Alex Mashinsky.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to the AG, Mashinsky misrepresented the financial condition of Celsius to investors, causing them significant losses.&nbsp;</p>
New York AG Sues Mashinsky&nbsp;
<p>Letitia James, Attorney General of New York, has filed a lawsuit against the founder and former CEO of Celsius, Alex Mashinsky. James alleged that Mashinsky had deliberately made several &ldquo;false and misleading&rdquo; statements, leading investors, including 26,000 New Yorkers, to lose billions. The lawsuit also alleged that Mashinsky lied to investors, hid the true extent of Celsius&rsquo;s financial problems, and also failed to meet state law registration requirements. James released a statement on Twitter, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m suing the former CEO of cryptocurrency platform @CelsiusNetwork for defrauding investors out of billions of dollars. Alex Mashinsky lied to people about the risks of investing in Celsius, hid its deteriorating financial condition, and failed to register in New York.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Attorney General further added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As the former CEO of Celsius, Alex Mashinsky promised to lead investors to financial freedom but led them down a path of financial ruin. The law is clear that making false and unsubstantiated promises and misleading investors is illegal. Today, we are taking action on behalf of thousands of New Yorkers who were defrauded by Mr. Mashinsky to recoup their losses.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The action comes against the backdrop of similar suits against crypto lender Nexo.&nbsp;</p>
Pushing A False Narrative&nbsp;
<p>James also accused Mashinsky of pushing a false narrative through various appearances at conferences, in interviews, and on social media. She further added that customers of Celsius did not have access to the same protections as those available to customers of traditional financial institutions because Celsius was not subject to regulatory norms and requirements. The lawsuit aims to ban Mashinsky from doing any business in New York in the future and pay damages, restitution, and disgorgement to Celsius users impacted by the collapse.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Mashinsky repeatedly claimed that Celsius made safe, low-risk investments and only lent assets to credible and reputable entities. However, investors&rsquo; assets were routinely exposed to high-risk counterparties and strategies, many of which resulted in losses that Mashinsky concealed from investors.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The lawsuit stated that Mashinsky, on several occasions, made statements contrary to the company&rsquo;s risk management hygiene. It cited a 13th April interview, where Mashinsky stated that Celsius did not offer non-collateralized loans. However, it increased its exposure to uncollateralized loans between 2020 and 2022, offering the riskier loans to counterparties, including Three Arrows Capital and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
The Celsius Collapse&nbsp;
<p>Celsius froze customer withdrawals at the beginning of June as its business model began unraveling. The company then filed for bankruptcy protection at the beginning of July. This left a sizable number of users with assets locked on Celsius, along with a significant gap in the company&rsquo;s balance sheet. In September, Mashinsky resigned as the CEO of the company, stating his role was an &ldquo;increasing distraction&rdquo; with users facing incredibly difficult financial circumstances.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the time of filing for bankruptcy, Celsius had 600,000 accounts in its Earn program, which had a market value of $4.2 billion as of 10th July 2022. This figure also included $23 million in pegged stablecoins. Furthermore, Celsius reported a $1.2 billion gap between assets and liabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Why Interoperability Matters]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/why-interoperability-matters</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-06-at-004445.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-06-at-004445.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-06-at-004445.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/why-interoperability-matters</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>What is Interoperability?</p>
<p>Interoperability in the context of Web 3.0 refers to the ability of different systems, platforms, or networks to work together and exchange information and data in a decentralized environment. Web 3.0 is the third generation of the World Wide Web, which is characterized by the use of blockchain technology and decentralized platforms.</p>
<p>In this context, interoperability is critical because Web 3.0 systems, such as decentralized exchanges, operate on different blockchain networks and protocols, which can make it difficult for them to communicate and exchange data with each other.</p>
<p>Web 3.0 interoperability solutions aim to enable different systems to work together and exchange data in a seamless and efficient manner. This includes the use of cross-chain protocols, which allow different blockchain networks such as Ethereum, Solana, and Ripple, to name a few, to communicate and exchange information, as well as the development of open standards and APIs that enable different systems to work together.</p>
<p>Overall, interoperability is a key factor that enables Web 3.0 systems to function effectively and unlock the full potential of decentralized platforms, which is why exchanges like MetaX are putting interoperability at the forefront &ndash; to foster a fully immersive experience within the GameFi, NFT, and Metaverse realm to its users who can buy, sell, and trade with ease.</p>
<p>By enabling users to access a wider range of products and services, reducing friction in the exchange process, and fostering innovation and collaboration within the digital ecosystem, interoperability is critical for the growth and development of the Web 3.0 ecosystem.</p>
<p>Why Interoperability matters</p>
<p>Although the most important aspect of Web 3.0 is interoperability &ndash; it is still one of the key challenges facing Web 3.0 exchanges. Since these exchanges operate on different blockchain networks and protocols, it can be difficult for them to communicate and exchange data with each other. This can create barriers for users who want to access a wide range of products and services, as they may need to navigate multiple exchanges and networks in order to complete transactions.</p>
<p>Web3 exchanges are decentralized platforms that allow users to buy, sell, and trade digital assets using blockchain technology. These exchanges operate on a peer-to-peer (P2P) basis, which means that they are not controlled by a central authority. This decentralized model enables Web3 exchanges to offer a number of benefits over traditional centralized exchanges, including increased security, transparency, and control for users.</p>
<p>One of the key challenges facing Web3 exchanges, however, is interoperability. Since these exchanges operate on different blockchain networks and protocols, it can be difficult for them to communicate and exchange data with each other. This can create barriers for users who want to access a wide range of products and services, as they may need to navigate multiple exchanges and networks in order to complete transactions.</p>
<p>Enter MetaX: A digital exchange that specializes in GameFi, Metaverse, and NFT projects. One of the key features of MetaX is its focus on interoperability, which refers to the ability of different systems, platforms, or networks to work together and exchange information and data.</p>
<p>In the world of digital exchanges, interoperability is critical for a number of reasons. Firstly, it allows users to access a wider range of products and services, as they can easily move between different exchanges and platforms. This is particularly important for the types of projects that MetaX focuses on, as the GameFi, Metaverse, and NFT markets are rapidly evolving and often involve multiple platforms and networks.</p>
<p>Secondly, interoperability helps to reduce friction and increase efficiency in the exchange process. By enabling seamless communication and data exchange between different systems, interoperability allows users to easily complete transactions and access the services they need without encountering barriers or delays.</p>
<p>Finally, interoperability helps to foster innovation and collaboration within the digital exchange ecosystem. By allowing different platforms and networks to work together, interoperability creates opportunities for new ideas and partnerships to emerge, which can drive growth and development in the industry.</p>
<p>By enabling users to access a wider range of products and services, reducing friction in the exchange process, and fostering innovation and collaboration within the digital ecosystem, interoperability is a key factor that sets Web3 exchanges like MetaX apart from traditional centralized exchanges. As the Web3 ecosystem continues to evolve and grow, interoperability will continue to play a critical role in driving innovation and enabling users to access the full potential of decentralized platforms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is Interoperability?</p>
<p>Interoperability in the context of Web 3.0 refers to the ability of different systems, platforms, or networks to work together and exchange information and data in a decentralized environment. Web 3.0 is the third generation of the World Wide Web, which is characterized by the use of blockchain technology and decentralized platforms.</p>
<p>In this context, interoperability is critical because Web 3.0 systems, such as decentralized exchanges, operate on different blockchain networks and protocols, which can make it difficult for them to communicate and exchange data with each other.</p>
<p>Web 3.0 interoperability solutions aim to enable different systems to work together and exchange data in a seamless and efficient manner. This includes the use of cross-chain protocols, which allow different blockchain networks such as Ethereum, Solana, and Ripple, to name a few, to communicate and exchange information, as well as the development of open standards and APIs that enable different systems to work together.</p>
<p>Overall, interoperability is a key factor that enables Web 3.0 systems to function effectively and unlock the full potential of decentralized platforms, which is why exchanges like MetaX are putting interoperability at the forefront &ndash; to foster a fully immersive experience within the GameFi, NFT, and Metaverse realm to its users who can buy, sell, and trade with ease.</p>
<p>By enabling users to access a wider range of products and services, reducing friction in the exchange process, and fostering innovation and collaboration within the digital ecosystem, interoperability is critical for the growth and development of the Web 3.0 ecosystem.</p>
<p>Why Interoperability matters</p>
<p>Although the most important aspect of Web 3.0 is interoperability &ndash; it is still one of the key challenges facing Web 3.0 exchanges. Since these exchanges operate on different blockchain networks and protocols, it can be difficult for them to communicate and exchange data with each other. This can create barriers for users who want to access a wide range of products and services, as they may need to navigate multiple exchanges and networks in order to complete transactions.</p>
<p>Web3 exchanges are decentralized platforms that allow users to buy, sell, and trade digital assets using blockchain technology. These exchanges operate on a peer-to-peer (P2P) basis, which means that they are not controlled by a central authority. This decentralized model enables Web3 exchanges to offer a number of benefits over traditional centralized exchanges, including increased security, transparency, and control for users.</p>
<p>One of the key challenges facing Web3 exchanges, however, is interoperability. Since these exchanges operate on different blockchain networks and protocols, it can be difficult for them to communicate and exchange data with each other. This can create barriers for users who want to access a wide range of products and services, as they may need to navigate multiple exchanges and networks in order to complete transactions.</p>
<p>Enter MetaX: A digital exchange that specializes in GameFi, Metaverse, and NFT projects. One of the key features of MetaX is its focus on interoperability, which refers to the ability of different systems, platforms, or networks to work together and exchange information and data.</p>
<p>In the world of digital exchanges, interoperability is critical for a number of reasons. Firstly, it allows users to access a wider range of products and services, as they can easily move between different exchanges and platforms. This is particularly important for the types of projects that MetaX focuses on, as the GameFi, Metaverse, and NFT markets are rapidly evolving and often involve multiple platforms and networks.</p>
<p>Secondly, interoperability helps to reduce friction and increase efficiency in the exchange process. By enabling seamless communication and data exchange between different systems, interoperability allows users to easily complete transactions and access the services they need without encountering barriers or delays.</p>
<p>Finally, interoperability helps to foster innovation and collaboration within the digital exchange ecosystem. By allowing different platforms and networks to work together, interoperability creates opportunities for new ideas and partnerships to emerge, which can drive growth and development in the industry.</p>
<p>By enabling users to access a wider range of products and services, reducing friction in the exchange process, and fostering innovation and collaboration within the digital ecosystem, interoperability is a key factor that sets Web3 exchanges like MetaX apart from traditional centralized exchanges. As the Web3 ecosystem continues to evolve and grow, interoperability will continue to play a critical role in driving innovation and enabling users to access the full potential of decentralized platforms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Twenty-Two Highlights from TRON’s Historic 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/twenty-two-highlights-from-trons-historic-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/test_1672946768LYx8qXvzwd_16729468062k1VQqti2N.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/test_1672946768LYx8qXvzwd_16729468062k1VQqti2N.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/test_1672946768LYx8qXvzwd_16729468062k1VQqti2N.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 19:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/twenty-two-highlights-from-trons-historic-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Geneva, Switzerland, 5th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>For TRON DAO, 2022 was a year of historic growth. Here are 22 highlights from the fastest growing public blockchain&rsquo;s record year:</p>
<p># 22 possibly the world&rsquo;s biggest DAO</p>
<p>On January 5, TRON announced its restructuring to become a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO). On April 11, Forbes declared that TRON DAO is probably the world&rsquo;s biggest DAO, as the TRON blockchain now boasts more than 132 million user accounts. </p>
<p># 21 APENFT Marketplace</p>
<p>On April 15, the APENFT Marketplace launched on the TRON blockchain.</p>
<p># 20 over 130 digital asset exchanges</p>
<p>TRX is now supported, listed, and traded on over 130 digital asset exchanges, payment systems, and trading platforms, including Binance.US, Meson, Crypto Finance (member of Deutsche B&ouml;rse Group), Fireblocks, Bitkub, Bitso, DMM Bitcoin, Kraken (TRX futures contracts), Plisio, BTCBOX, Wirex, OKCoin Japan, BitMEX, Blockchain.com, and Guardarian. </p>
<p># 19 the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance</p>
<p>TRON joined the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance to advance interoperable blockchain integration into daily business operations, focusing mainly in two working groups: Cross-Chain Interoperability and DeFi Risk Assessment, Management, and Accounting (DRAMA).</p>
<p># 18 expanded collaboration with Huobi&nbsp;</p>
<p>In October, the TRON founder and current ambassador H.E. Justin Sun was named to Huobi&rsquo;s Global Advisory Board, and the TRON ecosystem has started more partnerships with the exchange. </p>
<p># 17 the Peg Stability Module</p>
<p>On August 3, the Peg Stability Module (PSM) was rolled out, which allows users to swap between USDD and other mainstream stablecoins like USDT and USDC at a 1:1 ratio. </p>
<p># 16 sponsorships</p>
<p>In 2022, TRON was the major sponsor of Consensus, NFT NYC, Mainnet by Messari, Converge by Circle, Binance Blockchain Week in Paris, Smartcon by Chainlink, Token2049, and more. TRON also hosted several VIP in-person afterparties - TRON Whale Night, at Bitcoin 2022, Consensus, and Mainnet.</p>
<p># 15 the Binance CMC Crypto Top 10 EWI</p>
<p>On October 17, TRX was listed on the Binance CMC Cryptocurrency Top 10 Equal-Weighted Index, which tracks the performance of the top ten digital assets on CoinMarketCap as ranked by market capitalization.</p>
<p># 14 feel the burn</p>
<p>In 2022, the total amount of TRX burned from various utilities was 11.74 billion, considerably accelerating its deflation.</p>
<p># 13 TRON Academy</p>
<p>TRON Academy officially launched November 12, when 270+ students from top-tier university blockchain clubs gathered on the Harvard University campus for the "Hacker House" event. </p>
<p># 12 Travala.com</p>
<p>On August 10, Travala.com, the world's leading blockchain-based travel booking platform, announced its adoption of USDD and TRX as means of payment. &nbsp;</p>
<p># 11 the 2nd largest stablecoin ecosystem&nbsp;</p>
<p>TRON now has the second-largest total stablecoin circulation, next to Ethereum, with a market cap of $39.5 billion.</p>
<p># 10 the TRON DAO Ecosystem Fund</p>
<p>TRON DAO launched their Ecosystem Fund with 8 unique programs for funding, including TRON DAO Ventures, which intends to invest in promising blockchain startups.</p>
<p># 9 the national blockchain of Dominica</p>
<p>On October 7, the Commonwealth of Dominica announced TRON as its national blockchain and authorized seven TRON-based cryptocurrencies as legal tender for everyday use.</p>
<p># 8 the TRON DAO Reserve</p>
<p>On April 21, the TRON DAO Reserve was established to safeguard the overall blockchain industry and crypto market. </p>
<p># 7 greater influence</p>
<p>On August 1, Crypto Daily described H.E. Justin Sun as one of the premier leaders in the Web3 era. </p>
<p># 6 the stablecoin USDD</p>
<p>In May 2022, TRON launched USDD, the first over-collateralized, decentralized stablecoin, which is now held in more than 130,000 wallets. On November 2, Messari released the report &ldquo;State of USDD Q3 2022.&rdquo; USDD finished the year with a circulating supply of over 725 million and a collateral ratio of greater than 200%.</p>
<p># 5 one of the most eco-friendly blockchains</p>
<p>On August 24, in the report titled "Energy Efficiency and Carbon Footprint of the TRON Blockchain" released by the Crypto Carbon Ratings Institute (CCRI), TRON was rated as one of the most eco-friendly blockchains. </p>
<p># 4 the 4th anniversary of MainNet independence</p>
<p>On May 31, TRON celebrated the fourth anniversary of its MainNet launch. </p>
<p># 3 three stellar HackaTRONs</p>
<p>Three Seasons of the TRON Grand Hackathon, a.k.a. &ldquo;HackaTRON,&rdquo; took place in 2022, with over 2300 total participants and a combined total prize pool of over $2.7 million. </p>
<p># 2 TVL</p>
<p>According to DefiLlama, by the end of Q3, the Total Value Locked (TVL) on TRON had reached $6.33 billion, up 61% from Q2, surpassing BSC to become the blockchain network with the second-largest TVL worldwide. Messari released its first ever TRX research report on November 5, titled the &ldquo;State of TRON Q3 2022.&rdquo; </p>
<p># 1 from 69 million total TRON user accounts to 132 million</p>
<p>63 million new TRON user accounts were established in 2022. TRON aims to become the primary settlement layer of the global economy. As the global trend-setter in cryptocurrency, TRON is developing an ecosystem infrastructure that will be able to serve every human on the planet.
</p>
<p>About TRON DAO</p>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of January 2023, it has over 133 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 4.5 billion total transactions, and over $9.2 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN. In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. In May 2022, the over-collateralized decentralized stablecoin USDD was launched on the TRON blockchain, backed by the first-ever crypto reserve for the blockchain industry - TRON DAO Reserve, marking TRON's official entry into decentralized stablecoins. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which is the first time a major public blockchain partnering with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government&rsquo;s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (&ldquo;DMC&rdquo;), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica&rsquo;s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens - TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<p>TRONNetwork | TRONDAO | Twitter | YouTube | Telegram | Discord | Reddit | GitHub | Medium | Forum</p>ContactHayward Wongpress@tron.network]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Geneva, Switzerland, 5th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>For TRON DAO, 2022 was a year of historic growth. Here are 22 highlights from the fastest growing public blockchain&rsquo;s record year:</p>
<p># 22 possibly the world&rsquo;s biggest DAO</p>
<p>On January 5, TRON announced its restructuring to become a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO). On April 11, Forbes declared that TRON DAO is probably the world&rsquo;s biggest DAO, as the TRON blockchain now boasts more than 132 million user accounts. </p>
<p># 21 APENFT Marketplace</p>
<p>On April 15, the APENFT Marketplace launched on the TRON blockchain.</p>
<p># 20 over 130 digital asset exchanges</p>
<p>TRX is now supported, listed, and traded on over 130 digital asset exchanges, payment systems, and trading platforms, including Binance.US, Meson, Crypto Finance (member of Deutsche B&ouml;rse Group), Fireblocks, Bitkub, Bitso, DMM Bitcoin, Kraken (TRX futures contracts), Plisio, BTCBOX, Wirex, OKCoin Japan, BitMEX, Blockchain.com, and Guardarian. </p>
<p># 19 the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance</p>
<p>TRON joined the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance to advance interoperable blockchain integration into daily business operations, focusing mainly in two working groups: Cross-Chain Interoperability and DeFi Risk Assessment, Management, and Accounting (DRAMA).</p>
<p># 18 expanded collaboration with Huobi&nbsp;</p>
<p>In October, the TRON founder and current ambassador H.E. Justin Sun was named to Huobi&rsquo;s Global Advisory Board, and the TRON ecosystem has started more partnerships with the exchange. </p>
<p># 17 the Peg Stability Module</p>
<p>On August 3, the Peg Stability Module (PSM) was rolled out, which allows users to swap between USDD and other mainstream stablecoins like USDT and USDC at a 1:1 ratio. </p>
<p># 16 sponsorships</p>
<p>In 2022, TRON was the major sponsor of Consensus, NFT NYC, Mainnet by Messari, Converge by Circle, Binance Blockchain Week in Paris, Smartcon by Chainlink, Token2049, and more. TRON also hosted several VIP in-person afterparties - TRON Whale Night, at Bitcoin 2022, Consensus, and Mainnet.</p>
<p># 15 the Binance CMC Crypto Top 10 EWI</p>
<p>On October 17, TRX was listed on the Binance CMC Cryptocurrency Top 10 Equal-Weighted Index, which tracks the performance of the top ten digital assets on CoinMarketCap as ranked by market capitalization.</p>
<p># 14 feel the burn</p>
<p>In 2022, the total amount of TRX burned from various utilities was 11.74 billion, considerably accelerating its deflation.</p>
<p># 13 TRON Academy</p>
<p>TRON Academy officially launched November 12, when 270+ students from top-tier university blockchain clubs gathered on the Harvard University campus for the "Hacker House" event. </p>
<p># 12 Travala.com</p>
<p>On August 10, Travala.com, the world's leading blockchain-based travel booking platform, announced its adoption of USDD and TRX as means of payment. &nbsp;</p>
<p># 11 the 2nd largest stablecoin ecosystem&nbsp;</p>
<p>TRON now has the second-largest total stablecoin circulation, next to Ethereum, with a market cap of $39.5 billion.</p>
<p># 10 the TRON DAO Ecosystem Fund</p>
<p>TRON DAO launched their Ecosystem Fund with 8 unique programs for funding, including TRON DAO Ventures, which intends to invest in promising blockchain startups.</p>
<p># 9 the national blockchain of Dominica</p>
<p>On October 7, the Commonwealth of Dominica announced TRON as its national blockchain and authorized seven TRON-based cryptocurrencies as legal tender for everyday use.</p>
<p># 8 the TRON DAO Reserve</p>
<p>On April 21, the TRON DAO Reserve was established to safeguard the overall blockchain industry and crypto market. </p>
<p># 7 greater influence</p>
<p>On August 1, Crypto Daily described H.E. Justin Sun as one of the premier leaders in the Web3 era. </p>
<p># 6 the stablecoin USDD</p>
<p>In May 2022, TRON launched USDD, the first over-collateralized, decentralized stablecoin, which is now held in more than 130,000 wallets. On November 2, Messari released the report &ldquo;State of USDD Q3 2022.&rdquo; USDD finished the year with a circulating supply of over 725 million and a collateral ratio of greater than 200%.</p>
<p># 5 one of the most eco-friendly blockchains</p>
<p>On August 24, in the report titled "Energy Efficiency and Carbon Footprint of the TRON Blockchain" released by the Crypto Carbon Ratings Institute (CCRI), TRON was rated as one of the most eco-friendly blockchains. </p>
<p># 4 the 4th anniversary of MainNet independence</p>
<p>On May 31, TRON celebrated the fourth anniversary of its MainNet launch. </p>
<p># 3 three stellar HackaTRONs</p>
<p>Three Seasons of the TRON Grand Hackathon, a.k.a. &ldquo;HackaTRON,&rdquo; took place in 2022, with over 2300 total participants and a combined total prize pool of over $2.7 million. </p>
<p># 2 TVL</p>
<p>According to DefiLlama, by the end of Q3, the Total Value Locked (TVL) on TRON had reached $6.33 billion, up 61% from Q2, surpassing BSC to become the blockchain network with the second-largest TVL worldwide. Messari released its first ever TRX research report on November 5, titled the &ldquo;State of TRON Q3 2022.&rdquo; </p>
<p># 1 from 69 million total TRON user accounts to 132 million</p>
<p>63 million new TRON user accounts were established in 2022. TRON aims to become the primary settlement layer of the global economy. As the global trend-setter in cryptocurrency, TRON is developing an ecosystem infrastructure that will be able to serve every human on the planet.
</p>
<p>About TRON DAO</p>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of January 2023, it has over 133 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 4.5 billion total transactions, and over $9.2 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN. In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. In May 2022, the over-collateralized decentralized stablecoin USDD was launched on the TRON blockchain, backed by the first-ever crypto reserve for the blockchain industry - TRON DAO Reserve, marking TRON's official entry into decentralized stablecoins. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which is the first time a major public blockchain partnering with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government&rsquo;s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (&ldquo;DMC&rdquo;), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica&rsquo;s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens - TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<p>TRONNetwork | TRONDAO | Twitter | YouTube | Telegram | Discord | Reddit | GitHub | Medium | Forum</p>ContactHayward Wongpress@tron.network]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  17000 Tested - 6 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-17000-tested-6-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-5-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-5-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-5-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-17000-tested-6-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Softer After 16988 Print:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 6 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) softened below the 17000 figure early in the Asian session as the pair encountered selling pressure after peaking around the 16988 area, its strongest print since 20 December.&nbsp; The move higher also represents further gains above the 16880.44 level that represents the 23.6% retracement of the broad depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and it was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16721.41 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16786.71.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Softer After 16988 Print:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 6 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) softened below the 17000 figure early in the Asian session as the pair encountered selling pressure after peaking around the 16988 area, its strongest print since 20 December.&nbsp; The move higher also represents further gains above the 16880.44 level that represents the 23.6% retracement of the broad depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and it was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16721.41 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16786.71.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celsius Wins Rights Over Customer Crypto Deposits]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/celsius-wins-rights-over-customer-crypto-deposits</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-law-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-law-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-law-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/celsius-wins-rights-over-customer-crypto-deposits</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the latest court ruling, Celsius Network has been rewarded the rights to interest-bearing accounts, pushing actual account holders to the end of the repayment queue.&nbsp;</p>
Big Blow For Earn Account Holders&nbsp;
<p>Celsius customers can forget about getting their funds back from the defunct crypto lending platform as the new year has brought even more unfavorable tidings for them. On January 4, a New York judge ruled in Celsius&rsquo;s favor, establishing its rights to earn deposits on interest-bearing accounts held on the lending platform. This spells bad news for the customers as this means that Celsius Earn account holders can only get a fraction of their initial investment back.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Celsius is also currently under fire because of its pending bills with the mining company Core Scientific. According to an agreement between the two, Core Scientific has turned off power to 37,000 mining rigs belonging to Celsius due to non-payment of electricity bills.&nbsp;</p>
Judge Rules In Favor Of Celsius
<p>The company filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy back in July 2022 after taking major hits in the Terra LUNA debacle. According to the bankruptcy filings, the Celsius platform held around 600,000 accounts with total assets valued at a sizeable $4.2 billion. The latest ruling comes from bankruptcy judge Martin Glenn, who referenced the company&rsquo;s terms and conditions and declared that the funds in Earn accounts were company property.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The judge ruled,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Court concludes, based on Celsius&rsquo;s unambiguous Terms of Use &hellip; that when the cryptocurrency assets were deposited in Earn Accounts, the cryptocurrency assets became Celsius&rsquo;s property; and the cryptocurrency assets remaining in the Earn Accounts on the Petition Date became property of the Debtors&rsquo; bankruptcy estates.&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to the judge, the company&rsquo;s terms of service clearly stated that all customer deposits into Earn Accounts were under the company&rsquo;s ownership and would be treated as unsecured creditors in bankruptcy proceedings. This means that repaying these customers is not high on Celsius&rsquo;s priority list and that the company will repay its higher-priority debts first with the available funds.&nbsp;</p>
Previously Directed To Return Funds
<p>However, it is interesting to note that Judge Martin Glenn had previously directed Celsius to refund customer funds. Not long ago, in December 2022, Judge Glenn addressed the lending platform and advised it to return investors&rsquo; money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Judge said,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I want this case to move forward. I want creditors to recover as much as they possibly can as soon as they possibly can.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The judge had also stated that the funds held in escrow accounts must be returned to customers, even if they did not enter the company&rsquo;s interest-bearing accounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the latest court ruling, Celsius Network has been rewarded the rights to interest-bearing accounts, pushing actual account holders to the end of the repayment queue.&nbsp;</p>
Big Blow For Earn Account Holders&nbsp;
<p>Celsius customers can forget about getting their funds back from the defunct crypto lending platform as the new year has brought even more unfavorable tidings for them. On January 4, a New York judge ruled in Celsius&rsquo;s favor, establishing its rights to earn deposits on interest-bearing accounts held on the lending platform. This spells bad news for the customers as this means that Celsius Earn account holders can only get a fraction of their initial investment back.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Celsius is also currently under fire because of its pending bills with the mining company Core Scientific. According to an agreement between the two, Core Scientific has turned off power to 37,000 mining rigs belonging to Celsius due to non-payment of electricity bills.&nbsp;</p>
Judge Rules In Favor Of Celsius
<p>The company filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy back in July 2022 after taking major hits in the Terra LUNA debacle. According to the bankruptcy filings, the Celsius platform held around 600,000 accounts with total assets valued at a sizeable $4.2 billion. The latest ruling comes from bankruptcy judge Martin Glenn, who referenced the company&rsquo;s terms and conditions and declared that the funds in Earn accounts were company property.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The judge ruled,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Court concludes, based on Celsius&rsquo;s unambiguous Terms of Use &hellip; that when the cryptocurrency assets were deposited in Earn Accounts, the cryptocurrency assets became Celsius&rsquo;s property; and the cryptocurrency assets remaining in the Earn Accounts on the Petition Date became property of the Debtors&rsquo; bankruptcy estates.&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to the judge, the company&rsquo;s terms of service clearly stated that all customer deposits into Earn Accounts were under the company&rsquo;s ownership and would be treated as unsecured creditors in bankruptcy proceedings. This means that repaying these customers is not high on Celsius&rsquo;s priority list and that the company will repay its higher-priority debts first with the available funds.&nbsp;</p>
Previously Directed To Return Funds
<p>However, it is interesting to note that Judge Martin Glenn had previously directed Celsius to refund customer funds. Not long ago, in December 2022, Judge Glenn addressed the lending platform and advised it to return investors&rsquo; money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Judge said,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I want this case to move forward. I want creditors to recover as much as they possibly can as soon as they possibly can.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The judge had also stated that the funds held in escrow accounts must be returned to customers, even if they did not enter the company&rsquo;s interest-bearing accounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Silvergate Capital sees share value decrease 88% in 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/silvergate-capital-sees-share-value-decrease-88-percent-in-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/silv-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/silv-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/silv-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 15:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/silvergate-capital-sees-share-value-decrease-88-percent-in-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto bank Silvergate sees its share value fall as the crypto bear market continues to plague the sector.</p>
<p>Silvergate Capital Corp, a crypto-focused bank, has reported a significant drop in its fourth-quarter crypto-related deposits and announced plans to cut its workforce by 40%, or approximately 200 employees. This news comes as the company's shares have lost 88% of their value in 2022 and were down 40% in premarket trading.</p>
<p>According to a report by Reuters, preliminary earnings highlight that total deposits from digital asset customers declined to $3.8 billion at the end of December 2022, compared with $11.9 billion at the end of September 2022. In order to maintain liquidity, the bank sold $5.2 billion of debt securities in the fourth quarter, incurring a loss of $718 million.</p>
<p>The decline in the crypto sector, which saw over $1 trillion wiped out in value last year, has been attributed to rising interest rates and concerns of an economic downturn. The crash has also led to the demise of key industry players including crypto hedge funds, lending platforms, and exchanges.</p>
<p>A more recent calamity in the sector came when major crypto exchange FTX filed for bankruptcy protection in November, leading to increased regulatory scrutiny of how crypto firms hold funds and conduct business operations. Silvergate has also faced regulatory scrutiny in the wake of the FTX collapse.</p>
<p>Despite experiencing rapid growth in 2020 and 2021, bitcoin, the most popular digital currency, saw widespread declines last year, affecting the entire crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto bank Silvergate sees its share value fall as the crypto bear market continues to plague the sector.</p>
<p>Silvergate Capital Corp, a crypto-focused bank, has reported a significant drop in its fourth-quarter crypto-related deposits and announced plans to cut its workforce by 40%, or approximately 200 employees. This news comes as the company's shares have lost 88% of their value in 2022 and were down 40% in premarket trading.</p>
<p>According to a report by Reuters, preliminary earnings highlight that total deposits from digital asset customers declined to $3.8 billion at the end of December 2022, compared with $11.9 billion at the end of September 2022. In order to maintain liquidity, the bank sold $5.2 billion of debt securities in the fourth quarter, incurring a loss of $718 million.</p>
<p>The decline in the crypto sector, which saw over $1 trillion wiped out in value last year, has been attributed to rising interest rates and concerns of an economic downturn. The crash has also led to the demise of key industry players including crypto hedge funds, lending platforms, and exchanges.</p>
<p>A more recent calamity in the sector came when major crypto exchange FTX filed for bankruptcy protection in November, leading to increased regulatory scrutiny of how crypto firms hold funds and conduct business operations. Silvergate has also faced regulatory scrutiny in the wake of the FTX collapse.</p>
<p>Despite experiencing rapid growth in 2020 and 2021, bitcoin, the most popular digital currency, saw widespread declines last year, affecting the entire crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ThunderCore Blockchain Partners with Huobi, MyCointainer in Node Expansion]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/thundercore-blockchain-partners-with-huobi-mycontainer-in-node-expansion</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-30-155941.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-30-155941.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-30-155941.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/thundercore-blockchain-partners-with-huobi-mycontainer-in-node-expansion</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Top 5 blockchain ThunderCore is making an ecosystem-development push, partnering with a host of new validators as the chain rolls out its new cryptocurrency staking model. At the same time, ThunderCore is leveraging these promising developments to expand its presence in decentralized finance (DeFi), making overtures to leading protocols.</p>
<p>The newest ThunderCore validators include the famous virtual asset exchange Huobi and one of the earliest staking platforms in the space, MyCointainer. Users of both will now be able to stake ThunderCore&rsquo;s native asset TT to earn rewards.</p>
<p>Unlike proof-of-work (PoW) blockchains like Bitcoin, ThunderCore is an environmentally friendly proof-of-stake (PoS) chain, which means that its consensus mechanism for validating transactions is based on incentivized crypto staking.</p>
<p>ThunderCore&rsquo;s new PoS staking model, also known as ThunderCore 2.0, will dramatically increase both user staking and validator nodes. Such decentralization is crucial to secure PoSchains like ThunderCore, which must withstand coordinated attacks by malicious actors seeking to control two-thirds of the network, while adding more trustworthy validators also improves scalability and accelerates user growth.</p>
<p class="s9">Validator expansion</p>
<p>As a new partner, Huobi will implement and maintain a ThunderCore node, further securing the ThunderCore ecosystem. Additionally, Huobi's tens of millions of users will have access to ThunderCore PoS staking, while TT will be available to stake on Huobi Earn.</p>
<p>On top of operating a node, MyCointainer will allow for deposits and withdrawals on the platform. MyCointainer users will have access to TT trading pairs against BTC, USDT, and other major cryptos and fiat pairs.</p>
<p>The expansion of the validator network represents a significant step forward for ThunderCore, solidifying its position as a leading blockchain.</p>
<p class="s9">DeFi outreach</p>
<p>With the new ThunderCore 2.0 PoS staking model, the popular blockchain has overhauled its tokenomics, aiming to become an even bigger DeFi player in the years to come. Having already nurtured its native DeFi ecosystem, the ThunderCore developers are now seeking to court top DeFi protocols such as Curve Finance, AAVE, SushiSwap, Stargate and many others.</p>
<p>The ThunderCore team has begun this effort with making approaches to the leading DeFi projects. Here&rsquo;s one proposal from the developers presenting their case as to why the protocol should deploy on ThunderCore. Diversifying ThunderCore&rsquo;s native DeFi ecosystem allows the team to build a brighter future with the support of the project&rsquo;s multi-chain feature, decentralization, and community-driven economics.</p>
<p>The team offers ThunderCore's user-retention and mass-adoption strategy (over 400K monthly active users), one-stop-shop TT Wallet, high levels of interoperability, extensive partnerships, and range of developer incentives and tools, among other points.</p>
<p>Corresponding proposals are in the works for the other major DeFi protocols.</p>
<p class="s9">Future expectations</p>
<p>ThunderCore will continue to welcome new validators to its PoS network. This aligns with the team&rsquo;s commitment to providing a secure and decentralized platform for its users. Adding new, reputable organizations to the validator network enhances the security of the blockchain, making it a top choice for decentralized applications. Meanwhile, increased staking rewards under the new tokenomics are a tangible benefit to the community that furthers the same goals.</p>
<p>ThunderCore will also be encouraging more DeFi projects to open up shop. The high-performance chain offers many benefits for DeFi, including sub-second transactions, gas fees at a fraction of a cent, and massive scalability. These features make ThunderCore an ideal home for DeFi developers looking to build and grow on a reliable and secure network.</p>
<p class="s9">ThunderCore for developers</p>
<p>ThunderCore is among the most hospitable homes for developers in the Web3 industry. The company has long believed that if you attract the best developers, then the users will follow. To that end, they have made various efforts to nurture their developer community:</p>
<p class="s14">ThunderGene API Tool</p>
<p>ThunderCore&rsquo;s groundbreaking API tool allows for the easy integration of Web3 features into Web2 apps. With ThunderGene, it&rsquo;s possible to create non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and fungible tokens inside a Web2 app while outsourcing the burden of wallet security to the cutting-edge TT Wallet.</p>
<p class="s14">$100M Web3 Fund</p>
<p>Along with partners 886 Studios and Outliers Fund, ThunderCore maintains a $100M fund to assist those who would like to build decentralized applications on its chain.</p>
<p class="s14">Developer Growth Fund</p>
<p>In addition to the $100M Web3 Fund, ThunderCore also operates a Developer Growth Fund, which is about to undergo a major update. The fund guides projects to completion with technical, promotional, financial, and operational assistance.</p>
<p>Stay tuned over at the ThunderCore blog for the latest on the fund and other news.</p>
<p class="s15">About ThunderCore</p>
<p class="s16">ThunderCore is among the world&rsquo;s top 5 blockchains and the only platform growing DApp users organically through ecosystem retention, which will be the key driving force behind the real mass adoption of blockchain. Its proof-of-stake (PoS) architecture, EVM compatibility, entertainment-first ethos, and deep developer support provide a battle-tested home for the next generation of crypto innovators across Web3, DeFi, NFTs, GameFi, and the metaverse.</p>
<p class="s16">Thanks to its unique PaLa consensus mechanism, ThunderCore can handle 4,000+ TPS with sub-second confirmation times and ultra-low gas fees kept at a fraction of a cent.</p>
<p class="s16">ThunderCore Token (TT), the chain&rsquo;s popular native asset, can be stored in the feature-rich TT Wallet, together with other supported ecosystem assets.</p>
<p class="s16">Created in 2017 by Silicon Valley tech entrepreneur Chris Wang to help solve Ethereum&rsquo;s scalability issues, ThunderCore was able to reach such an achievement in ecosystem retention because of the proven, stable, scalable, and secure blockchain technology built over the last five years.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Top 5 blockchain ThunderCore is making an ecosystem-development push, partnering with a host of new validators as the chain rolls out its new cryptocurrency staking model. At the same time, ThunderCore is leveraging these promising developments to expand its presence in decentralized finance (DeFi), making overtures to leading protocols.</p>
<p>The newest ThunderCore validators include the famous virtual asset exchange Huobi and one of the earliest staking platforms in the space, MyCointainer. Users of both will now be able to stake ThunderCore&rsquo;s native asset TT to earn rewards.</p>
<p>Unlike proof-of-work (PoW) blockchains like Bitcoin, ThunderCore is an environmentally friendly proof-of-stake (PoS) chain, which means that its consensus mechanism for validating transactions is based on incentivized crypto staking.</p>
<p>ThunderCore&rsquo;s new PoS staking model, also known as ThunderCore 2.0, will dramatically increase both user staking and validator nodes. Such decentralization is crucial to secure PoSchains like ThunderCore, which must withstand coordinated attacks by malicious actors seeking to control two-thirds of the network, while adding more trustworthy validators also improves scalability and accelerates user growth.</p>
<p class="s9">Validator expansion</p>
<p>As a new partner, Huobi will implement and maintain a ThunderCore node, further securing the ThunderCore ecosystem. Additionally, Huobi's tens of millions of users will have access to ThunderCore PoS staking, while TT will be available to stake on Huobi Earn.</p>
<p>On top of operating a node, MyCointainer will allow for deposits and withdrawals on the platform. MyCointainer users will have access to TT trading pairs against BTC, USDT, and other major cryptos and fiat pairs.</p>
<p>The expansion of the validator network represents a significant step forward for ThunderCore, solidifying its position as a leading blockchain.</p>
<p class="s9">DeFi outreach</p>
<p>With the new ThunderCore 2.0 PoS staking model, the popular blockchain has overhauled its tokenomics, aiming to become an even bigger DeFi player in the years to come. Having already nurtured its native DeFi ecosystem, the ThunderCore developers are now seeking to court top DeFi protocols such as Curve Finance, AAVE, SushiSwap, Stargate and many others.</p>
<p>The ThunderCore team has begun this effort with making approaches to the leading DeFi projects. Here&rsquo;s one proposal from the developers presenting their case as to why the protocol should deploy on ThunderCore. Diversifying ThunderCore&rsquo;s native DeFi ecosystem allows the team to build a brighter future with the support of the project&rsquo;s multi-chain feature, decentralization, and community-driven economics.</p>
<p>The team offers ThunderCore's user-retention and mass-adoption strategy (over 400K monthly active users), one-stop-shop TT Wallet, high levels of interoperability, extensive partnerships, and range of developer incentives and tools, among other points.</p>
<p>Corresponding proposals are in the works for the other major DeFi protocols.</p>
<p class="s9">Future expectations</p>
<p>ThunderCore will continue to welcome new validators to its PoS network. This aligns with the team&rsquo;s commitment to providing a secure and decentralized platform for its users. Adding new, reputable organizations to the validator network enhances the security of the blockchain, making it a top choice for decentralized applications. Meanwhile, increased staking rewards under the new tokenomics are a tangible benefit to the community that furthers the same goals.</p>
<p>ThunderCore will also be encouraging more DeFi projects to open up shop. The high-performance chain offers many benefits for DeFi, including sub-second transactions, gas fees at a fraction of a cent, and massive scalability. These features make ThunderCore an ideal home for DeFi developers looking to build and grow on a reliable and secure network.</p>
<p class="s9">ThunderCore for developers</p>
<p>ThunderCore is among the most hospitable homes for developers in the Web3 industry. The company has long believed that if you attract the best developers, then the users will follow. To that end, they have made various efforts to nurture their developer community:</p>
<p class="s14">ThunderGene API Tool</p>
<p>ThunderCore&rsquo;s groundbreaking API tool allows for the easy integration of Web3 features into Web2 apps. With ThunderGene, it&rsquo;s possible to create non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and fungible tokens inside a Web2 app while outsourcing the burden of wallet security to the cutting-edge TT Wallet.</p>
<p class="s14">$100M Web3 Fund</p>
<p>Along with partners 886 Studios and Outliers Fund, ThunderCore maintains a $100M fund to assist those who would like to build decentralized applications on its chain.</p>
<p class="s14">Developer Growth Fund</p>
<p>In addition to the $100M Web3 Fund, ThunderCore also operates a Developer Growth Fund, which is about to undergo a major update. The fund guides projects to completion with technical, promotional, financial, and operational assistance.</p>
<p>Stay tuned over at the ThunderCore blog for the latest on the fund and other news.</p>
<p class="s15">About ThunderCore</p>
<p class="s16">ThunderCore is among the world&rsquo;s top 5 blockchains and the only platform growing DApp users organically through ecosystem retention, which will be the key driving force behind the real mass adoption of blockchain. Its proof-of-stake (PoS) architecture, EVM compatibility, entertainment-first ethos, and deep developer support provide a battle-tested home for the next generation of crypto innovators across Web3, DeFi, NFTs, GameFi, and the metaverse.</p>
<p class="s16">Thanks to its unique PaLa consensus mechanism, ThunderCore can handle 4,000+ TPS with sub-second confirmation times and ultra-low gas fees kept at a fraction of a cent.</p>
<p class="s16">ThunderCore Token (TT), the chain&rsquo;s popular native asset, can be stored in the feature-rich TT Wallet, together with other supported ecosystem assets.</p>
<p class="s16">Created in 2017 by Silicon Valley tech entrepreneur Chris Wang to help solve Ethereum&rsquo;s scalability issues, ThunderCore was able to reach such an achievement in ecosystem retention because of the proven, stable, scalable, and secure blockchain technology built over the last five years.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
