<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Malaysian Police Bust ‘USDT-powered Crypto Exchange’ – Suspects ‘Sold Crypto to China’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/malaysian-police-bust-usdt-powered-crypto-exchange-suspects-sold-crypto-to-china.htm</link><description>Malaysian police have swooped on what they suspect to be an illegal, international USDT-powered crypto exchange. &lt;br /&gt;
Forty people were arrested. &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange was allegedly allowing Mainland Chinese citizens to trade USDT for cash. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Malaysian media outlet Oriental Daily, the bust was co-conducted by the police’s commercial crime investigation team and the National Financial Crime Center....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/malaysian-police-bust-usdt-powered-crypto-exchange-suspects-sold-crypto-to-china.htm"&gt;Read More: Malaysian Police Bust ‘USDT-powered Crypto Exchange’ – Suspects ‘Sold Crypto to China’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Malaysia</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/malaysian-police-bust-usdt-powered-crypto-exchange-suspects-sold-crypto-to-china.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114739/276883/adobestock-213930155.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="367862"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 23 May – Conflux, Copium, Neo, AiDoge.com, Kava, Sponge, Ecoterra</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-23-may-conflux-copium-neo-aidogecom-kava-sponge-ecoterra.htm</link><description>Hong Kong's financial regulator announced it will allow retail investors to trade certain cryptocurrencies starting June 1, perhaps contributing to a small boost to Bitcoin's price in the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
The leading cryptocurrency is up by 1.3% so far today at $27,384 following the policy change by Hong Kong's Securities and Futures Commission. &lt;br /&gt;
With this new development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-23-may-conflux-copium-neo-aidogecom-kava-sponge-ecoterra.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 23 May – Conflux, Copium, Neo, AiDoge.com, Kava, Sponge, Ecoterra&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Conflux</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>NEO</category><category>AiDoge.com</category><category>KAVA</category><category>Sponge</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>CFX</category><category>AI</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>NFT</category><category>Metaverse</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-23-may-conflux-copium-neo-aidogecom-kava-sponge-ecoterra.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114756/276901/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Reuters Says They Stand by Its Reporting On Binance Commingling Customer Funds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/reuters-says-they-stand-by-their-reporting-binance-commingling-customer-funds.htm</link><description>Reuters says it stands by its reporting following criticism it received from a Binance executive on its story that said the world’s largest crypto exchange commingled customer funds.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a story published on Tuesday, Reuters reporters said that Binance commingled customer funds with company revenue in 2020 and 2021, citing sources familiar with the situation. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/reuters-says-they-stand-by-their-reporting-binance-commingling-customer-funds.htm"&gt;Read More: Reuters Says They Stand by Its Reporting On Binance Commingling Customer Funds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>CZ binance</category><category>CFTC</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/reuters-says-they-stand-by-their-reporting-binance-commingling-customer-funds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114754/276898/adobestock-494313732-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="247808"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as Halving 70 Days Away - Can LTC Hit $1,000 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-halving-70-days-away-can-ltc-hit-1000-in-2023.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC), the cryptocurrency that powers the payments-focused Litecoin blockchain, is consolidating in the $91 area, just above its 50 and 100-Day Moving Averages, both of which reside around $89.50. &lt;br /&gt;
Litecoin traders continue to count down for the upcoming halving event, which is now just 70 days away....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-halving-70-days-away-can-ltc-hit-1000-in-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as Halving 70 Days Away - Can LTC Hit $1,000 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-halving-70-days-away-can-ltc-hit-1000-in-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114752/276894/ltc.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="10749331"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Asks the Court To Step In To Get Answers on Its Rulemaking Petition</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-asks-court-step-get-answers-its-rulemaking-petition.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase called on a court to issue a “writ of mandamus” telling the US Securities and Exchange Commission to respond to its rulemaking petition within seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
A mandamus “is warranted because the SEC has made up its mind to deny Coinbase’s petition,” the exchange said in a court filing on Monday. &lt;br /&gt;
A mandamus is an order from a court to a government official ordering it to fulfill certain duties, according to Cornell University.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-asks-court-step-get-answers-its-rulemaking-petition.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Asks the Court To Step In To Get Answers on Its Rulemaking Petition&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-asks-court-step-get-answers-its-rulemaking-petition.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114749/276893/adobestock-521876474-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="375020"/></item><item><title>Symmetrical Triangle Breakout: Bitcoin Price Prediction Targets $27,600 Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/symmetrical-triangle-breakout-bitcoin-price-prediction-targets-27600-today.htm</link><description>In the exciting world of Bitcoin trading, all eyes are on the market as Bitcoin's price shows signs of a symmetrical triangle breakout.  &lt;br /&gt;
This pattern, characterized by converging trendlines, indicates a period of consolidation and signals an imminent price movement.  &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin enthusiasts and traders are eagerly anticipating whether this breakout will propel the price toward the key resistance level of $27,600. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/symmetrical-triangle-breakout-bitcoin-price-prediction-targets-27600-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Symmetrical Triangle Breakout: Bitcoin Price Prediction Targets $27,600 Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/symmetrical-triangle-breakout-bitcoin-price-prediction-targets-27600-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114689/276820/23-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482329"/></item><item><title>5 Top Trending Crypto Coins on Dextools Today - PLOUTΩS, RFD, COPIUM, BEN, GEN</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-crypto-coins-dextools-today-1.htm</link><description>Meme coin markets are currently in a frenzy, with new coins popping up every day and investors piling in in the hope of making a quick buck. &lt;br /&gt;
Here at the top five trending pairs on popular decentralized exchange analytics tool DEX Tools. &lt;br /&gt;
After an explosive start to life on Monday, the PloutΩs Coin has been choppily in the last hour. &lt;br /&gt;
PLOUTΩS was last trading around $0.000036, sharply lower versus a recent spike to the $0.00015 level....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-crypto-coins-dextools-today-1.htm"&gt;Read More: 5 Top Trending Crypto Coins on Dextools Today - PLOUTΩS, RFD, COPIUM, BEN, GEN&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Ploutos</category><category>Ben Coin</category><category>Generation Wealth</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>Refund</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-crypto-coins-dextools-today-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114742/276885/memecoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2822596"/></item><item><title>Namada, Osmosis to Co-fuse Blockchain to Fund Public Goods</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/namada-osmosis-to-co-fuse-blockchain-to-fund-public-goods.htm</link><description>Privacy-focused blockchain firm Namada is seeking to partner with Osmosis to fund software “public goods” and airdrop its planned NAM token to OSMO investors. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent blog post, Namada co-founder Christopher Goes revealed that he has proposed a partnership with Cosmos-based Osmosis that would enrich the respective ecosystems and offer benefits to OSMO token holders, stakers, and liquidity providers.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/namada-osmosis-to-co-fuse-blockchain-to-fund-public-goods.htm"&gt;Read More: Namada, Osmosis to Co-fuse Blockchain to Fund Public Goods&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Namada</category><category>Osmosis</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/namada-osmosis-to-co-fuse-blockchain-to-fund-public-goods.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114717/276844/opengraph.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="83276"/></item><item><title>Binance Denies Reuters Report That It Commingled Customer Funds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-denies-reuters-report-that-it-commingled-customer-funds.htm</link><description>Binance is pushing back against a Reuters report that said the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange commingled customer funds with company revenue in 2020 and 2021.  &lt;br /&gt;
Binance Chief Communications Officer Patrick Hillmann called the story “weak,” in a five paragraph tweet on Tuesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-denies-reuters-report-that-it-commingled-customer-funds.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Denies Reuters Report That It Commingled Customer Funds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>CFTC</category><category>CZ binance</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-denies-reuters-report-that-it-commingled-customer-funds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114735/276879/adobestock-456009336-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="126355"/></item><item><title>Unleashing the Power of AI and Memes: AiDoge AI Meme Coin Presale Rockets Past $12 Million to Challenge Pepe</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/aidoge-presale-surpasses-12-million-dawn-of-new-ai-meme-coin-era.htm</link><description>AiDoge, an AI-driven meme-generating crypto project, has successfully raised $2 million within a mere three-day span, pushing its presale total to an impressive $12 million.  &lt;br /&gt;
With only 20% of the tokens remaining for presale, the clock is ticking for potential investors seeking to secure their stake at the lowest possible prices before the official listing of the AI meme coin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/aidoge-presale-surpasses-12-million-dawn-of-new-ai-meme-coin-era.htm"&gt;Read More: Unleashing the Power of AI and Memes: AiDoge AI Meme Coin Presale Rockets Past $12 Million to Challenge Pepe&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ai Meme</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Ai Meme Coin</category><category>Meme-generating</category><category>Crypto venture</category><category>AI technology</category><category>Internet memes</category><category>M2E ecosystem</category><category>AI-themed coins</category><category>$AI token</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/aidoge-presale-surpasses-12-million-dawn-of-new-ai-meme-coin-era.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114733/276878/ai-doge-ai-memecoin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1307413"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Ripple CEO Announces Plan to Utilize $1 Billion Cash Reserves for Company Expansion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-announces-plan-utilize-1-billion-cash-reserves-for-company-expansion.htm</link><description>XRP, the cryptocurrency issued by US fintech firm Ripple, could see massive price gains if CEO Brad Garlinghouse’s plan to spend $1 billion on acquisitions proves successful. &lt;br /&gt;
The plan to spend up to a billion dollars from the company’s cash reserves was announced by Garlinghouse in an on-stage interview at the Dubai Fintech Summit last week, where the CEO made it clear that Ripple is ready to grow....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-announces-plan-utilize-1-billion-cash-reserves-for-company-expansion.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Ripple CEO Announces Plan to Utilize $1 Billion Cash Reserves for Company Expansion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ripple</category><category>XRP</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-announces-plan-utilize-1-billion-cash-reserves-for-company-expansion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114731/276861/brad-garlinghouse.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="78022"/></item><item><title>Bitget Restricts Use of AI Tools Following Troubling Results and Negative User Experiences</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitget-restricts-use-of-ai-tools-following-troubling-results-negative-user-experiences.htm</link><description>Crypto derivatives exchange Bitget has decided to limit how much it uses artificial intelligence (AI) tools like ChatGPT due to the potential for misinformation. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the exchange, problematic results, including false information about crypto-related topics, have come from the use of AI-based chat bots, which Bitget previously has used to handle customer service inquiries....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitget-restricts-use-of-ai-tools-following-troubling-results-negative-user-experiences.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitget Restricts Use of AI Tools Following Troubling Results and Negative User Experiences&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>AI</category><category>chatGPT</category><category>Bitget</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitget-restricts-use-of-ai-tools-following-troubling-results-negative-user-experiences.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114716/276843/ai-chip.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1496113"/></item><item><title>Charles Hoskinson of Cardano Highlights Open-Source Software and Security in Response to Ledger Controversy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/charles-hoskinson-of-cardano-highlights-open-source-software-and-security-in-response-to-ledger-controversy.htm</link><description>Cardano is one of the popular smart contract networks reputed for high transaction speeds and scalability. &lt;br /&gt;
The founder of Cardano, Charles Hoskinson, had claimed the network’s transaction speed to be quite outstanding and that Ethereum lags behind it despite the Merge.   &lt;br /&gt;
However, the network is recently battling with issues, creating a loop to lose out to its competitors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/charles-hoskinson-of-cardano-highlights-open-source-software-and-security-in-response-to-ledger-controversy.htm"&gt;Read More: Charles Hoskinson of Cardano Highlights Open-Source Software and Security in Response to Ledger Controversy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/charles-hoskinson-of-cardano-highlights-open-source-software-and-security-in-response-to-ledger-controversy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114728/276858/screenshot-2023-05-23-212012.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="355648"/></item><item><title>PloutΩs Coin Skyrockets 50,000% in 24 Hours: Find the Next Crypto to Explode with yPredict Market Research Tool</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ploutos-coin-skyrockets-50000-24-hours-find-next-crypto-explode-with-ypredict-market-research-tool.htm</link><description>As meme coin season continues to keep traders glued to charts, unlikely superstar PloutΩs coin has skyrocketed an eye-watering 50,000% in the latest millionaire maker pump. &lt;br /&gt;
Playing on the love of the ancient Greeks in the ever-growing meme community, PloutΩs Coin launched to a resounding pump - the likes of which has never been seen before in traditional equities markets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ploutos-coin-skyrockets-50000-24-hours-find-next-crypto-explode-with-ypredict-market-research-tool.htm"&gt;Read More: PloutΩs Coin Skyrockets 50,000% in 24 Hours: Find the Next Crypto to Explode with yPredict Market Research Tool&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ploutos-coin-skyrockets-50000-24-hours-find-next-crypto-explode-with-ypredict-market-research-tool.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114719/276853/space-g1084ed724-1920-overlay.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="811447"/></item><item><title>Global Standard Setter Recommends More Investor Protection Following Turmoil Over the Past Year</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-standard-setter-recommends-more-investor-protection-following-turmoil-over-past-year.htm</link><description>The International Organization of Securities Commissions called for more consistency and protection for retail investors following turmoil over the past year in its newly drafted cryptocurrency recommendations.  &lt;br /&gt;
IOSCO, which has members that regulate more than 95 percent of the world’s securities markets, published 18 policy recommendations on Tuesday on how crypto should be regulated....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/global-standard-setter-recommends-more-investor-protection-following-turmoil-over-past-year.htm"&gt;Read More: Global Standard Setter Recommends More Investor Protection Following Turmoil Over the Past Year&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-standard-setter-recommends-more-investor-protection-following-turmoil-over-past-year.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114725/276848/earth-g78fc97b00-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="422163"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: FBI Issues Alert About Scam Crypto Job Ads, Binance Dismissed from a Tinder-Related Lawsuit, Hong Kong to Allow Licensed Platforms to Serve Retail Investors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-fbi-issues-alert-about-scam-crypto-job-ads-binance-dismissed-from-a-tinder-related-lawsuit-hong-kong-to-allow-licensed-platforms-to-serve-retail-investors.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-fbi-issues-alert-about-scam-crypto-job-ads-binance-dismissed-from-a-tinder-related-lawsuit-hong-kong-to-allow-licensed-platforms-to-serve-retail-investors.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: FBI Issues Alert About Scam Crypto Job Ads, Binance Dismissed from a Tinder-Related Lawsuit, Hong Kong to Allow Licensed Platforms to Serve Retail Investors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FBI</category><category>USA</category><category>Security</category><category>Asia</category><category>advertising</category><category>Scam</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Ledger</category><category>Binance</category><category>Legal</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Poland</category><category>OKX</category><category>France</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-fbi-issues-alert-about-scam-crypto-job-ads-binance-dismissed-from-a-tinder-related-lawsuit-hong-kong-to-allow-licensed-platforms-to-serve-retail-investors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114699/276822/adobestock-tim-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="184430"/></item><item><title>Join the Hype: AiDoge.com, the Next Pepe Coin? $12 Million Raised as Sell Out Approaches</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/join-hype-aidogecom-next-pepe-coin-12-million-raised-as-sell-out-approaches.htm</link><description>Crypto has become the modern-day gold rush, and AiDoge.com is the shiny nugget in the pan that's causing an uproar. &lt;br /&gt;
In recent weeks, the crypto markets has been transformed and invigorated by the influx of meme coins like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. &lt;br /&gt;
But with AiDoge, the first of its kind, merging artificial intelligence and meme culture, there's an opportunity to not just ride the wave but to craft it....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/join-hype-aidogecom-next-pepe-coin-12-million-raised-as-sell-out-approaches.htm"&gt;Read More: Join the Hype: AiDoge.com, the Next Pepe Coin? $12 Million Raised as Sell Out Approaches&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/join-hype-aidogecom-next-pepe-coin-12-million-raised-as-sell-out-approaches.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114709/276841/fvl9ay6xwaazz-a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="398950"/></item><item><title>Baidu Ai Chatbot Raises Questions With Its Claim of 'improved' Communication</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/baidu-ai-chatbot-raises-questions-with-its-claim-of-improved-communication.htm</link><description>Chinese-based multinational tech firm Baidu recently unveiled its latest AI chatbot, with intriguing claims about its capabilities. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Baidu, the new chatbot can communicate with zero errors on sensitive topics. &lt;br /&gt;
However, Baidu’s claims raise questions, given the extent of the capabilities of the many AI chatbots available today.  &lt;br /&gt;
The question is: Does Baidu’s AI possess the touted ability, or is it a censorship strategy?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/baidu-ai-chatbot-raises-questions-with-its-claim-of-improved-communication.htm"&gt;Read More: Baidu Ai Chatbot Raises Questions With Its Claim of 'improved' Communication&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/baidu-ai-chatbot-raises-questions-with-its-claim-of-improved-communication.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114713/276837/hd-wallpaper-g2549229f8-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="51817"/></item><item><title>Scott Lawin, CEO of Candy Digital, on the Intersection of Web3, The Sports Industry, and Community | Ep. 232</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/scott-lawin-ceo-of-candy-digital-intersection-of-web3-sports-industry-community-ep-232.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Scott M. Lawin, CEO/COO of Candy Digital, talks about the intersection of Web3, the Sports Industry, and the impact of NFTs on fans in the digital landscape. &lt;br /&gt;
Scott M. Lawin is CEO/COO of Candy Digital, Inc., a next-generation sports and culture digital asset platform, providing authentic objects and experiences that deepen fan engagement and connect people to their passions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/scott-lawin-ceo-of-candy-digital-intersection-of-web3-sports-industry-community-ep-232.htm"&gt;Read More: Scott Lawin, CEO of Candy Digital, on the Intersection of Web3, The Sports Industry, and Community | Ep. 232&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/scott-lawin-ceo-of-candy-digital-intersection-of-web3-sports-industry-community-ep-232.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114701/276823/scott-lawin-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="119165"/></item><item><title>Meme Coin $COPIUM Price Pumps as 18:00 CET Burn Event Powers Buying Frenzy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-coin-copium-price-pumps-as-1800-cet-burn-event-powers-buying-frenzy.htm</link><description>Top meme coin $COPIUM is blasting higher today as news of its huge burn event ignites a buying frenzy. Thirty per cent of token supply will be burned at 18:00 CET today, Tuesday 23rd May. &lt;br /&gt;
$COPIUM is already 36% higher, from $0.005072 to $0.06993 as it looks to reclaim its all-time high and pump higher from there.  &lt;br /&gt;
The $COPIUM price has put in a solid floor at $0.0032 and is not looking back, as the price climbs higher on an ascending trendline....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-coin-copium-price-pumps-as-1800-cet-burn-event-powers-buying-frenzy.htm"&gt;Read More: Meme Coin $COPIUM Price Pumps as 18:00 CET Burn Event Powers Buying Frenzy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-coin-copium-price-pumps-as-1800-cet-burn-event-powers-buying-frenzy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114688/276812/copium-price-burn-event.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="199702"/></item></channel></rss>
