<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:37:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>TRON DAO Ventures Invests $2 Million in CRV and Curve to Launch on TRON and BTTC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tron-dao-ventures-invests-2-million-in-crv-and-curve-to-launch-on-tron-and-bttc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267028</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/46c45ae6-5a58-4053-9878-db127a03acb5_1692259989D7hFvsQULj.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/46c45ae6-5a58-4053-9878-db127a03acb5_1692259989D7hFvsQULj.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 17th, 2023] TRON DAO Ventures, the investment arm of TRON DAO, has recently bought $2 million worth of CRV tokens. As part of this strategic partnership, Curve will launch on both the TRON and the BTTC networks. Curve is a decentralized exchange acclaimed for its automated market makers (AMMs) [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 17th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>TRON DAO Ventures, the investment arm of <a href="http://trondao.org" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">TRON DAO</a>, has recently bought $2 million worth of CRV tokens. As part of this strategic partnership, Curve will launch on both the TRON and the BTTC networks.</p>
<p>Curve is a decentralized exchange acclaimed for its automated market makers (AMMs) tailored for stablecoin trading. Having experienced an exponential surge in the latter half of 2020, it once established itself as the epitome of DeFi platforms. Currently, Curve ranks as the world&#8217;s second-largest decentralized exchange (DEX) and the largest DEX for stablecoin trading.</p>
<p>The recent hack targeting the platform has led to a chain reaction in the DeFi space. TRON founder Justin Sun promptly expressed his support for Curve after the incident, stating, &#8220;Curve is an essential DeFi infrastructure for the blockchain industry. Our thoughts are with the team and the users affected. As a community, let&#8217;s support and strengthen the security measures to protect our decentralized ecosystem.&#8221;</p>
<p>Amidst the volatile market on August 1, TRON forged a partnership with Curve, introducing a stUSDT pool on the platform. stUSDT, the world&#8217;s first rebase real-world asset (RWA) protocol on the TRON blockchain, is hailed as the Web3 world&#8217;s version of Yu&#8217;E Bao (once China’s largest money market fund). According to <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/stusdt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Defillama</a>, the TVL on stUSDT has already exceeded $700 million.</p>
<p>Following that, TRON DAO Ventures announced its investment in Curve, underscoring TRON&#8217;s ecosystem support not only through collaboration but also through financial backing. Meanwhile, Curve will integrate with the TRON and the BTTC networks as part of the partnership.</p>
<p>The collaboration among TRON, BTTC, and Curve is set to generate crucial synergies for the industry. Curve, a foundation infrastructure in the DeFi domain, offers significant advantages in terms of reduced financial costs and time inefficiencies while also supporting prominent public blockchains like Ethereum, Arbitrum, and Avalanche. This collaboration is poised to help further develop TRON&#8217;s DeFi ecosystem. Meanwhile, as a major driver of DeFi innovation, TRON will share its most secure and cutting-edge products with Curve.</p>
<p>The integration between Curve and BTTC will also fuel the growth of DeFi ecosystems, especially DEX platforms. As the industry&#8217;s first heterogeneous cross-chain interoperability protocol, BTTC has supported cross-chain functionality between TRON, Ethereum, and BNB Chain upon its release. It will also introduce zero-knowledge (ZK) proof technology later this year, which enables users to build dApps seamlessly across different blockchains, promoting an inclusive ecosystem open to everyone.</p>
<p>With the backing of TRON and BTTC, Curve anticipates a rapid rebound, and users are bound to witness a more vibrant DeFi ecosystem in the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>About TRON DAO</h2>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of August 2023, it has over 179.07 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 6.26 billion total transactions, and over $13.01 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN.</p>
<p>In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which marks the first time a major public blockchain partnered with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government’s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (“DMC”), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica’s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens &#8211; TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<h2>About Curve</h2>
<p>Founded by Michael Egorov and launched in January 2020, Curve Finance positions itself as a DEX built on an AMM model. It focuses on the trading of stablecoins (USDT, USDC, DAI), synthetic assets/derivatives/staking assets (wBTC, renBTC, stETH), etc. In addition to its stronghold Ethereum, Curve also extended its presence across other chains such as Fantom, Polygon, Avalanche, Arbitrum, and Optimism.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-dao-ventures-invests-2-million-in-crv-and-curve-to-launch-on-tron-and-bttc/" rel="nofollow">TRON DAO Ventures Invests $2 Million in CRV and Curve to Launch on TRON and BTTC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Experiences Major Issues on Day 1: Details</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267015</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shiba_inu_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/shiba_inu_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shibarium's launch causes stir as community slams "non-functional" RPC, "awful" blockchain explorer, and an overall "sloppy" experience.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The highly awaited Shibarium finally made its debut this week. The spotlight was firmly fixed at layer-2 primarily because it aimed to elevate the meme coin&#8217;s status in the industry into a more substantial contender. The launch, however, did not meet the expectation as SHIB, BONE, LEASH, and TREAT are experiencing declines in the aftermath.</p>
<p>Transactions stuck on the Shibarium in a pending state is to blame. The community has also pointed to issues plaguing the remote procedure call system, also known as the RPC.</p>
<h2>Shibarium&#8217;s &#8216;Sloppy&#8217; Start</h2>
<p>According to the blockchain security platform Beosin, there are currently $1.7 million in funds <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1692003409602445743" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">locked</a> in Shibarium. It advised users to temporarily stop using the blockchain. The figure was further confirmed by another blockchain security expert, PeckShied, which revealed that 956 ETH was stuck on the Shibarium bridge.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">In case yall were wondering how Shibarium is going <a href="https://t.co/S5vjTxoMDk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/S5vjTxoMDk</a></p>
<p>— ʎppɐꓷ ɯooɹɥS (@shroom_daddy) <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953231289528683?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Shibarium is a layer-2 solution for the Shiba Inu blockchain that was designed to reduce gas fees and ramp up transactions.</p>
<p>However, a screenshot allegedly depicting an internal conversation on Telegram between Shiba Inu’s lead developer, who goes by the pseudonym Shytoshi Kusama, and other members of the team indicates the failure to retrieve assets bridged to the Shibarium network.</p>
<p>An additional <a href="https://twitter.com/shroom_daddy/status/1691953687994757292" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">screenshot</a> has been going around that purportedly displayed a Shibarium user encountering a technical issue with the block scanner. They mentioned being unable to retrieve their bridged balance through the RPC query. Meanwhile, the Shibarium RPC website remains inaccessible as well.</p>
<p>Prominent crypto sleuth ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1691962886585815081" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">described</a> the launch as a &#8220;sloppy&#8221; one. Shibarium&#8217;s blockchain explorer, which has faced <a href="https://twitter.com/Boo_Koo_Bucks/status/1691963193147674918" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">criticism</a> for being subpar, <a href="https://www.shibariumscan.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">indicates</a> that the most recent block was added three hours ago.</p>
<h2>Shib Inu Tokens Suffer Losses</h2>
<p>The botched launch has had a negative impact on the price of all the tokens associated with the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The SHIB meme coin, for one, lost almost 10% in the last 24 hours. However, it is the Shibarium’s governance tokens &#8211; BONE and LEASH &#8211; that suffered the most, recording approximately 15% and 24% drawdowns during the same period. Meanwhile, TREAT was also down by more than 22%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu&#8217;s Shibarium Experiences Major Issues on Day 1: Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Shiba Inu (SHIB) Crashing Despite Shibarium Launch? 2 Possible Reasons</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-shiba-inu-shib-crashing-despite-shibarium-launch-2-possible-reasons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267041</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) is crashing. Here's why.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu is going through major developments throughout the past few days that the community has been long looking forward to.</p>
<p>As <em>CryptoPotato </em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-team-announces-launch-of-shibarium-mainnet/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> yesterday, Shiba Inu developers appeared on stage at the Blockchain Futurist Conference in Toronto to announce the launch of the Shibarium mainnet.</p>
<p>The price, however, hasn&#8217;t perceived the news positively and is, in turn, crashing during the past 24 hours. But why?</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267043" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg" alt="shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_red_arrow_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Shibarium Launched Not Without Problems</h2>
<p>First of all, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-shibarium/" data-wpel-link="internal">Shibarium</a> &#8211; Shiba Inu&#8217;s much-anticipated layer 2 blockchain &#8211; launched its mainnet yesterday but not without its issues.</p>
<p>Data from Shibarium&#8217;s blockchain scanner reveals that transactions on the protocol had been stalling for no less than many hours.</p>
<p>In addition, the Shib Mainnet RPC, which should be accessible via <a href="https://www.shibrpc.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">this website</a>, is also not functioning properly.</p>
<p>There are also reports circling, which indicate that bridging to Shibarium is also impossible.</p>
<p>The underwhelming launch of the much-anticipated Shibarium network might as well be one of the main reasons, if not the main one, for the price&#8217;s decline throughout the past 24 hours.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267044" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267044" style="width: 810px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267044" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231.jpg" alt="shib_chart_1708231" width="810" height="543" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231.jpg 810w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231-300x201.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231-768x515.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_chart_1708231-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 810px) 100vw, 810px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267044" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sell The News</h2>
<p>Shibarium had been announced for quite a while now, and many were already speculating that yesterday was going to be its official launch date.</p>
<p>Events of this kind, which are highly anticipated and present a considerable shift in the development of a cryptocurrency&#8217;s ecosystem, oftentimes turn out to be &#8220;sell the news&#8221;  events.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s a common investment saying which goes like this:</p>
<blockquote><p>Buy the rumor, sell the news.</p></blockquote>
<p>In essence, this entails that investors in the know will bet on an upcoming event, buying when there&#8217;s no certainty in anticipation of a considerable increase once the event gets to see the light of day. Then, once the rest who failed to chip in earlier start buying, those who bought would take advantage of the liquidity and sell at profit.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-shiba-inu-shib-crashing-despite-shibarium-launch-2-possible-reasons/" rel="nofollow">Why is Shiba Inu (SHIB) Crashing Despite Shibarium Launch? 2 Possible Reasons</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Crashes 7% Daily, How Low Can it Go? 3 Things to Watch This Week (Shiba Inu Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shib-crashes-7-daily-how-low-can-it-go-3-things-to-watch-this-week-shiba-inu-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267017</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With the bullish momentum lost, buyers have a difficult task at stopping this correction. Key Support levels: $0.0000090, $0.0000080 Key Resistance levels: $0.000010  1. Sharp Reversal The price made a U-turn after reaching $0.000011 for a brief period. Sellers took full control of the price action in the past five days and they pushed SHIB [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">With the bullish momentum lost, buyers have a difficult task at stopping this correction.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.0000090, $0.0000080</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.000010 </strong></p>
<h2>1. Sharp Reversal</h2>
<p>The price made a U-turn after reaching $0.000011 for a brief period. Sellers took full control of the price action in the past five days and they pushed SHIB back under $0.000010 which is the current resistance.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267022" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267022" style="width: 2448px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267022" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50" width="2448" height="1199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50.png 2448w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50-1536x752.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50-2048x1003.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-03-50-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2448px) 100vw, 2448px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267022" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>2. Critical Support</h2>
<p>The support at $0.0000090 has to hold as the alternative is quite grim for SHIB. The last time the price tested the top of this wedge, it turned bullish. Failure here and this meme coin will tank further.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267021" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267021" style="width: 2447px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267021" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03" width="2447" height="1199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03.png 2447w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03-1536x753.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03-2048x1003.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-04-03-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2447px) 100vw, 2447px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267021" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>3. Bearish Cross on MACD</h2>
<p>The daily MACD is giving a clear sell signal after the moving averages did a bearish cross. This could be the start of a prolonged correction and SHIB may revisit lower levels before it finds good support.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267020" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267020" style="width: 2447px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267020" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12" width="2447" height="1199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1.png 2447w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1-1536x753.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1-2048x1003.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-17_15-05-12-1-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2447px) 100vw, 2447px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267020" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for SHIB is bearish.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for SHIB Price</h2>
<p>Wait to see if the support at $0.0000090 holds. If not, then expect $0.0000080 next. The bearish momentum may also intensify if the current support breaks which could see SHIB fall lower quite fast.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-crashes-7-daily-how-low-can-it-go-3-things-to-watch-this-week-shiba-inu-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">SHIB Crashes 7% Daily, How Low Can it Go? 3 Things to Watch This Week (Shiba Inu Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Markets Lost $40B in 2 Days as BTC Plummets Toward $28K (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-lost-40b-in-2-days-as-btc-plummets-toward-28k-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267023</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SHIB, BCH, and UNI are among the poorest performance in the past 24 hours.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price action took another hit in the past 24 hours, and the asset plummeted to $28,300 for the first time in roughly two months.</p>
<p>The altcoins have suffered even more, with ETH slipping below $1,800 and the total market cap losing another $20 billion daily.</p>
<h2>BTC Sees 2-Month Low</h2>
<p>Bitcoin spent most of last week trading sideways in a tight range between $29,200 and $29,500. It was its most impressive price increase on Monday following <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe-with-interesting-twist/" data-wpel-link="internal">news</a> about the first spot BTC ETF launching in Europe. The initial hype drove the asset to $29,700 (on Bitstamp).</p>
<p>However, the tides <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dominance-on-the-rise-as-these-alts-tumbled-daily-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">turned</a> quickly after that, and BTC started losing value rather quickly. It found itself dipping to $29,000 by Tuesday, but the landscape worsened in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The bears took complete control over the market and pushed the cryptocurrency south even more. This time, the asset fell to $28,300, which became its lowest price tag since mid-June.</p>
<p>Despite recovering a few hundred dollars since that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fundstrat-predicts-150k-bitcoin-price-but-btc-drops-to-8-week-low/" data-wpel-link="internal">multi-month low</a>, BTC is still about 2% down on the day. Its market cap has declined to $556 billion, but its dominance over the alts stands still at 49%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267029" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267029" style="width: 1793px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267029" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1793" height="765" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6.png 1793w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6-300x128.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6-1024x437.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6-768x328.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6-1536x655.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-6-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1793px) 100vw, 1793px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267029" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Alts See Red (Again)</h2>
<p>The alternative coins dropped hard yesterday, and the situation today is quite similar. Ethereum is down from over $1,850 two days ago to just below $1,800.</p>
<p>Binance Coin has declined by a similar percentage to just over $230. Ripple, Cardano, Dogecoin, Solana, Tron, Polkadot, and Polygon are all in the red as well.</p>
<p>Even more losses come from the likes of Litecoin, Shiba Inu, TONCOIN, Uniswap, and Bitcoin Cash, which have all dumped by up to 8% in a day.</p>
<p>With most other lower- and mid-cap alts trading in the red today, it&#8217;s no wonder that the crypto market cap is down to $1.130 trillion on CMC. This means that the metric has seen $20 billion gone in the past 24 hours and $40 billion evaporated since Tuesday.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267030" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267030" style="width: 1858px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267030" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1858" height="729" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6.jpg 1858w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6-300x118.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6-1024x402.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6-768x301.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6-1536x603.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-6-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1858px) 100vw, 1858px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267030" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-lost-40b-in-2-days-as-btc-plummets-toward-28k-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Markets Lost $40B in 2 Days as BTC Plummets Toward $28K (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fundstrat Predicts $150K Bitcoin Price but BTC Drops to 8-Week Low</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fundstrat-predicts-150k-bitcoin-price-but-btc-drops-to-8-week-low/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom Lee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267002</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Market strategy and research firm Fundstrat made a bold Bitcoin price prediction a few hours before the asset tanked to a two-month low.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Speaking to CNBC on Aug. 16, Fundstrat analyst Tom Lee said that if the spot BTC ETF gets approved, the demand for Bitcoin will be greater than the supply.</p>
<p>He added that the firm’s crypto strategists predicted a clearing price of $150,000 to $180,000.</p>
<p>The bold prediction is before the end of next year and only if a spot ETF is approved in the United States, he reiterated.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">“If the Spot <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> ETF gets approved … the clearing price of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$BTC</a> is above $150,000.” – Tom Lee <a href="https://twitter.com/fundstrat?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@fundstrat</a> <a href="https://t.co/ILQZqdjsZA" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/ILQZqdjsZA</a></p>
<p>— Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1691805485018607878?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>No Six Figures Without ETF</h2>
<p>When asked what would happen if the ETF applications are rejected, Lee said the halving will still create demand and price gains, “but it won’t be six figures.”</p>
<p>It should be noted that Tom Lee is an uber-Bitcoin bull who has made bold predictions in the past. In late December 2020, Lee <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/better-than-this-year-bitcoin-price-to-hit-120000-in-2021-tom-lee-predicts/" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> BTC would reach $120,000 the following year.</p>
<p>In August 2021, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-could-reach-100000-by-the-end-of-2021-fundstrats-tom-lee/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that BTC prices would reach $100,000 by the end of the year. In reality, it peaked at $69,000 in November and declined into a multi-year bear market after that.</p>
<p>In February 2022, the Fundstrat Managing Partner <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fundstrats-tom-lee-explains-how-bitcoin-could-hit-200000/" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> that the Bitcoin price could surge to $200,000. However, by the end of 2022, BTC had slumped to a bear market cycle low of $16,000.</p>
<p>Now just a few hours after he offered a $150,000 BTC price forecast, the asset has slumped to a two-month low.</p>
<p>BTC has fallen 2% on the day to an intraday and two-month low of $28,430 during the Thursday morning Asian trading session.</p>
<p>The move followed the release of the minutes of a Federal Reserve meeting in which it said it did not expect a recession though officials still saw the need for higher rates.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Bears Lurking</h2>
<p>Despite the fact that Bitcoin is still <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-investors-reach-all-time-low-in-on-chain-spending-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal">trading sideways</a> on longer-term charts, the bearish sentiment is seeping in.</p>
<p>Analysts were saying that BTC looks very weak and a “savage breakdown” could be imminent.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">looking like <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/btc?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#btc</a> is about to lose this channel we formed over the last 2 weeks, all bounces from the highs have been super shallow with none even reaching any 0.618 fib levels.</p>
<p>btc looking super weak to me with alts looking even worse and i cant help but feel a savage breakdown… <a href="https://t.co/WYPwgQGSGU" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/WYPwgQGSGU</a></p>
<p>— Bluntz (@Bluntz_Capital) <a href="https://twitter.com/Bluntz_Capital/status/1691938883179823311?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Willy Woo <a href="https://twitter.com/woonomic/status/1691854547273282010" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> it was “crunch time for BTC,” adding:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Macro headwinds from US dollar strength. Meanwhile there’s increasing demand on futures market (pro traders) and on-chain fundamentals picking up. Either way, up or down, we are now setting up for a strong move. Volatility squeeze incoming.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The dip is the largest since July 24 but is pretty minor when zooming out to view the multi-month view.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fundstrat-predicts-150k-bitcoin-price-but-btc-drops-to-8-week-low/" rel="nofollow">Fundstrat Predicts $150K Bitcoin Price but BTC Drops to 8-Week Low</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON Joins Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 05:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266972</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Untitled_1692216043q3dmsuXTjG.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Untitled_1692216043q3dmsuXTjG.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 16th, 2023] TRON DAO (“TRON”) is pleased to announce that it has joined the Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (“JCBA”) as an associate member starting from August 1st, 2023. As a leading global blockchain, TRON is committed to building cooperation and collaboration with other JCBA members to promote the growth [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 16th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://trondao.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>TRON DAO</strong></a><strong> (“TRON”)</strong> is pleased to announce that it has joined the <a href="https://cryptocurrency-association.org" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Japan Cryptoasset Business Association</strong></a><strong> (“JCBA”)</strong> as an associate member starting from August 1st, 2023. As a leading global blockchain, TRON is committed to building cooperation and collaboration with other JCBA members to promote the growth of the crypto industry in Japan and all across Asia.</p>
<p>Established in 2016, JCBA is a Japanese-based association for stakeholders within the Web3 ecosystem. It aims to foster a promising environment for the development of digital assets, including cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and stablecoins. Currently, JCBA has 134 members from both Web3 and traditional industries based in Japan and internationally.</p>
<p>By joining as an associate member of JCBA, TRON strives to closely collaborate with the Japanese market and contribute to JCBA&#8217;s vision by leveraging TRON&#8217;s efficient network and robust userbase.</p>
<h2>About TRON DAO</h2>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of August 2023, it has over 179.07 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 6.26 billion total transactions, and over $13.01 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN.</p>
<p>In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which marks the first time a major public blockchain partnered with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government’s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (“DMC”), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica’s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens &#8211; TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<h2>About JCBA</h2>
<p>The Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA) was established in 2016 as a membership organization for stakeholders in the public blockchain and Web3.0 ecosystems who conduct business related to crypto assets, NFTs, stablecoins, and other digital assets in Japan, with the goal of improving the environment.</p>
<p>Website of JCBA: <a href="https://cryptocurrency-association.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://cryptocurrency-association.org/</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-joins-japan-cryptoasset-business-association-jcba/" rel="nofollow">TRON Joins Japan Cryptoasset Business Association (JCBA)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dubai Authorities Fined OPNX $2.7 Million for a Market Offense</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-authorities-fined-opnx-2-7-million-for-a-market-offense/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266904</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Dubai.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Dubai.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A month after going live, OPNX created by founders of the collapsed 3AC, was slammed with a $2.7 million fine by Dubai's VARA.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Dubai&#8217;s Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA) fined OPNX — the cryptocurrency project created by founders of the defunct digital asset hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) — along with the project&#8217;s founders and CEO, shortly after issuing a reprimand in May.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the executives have paid their fine, VARA said OPNX is yet to make payment, with the regulator considering taking actions against the platform.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">VARA Fined OPNX, CEO, and Founders $2.7M</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In an <a href="https://www.vara.ae/en/regulations/regulatory-notices/vara-notice-of-fines-opnx-exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">enforcement notice</a> published on Wednesday (Aug. 16, 2023), VARA revealed that OPNX was yet to pay a fine of 10 million AED ($2.72 million) issued against it on May 2 for a market offense.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The regulator also issued a penalty fine of 200,000 AED ($54,450) to OPNX CEO Leslie Lamb, 3AC founders Su Zhu and Kylie Davies, and OPNX co-founder Mark Lamb on the same day for violating marketing, advertising, and promotions regulations. According to VARA, all four individuals have fully paid their fines.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The launch of OPNX in April 2023 was met with criticisms from the crypto community, majorly because the platform was created by Zhu and Davies, who were behind a previous cryptocurrency project that collapsed and left investors with huge losses. Currently, OPNX&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/OPNX_Official/status/1691607311167455338?t=vHYICC9bt8bclcBfL1TTSg&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">average daily volume</a> is $102 million, with a 24-hour trade volume of over $165.8 million and a seven-day trade volume of $715 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">OPNX later went ahead to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-founders-launch-brand-new-vc-fund-tied-to-opnx/" data-wpel-link="internal">announce</a> a new ecosystem partner, a venture capital fund called 3AC Ventures (separate from the defunct hedge fund 3AC), with Davies <a href="https://twitter.com/KyleLDavies/status/1671505640848515072?t=71lRoJ0JDbDTiXSTXa4oAg&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stating</a>, &#8220;3AC is dead, long live 3AC Ventures.&#8221; The VC fund, which, unsurprisingly, was not well received by community members, offers &#8220;superior risk-adjusted returns without leverage,&#8221; according to its website.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Dubai Taking Tough Stance Against OPNX</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Before the fines, VARA <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-regulator-reprimands-opnx-founders-for-conducting-unregulated-activity/" data-wpel-link="internal">reprimanded</a> Zhu, Davies, Mark Lamb, Leslie Lamb, and Sudhu Arumugan for carrying out unregulated activities in Dubai and for also promoting and marketing OPNX to residents without regulatory approval.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the regulator is looking to take further actions against OPNX for its failure to pay its fine.</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;Vara shall determine consequential actions warranted against OPNX, which may include further fines, penalties, and/or taking any actions necessary to recover payment and definitively remedy the behavior including, but not limited to, referring the matter to any law enforcement agency(ies) or competent courts.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-authorities-fined-opnx-2-7-million-for-a-market-offense/" rel="nofollow">Dubai Authorities Fined OPNX $2.7 Million for a Market Offense</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple (XRP) Rival Stellar (XLM) Becomes Minority Investor in MoneyGram</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-rival-stellar-xlm-becomes-minority-investor-in-moneygram/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266743</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/moneygram_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/moneygram_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SDF's commercial partnership with MoneyGram officially began in 2021.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Stellar Development Foundation (SDF) &#8211; the organization behind the Stellar network that facilitates cross-border transactions &#8211; announced becoming a minority investor in payments giant MoneyGram International.</p>
<p>The latest investment is the first of its kind made from SDF&#8217;s treasury which includes a position on MGI&#8217;s Board of Directors. Denelle Dixon, SDF CEO and Executive Director, will occupy that role, according to the official announcement.</p>
<h2>Stellar x MoneyGram</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://stellar.org/blog/sdfs-investment-in-moneygram-international" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">investment</a> was sourced from SDF&#8217;s internal cash reserve, Dixon said in a statement. This cash reserve is designated to support the operations of the non-profit organization rather than the Enterprize Fund, which targets investments in startups and emerging businesses.</p>
<p>The exec mentioned that the investment is expected to position SDF as a crucial player aiding MoneyGram in expanding its digital business, exploring blockchain technology, and contributing to the many other ways the fintech company allows consumers and businesses to transfer and manage money in nearly every country across the globe.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This is an exciting time for SDF and MGI, and I believe the opportunities will only grow. Continuing to build strong partnerships with organizations across the payments space puts SDF one step closer to achieving our mission of creating equitable access to financial services.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>MoneyGram and SDF&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stellar-lumens-xlm-spikes-12-after-news-of-a-partnership-between-moneygram-and-the-stellar-foundation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnership</a> dates back to October 2021, when the two joined forces to settle transactions with USDC stablecoin for instant and cheaper transactions.</p>
<h2>Bidding Ripple Adieu</h2>
<p>The payments firm previously partnered with Stellar&#8217;s direct competitor to leverage the RippleNet as part of the exchange settlements process for international remittances. MoneyGram also received financial incentives in the form of XRP in exchange for giving Ripple an equity stake in the company.</p>
<p>MoneyGram, however, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-and-moneygram-part-ways-amid-sec-litigation-while-xrp-eyes-0-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">severed its ties</a> with Ripple in March 2021, a few months after the SEC slapped the blockchain firm with a lawsuit over XRP. At that time, Ripple maintained that the decision to part ways was mutual and hinted at a potential rekindling once the legal spat was over.</p>
<p>While Ripple secured a partial victory against the SEC this year, MoneyGram has not yet revisited the idea of reinstating the partnership. With SDF, on the other hand, the payment company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/moneygram-to-partner-with-stellar-to-provide-stablecoin-remittances/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to offer stablecoin remittances last year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-rival-stellar-xlm-becomes-minority-investor-in-moneygram/" rel="nofollow">Ripple (XRP) Rival Stellar (XLM) Becomes Minority Investor in MoneyGram</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Team Announces Launch Of Shibarium Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shib-team-announces-launch-of-shibarium-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266984</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/shibainu_downtrend_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/shibainu_downtrend_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Shibarium mainnet is now live and ready for users and developers alike.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Wednesday, Shiba Inu (SHIB) developers appeared on stage at the Blockchain Futurist Conference in Toronto to discuss the “End Game” for Shibarium – the meme token’s metaverse and NFT-oriented layer 2 blockchain.</p>
<p>The team said that the Shibarium mainnet has gone live, allowing developers to begin building apps on the blockchain.</p>
<ul>
<li>The ecosystem will include “Shibdentities,” a proof of personhood solution that lets users retain control of their data and privacy.</li>
<li>Shibdentities can be used to create digital wills, which transfer assets to another user’s wallet after one person’s death is confirmed.</li>
<li>“We are building a decentralized, autonomous, digital nation state,” said the team during its keynote presentation.</li>
<li>Regarding the Shibarium metaverse, the ecosystem will feature “seamless transactions” and its “Shiboshi” NFTs.</li>
<li>Shibarium will also use an “super app” called the ShibaHub – a common location for accessing a users’ favorite dapps.</li>
<li>Like many layer 2 solutions, “Shibarium” aims to address the scaling issues and transaction costs that plague Ethereum’s base layer.</li>
<li>Until now, details about Shibarium’s technical development have been largely a mystery.</li>
<li>However, lead developer Shytoshi Kusama has provided many hints about what features it will include, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-pumps-after-lead-developer-shares-shibarium-update-details/" data-wpel-link="internal">real-world asset authentication</a>.</li>
<li>SHIB is currently the 13th largest crypto by market cap.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-team-announces-launch-of-shibarium-mainnet/" rel="nofollow">SHIB Team Announces Launch Of Shibarium Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
