<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:08:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Investing Retirement Funds in Bitcoin Remains a Good Idea: Senator Lummis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/investing-retirement-funds-in-bitcoin-remains-a-good-idea-senator-lummis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228495</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/CynthiaLummis.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/CynthiaLummis.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["Im very comfortable with making sure that people can include bitcoin in their retirement funds," Cynthia Lummis said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Republican Senator Cynthia Lummis remains unfazed by the ongoing bear market, saying Americans should feel safe investing their retirement savings in bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The politician is among the biggest advocates of the primary cryptocurrency and is even a HODLer.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Bitcoin is Different&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The turmoil in the world of crypto, the numerous bankruptcies, the scandals, and the price decline of most digital currencies, have not changed Senator Lummis&#8217; stance on bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.semafor.com/article/12/12/2022/lummis-bitcoin-401k" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Semafor, she reiterated her view that adding BTC to 401(k) plans could be a prosperous move:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I&#8217;m very comfortable with making sure that people can include bitcoin in their retirement funds because it&#8217;s just different than other cryptocurrencies.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Senator Lummis once again praised the asset for its scarcity and a limited maximum cap of 21 million. According to her, that will drive its USD valuation up in the future:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;That&#8217;s a personal belief, just based on its scarcity.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_102822" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-102822" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-102822" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover.jpg" alt="Cynthia_lummis_cover" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-102822" class="wp-caption-text">Cynthia Lummis, Source: Twitter</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some American politicians are not so supportive of investing retirement funds in bitcoin. Earlier this year, Senator Warren </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sen-elizabeth-warren-concerned-about-fidelitys-bitcoin-401k-plan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">questioned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Fidelity&#8217;s decision to enable investors to put bitcoin into their 401(k) plans.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Investing in cryptocurrencies is a risky and speculative gamble, and we are concerned that Fidelity would take these risks with millions of Americans&#8217; retirement savings,&#8221; she said at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lummis also intends to reintroduce her crypto bill in January and will meet with the SEC to discuss all the details. The proposed legislation aims to grant consumers maximum protection and set certain taxation standards.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Thank God for Bitcoin&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Republican Senator </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-lummis-thanks-god-for-bitcoin-as-the-us-raises-debt-ceiling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">criticized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the US authorities for letting the country slip into such a monetary crisis last year. In her view, the American dollar could lose its power in the future, which is why officials should ensure that &#8220;non-fiat currencies&#8221; can flourish instead.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin&#8217;s decentralized nature could give people the financial freedom they need and act as a shield if such an event occurs:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Thank god for Bitcoin and other digital currencies that transcend the irresponsibility of governments – including our own. That is an indictment of our responsibility to address this looming, predictable, massive issue.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lummis has been a BTC advocate for years and has even invested some of her wealth in it. She bought five bitcoins in 2013 when its price was hovering around $300 and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-cynthia-lummis-bought-up-to-100000-worth-of-btc-in-august/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">topped up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> her stash with up to $100,000 worth of BTC last August.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/investing-retirement-funds-in-bitcoin-remains-a-good-idea-senator-lummis/" rel="nofollow">Investing Retirement Funds in Bitcoin Remains a Good Idea: Senator Lummis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stringent Crypto Regulation Incoming After FTX Collapse: Warns Thai SEC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stringent-crypto-regulation-incoming-after-ftx-collapse-warns-thai-sec/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thailand]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228508</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Thailand.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Thailand.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The agency is currently in the process of improving digital asset governance and the modifications are expected to mirror the supervision of international regulators.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The FTX collapse spurred action from yet another financial watchdog. The Thailand Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is gearing up to impose more stringent regulations on crypto assets similar to that of the global market in a bid to protect investors.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.bangkokpost.com/business/2459245/sec-readies-stricter-rules-for-digital-assets" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Bangkok Post</a>, the SEC said that regulators should play a greater role in enhancing investor protection mechanisms.</p>
<ul>
<li>The regulator has established a working committee consisting of relevant government agencies and private sector representatives to study and propose ways to enhance the laws to adapt to the market.</li>
<li>The use of decentralized ledger technology (DLT) in business will also be a focus of the recommendation.</li>
<li>Monitoring new potential risks and investor protection will take the center stage.</li>
<li>The SEC has also asserted that matters relating to governing advertisements and product promotions, preventing conflicts of interest, as well as strengthening cybersecurity will be addressed with effective regulations.</li>
<li>The collapse of the algorithmic stablecoin in the Terra ecosystem triggered the fall of a slew of crypto lenders, such as Three Arrows Capital, creating a credit crunch in the ecosystem.</li>
<li>However, the severity of the market downturn was only known after the unraveling of FTX, which prompted a massive reduction in capital inflows.</li>
<li>There is also an increased threat that some of the existing centralized exchanges could follow suit. These events highlight the vulnerability of the digital asset industry and the lack of proper oversight, according to the Thai SEC.</li>
<li>The latest development comes three months after SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thai-sec-toughens-crypto-ad-regulations-amid-broader-market-downturn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">issued</a> a statement asking cryptocurrency companies to include clear and visible warnings about the risks associated with virtual tokens and crypto investments.</li>
<li>The regulator had also warned the companies operating in the country to abstain from giving false and misleading information in their ads.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stringent-crypto-regulation-incoming-after-ftx-collapse-warns-thai-sec/" rel="nofollow">Stringent Crypto Regulation Incoming After FTX Collapse: Warns Thai SEC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF To Spend Christmas In Prison After Being Denied Parole By The Bahamas</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-to-spend-christmas-in-prison-after-being-denied-parole-by-the-bahamas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228653</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Sam-Bankman-Fried-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Sam-Bankman-Fried-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SBF is going to have a lonely Christmas. One day after his arrest, the Bahamas denied him the possibility of bail.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On December 13, 2022, Bahamian authorities denied parole to Sam Bankman-Fried, also known as SBF, after he was charged by U.S. lawmakers with eight counts of financial fraud.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/bankman-fried-appear-bahamas-court-us-unveil-charges-2022-12-13/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by Reuters, Bahamian Chief Magistrate JoyAnn Ferguson-Pratt denied Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s lawyers&#8217; request for parole, citing a &#8220;great&#8221; risk of him becoming a fugitive.</p>
<p>Therefore, SBF, now inmate 1472, must spend Christmas in a Bahamian correctional facility, per Magistrate Ferguson-Pratt&#8217;s order, and stay there at least until February 8, 2023.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Faces a 115-Year Prison Term</h2>
<p>SBF faces a maximum sentence of 115 years in prison. The magnitude of the case is so large that it may vary depending on new evidence that comes to light against the defendant, Reuters reported.</p>
<p>Mark S. Cohen, one of SBF&#8217;s defense attorneys, said they are reviewing all of the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-what-sbf-is-facing-after-the-sec-charged-him-with-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">fraud charges</a> brought against SBF and the legal team hired by the defendant.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Mr. Bankman-Fried is reviewing the charges with his legal team and considering all of his legal options&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>His extradition hearing is set for February 8, 2023.</p>
<h2>Sam Bankman-Fried Conspired To Fraud</h2>
<p>Merrick Garland, U.S. Attorney General, <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/ftx-founder-indicted-fraud-money-laundering-and-campaign-finance-offenses" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> Sam Bankman-Fried conspired to defraud FTX customers and misappropriate their deposits for his personal benefit, making him liable for multiple charges, including money laundering and securities fraud.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We allege that the defendant conspired to defraud customers by misappropriating their deposits; to defraud lenders; to commit securities fraud and money laundering; and to violate campaign finance laws,&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Damian Williams, U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York, said that Sam Bankman-Fried donated &#8220;tens of millions of dollars in illegal campaign contributions&#8221; to both Democratic and Republican politicians with &#8220;money stolen from clients.&#8221; He further added that the FTX collapse was one of the &#8220;biggest financial frauds in American history.&#8221;</p>
<h2>U.S. Regulators to take strong action against SBF</h2>
<p>Alexander N. Green, Member of the U.S. House of Representatives from Texas&#8217; 9th district, said during today&#8217;s hearing that many people were hurt by SBF, so they have a duty to &#8220;<a href="https://financialservices.house.gov/events/eventsingle.aspx?EventID=410002#Webcast" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">send a message</a>&#8221; to those who want to harm others that the U.S. will not tolerate such a thing.</p>
<p>He further added that he finds it hard to believe that they are dealing with &#8220;unknowing stupidity,&#8221; criticizing SBF&#8217;s different interviews and media appearances, conveying that he was not committing fraud but just being a poor manager.</p>
<p>As lawyers say, &#8220;ignorance of the law does not exempt from compliance,&#8221; so probably the ignorance that SBF has wanted to preach through its interviews regarding the use of funds of its users will not be able to be used in its favor in court.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-to-spend-christmas-in-prison-after-being-denied-parole-by-the-bahamas/" rel="nofollow">SBF To Spend Christmas In Prison After Being Denied Parole By The Bahamas</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Used Client Assets for Margin Trading at Alameda, Confirms Bankruptcy Lawyer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-used-client-assets-for-margin-trading-at-alameda-confirms-bankruptcy-lawyer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 23:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228645</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/1200x-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/1200x-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[John Ray confirmed what many industry leaders expect, and what Sam Bankman-Fried has avoided directly stating.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">FTX’s bankruptcy attorney and new CEO, John Ray, spoke to the House Financial Services Committee on Friday to break down some of the internal details of the exchange’s fallout. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ray said that FTX customers’ assets were used by Alameda Research for margin trading, confirming a long-held suspicion about the two companies that former boss Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) has been hesitant to admit. </span></p>
<h2>Confirming the Fraud</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">During his </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ovhBvQ5-vCY&amp;ab_channel=WashingtonPost" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">preliminary remarks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Ray said that while his investigation was still at an early stage, certain critical facts had already been made clear. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“First, customer assets at FTX.com were comingled with assets from the Alameda trading platform,” he said. “That much is clear.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Second, Alameda used client funds to engage in margin trading, which exposed customer funds to massive losses,&#8221; he added. As a market maker, Alameda had deployed funds to “various third-party exchanges” that were “inherently unsafe”, and subject to limited market protections within those jurisdictions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When asked about governance ties between both FTX and Alameda, Ray said there was virtually “no separateness” between the entities, nor internal risk management controls. The entire FTX Group, consisting of over 130 companies including FTX.com, FTX US, and Alameda, were “owned and controlled by Sam Bankman-Fried.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While there was a “public distinction” between both FTX and FTX US, Ray said that crypto assets for both firms were housed in the AWS system. Still, these were independent of Alameda’s assets – giving possible credence to Bankman-Fried’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-says-ftx-us-should-be-solvent-unsure-why-withdrawals-not-enabled/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">prior assertions</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that FTX US is still solvent.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When responding to the former billionaire’s claims about not making decisions around Alameda’s governance, Ray’s statements were much more skeptical. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I will note that he owned 90% of Alameda. There’s no distinction whatsoever. The owners of the company could have free reign across all siloes.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Contributing to FTX’s financial trouble was a so-called “spending binge” throughout both 2021 and 2022, during which $5 billion were spent on businesses and investments. The company’s profligate spending on various sponsorships, a stadium, and other </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-ftx-buys-ad-for-the-super-bowl/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">promotional deals</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> has been subject to much criticism from rival exchange leaders, including Binance’s </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1601140890336395264" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Changpeng Zhao</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Kraken’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/krakens-jesse-powell-blasts-ftx-ceo-lists-all-red-flags-about-sbf/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Jesse Powell</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<h2>Bankman-Fried’s Claims</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Sam Bankman-Fried has avoided directly answering whether client assets were used for margin trading at Alameda Research, </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SCW89n9ooRY&amp;t=1s&amp;ab_channel=AltcoinDaily" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">claiming</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that he “did not know” there was any improper use of customer funds. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, he has </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4o_jPzBZSIo&amp;t=1s&amp;ab_channel=PowerfulJRE" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">stated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in previous interviews that customer assets were treated with “fungibility” during the bank run against his exchange in early November. That means customers holding digital assets on the exchange, which had guaranteed safety under his exchange’s terms of service, were treated equally to assets used for futures and margin trading. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bankman-Fried was supposed to appear at the congressional hearing alongside John Ray, but was arrested by Bahamian regulators on Monday. In his prepared remarks, he </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-sam-bankman-fried-planned-to-tell-congress-about-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">confirmed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that FTX lacked a risk management team.</p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of Bloomberg.</em><br />
</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-used-client-assets-for-margin-trading-at-alameda-confirms-bankruptcy-lawyer/" rel="nofollow">FTX Used Client Assets for Margin Trading at Alameda, Confirms Bankruptcy Lawyer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Responds to FUD, Promises Zero Secured Loans in 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-responds-to-fud-promises-zero-secured-loans-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228640</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tether.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tether.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether is putting in more effort to silence its critics as post-FTX skepticism sweeps across the crypto industry.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tether is back again with criticism of the mainstream media, which has once again called out the stablecoin provider for having potentially unreliable reserves.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In response to the “recent cycle of Tether FUD,” the company has promised to reduce the secured loans in its reserves to zero by the end of 2023. </span></p>
<h2>What’s the FUD About?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Earlier this month, the </span><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/rising-tether-loans-add-risk-to-stablecoin-crypto-world-11669875590" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Wall Street Journal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> called out Tether for its “secured loans” – whereby Tether lends out its own stablecoin tokens rather than selling them upfront for hard currency. According to the company’s </span><a href="https://tether.to/en/transparency/#reports" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, these loans comprised $6.1 billion, or 9%, of its reserves as of September 30th. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Tether claims these loans are overcollateralized by “extremely liquid” assets, it gives few details about the exact nature of that collateral, and who its borrowers are. WSJ used this angle to suggest that these loans create risks for the company to continue satisfying stablecoin redemptions. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Tether can’t be certain the loans will be paid back, that it could sell the loans to a buyer for dollars in a pinch or that the collateral it holds will be adequate,” wrote the company. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tether’s generalized </span><a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-addresses-fud-around-secured-loans-reveals-plans-to-reduce-these-to-zero-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">response</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, written on Tuesday, dismissed criticisms of its secured loans as more “disinformation” concocted by “Tether truthers” and the mainstream media (MSM). Nevertheless, in a commitment to restoring faith in crypto following the collapse of FTX, it has decided to entirely sell them off in 2023. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Tether is professionally and conservatively managed and this will be demonstrated once again by successfully winding down the lending business without losses (since all loans are over-collateralized by liquid assets),” wrote Tether. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The company reviewed a series of other ways in which the MSM has been “wrong” about Tether, including suspicions that its held 70% of its reserves with </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-evergrande-debt-crisis-in-china-and-what-it-could-mean-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Evergrande</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, and that the commercial paper held in its reserves was unreliable. In October, Tether </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stablecoin-issuer-tether-now-holds-zero-commercial-paper/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">confirmed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that its commercial paper holdings had been entirely sold off.</span></p>
<h2>Skepticism Running Rampant</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">With the downfall of multiple major industry players like Celsius, FTX, and Alameda, members of the crypto community are turning against one another with theories about who will go down next. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Panic swelled on Twitter on Tuesday as Binance struggled to process billions of dollars worth off withdrawals – particularly those denominated in USDC. Its CEO, Chanpeng Zhao (CZ), has </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1602579499903852544" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">assured</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> any withdrawal delays are simply due to the need to swap BUSD into USDC, which has now </span><a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1602708590271385600" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">been done</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Speaking of USDC: The popular Bitcoiner and economic journalist Max Keiser theorized last week that Circle will be the next big player to fall. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Circle pays people to use [USDC] &amp; as such they are on the verge of bankruptcy, whereas with Tether, they don&#8217;t pay anyone to use [USDT],” he </span><a href="https://twitter.com/NerdNationUnbox/status/1601385418494443520" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Friday. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CZ has even shown skepticism of Coinbase in recent weeks over how much Bitcoin it claims to hold on behalf of Grayscale. However, the CEO quickly </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-assures-fully-backed-bitcoin-reserves-cz-deletes-doubtful-tweet/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">retracted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> doubtful claims after having a look at Coinbase’s audited financials. </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-responds-to-fud-promises-zero-secured-loans-in-2023/" rel="nofollow">Tether Responds to FUD, Promises Zero Secured Loans in 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>There&#8217;s at Least one More Major Market Capitulation: Datadash Explains</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/theres-at-least-one-more-major-market-capitulation-datadash-explains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 20:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228500</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/crash_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/crash_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Nicholas Merten believes Genesis or another crypto entity that "we least expect" could collapse like FTX, causing further troubles for the industry.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Popular Youtuber Nicholas Merten (DataDash) argued that investors have not rushed to &#8220;buy the dip&#8221; on worries of the inflation numbers, which clocked in lower than the expectations earlier today.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Based on his research, the number of people buying and selling BTC has been dropping each week recently, which indicates that its price will likely continue to fall. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">More Pain Coming</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In his most recent <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CR3Ym_PdHTQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">video</a>, Merten claimed that the traditional bear market for bitcoin is yet to begin. He envisioned that the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX collapse</a> will not be the last adverse event in the industry as Genesis or a platform that nobody expects could suffer the same fate:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We&#8217;ve still got one or two major dominoes out there yet to fall. Is it going to be Genesis, is it going to be the entirety of the digital currency group, is it going to be a major exchange that we least expect? There&#8217;s a lot still rotting under the table. The capitulation, the contagion more specifically, is still real.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The additional turbulence that an event of this kind could trigger might push bitcoin&#8217;s price further down. The asset has already lost over 62% since the beginning of the year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The FOMC meeting, which will be held later this week, is another event that investors are waiting for. Most consumers expect the Federal Reserve will raise interest rates by 50 bps. However, Merten argued that the financial institution might change its intention once seeing the results of the CPI report.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Why are people not buying the dip? The reason, in my opinion, is what&#8217;s coming up here next week, and it has to do with the upcoming inflation numbers from the CPI report as well as the Fed at the FOMC meeting,&#8221; Merten said.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Inflation and Bitcoin</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contrary to the assumptions of some that the leading cryptocurrency could serve as a hedge against inflation and its price should go up in that environment, this has not been the case so far.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The COVID-19 pandemic and the measures that reduced the impact of the health disaster, including the mass printing of fiat currency, have taken their toll, and most countries have experienced a significant inflationary crisis during 2022. The rise in electricity costs, as well as the military conflict between Russia and Ukraine, have also added to the issue.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The inflation rate in the USA <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-inflation-clocks-in-at-9-1-for-june/" data-wpel-link="internal">surpassed</a> 9% in June, a record high for the past 41 years. Bitcoin tumbled.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">During the following months, though, inflation slowed down its temps, and BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-towards-24k-as-us-inflation-slows-down-to-8-5/" data-wpel-link="internal">reacted</a> positively to the news each time.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/theres-at-least-one-more-major-market-capitulation-datadash-explains/" rel="nofollow">There&#8217;s at Least one More Major Market Capitulation: Datadash Explains</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin and Ether in for Quiet Holidays According to Glassnode</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-and-ether-in-for-quiet-holidays-according-to-glassnode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228488</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_holiday_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_holiday_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin and crypto markets could be in for a quiet time over the holiday period following a highly tumultuous year. However, long-term supply hodled has reached a new high.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto and Bitcoin markets are heading for a lull period if the on-chain activity is anything to go by. In its last weekly on-chain report for the year, analytics provider Glassnode reported that Bitcoin annualized realized volatility has been the lowest since October 2020.</p>
<p>The metric matches similar low volatility levels at the previous <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-on-chain-indicators-suggest-bitcoins-bottom-draws-near/" data-wpel-link="internal">cycle bottom</a> in late 2018.</p>
<ul>
<li>Futures volumes are also severely depressed at multi-year lows, it <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1602317354582642692" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stated</a>, adding:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“This shows the massive impact of tightening liquidity, widespread deleveraging, and the impairment of many lending and trading desks in the space.”</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The FTX implosion has doused the fires of futures markets, and open interest (OI) has slumped as a result. OI is a measure of the number of futures or options contracts that are held by traders and investors in active or open positions.</li>
<li>Leverage ratios have also fallen, which is generally a good thing for crypto markets as most of the leveraged positions have been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-capital-reset-underway-following-final-flushout-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal">flushed out</a>. What remains are hodlers and investors, not speculators and margin traders.</li>
<li>Since the record realized profit at the peak of the 2021 bull market, there have been $213 billion in realized losses. This equates to 46.8% of the bull profits, a very similar figure to the 2018 bear market, which saw 47.9% in returned realized losses.</li>
<li>However, the long-term holder supply has reached an all-time high of 13.9 million BTC.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“Despite these spectacularly large losses, the age of the coin supply, and propensity for HODLing by those who remain continues to rise.”</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Glassnode concluded with what we already know: 2022 was a brutal year. It has driven volatility and volumes to multi-year lows as liquidity and speculation dries up, it added.</li>
<li>However, “investors appear to be stepping in with increasing coin volume on each price leg down,” it stated.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-and-ether-in-for-quiet-holidays-according-to-glassnode/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin and Ether in for Quiet Holidays According to Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>13 Years Since Satoshi Nakamoto Was Last Active on Bitcointalk</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/13-years-since-satoshi-nakamoto-was-last-active-on-bitcointalk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228535</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/satoshi-era_btc_tx_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/satoshi-era_btc_tx_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It has been 13 years since Satoshi Nakamoto logged into the forum bitcointalk.org one last time, and left the Bitcoin community for good.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Satoshi Nakamoto was last active on the popular and veteran bitcointalk forum on this date 13 years ago.</p>
<p>Nakamoto did not want to be a &#8220;mysterious shadowy figure.&#8221; Instead, the creator of the world&#8217;s largest crypto-asset wanted to focus on the open-source project and give more credit to the dev contributors.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228608" style="width: 900px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228608 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19.jpg" alt="photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19" width="900" height="359" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19.jpg 900w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19-300x120.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19-768x306.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/photo_2022-12-13_10-06-19-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228608" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Bitcointalk</figcaption></figure>
<h2>&#8220;More Work To Do&#8221;</h2>
<p>Over a decade later, the identity of Satoshi Nakamoto continues to be an unsolved mystery. The Bitcoin creator contributed significantly from 2008 to 2010. In a final message to the community, Nakamoto added to the thread on bitcointalk.org <a href="https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=2228.msg29479#msg29479" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">called</a>: &#8220;Added some DoS limits, removed safe mode.&#8221; In the last message, they emphasized that &#8220;there’s more work to do.&#8221;</p>
<p>Leading up to the fact, Nakamoto was quite active on the forum. This was the time when Bitcoin was trading at $0.20, and the network was &#8220;not at all resistant to DoS attack.&#8221; A few days before that, Nakamoto also expressed annoyance over Wikileaks leveraging bitcoin donations when the network was still very small. The move followed the US finance blockade faced by Wikileaks as payment companies such as Paypal, Mastercard, and Visa stopped servicing the nonprofit whistleblowers.</p>
<p>The 2008 financial meltdown triggered bank bailouts and a cycle of austerity. This subsequently weakened the public’s trust in governments and institutions, and Bitcoin emerged as a response to this global crisis of legitimacy.</p>
<h2>What&#8217;s Changed?</h2>
<p>A lot has changed in Bitcoin&#8217;s existence. Since the very early days, Satoshi Nakamoto predicted that layers being built on top of the Bitcoin blockchain would enable it to expand its narrative beyond &#8220;sound money.&#8221; Programmability is touted to be one of the many factors that would potentially transform Bitcoin into the optimal framework to build out Web3 capabilities.</p>
<p>The ambitious Taproot upgrade implemented last November essentially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-taproot-upgrade-is-finally-here-went-live-successfully/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">paved</a> the way for accelerating decentralized financial services through the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>2022 has been a rather chaotic, volatile, and financially brutal year marked by numerous bankruptcies, the unfortunate collapse of the multi-billion dollar Terra ecosystem, and the catastrophic bankruptcy of FTX. But Bitcoin remained resilient. Moreover, the adoption of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies has grown more than 800% in the past year.</p>
<p>Not to forget, Bitcoin has been adopted to function as a legal currency in El Salvador and the Central African Republic (CAR). Speculations abound that many other countries are likely to follow suit.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/13-years-since-satoshi-nakamoto-was-last-active-on-bitcointalk/" rel="nofollow">13 Years Since Satoshi Nakamoto Was Last Active on Bitcointalk</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business as Usual Says CZ, Confirming Over $1 Billion Daily Withdrawals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/business-as-usual-says-cz-confirming-over-1-billion-daily-withdrawals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228584</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance users have withdrawn around $1.14 worth of crypto from the platform today (December 13), CEO Zhao confirmed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Changpeng Zhao &#8211; CEO of Binance &#8211; said clients had withdrawn approximately $1.14 billion worth of crypto today (December 13) from the platform.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The executive assured they handled the demand and that business continues to operate &#8220;as usual.&#8221;</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Zhao stated on Twitter that the recent withdrawal requests are not a black swan event, reminding that Binance has processed such an amount of transactions before, as also seen on the following chart by Nansen.</span></li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_228618" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228618" style="width: 450px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228618" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201.jpg" alt="token_withdrawals_binance_131201" width="450" height="440" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201.jpg 900w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201-300x293.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201-768x750.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/token_withdrawals_binance_131201-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228618" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Nansen</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li>The CEO maintained his trading venue was not negatively affected and even believes it would be a &#8220;good idea&#8221; if each centralized exchange carried out &#8220;stress test withdrawals&#8221; from time to time.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We saw some withdrawals today (net $1.14b ish). We have seen this before. Some days we have net withdrawals; some days we have net deposits. Business as usual for us.</p>
<p>I actually think it is a good idea to “stress test withdrawals” on each CEX on a rotating basis. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4aa.png" alt="💪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>1/2 <a href="https://t.co/uF9lLPDSyS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/uF9lLPDSyS</a></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1602676998094069760?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 13, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Such experiments could cost some network fees, but they can keep the industry &#8220;healthy,&#8221; he suggested.</li>
<li>For its part, Tether &#8211; the company that issues the stablecoin USDT &#8211; <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1602654597805445123" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to assist Binance by performing a multi-billion chain swap from the Tron network to the Ethereum network:</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;In a few minutes Tether will coordinate with Binance to perform a chain swap, converting from Tron to Ethereum ERC20, for 3B USDT. The Tether total supply will not change during this process.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/business-as-usual-says-cz-confirming-over-1-billion-daily-withdrawals/" rel="nofollow">Business as Usual Says CZ, Confirming Over $1 Billion Daily Withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Poloniex adds cross-margin mode for spot trading</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/poloniex-adds-cross-margin-mode-for-spot-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228595</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/poloniex-pr3.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/poloniex-pr3.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PR &#8211; Panama City, Panama City, 12th December, 2022, Chainwire] Poloniex, a global crypto exchange, is thrilled to announce the launch of its cross margin mode for spot trading to further enhance users’ trading experience in an ever changing market. With up to 3x leverage, Poloniex’s cross-margin mode enhances users’ capital and financing flexibility. It [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PR &#8211; Panama City, Panama City, 12th December, 2022, Chainwire]</strong></p>
<p>Poloniex, a global crypto exchange, is thrilled to announce the launch of its cross margin mode for spot trading to further enhance users’ trading experience in an ever changing market.</p>
<p>With up to 3x leverage, Poloniex’s cross-margin mode enhances users’ capital and financing flexibility. It features a unified spot and cross-margin account so that users don’t need to transfer assets to a different margin account. This makes the operation more convenient.</p>
<p>Poloniex’s cross-margin mode also comes with auto-borrow and repay functions. After the user enables &#8220;auto-borrow&#8221; on the trade page, they can initiate a loan when trading, transferring, or withdrawing tokens. The user&#8217;s maximum borrowable amount will be determined according to the overall margin level of the user&#8217;s spot account.</p>
<p>As for the “repay” capability, every time a user trades, transfers or deposits a token, the asset will be used to automatically repay the loan while avoiding additional interest burdens on the user.</p>
<p>With a convenient user interface and low-interest rates, Poloniex is enhancing the users’ overall trading experience with the possibility of increased gains. For example, users can search and switch to different trading pairs with a clearer and more optimized interface on top of a new onboarding user guide and asset information. Currently, Poloniex supports USDT, BTC, ETH, and TRX as margin assets, and will support more in the future.</p>
<p>To celebrate the debut of its cross-margin mode, Poloniex is running a campaign to reward its users. Additionally, more exciting products are also in the pipeline for 2023.</p>
<p>For more information, please visit <a href="https://support.poloniex.com/hc/en-us/articles/10750566481047" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://support.poloniex.com/hc/en-us/articles/10750566481047</a></p>
<h2>About Poloniex</h2>
<p>Founded in January 2014, Poloniex is a global cryptocurrency exchange that supports spot and futures trading. With a world-class trading platform, Poloniex received funding from H.E. Justin Sun, Founder of TRON, in 2019 to widen its international customer base. Poloniex now provides services in over 100 countries and regions, in various languages. In 2022, Poloniex launched its new trading system with higher speed, stability, and usability. Joining hands with TRON, which is the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica with TRX granted statutory status as legal tender in the country, Poloniex will continue on its mission to connect users to the power of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/poloniex-adds-cross-margin-mode-for-spot-trading/" rel="nofollow">Poloniex adds cross-margin mode for spot trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
