<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 21:02:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chinese Official Sentenced to Life Imprisonment for Bitcoin Mining Operation and Corruption Charges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-official-sentenced-to-life-imprisonment-for-bitcoin-mining-operation-and-corruption-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268205</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/ChinaBitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/ChinaBitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The official secretly assisted a massive Bitcoin mining operation in Fuzhou, which once consumed 10% of the city’s power.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A former Chinese government official, Xiao Yi, has been sentenced to life in prison for helping subsidize a secret, large-scale Bitcoin mining operation within the country’s borders, alongside unrelated acts of corruption.</p>
<p>Yi pled guilty to the charges, and the government has already seized all of his bribes and profits.</p>
<h2>Illegally Helping A Bitcoin Miner</h2>
<p>On Tuesday, Yi was specifically <a href="https://www.workercn.cn/c/2023-08-22/7954854.shtml" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">convicted</a> of abusing his power by providing financial and electricity subsidies to Jiumu Group Genesis Technology, a company based in Fuzhou. This firm was responsible for operating over 160,000 Bitcoin mining machines at one point and accounted for 10% of the city’s electricity consumption between 2017 and 2020.</p>
<p>Prosecutors contend that Xiao Yi attempted to conceal the illicit mining operation by orchestrating the creation of fabricated statistical reports and manipulating electricity consumption data.</p>
<p>In an attempt to mitigate the charges, Xiao Yi admitted guilt, expressed remorse, returned the stolen funds, and saw the seizure of both the bribes and his gains, as stated by the ruling magistrate of the Hangzhou People’s Court.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the additional corruption allegations pertain to bribery activities spanning from from 2008 to 2021. The politician allegedly abused his multiple positions, including director of the Beijing Office of the Jiangxi Provincial People&#8217;s Government, secretary of the Fuzhou Municipal Party Committee of Jiangxi Province, and vice chairman of the Jiangxi Provincial Political Consultative Conference.</p>
<p>The politician “illegally received property equivalent to more than 125 million yuan ($17 million), of which more than 57.82 million yuan ($7.9 million) has not been actually obtained,” according to a translated local report on the ruling. “The circumstances are particularly serious, and the impact is particularly serious.”</p>
<h2>China&#8217;s Crypto Crackdown</h2>
<p>China currently enforces a blanket ban on all crypto-related activities beyond simple ownership. That includes crypto mining, exchange services, fiat-to-crypto onboarding, and transactions.</p>
<p>Effectively enforcing such bans is proving a challenge, however. Data from the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/china-emerges-as-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub-a-year-after-crackdown-cambridge-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cambridge Bitcoin Mining Map</a> shows that China still accounts for 21% of the global Bitcoin hash rate, making it the largest country for mining aside from the United States.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, China continues vying for more control of the world of digital assets. The state-owned telecom operator recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/maximum-contol-china-plans-to-monitor-all-metaverse-users-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">proposed</a> a “Digital Identity System” to keep track of all local metaverse users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-official-sentenced-to-life-imprisonment-for-bitcoin-mining-operation-and-corruption-charges/" rel="nofollow">Chinese Official Sentenced to Life Imprisonment for Bitcoin Mining Operation and Corruption Charges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thailand Could Shut Down Facebook (Meta) Over Crypto Scam Allegations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/thailand-could-shut-down-facebook-meta-over-crypto-scam-allegations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 22:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thailand]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268042</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Thailand.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Thailand.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The proposal regarding the closure of Facebook (Meta) in Thailand could be introduced by the end of August.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thailand&#8217;s Minister of Digital Economy and Society (DES) said he might propose to the court to close Meta (previously known as Facebook) to aid the investing of financial scams, including such involving cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to him, some fraudsters use the social media platform to sponsor their fraudulent schemes and thus con victims.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">No More Meta for Thais?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Ministry of Digital Economy and Society of Thailand has detected that scammers publish fake ads on popular social platforms, such as Meta, to deceive people into investing and later drain their funds. The lawmakers have also noticed that wrongdoers often use the image of well-known figures to display their schemes as more trustworthy.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As such, Chaiwut Thanakmanusorn &#8211; Minister of DES &#8211; </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stated</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that his team might submit a proposal to close the social media giant at the end of the month. Barring access to Meta could help the authorities investigate who stands behind the scams that lure people to distribute money in gold stocks, high-yield lending companies, foreign exchange trading, and cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;DES is in the process of compiling evidence from offenders on the Facebook platform to send the court to close Facebook by the end of this month and ask the court to order the closure of the Facebook region within seven days by Facebook&#8217;s offense,&#8221; the politician <a href="https://www.mdes.go.th/news/detail/7229-%E0%B8%94%E0%B8%B5%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%B5%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%AA-%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%94%E0%B8%B7%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%94--%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%95%E0%B8%A3%E0%B8%B5%E0%B8%A2%E0%B8%A1%E0%B8%A3%E0%B9%89%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%87%E0%B8%A8%E0%B8%B2%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%9B%E0%B8%B4%E0%B8%94-Facebook-%E0%B9%83%E0%B8%99%E0%B9%84%E0%B8%97%E0%B8%A2-%E0%B8%AB%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%B1%E0%B8%87%E0%B9%80%E0%B8%A1%E0%B8%B4%E0%B8%99-%E0%B8%9B%E0%B8%A5%E0%B9%88%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%A2%E0%B8%A1%E0%B8%B4%E0%B8%88%E0%B8%89%E0%B8%B2%E0%B8%8A%E0%B8%B5%E0%B8%9E%E0%B8%A2%E0%B8%B4%E0%B8%87-Ad--%E0%B8%AB%E0%B8%A5%E0%B8%AD%E0%B8%81%E0%B8%9B%E0%B8%A3%E0%B8%B0%E0%B8%8A%E0%B8%B2%E0%B8%8A%E0%B8%99" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stated</a>.<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_268068" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-268068" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chaiwut-Thanakmanusorn.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-268068" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chaiwut-Thanakmanusorn.webp" alt="Chaiwut Thanakmanusorn" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chaiwut-Thanakmanusorn.webp 960w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chaiwut-Thanakmanusorn-300x200.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chaiwut-Thanakmanusorn-768x512.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Chaiwut-Thanakmanusorn-50x33.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-268068" class="wp-caption-text">Chaiwut Thanakmanusorn, Source: Thaiger</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thanakmanusorn estimated that such schemes had affected over 200,000 individuals, siphoning almost $300,000 from them.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Ministry has also sent a warning letter to Meta and other similar companies to block over 5,300 fraudulent ads and pages that could harm users.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">How to Prevent Such Fraud?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawmakers gave locals valuable tips on detecting and avoiding online scams. They alerted that investment options offering high returns in a short period or featuring a celebrity&#8217;s face could be seen as a red flag. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, fraudsters often urge people to invest as quickly as possible, telling them they will otherwise miss an excellent opportunity to generate good returns.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We would like to warn people not to be fooled by any solicitation of investment via social media and ask people to verify the facts from the cited agencies or related agencies before publishing and forwarding such information on various social media channels,&#8221; the Ministry concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thailand-could-shut-down-facebook-meta-over-crypto-scam-allegations/" rel="nofollow">Thailand Could Shut Down Facebook (Meta) Over Crypto Scam Allegations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Ventures-Backed CoinDCX Lays Off 12% of its Workforce</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ventures-backed-coindcx-lays-off-12-of-its-workforce/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 20:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268077</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/CoinDCX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/CoinDCX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The exchange is laying off 71 employees due to incessant bear market coupled with India's hostile tax policy. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CoinDCX is the latest crypto company to slash staff as it tries to navigate through market challenges. The Coinbase Ventures-backed Indian crypto unicorn cited the prolonged bear market and the impact of TDS on domestic exchanges to lay off 12% of its workforce, or 71, out of its total 590 employees.</p>
<p>The development comes after the company went through an internal restructuring earlier this year.</p>
<h2>CoinDCX Lay Offs</h2>
<p>Founded by Neeraj Khandelwal and Sumit Gupta in 2018, CoinDCX revealed undertaking several proactive measures, including direct cost optimization and investment in automation, aimed at enhancing efficiency and productivity.</p>
<p>The platform also reprioritized several initiatives/products that align with its long-term business strategy by resizing certain teams and steering the business toward profitable and sustainable growth.</p>
<p>The founders further <a href="https://info.coindcx.com/announcement/a-tough-decision-for-a-brighter-future-coindcx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stated</a> there are specific roles that are not in line with the current business priorities and went on to add,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’ve tried our utmost to explore various alternatives, but current market realities compel us to take some tough decisions. We believe that this is the right thing to do for the business. We understand the emotional toll of this decision, and we bear its weight, both in responsibility and in emotion.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>CoinDCX achieved &#8220;unicorn&#8221; status in August 2021 after securing $90 million in a Series C funding round. The crypto exchange further increased its valuation to over $2 billion by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indian-crypto-exchange-coindcx-raises-135-million-valuation-reaches-2-15-billion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">raising</a> an additional $135 million last April.</p>
<h2>India Crypto Taxation</h2>
<p>India has enforced significant taxes on cryptocurrencies, which encompass a 30% tax on profits generated from digital assets and the more contentious 1% Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) on all transactions starting from February 1, 2022.</p>
<p>The implementation of TDS, coupled with the global downturn in the crypto market, has adversely affected trading volumes and, subsequently, on revenue of many crypto firms in the country, including CoinDCX.</p>
<p>The Indian government <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/low-tds-collection-on-crypto-may-spur-indian-government-to-reduce-transaction-tax/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> collecting only around $7.4 million in TDS on crypto transfers during July-December 2022.  Hence, anticipations were high that the finance ministry would reduce the tax rate to a range of 0.05% to 0.1%, aligning with the industry&#8217;s request. However, the authorities did not grant any such relief.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ventures-backed-coindcx-lays-off-12-of-its-workforce/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Ventures-Backed CoinDCX Lays Off 12% of its Workforce</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Stuck in Bear Trap: 99.5% of AVAX Investors Are Holding Tokens at Loss</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-stuck-in-bear-trap-99-5-of-avax-investors-are-holding-tokens-at-loss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 19:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268133</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Avalanche_Bear_Trap.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Avalanche_Bear_Trap.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[AVAX has lost nearly 50% of its value since the beginning of 2023. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The brutal bear market in crypto has significantly affected the price of AVAX. The latest downturn not just extended its weekly losses beyond 17% but also pushed the crypto asset to a multi-year low of $10.14.</p>
<p>As a result, the number of AVAX holders in profit has reached an all-time low. Nearly 99.5% of the investors who own Avalanche&#8217;s native token are currently at a loss. According to IntoTheBlock&#8217;s latest findings, this isn&#8217;t the first time the asset has witnessed similar levels.</p>
<ul>
<li>Previous lows were recorded in June following the dual implosion of Terra&#8217;s UST and LUNA, followed by December, a month after FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy.</li>
<li>However, ITB <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1693925000909086796" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that it is the first time that nearly all AVAX holders are holding at a loss.</li>
<li>The AVAX ecosystem had several crucial developments this year. This includes Alibaba Cloud &#8211; a subset of Chinese e-commerce conglomerate Alibaba &#8211; joining forces with Avalanche for a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alibaba-cloud-builds-launchpad-to-deploy-metaverse-on-avalanche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launchpad</a> to deploy metaverses on the layer 1 blockchain.</li>
<li>Avalanche, along with other crypto players, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mastercard-teams-up-with-aptos-polygon-avalanche-solana-to-strengthen-web3-foothold/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">teamed up</a> with MasterCard, a collaboration that was aimed at helping the payments giant strengthen its foothold in the Web3 space.</li>
<li>More recently, the Avalanche Foundation <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-launches-50-million-real-world-asset-tokenization-initiative/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> a $50 million initiative &#8211; Avalanche Vista &#8211; to invest in real-world asset (RWA) tokenization.</li>
<li>It was also found that the brief depeg of USDC stablecoin in the first quarter of 2023 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-transactions-mooned-during-usdcs-temporary-de-peg-in-q1-2023-nansen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">triggered</a> a surge in transactions and active users on Avalanche. However, the ecosystem developments had a negligible impact on the price side of things.</li>
<li>In fact, AVAX is currently under significant pressure, and the upcoming token unlock worth approximately $99 million, which is slated to be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avax-crash-incoming-avalanche-to-unlock-over-9-5-million-tokens-this-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">released</a> on August 26th, is further expected to increase the selling pressure.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-stuck-in-bear-trap-99-5-of-avax-investors-are-holding-tokens-at-loss/" rel="nofollow">Avalanche Stuck in Bear Trap: 99.5% of AVAX Investors Are Holding Tokens at Loss</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Traders Brace for &#8216;Choppy Waters&#8217; Following Bitcoin&#8217;s Plunge to $25.3K: Bitfinex Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-traders-brace-for-choppy-waters-following-bitcoins-plunge-to-25-3k-bitfinex-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268038</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin_Price_Swings.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin_Price_Swings.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitfinex said implied volatility outpacing the historical metric indicates that traders foresee wilder price swings ahead.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The latest edition of the Bitfinex Alpha report revealed that cryptocurrency traders are bracing themselves for &#8220;choppy waters&#8221; ahead due to bitcoin&#8217;s sudden plunge after a languid period.</span></p>
<p>On-chain data analyzed by researchers at crypto exchange Bitfinex showed a surge and flatline in implied and historical volatility metrics, suggesting that traders have adjusted their strategies in preparation for impending volatility over the next month at least.</p>
<h2>Choppy Waters Ahead</h2>
<p>Last week, bitcoin&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-crashed-to-25-3-but-these-altcoins-have-it-worse-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">sudden plunge</a> toward the $25,000 mark left markets reeling with over $1 billion in futures liquidations. The asset had enjoyed an almost serene period before the decline as traders sought the next catalyst to trigger a sharp move in the market. This was evident in bitcoin&#8217;s open interest indicator, which recorded a rapid spike in the days leading to the sudden slump.</p>
<p>The downward move was followed by a major open interest wipeout, considered one of the largest in the asset&#8217;s history. Roughly $3 billion in open interest was obliterated within a few hours after the crash. Bitfinex said it was one of the largest reductions in day-to-day open interest since December 2021, when BTC hit its all-time high of $69,000.</p>
<p>While the crypto community is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-flash-crash-to-25-3k-triggers-speculation-spacex-write-down-in-focus/" data-wpel-link="internal">speculating</a> on the specific reason for bitcoin&#8217;s recent crash, on-chain data has shown notable movement in historical and implied volatility metrics, suggesting what should be expected in the next few weeks.</p>
<p>The former uses historical data to reflect the past movement of an asset price, while the latter is a forward-looking measure that shows the market&#8217;s expectations about the future volatility of an asset.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin to See Wilder Price Swings</h2>
<p>The current market scenario shows the implied volatility metric surging to 40%, a rising trend in bitcoin options open interest, and a stable historical volatility indicator. Bitfinex said implied volatility outpacing the historical metric indicates that traders foresee wilder price swings ahead.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Historically, Bitcoin&#8217;s price had been somewhat predictable, but this change in HV pointed to a newfound turbulence. More interestingly, the subsequent plateauing or flatlining of HV suggests a market acceptance of this elevated volatility, hinting that traders have adjusted their strategies to this &#8220;new normal&#8221; of heightened price fluctuations,&#8221; the exchange said.</p></blockquote>
<p>While the anticipation could be attributed to several factors, including macroeconomic shifts and regulatory changes, the underlying message remains clear: there are stormier seas ahead in the crypto market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-traders-brace-for-choppy-waters-following-bitcoins-plunge-to-25-3k-bitfinex-report/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Traders Brace for &#8216;Choppy Waters&#8217; Following Bitcoin&#8217;s Plunge to $25.3K: Bitfinex Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will the Shiba Inu Price Recover After Tanking Over 20%? Wall Street Memes Emerges as Alternative with $26 Million Raised</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-shiba-inu-price-recover-after-tanking-over-20-wall-street-memes-emerges-as-alternative-with-26-million-raised/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 16:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268166</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/wsm_sonik_shib_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/wsm_sonik_shib_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu ($SHIB) has tanked over 20% in the past week as investors grow increasingly bearish on the popular meme coin. Having lost considerable momentum since the high of August 12, $SHIB is struggling to regain bullish traction. However, while $SHIB falters, the new meme coin Wall Street Memes ($WSM) is showcasing strength, providing a [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu ($SHIB) has tanked over 20% in the past week as investors grow increasingly bearish on the popular meme coin.</p>
<p>Having lost considerable momentum since the high of August 12, $SHIB is struggling to regain bullish traction.</p>
<p>However, while $SHIB falters, the new meme coin Wall Street Memes ($WSM) is showcasing strength, providing a viable alternative for those looking to avoid Shiba Inu&#8217;s price swings.</p>
<h2>Technicals Reflect Ongoing Bearish Momentum for $SHIB</h2>
<p>It has been a challenging ten days for $SHIB holders, with the token’s value crashing nearly 30% from its local high.</p>
<p>$SHIB has closed in the red in eight of the last nine trading days, marking its worst run since early March.</p>
<p>More worryingly for investors, $SHIB’s price has easily bypassed the 20-day and 50-day Exponential Moving Averages (EMAs) to the downside – signaling that the short-term and medium-term trends have flipped bearish.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268171" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-1.jpg" alt="" width="451" height="213" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-1.jpg 451w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-1-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-1-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></a></p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index, which measures buying and selling momentum, sits at 40, reflecting weak buying pressure.</p>
<p>Unless $SHIB can reclaim and hold above its moving averages, the technical picture remains decidedly negative.</p>
<p>Moreover, with <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap data</a> showing that $SHIB trading volume rose 8% in the past day, many token holders are opting to liquidate their holdings rather than withstand the storm.</p>
<h2>Community Sentiment Provides Hope for Shiba Inu Rebound</h2>
<p>Given this confluence of bearish catalysts, can Shiba Inu recover soon?</p>
<p>The good news for investors is that $SHIB rejected the support zone around $0.0000072 with a long wick, indicating a high volume of buy orders in the area.</p>
<p>Avi Lev, a prominent crypto analyst with 107,000 YouTube subscribers, uploaded a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yfv68OZ56Pk&amp;ab_channel=MoneyMaker-AviLev" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video detailing his bullish stance on $SHIB</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268170" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-2.jpg" alt="" width="451" height="125" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-2.jpg 451w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-2-300x83.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture-2-50x14.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></a></p>
<p>In this video, Lev highlighted the misinformation surrounding the technical issues associated with Shibarium’s launch, pointing out that he expects $SHIB to rebound in the near term.</p>
<p>This forecast aligns with information from the <a href="https://twitter.com/shibburn/status/1693714647205982213?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shibburn Twitter account</a>, which highlights a 465% increase in the $SHIB burn rate in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>While the market’s outlook on Shiba Inu may still be bearish, these signs of optimism from key figures in the community and the increased burn rate suggest that $SHIB may be able to stage a relief rally after the recent sell-off.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Presale Hits $26 Million Amid Hype for Tier-1 Exchange Launch</h2>
<p>Although Shiba Inu has been struggling lately, numerous other meme coins are withstanding the bearish wave and making impressive progress.</p>
<p>One of the standout performers has been <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=will-the-shiba-inu-price-recover-after-tanking-over-20-wall-street-memes-emerges-as-alternative-with-26-million-raised" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a>, now in the final stage of a highly-successful presale phase.</p>
<p>During this presale, Wall Street Memes has raised a staggering $26 million in funding, inching closer to its hard cap of $30.5 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268169" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2-1.jpg" alt="" width="451" height="222" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2-1.jpg 451w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2-1-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2-1-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></a></p>
<p>Prospective investors have one final chance to purchase $WSM, Wall Street Memes&#8217; native token, ahead of the token&#8217;s exchange debut – scheduled for the end of September.</p>
<p>Although no specific names have been mentioned, Wall Street Memes’ website notes plans to list on “multiple” Tier-1 exchanges, adding to investors’ anticipation.</p>
<p>Additionally, the recent launch of <a href="https://wallstmemes.com/en/dashboard" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes’ staking protocol</a> has boosted engagement, offering a compelling feature that could enhance $WSM’s growth prospects following its open market debut.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268168" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3.jpg" alt="" width="451" height="352" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3.jpg 451w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3-300x234.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3-50x39.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></a></p>
<p>An array of high-profile influencers, including <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oN7PfL90uRc&amp;pp=ygUgd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRvIHNhdG9zaGk%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Satoshi Stacker</a>, who boasts over 282,000 YouTube subscribers, are taking note of $WSM, speculating that it could be the “next meme coin to take off.”</p>
<p>With <a href="https://t.me/wallst_memes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes’ Telegram community</a> growing to nearly 20,000 people and the presale momentum showing no signs of slowing, the enthusiasm around $WSM appears well-founded – positioning it for a strong launch in the coming month.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=will-the-shiba-inu-price-recover-after-tanking-over-20-wall-street-memes-emerges-as-alternative-with-26-million-raised" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Stake-to-Earn Sonik Coin Presale Momentum Ramps Up After $300,000 Raised in 7 Days</h2>
<p>Another meme coin that’s performing admirably while Shiba Inu struggles is <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/box_3bb03a9e65107f306e2760608ad07313?referrer=will-the-shiba-inu-price-recover-after-tanking-over-20-wall-street-memes-emerges-as-alternative-with-26-million-raised" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sonik Coin ($SONIK)</a>.</p>
<p>Sonik Coin has raised over $300,000 in its public presale phase so far, which allows early backers to purchase $SONIK tokens for just $0.000014.</p>
<p>Once the presale’s hard cap of $2 million has been hit, $SONIK will be listed on Uniswap– the world’s largest DEX by daily trading volume.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268167" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4.jpg" alt="" width="451" height="224" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4.jpg 451w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4-300x149.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></a></p>
<p>Beyond viral meme appeal, Sonik Coin sets itself apart from its peers through an innovative staking protocol allowing $SONIK holders to lock up their tokens and earn passive income.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.sonikcoin.com/en/dashboard" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sonik Coin’s staking dashboard</a>, the current yield on offer is 208% per year – with over 11.5 billion $SONIK tokens already staked.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, <a href="https://www.sonikcoin.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sonik Coin’s whitepaper</a> notes plans to continue building the $SONIK community and hit a $100 million market cap.</p>
<p>Although ambitious, these plans look increasingly achievable given the project’s early traction and real-world utility – positioning $SONIK as a token to watch closely in the weeks ahead.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/box_3bb03a9e65107f306e2760608ad07313?referrer=will-the-shiba-inu-price-recover-after-tanking-over-20-wall-street-memes-emerges-as-alternative-with-26-million-raised" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Sonik Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<div class="coincodex-content">
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</p>
</div>
<div class="share"></div>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-shiba-inu-price-recover-after-tanking-over-20-wall-street-memes-emerges-as-alternative-with-26-million-raised/" rel="nofollow">Will the Shiba Inu Price Recover After Tanking Over 20%? Wall Street Memes Emerges as Alternative with $26 Million Raised</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Are Whales Buying Millions Worth of XRP and SHIB?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-are-whales-buying-millions-worth-of-xrp-and-shib/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 15:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268159</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_shiba_whale_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_shiba_whale_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Massive transactions of XRP and SHIB have taken place throughout the past couple of days. Does someone know something we don't?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">XRP and SHIB whales are inducing ripples in the crypto market, with massive new token purchases igniting speculations of potential price actions in these assets.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data from Whale Alerts reveals a string of significant transactions involving trillions of SHIB moving between wallets. On Aug. 21, an investor and holder of wallet 0xc684d6c5 </span><a href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/ethereum/0x7e242ccda70eea3b10cd755cc089123cf74c3478523fbee8f568cf6afb6c6bec" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">purchased</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> 4,653,778,173,637 SHIB worth $36,797,424 from a Bitvavo sender. Later, wallet 0xc684d6c5 sent about 4,639,778,173,637 SHIB valued at $36,696,005 to 0x3442cc07. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the latest transaction, wallet 0x3442cc07 </span><a href="https://whale-alert.io/transaction/ethereum/0x3196d9b09a42c9f3db74312bb74b5436446a5e1c988a67527634c76d6fc6e66a" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">transferred</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> 4,627,778,173,637 SHIB to another wallet 0xa9d152f9 today. This final amount of transferred SHIB is worth $36,601,097 at the current market price. While the wallets seem to have some connection, the identity of the investor/s remains a mystery.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data analysis suggests that XRP whales follow a similar pattern with significant transactions. For instance, about 221 wallets have recently </span><a href="https://app.santiment.net/charts?settings=%7B%22slug%22%3A%22xrp%22%2C%22ticker%22%3A%22XRP%22%2C%22from%22%3A%222023-02-21T07%3A59%3A59.071Z%22%2C%22to%22%3A%222023-08-21T06%3A59%3A59.071Z%22%7D&amp;widgets=%5B%7B%22widget%22%3A%22HolderDistributionCombinedBalanceWidget%22%2C%22wm%22%3A%5B%22holders_distribution_combined_balance_10M_to_100M%22%2C%22holders_distribution_combined_balance_100M_to_1B%22%2C%22price_usd%22%5D%2C%22whm%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wax%22%3A%5B0%2C1%2C2%5D%2C%22wpax%22%3A%5B%5D%2C%22wc%22%3A%5B%22%2368DBF4%22%2C%22%23FFCB47%22%2C%22%230a481b%22%5D%2C%22ws%22%3A%7B%222%22%3A%7B%22node%22%3A%22bar%22%7D%7D%7D%5D" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">accumulated 16 billion XRP</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Additionally, there has been a rapid surge in wallets holding more than 100 million XRP.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Investors Gearing Up for Possible Price Movements</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Analysts believe that the recent price actions could be in anticipation of robust positive price movements in the coming days. SEC’s possible shift of stance in a lawsuit against Ripple could drive the token to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-xrp-looking-to-breach-0-60-as-sec-stance-in-lawsuit-questionable/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">over $0.6</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in the coming days.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The case is the same for SHIB. With analysis suggesting the SHIB is now at its </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-shib-price-hasnt-done-this-in-9-months/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">local bottom</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, the possibility of gains for the currency has increased. An analyst </span><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1691431293341384704" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Michael van de Poppe</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, recently predicted that SHIB could hit $0.000013 in the coming weeks.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-are-whales-buying-millions-worth-of-xrp-and-shib/" rel="nofollow">Why Are Whales Buying Millions Worth of XRP and SHIB?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>John Deaton Says SEC Lawsuit Affected XRP Adoption</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/john-deaton-says-sec-lawsuit-affected-xrp-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268087</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ripple_sec_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ripple_sec_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[John Deaton has wondered if Coinbase may have invested in Ripple if the SEC never filed its lawsuit against the company.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Despite Ripple scoring a win in the ongoing lawsuit with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), some members of the community believe the legal battle caused damages for the firm and its native token.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to lawyer and founder of CryptoLaw, John Deaton, who also represents thousands of XRP holders, the SEC lawsuit affected potential mass adoption of XRP in the last three years.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Counting the Losses</h2>
<p dir="ltr">John Deaton took to X (formerly Twitter) on August 22 to detail the level of adoption XRP enjoyed before the SEC lawsuit, stating that the token may have seen greater adoption if the regulator never filed charges.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Deaton mentioned that outside of the blockchain company Ripple, major crypto exchange Coinbase and money transfer giant MoneyGram were one of the biggest adopters that utilized XRP for cross-border payments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The lengthy X thread particularly focused on Coinbase&#8217;s promotion of XRP and the regulatory steps carried out by the exchange before listing Ripple&#8217;s native token on its platform.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the lawyer, Coinbase met with the SEC in 2019, informing the regulator that XRP was not a security after conducting a stringent assessment. The exchange sought the SEC to determine if the latter had any opposition to its assessment and also to prevent running afoul of securities laws.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, as stated by Deaton, the American securities regulator neither refuted Coinbase&#8217;s evaluation of XRP nor discouraged the exchange, leading the company to list the token on its platform. Deaton also argued that tens of thousands of US residents bought XRP following Coinbase&#8217;s promotion of the asset.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Things, however, took a different turn in December 2020 when the SEC sued Ripple for selling unregistered securities worth $1.3 billion. Consequently, companies like Coinbase, who formerly touted XRP, delisted the token from its platform, with several other exchanges following suit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">MoneyGram, which previously struck a partnership deal with Ripple in 2019 to use XRP for cross-border payments, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-and-moneygram-part-ways-amid-sec-litigation-while-xrp-eyes-0-50/" data-wpel-link="internal">ended</a> the partnership agreement with the blockchain company a few months after the SEC lawsuit, with Ripple stating that it was a joint decision.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Would Coinbase Have Invested in Ripple?</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Ripple won against the SEC according to a recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/history-in-the-making-with-ripple-scoring-massive-win-in-court-in-xrp-security-case-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruling</a> that declared XRP as not a security, Deaton believes the lawsuit harmed XRP&#8217;s adoption and possibly affected potential major developments in the last three years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Reacting to the latest news about Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-purchases-equity-in-circle-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">purchasing a stake</a> in stablecoin issuer Circle, the XRP holders&#8217; lawyer asked whether the crypto exchange may have invested in Ripple instead if the lawsuit never happened.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We know the rest. It is so clear the lawsuit was used as a weapon. I said it only 9 days after the Ripple lawsuit in a federal pleading, when I filed the Writ of Mandamus against the SEC, and all the evidence uncovered during the last 3 years proves it to be true.</p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1693798236379550049?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 22, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Although Coinbase relisted XRP after the historic ruling, MoneyGram did not renew its partnership with Ripple. Instead, the international payments company formed a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stellar-lumens-xlm-spikes-12-after-news-of-a-partnership-between-moneygram-and-the-stellar-foundation/" data-wpel-link="internal">new relationship</a> with Ripple&#8217;s rival Stellar Development Foundation (SDF) in October 2021 to enable transfers with the USDC stablecoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In August 2023, SDF bought a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-rival-stellar-xlm-becomes-minority-investor-in-moneygram/" data-wpel-link="internal">minority stake</a> in MoneyGram.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/john-deaton-says-sec-lawsuit-affected-xrp-adoption/" rel="nofollow">John Deaton Says SEC Lawsuit Affected XRP Adoption</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>World Mobile Taps SingularityNET to Introduce Blockchain-Based Loans</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/world-mobile-partners-with-singularitynet-to-introduce-blockchain-based-loans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267752</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/World_Mobile.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/World_Mobile.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The mobile network operator will roll out the blockchain-based lending solution in three phases.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The UK-based mobile network operator &#8211; World Mobile &#8211; teamed up with the decentralized artificial intelligence (AI) marketplace &#8211; SingularityNET &#8211; to develop credit ratings for a lending program that utilizes blockchain technology.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The partnership will also enable World Mobile to scale its network and expand to new regions.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Combining AI and Blockchain Technology</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a document seen by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the collaboration with SingularityNET will upgrade World Mobile&#8217;s customer service as it will use AI technology to answer clients&#8217; generic questions. The mobile network operator will also integrate the technology to establish a blockchain-based lending solution.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It will introduce the option in phases, with the first involving provisioning credit to observe who will be eligible to use the offering. Second, the entity will check whether it can provide additional loans to loyal customers. Finally, the program will reach global users served by traditional financial institutions. Speaking on the matter was World Mobile&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Micky Watkins:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are proud to partner with SingularityNet on the integration of AI technology for customer support and introducing blockchain-based data loans. This strategic partnership reflects our shared commitment of delivering cutting-edge innovations to solve real world problems. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">With AI-driven assistance, decentralized identifiers, and secure blockchain transactions, we are empowering users with seamless experiences and unlocking new possibilities in the mobile industry.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Janet Adams &#8211; COO of SingulrityNET &#8211; described this partnership as a &#8220;key component&#8221; of his company&#8217;s journey since it will allow it to get &#8220;vital funds to those the traditional financial system has previously excluded.&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We look forward to collaborating more closely with World Mobile to pioneer a fairer, decentralized future,&#8221; the exec added.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">World Mobile&#8217;s Previous Efforts</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-based-network-world-mobile-introduces-a-buyback-program/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">launched</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a token buyback program in June to advance the growth of its sharing economy. Specifically, World Mobile&#8217;s treasury was set to purchase its native coin WMT from the open market and distribute rewards to some of its users. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;By repurchasing World Mobile Tokens (WMT) from the open market, we aim to build a sustainable sharing economy for all our participants.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">We believe that by executing on our business model and initiating buybacks from real-world revenue is a large step towards mass adoption and strengthens the overall stability and utility of the World Mobile ecosystem,&#8221; CEO Watkins said at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">World Mobile also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/conflux-and-world-mobile-join-forces-to-expand-blockchain-based-mobile-access/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">teamed up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with Conflux Network (a blockchain platform developed in China) last month to expand its network access.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/world-mobile-partners-with-singularitynet-to-introduce-blockchain-based-loans/" rel="nofollow">World Mobile Taps SingularityNET to Introduce Blockchain-Based Loans</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Continues to Slide &#038; Threatens to Drop Below $0.50 – Could LPX Token Be an Alternative?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-continues-to-slide-threatens-to-drop-below-0-50-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=268112</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/LaunchpadXYZ_XRP.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/LaunchpadXYZ_XRP.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[XRP ($XRP) continues to face instability, sliding dangerously close to the $0.50 mark and eliciting concern among investors. Confidence in $XRP is waning, meaning many are opting to seek out stable alternatives with clearer price prospects. Among the emerging options, Launchpad XYZ ($LPX), a groundbreaking Web3 platform, is drawing attention as a promising and innovative [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP ($XRP) continues to face instability, sliding dangerously close to the $0.50 mark and eliciting concern among investors.</p>
<p>Confidence in $XRP is waning, meaning many are opting to seek out stable alternatives with clearer price prospects.</p>
<p>Among the emerging options, Launchpad XYZ ($LPX), a groundbreaking Web3 platform, is drawing attention as a promising and innovative solution, which some believe could outshine $XRP in the coming months.</p>
<h2>Uncertainty &amp; Technical Hurdles Threaten Further $XRP Decline</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, the $XRP price is hovering around $0.517, a 44% drop from July’s peak.</p>
<p>A colossal sell-off has occurred since Ripple Labs&#8217; lawsuit victory, with many $XRP holders opting to cash in while the token&#8217;s value was high rather than wait for a sustained bull run.</p>
<p>This sell-off has led to a significant shift in $XRP&#8217;s dynamics, creating uncertainty and volatility challenging both speculators and long-term holders.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/111111.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268118" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/111111.jpg" alt="" width="512" height="243" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/111111.jpg 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/111111-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/111111-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>Things don&#8217;t appear to be improving from a technical perspective, with $XRP&#8217;s price now trading sideways after Thursday&#8217;s crash.</p>
<p>Some in the crypto community believe this range-bound trading could precipitate another drop, fueling concerns over $XRP’s resilience.</p>
<p>Moreover, with the <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> at its lowest level since the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank in March, the negative market sentiment is further compounding $XRP’s precarious position.</p>
<h2>SEC Appeal &amp; Hawkish Fed Weigh on $XRP Price</h2>
<p>The recent decline in $XRP’s value can be attributed to the ongoing legal turmoil surrounding Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>As reported last week, Judge Analisa Torres granted a request from the SEC to file a motion for an interlocutory appeal against Ripple Labs – despite the latter’s opposition.</p>
<p>This decision has led to renewed uncertainty in the market, contributing to $XRP’s sell-off.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/22222.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268119" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/22222.jpg" alt="" width="512" height="243" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/22222.jpg 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/22222-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/22222-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>The possibility of a protracted legal process has affected investor confidence, much like it did in the years before Ripple Labs&#8217; recent court victory.</p>
<p>$XRP’s woes were compounded further when the minutes from the US Federal Reserve’s most recent FOMC meeting were released last week.</p>
<p>These minutes highlighted the Fed&#8217;s overall hawkish stance, hinting at another interest rate hike before the end of 2023.</p>
<p>This announcement has led to broader market apprehension, as higher interest rates often dampen investor enthusiasm for riskier asset classes like cryptocurrency – thereby putting additional pressure on $XRP.</p>
<h2>Could Launchpad XYZ be an Alternative? Web3 Investment Portal Raises $1.3M During Presale</h2>
<p>In contrast to the uncertainty surrounding $XRP, <a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=xrp-price-continues-to-slide-threatens-to-drop-below-0-50-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ ($LPX)</a> presents a fresh opportunity in the crypto space, potentially offering an alternative for investors.</p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ is a community-driven Web3 ecosystem that aims to help digital asset investors make more informed market decisions.</p>
<p>The ecosystem contains various innovative features, including AI-powered trading insights, a lightning-quick trading terminal, and an NFT DEX, establishing it as a valuable tool for Web3 enthusiasts.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3333.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268121" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3333.png" alt="" width="512" height="292" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3333.png 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3333-300x171.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/3333-50x29.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>As noted in <a href="https://launchpad.xyz/assets/documents/LaunchpadXYZ_Whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ’s whitepaper</a>, the developers are on a mission to simplify the complex world of digital asset investing, making it more accessible for newcomers and veterans alike.</p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ is in its presale phase, where investors can purchase $LPX, the project&#8217;s native token, for a favorable price of $0.0445.</p>
<p>Over $1.3 million has been raised through the presale – although with a token price increase slated for once $1.55 million has been raised, investors must act swiftly if they wish to take advantage of the lower price.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4444.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-268122" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4444.png" alt="" width="512" height="250" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4444.png 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4444-300x146.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/4444-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>Adding to the growing buzz around Launchpad XYZ is that an engaged community has begun forming, evidenced by over 7,900 people following the <a href="https://twitter.com/launchpadlpx" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">project’s official Twitter page</a>.</p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ has even caused a commotion in the influencer community, with popular YouTuber Crypto Pablo <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yzp_7YWQBhU&amp;pp=ygUNbGF1bmNocGFkIHh5eg%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">praising</a> the project in a recent video.</p>
<p>With these endorsements and the innovative solutions it offers, Launchpad XYZ looks poised to become a significant player in the Web3 space.</p>
<p><a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=xrp-price-continues-to-slide-threatens-to-drop-below-0-50-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-continues-to-slide-threatens-to-drop-below-0-50-could-lpx-token-be-an-alternative/" rel="nofollow">XRP Price Continues to Slide &#038; Threatens to Drop Below $0.50 – Could LPX Token Be an Alternative?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
