<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 18:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stellar Becomes Newest Member of CFTC&#8217;s Committee</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stellar-becomes-newest-member-of-cftcs-committee/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 01:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234301</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cftc.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cftc.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SDF is the only organization representing a blockchain on the committee. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The non-profit organization &#8211; Stellar Development Foundation &#8211; announced joining a new advisory committee of the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).</p>
<p>According to the firm&#8217;s <a href="https://stellar.org/blog/representing-blockchain-on-the-commodity-futures-trading-commissions-global-market-advisory-committee" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a>, SDF will be one of the four crypto-focused organizations at the Global Markets Advisory Committee (GMAC), which is one of the five active Advisory Committees overseen by the CFTC. The firm behind the Stellar blockchain will join representatives from traditional finance players, including the likes of J.P. Morgan, Goldman Sachs, and BlackRock.</p>
<h2>SDF&#8217;s Role in GMAC</h2>
<p>Since SDF represents the blockchain industry on the GMAC, the foundation expects to bring the focus on Layer 1 protocols and remittances. The organization also plans on highlighting the role of stablecoins in the digital asset markets and real-world use cases as part of the committee.</p>
<p>In the statement, SDF stated that it is excited to join the many traditional finance players on CFTC&#8217;s new committee. It also believes GMAC will serve as an opportunity for conventional finance and blockchain to find prospects for integration to ensure the integrity and competitiveness of US markets.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;After an active 2022, SDF&#8217;s engagement with government agencies is more critical than ever. Our inclusion in the CFTC&#8217;s GMAC is yet another opportunity to push the industry toward mainstream adoption. I look forward to the work ahead of us under Commissioner Pham&#8217;s leadership and the chance to represent blockchain technology and our industry.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to SDF, officials from the Chamber of Digital Commerce, Uniswap Labs, and CoinFund are some of the members.</p>
<h2>GMAC&#8217;s Functions</h2>
<p>The GMAC is tasked with guiding the CFTC on issues related to &#8220;the integrity and competitiveness&#8221; of US markets as well as the domestic firms engaged in global business. Regulatory challenges of global marketplaces are also some of the aspects of global marketplaces that the committee is required to make recommendations to the watchdog agency.</p>
<p>Setting international standards for regulating futures, swaps, options, and derivatives markets, as well as intermediaries, also fall under GMAC&#8217;s purview. Its members include financial market infrastructures, market participants, end-users, service providers, and regulators.</p>
<p>CFTC commissioner Caroline Pham is the new sponsor of the GMAC. It was recently <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8648-23" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that the first meeting under her sponsorship will be devoted to organizational issues.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stellar-becomes-newest-member-of-cftcs-committee/" rel="nofollow">Stellar Becomes Newest Member of CFTC&#8217;s Committee</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>69% of Retail Investors Unfazed by 2022 Crypto Winter: Survey</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/69-of-retail-investors-unfazed-by-2022-crypto-winter-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 22:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eToro]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234270</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto_Winter.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Crypto_Winter.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The study found that younger investors are less fearful of the crypto market after the crash last year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Most retail investors are still very much interested in investing in digital assets despite experiencing what is arguably the worst bear market in crypto history.</p>
<p class="p2">According to a <span class="s1">recent survey <a href="https://www.etoro.com/news-and-analysis/press-releases/retail-investors-shrug-off-bear-market-blues-two-thirds-say-downturn-has-not-dented-their-investing-appetite/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a></span> by the social trading platform <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-etoro-beginners-guide-to-the-social-trading-platform/" data-wpel-link="internal">eToro</a>, more than two-thirds, approximately 69%, of retail investors revealed that they are positive or have mixed feelings about the impact of the prolonged market downturn recorded last year. The remaining one-third, approximately 31%, stated that they are wary of investing in the industry after the crash.</p>
<p class="p2">Commenting on this renewed interest from retail investors, eToro&#8217;s Global Markets Strategist, Ben Laidler, said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;The fact that two-thirds of retail investors feel indifferent, or even more positive, after the worst year for markets in a generation might seem odd. But the majority of this cohort thinks in years and decades. For those with longer time horizons, the back end of 2022 has offered a chance to buy companies at lower valuations, improving the outlook for long-term returns.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Investor Confidence Returns as Threat of Inflation Reduces</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The report, which surveyed 10,000 retail investors from 13 countries and three continents, revealed that the biggest driver of renewed investor confidence in crypto investing is the dwindling fear of the perceived threat of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-inflation-gauge-pce-clocks-in-at-4-7-yoy/" data-wpel-link="internal">inflation</a> among investors.</p>
<p class="p2">The study found that at the end of Q3 2022, about 24% of retail investors considered the perceived threat of inflation the biggest risk to their investment portfolios.</p>
<p class="p2">However, by the end of 2022, the inflation worry had dropped to 19%, while about 22% of respondents cited the global recession as the main threat to their investment portfolios going forward into 2023.</p>
<p class="p2">As a result, many investors are adjusting their portfolios, with cash allocation climbing to 50% and adding more defensive assets like healthcare and utilities.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Young Retail Investors Prove More Risk Tolerant</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The survey also found that younger investors have the least fear of the crypto market, while older investors looking at a looming retirement are more reluctant.</p>
<p class="p2">About 76% of young retail investors between the ages of 18-34 feel positive or indifferent about the downtrend, while only 60% of older investors above 55 years old feel the same way about the crypto market.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;2022 will have been the first major bear market for many less experienced retail investors, yet the data shows that it is older investors with shorter retirement time horizons who are feeling the strain the most,&#8221; the report added.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/69-of-retail-investors-unfazed-by-2022-crypto-winter-survey/" rel="nofollow">69% of Retail Investors Unfazed by 2022 Crypto Winter: Survey</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Is The Most Popular Starter Crypto: Nansen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-is-the-most-popular-starter-crypto-nansen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 19:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233987</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shiba-inu.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/shiba-inu.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu was the most popular cryptocurrency in new wallets over the past week, according to on-chain analysis.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu was the most popular crypto in new wallets over the past week, an on-chain analytics firm recently found. Banking was a boring subject for the Baby Boomer generation, but in the Internet of programmable money, finance is fun.</p>
<p>If asked to guess what they thought was the most popular first coin for new crypto adopters over the past week, many people would probably guess Bitcoin. But that doesn&#8217;t seem to be the case. Neither is it the number two crypto by market cap, the peer-to-peer network computer, Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Is Currently Cryptocurrency&#8217;s Most Popular Starter Coin</h2>
<p>On-chain data discovered by Nansen reveals the most popular non-stable coin digital asset for newly funded crypto wallets over the past seven days was Shiba Inu.</p>
<p>Over that period, Nansen clocked over $56 million in SHIB tokens flow into some 12,000 new wallets. The ERC-20 token was the most common crypto other than stablecoins to appear in these balances, according to Nansen.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu went through a slight correction, in line with the rest of the market.</p>
<p>The pullback coincided with stock prices edging lower after running higher in January. Analysts and commentators widely pointed to disappointed economic data and more hawkish interest rate talk from the Fed as the reason for the rout.</p>
<h2>SHIB Token Enthusiasts Eagerly Await &#8216;Shibarium&#8217;</h2>
<p>Wrapped Ether on Uniswap and ShibaSwap is the most dominant trading pair partner for SHIB by volume. But Binance holds the most Shiba Inu in SHIB balances.</p>
<p>There were recent misreports that Binance has delisted Shiba Ina.</p>
<p>The centralized crypto exchange only, however, delisted some trading pairs that included SHIB. The Dogecoin (DOGE) inspired Ethereum meme token is on Binance to stay.</p>
<p>The ancient Japanese dog breed, Shiba Inu, became the face of Dogecoin, the Bitcoin-forked PoW crypto that started as a joke. It went on to become one of the most highly capitalized cryptocurrencies in history and inaugurated the memecoin segment. Then DOGE even went on to inspire the Ethereum competitor.</p>
<p>Today SHIB enthusiasts are eagerly anticipating the recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-soars-to-2-month-high-on-shibarium-launch-update/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> Shibarium, an Ethereum layer 2 ecosystems for launching decentralized apps using SHIB as a native token</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-is-the-most-popular-starter-crypto-nansen/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu Is The Most Popular Starter Crypto: Nansen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Following Bitcoin&#8217;s Rally, This is the Next Major Target for BTC (Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/following-bitcoins-rally-this-is-the-next-major-target-for-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234378</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has initiated an explosive rally after finding support amid the $16K price level. Since then, BTC surpassed the 100-day and 200-day moving averages at $18K and $19.6K. After a prolonged downtrend, the price breaking above the 200-day moving average is a substantial bullish sign for the market. If the bulls maintain the MA-200 level, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has initiated an explosive rally after finding support amid the $16K price level. Since then, BTC surpassed the 100-day and 200-day moving averages at $18K and $19.6K.</p>
<p>After a prolonged downtrend, the price breaking above the 200-day moving average is a substantial bullish sign for the market. If the bulls maintain the MA-200 level, adequate demand will likely return to the market, and the sentiment will continue in the short term.</p>
<p>However, there is an evident bearish divergence between the price and the RSI indicator on the daily timeframe, which might result in a need for a correction over the next days and following the rally.</p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-234383" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Professional traders use pivot points to determine support and resistance levels. Simply put, a pivot point is a level at which a price movement’s direction can start a reversal.</p>
<p>The following chart shows that the BTC price has recently surpassed two significant pivot points and is consolidating around the $23K level. The next crucial resistance level for Bitcoin is the next major pivot <strong>at the $25K price level</strong>, which has also been a static resistance level for the past few months.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the bearish divergence is also seen in the 4-hour timeframe. There is a higher possibility that the price enters a short-term consolidation phase between the $23K and the $21K levels before spiking toward the $25K crucial resistance region.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-234382" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-4-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>The following chart provides an overview of the last four Bitcoin price cycles, including the 2017-2018 and 2019-2023 bull and bear markets. It contains the Bitcoin price alongside the MVRV metric, which implies the ratio of the Market Cap to its Realized Cap, indicating whether the price is overvalued.</p>
<p>Historically, the metric falls to the green zone during the bearish market phases, signifying that Bitcoin is trading at the under-valued section and the cycle’s bottom is forming. However, as the chart demonstrates, each time the MVRV metric spiked above 1, Bitcoin experienced a surge, and the bull market started.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s recent rally has resulted in a sharp increase in the MVRV metric. Hence, the market might have entered a bullish mid-term phase, followed by sudden moves and increased volatility.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-234381" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-MVRV-Ratio-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-bitcoins-rally-this-is-the-next-major-target-for-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Following Bitcoin&#8217;s Rally, This is the Next Major Target for BTC (Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum and Cardano Record Highest Level of Developer Activity in 2022: DappRadar</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-and-cardano-record-highest-level-of-developer-activity-in-2022-dappradar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 16:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234313</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Cardano.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Cardano.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In an intersting trend, modular blockchains saw significant traction in terms of developer activity.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum and Cardano have always been at loggerheads. The two blockchain network&#8217;s development activity has been pitted against each other even before the former&#8217;s transition to Proof-of-Stake (PoS). Needless to say, Ethereum and Cardano went on to become the blockchains with the most active developers in 2022, with 223 and 151 average daily devs throughout the year.</p>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/blockchain-and-dapp-adoption-report-2022" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by DappRadar, Ethereum saw the smallest decrease of 9.37% in active developers and managed to retain its dominance. Cardano&#8217;s developer count declined by 26.47% from the previous year.</p>
<ul>
<li>Developer activity indicates the blockchain&#8217;s health and growth. As explained by DappRadar, the metric gives an insight into the level of interest and engagement by devs, which is crucial &#8220;for the development of new features, increased security, network effects, innovation, and thus, adoption.&#8221;</li>
<li>Apart from the established players, three modular blockchains, namely Polkadot, Kusama, and Cosmos, completed the top 5.</li>
<li>The developer activity in Polkadot and Kusama increased by 16,06% and 12,80%, respectively, attracting 129 daily active devs on average. Cosmos, on the other hand, recorded 117 average daily developers.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, Solana and Internet Computer (ICP) saw the most significant increase in active devs in 2022. Since the previous year, the two blockchain networks surged by 1,320% and 1,050%, respectively.</li>
<li>The report also stated that Solana looks promising despite being the most <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-suffers-major-setback-as-development-activity-plunges-sol-dumps-hard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">impacted</a> in the FTX-induced drawdown.</li>
<li>The average number of daily active developers on the blockchain noted a decline of 31.4% over the past 30 days and continued to attract an average of 69 daily active developers.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-and-cardano-record-highest-level-of-developer-activity-in-2022-dappradar/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum and Cardano Record Highest Level of Developer Activity in 2022: DappRadar</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Minister Says Crypto Transactions Are Fine as Long as They Follow Laws </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/indian-minister-says-crypto-transactions-are-fine-as-long-as-they-follow-laws/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 14:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234322</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/India.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/India.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Remarks coming barely two weeks before the annual budget hints that the government may go soft on crypto regulations. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a significant development that indicates that the Indian government may not fully chime with the central bank&#8217;s overly hostile stance against cryptocurrencies, a junior minister explained that such activities are fine as long as they follow existing laws. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is in sharp contrast to the Reserve Bank of India&#8217;s (RBI) ban on crypto in 2018 and not fully opening up to the sector even when the Supreme Court scrapped the RBI order in 2022, calling it illegal.  </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Is Fine </span></h2>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“There is nothing today that outlaws crypto as long as you follow the legal process,” Rajeev Chandrasekhar, Minister of State for Information Technology and Electronics, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/india/no-issue-with-crypto-india-if-laws-are-followed-minister-2023-01-19/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">told</a> an event on Thursday.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">These remarks assume significance as the Indian government will be presenting the annual budget for the upcoming fiscal on February 1. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Local crypto exchanges and investors who have been facing an extremely unfriendly regulatory environment &#8211; from high taxation to denial of banking services &#8211; have asked for and are expecting some <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indian-crypto-association-seeks-relief-from-high-taxes/" data-wpel-link="internal">relief</a> to be announced in the budget proposals, which come into force, after deliberations in the parliament, from April 1. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Notably, through our representation for the upcoming Union Budget 2023 – 2024, we have suggested that the rate of TDS be brought down to 0.01%. This lower rate will help Indian VDA businesses offer competitive prices to Indian VDA users and protect them from exposure to unregulated foreign exchanges,” Sumit Gupta, Co-Founder and CEO of CoinDCX, said in a statement. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">RBI&#8217;s Tough Stance</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the past months, RBI Governor Shaktikanta Das has described cryptocurrencies as something having no underlying value and a poor cousin of gambling, which can lead to the dollarization of the economy and even trigger a global financial crisis if efforts are made to regulate and allow them to function. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">But a recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rapid-tech-adoption-and-talents-make-india-a-key-player-in-global-web3-market-study/" data-wpel-link="internal">study</a> by Nasscom suggests that India&#8217;s talent pool is driving the global Web3 push and accounts for at least 11% of the workforce. It also underscores the fact that over 60% of Indian Web3 startups are registered outside the country because of the unfavorable regulatory environment. Available data suggest that at least 7% of Indians either hold or have made crypto transactions. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ecosystem </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pain Points </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Right now, the pain point in the Indian crypto ecosystem is the high tax regime that provides for a 1% transaction tax and a 30% tax on gains made on cryptocurrency transactions. The government&#8217;s logic for introducing a 1% crypto transaction tax was to track all such transactions for taxation purposes. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto industry players such as Sumit Gupta have been arguing that this purpose can be achieved by levying a lower tax rate. As high taxes and strict regulations have prompted several startups to move out of India to favorable jurisdictions such as Singapore and Dubai, it&#8217;s expected that the government may relax them to &#8220;foster innovation&#8221; in the blockchain space. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Indian tax authorities have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/low-tds-collection-on-crypto-may-spur-indian-government-to-reduce-transaction-tax/" data-wpel-link="internal">collected</a> approximately $7.4 million in crypto transaction taxes since their implementation in July to mid-December. The low tax collection is another argument put forward in favor of reducing the transaction tax, which is proving to be prohibitive. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indian-minister-says-crypto-transactions-are-fine-as-long-as-they-follow-laws/" rel="nofollow">Indian Minister Says Crypto Transactions Are Fine as Long as They Follow Laws </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ransomware Revenue Drops Amidst Less Successful Extortion Attempts: Chainalysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ransomware-revenue-drops-amidst-less-successful-extortion-attempts-chainalysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ransomware]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234192</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hack_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hack_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Chainalysis acknowledged that the "true totals" of ransomware attacks could be much higher but victims are becoming less reluctant to pay up.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2022 has been a turbulent year. One good thing to come out of it is that &#8211; ransomware earnings are significantly down.</p>
<p>Attacks on the crypto industry remain rampant. However, data suggests that victims are increasingly refusing to pay ransomware attackers. Blockchain analytics company Chainalysis, in a new <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/crypto-ransomware-revenue-down-as-victims-refuse-to-pay/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report,</a> shed light on the changing dynamics in the ransomware industry.</p>
<h2>Zooming in on Ransomware Attacks 2022</h2>
<p>It found that over 10,000 unique strains were active in the first half of the year alone &#8211; a trend that was also confirmed by on-chain data. In comparison, around 5,400 unique strains were recorded to be active over the same period of 2021. The number of active strains has increased substantially in recent years, a major portion, however, goes to a small group of strains at any given time.</p>
<p>Lifespans of ransomware have slid in 2022. In fact, the average ransomware strain was found to be active for just 70 days, down from 153 in 2021 and 265 in 2020. Most attackers funnel the extorted funds to mainstream centralized cryptocurrency exchanges. This number surged from 39.3% in 2021 to 48.3% in 2022.</p>
<p>On the other hand, ill-gotten funds being moved to high-risk exchanges fell from 10.9% to 6.7%. A similar declining trend was seen in the usage of illicit services such as darknet markets for ransomware money laundering. However, the usage of coin mixers for the same purpose has increased from 11.6% to 15.0%.</p>
<h2>Less Frequent Ransom Payments</h2>
<p>Chainalysis stated that the estimate for 2022’s total ransomware revenue fell by 40.3% to at least $456.8 million in 2022 from $765.6 million in 2021. The drop is substantial and demonstrated increasing unwillingness among the victims to pay ransomware attackers and not a decline in the actual number of exploits.</p>
<p>While asserting that ransomware continues to be a major cyber threat to businesses and enterprises, Michael Phillips, Chief Claims Officer of cyber insurance firm Resilience, noted:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There have, however, been signs that meaningful disruptions against ransomware actor groups are driving lower than expected successful extortion attempts.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Especially over the past four years, the probability of victims paying a ransom has seen a dramatic shift. An analysis conducted by Bill Siegel, CEO of ransomware incident response company Coveware, suggested that victim payment rates have dropped from 76% in 2019  to 41% in 2022.</p>
<p>This shift can be attributed to the fact that paying ransoms has become legally riskier, especially after the advisory issued by the US Treasury Department&#8217;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) in September 2021 on the potential for sanctions violations when paying ransoms.</p>
<p>Another big factor playing a crucial role in the developing trend is the reimbursement to victims of ransomware attacks by cyber insurance firms. Phillips highlighted that companies have to meet stringent cybersecurity and backup measures to be insured for ransomware coverage. The demand for better cybersecurity measures has made it possible for companies to recover from attacks rather than giving in to ransom demands.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;An increased focus on underwriting against factors that contribute to ransomware has led to lower incident costs for companies and contributed to a decreasing trend in extortion payments.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ransomware-revenue-drops-amidst-less-successful-extortion-attempts-chainalysis/" rel="nofollow">Ransomware Revenue Drops Amidst Less Successful Extortion Attempts: Chainalysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Explodes 95% Weekly to ATH, Bitcoin Calms Amid $23K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-explodes-95-weekly-to-ath-bitcoin-calms-amid-23k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 09:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234364</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Aptos-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Aptos-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aptos (APT) is the best performer on a weekly scale from the top 100 cryptocurrencies.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the end of the week coming, bitcoin continued to gradually increase in value and tapped yet another multi-month high well above $23,000 before retracing slightly.</p>
<p>Most altcoins have calmed on a daily scale, aside from OKB and APT. The latter has soared by almost triple digits in the past seven days.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Recent Journey</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s 2023 so far is in sharp contrast to 2022 and especially the end of last year. The cryptocurrency entered the new year at $16,500, and it took around a week to reclaim $17,000.</p>
<p>That turned out to be a significant breakout line as the asset exploded in the next two weeks. This resulted in breaking above $20,000 for the first time since December, but BTC only <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/market-watch-shiba-inu-skyrockets-16-bitcoin-tapped-3-month-high/" data-wpel-link="internal">kept climbing</a>.</p>
<p>The culmination, at least for now, came on Saturday morning and in the afternoon when bitcoin exploded to above $23,400. Not only did this surge cause <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/300m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-soars-to-18-week-high/" data-wpel-link="internal">multi-million dollar losses</a> for over-leveraged investors, but it helped BTC chart its highest price tag since early September.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has retraced by a few hundred dollars as of now and sits at just under $23,000. Nevertheless, its market cap is still north of $440 billion, and its dominance over the altcoins is above 42%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234366" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234366" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234366" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="688" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22-300x115.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22-1024x393.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22-768x295.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22-1536x590.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-22-50x19.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234366" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>APT Steals the Weekly Show</h2>
<p>Launched just months ago, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-apt-guide/" data-wpel-link="internal">Aptos</a> has been among the best performers since the market started to rally a few weeks ago. The past seven days were particularly impressive for the native token, which has soared by 95% within this timeframe. As a result, APT charted an all-time high at over $14 earlier today.</p>
<p>ApeCoin and OKB are the two other notable gainers from the larger-cap alts. Both have surged by around 7% to $5.5 and $37, respectively.</p>
<p>Cardano is up by 4.5% and has neared $0.4. Most other top 10 altcoins are slightly in the red, retracing from yesterday&#8217;s explosion.</p>
<p>Still, the total crypto market cap is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-reclaims-1t-as-sol-okb-apt-explode-by-double-digits-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">well above $1 trillion</a> on both CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko. The metric has added over $200 billion since the start of the year.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234367" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234367" style="width: 1863px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234367" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1863" height="736" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15.jpg 1863w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15-300x119.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15-1024x405.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15-768x303.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15-1536x607.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-15-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1863px) 100vw, 1863px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234367" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-explodes-95-weekly-to-ath-bitcoin-calms-amid-23k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Aptos Explodes 95% Weekly to ATH, Bitcoin Calms Amid $23K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Expands its Partnership With German Soccer Club Borussia Dortmund (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-expands-its-partnership-with-german-soccer-club-borussia-dortmund-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 05:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234172</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Coinbase_BVB.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Coinbase_BVB.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase will serve as the Premium Partner of Borussia Dortmund until the end of June, 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US-based cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Coinbase &#8211; reportedly doubled down on its agreement with one of the most successful German soccer teams &#8211; Borussia Dortmund (BVB).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The deal, which turned the platform into a Premium Partner of the Bundesliga club, will last until the end of June.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Making the Collaboration Public</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase started its partnership with Borussia Dortmund in July last year by running ads on the video screens in the club&#8217;s stadium. According to recent <a href="https://www.handelsblatt.com/finanzen/banken-versicherungen/banken/fussball-bundesligist-coinbase-macht-partnerschaft-mit-borussia-dortmund-oeffentlich/28932058.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">coverage</a>, the two have expanded their collaboration. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following the new terms, Coinbase will serve as BVB&#8217;s Premium Partner, promote its products and services on Signal-Iduna-Park (the club&#8217;s home ground and Germany&#8217;s largest stadium), and provide crypto education programs for the team&#8217;s employees. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It remains unknown how much Coinbase spent to strike the deal. Borussia Dortmund&#8217;s Managing Director &#8211; Carsten Cramer &#8211; said it will last until the end of June but might get extended depending on the future condition of the cryptocurrency sector:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The industry is very exciting but still new. That&#8217;s why we want to keep our flexibility open.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cramer added that Coinbase&#8217;s BaFin license was a &#8220;basic requirement&#8221; for striking the partnership. The company is among the few cryptocurrency entities registered with the German financial watchdog. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite its recent expansion, the exchange has been coping with severe problems during the bear market. It dismissed around 18% of its total workforce last summer and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-dismisses-950-people-citing-current-economic-climate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">laid off</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> additional 950 people earlier this month.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-exit-japanese-market-after-kraken/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it will stop operating on the Japanese market, citing adverse economic conditions. Local users have until mid-February to withdraw their holdings from the platform, while deposits were halted today (January 20).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Rivals Have Already Dived Into the Soccer Field</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Leading cryptocurrency trading venues, including Binance, Crypto.com, and Bitget, have collaborated with soccer giants or famous players over the past few years.</span></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-becomes-the-new-global-sponsor-of-argentinas-national-soccer-team/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> serves as the main jersey partner of the Italian Lazio and is the main global sponsor of Argentina&#8217;s national team (the reigning world champion). It also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cristiano-ronaldo-to-launch-first-nft-collection-on-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">teamed up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the winner of five Ballon d&#8217;Or awards &#8211; Cristiano Ronaldo &#8211; to drop an NFT collection.</span></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-unveiled-as-fifa-world-cup-qatar-2022-official-sponsor" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto.com</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> was the official sponsor of the FIFA World Cup Qatar 2022, and its logo was visible during each of the 64 matches played in the tournament. </span></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-continuing-the-successful-journey-as-juventus-official-sleeve-partner/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitget</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> is the sleeve partner of Italy&#8217;s most successful soccer club &#8211; Juventus. It also partnered with arguably the greatest player of our times &#8211; Lionel (Leo) Messi &#8211; to allow fans to explore Web3 and the potential of crypto trading on the platform.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-expands-its-partnership-with-german-soccer-club-borussia-dortmund-report/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Expands its Partnership With German Soccer Club Borussia Dortmund (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>21Shares&#8217; New ETP Provides Exposure to PoS Cryptocurrencies But No ETH</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/21shares-new-etp-provides-exposure-to-pos-cryptocurrencies-but-no-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 23:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake (PoS)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233813</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/21Shares.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/21Shares.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Zug-based crypto firm is now eyeing to list the new product on Xetra Deutsche Boerse.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>21Shares announced the launch of first-of-its-kind crypto staking index ETP focused on proof-of-stake-based coins.</p>
<p>Dubbed 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP (STAKE), the product will essentially provide exposure to staking rewards while tracking the performance of underlying staked coins via a single ETP.</p>
<h2>World&#8217;s First Crypto Staking Index ETP</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/21shares-unveils-worlds-first-crypto-staking-index-etp-301723801.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, the index will track ten crypto-assets, including Binance Coin (BNB), Cardano (ADA), Cosmos (ATOM), Polkadot (DOT), Solana (SOL), and Tezos (XTZ).</p>
<p>It is expected to address demands from both retail and institutional investors across the world.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that STAKE is designed to track PoS-based coins, the product, however, does not include Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p>In a statement, the company further revealed that the index will rebalance in March and September on a semi-annual basis to demonstrate shifts in the crypto market.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s parent firm, 21.co&#8217;s Director of ETP Product, <span class="xn-person">Arthur Krause highlighted the increased investor demand for &#8220;diversified, crypto-native return streams,&#8221; especially amid the bear market. Staking, for one, was touted as one of the most attractive of them all. </span></p>
<p>He went on to add,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In particular, we&#8217;ve heard demand for a reliable and safe way to access staking, one of the most attractive potential return streams available in the crypto ecosystem. The 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP does just that, and will be an attractive addition to many portfolios.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The 21Shares Staking Basket Index ETP, which was made available on for trading on January 18th on the BX Swiss exchange, was developed in collaboration with Swedish index provider Vinter.</p>
<p>Its CEO, Jacob Lindberg, said the two firms will continue to work on launching more investment products that &#8220;build bridges into the crypto world.&#8221;</p>
<h2>21Shares&#8217; Expansion and More</h2>
<p>With the latest launch, 21Shares and it&#8217;s parent firm listed more than 40 products across 12 exchanges in 8 countries.</p>
<p>Last October, the Swiss fintech company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/21shares-focuses-on-the-middle-east-by-rolling-out-a-bitcoin-etp-on-nasdaq-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> Bitcoin exchange-traded product on Nasdaq Dubai. This marked the first physically-backed BTC ETP in the Middle East.</p>
<p>21.co, on the other hand, fetched $25 million in a funding round in September. The move catapulted its valuation to $2 billion, and made it &#8220;Switzerland’s largest crypto unicorn.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/21shares-new-etp-provides-exposure-to-pos-cryptocurrencies-but-no-eth/" rel="nofollow">21Shares&#8217; New ETP Provides Exposure to PoS Cryptocurrencies But No ETH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
