<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction for 2023 – Can LUNC Go to $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-for-2023-can-lunc-go-1.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic struggles to hold support above support at $0.00014, hours ahead of the New Year. The previous year – 2021, saw investors and crypto enthusiasts beam with the hope that 2022 would be laced with world-class developments and key milestones....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-for-2023-can-lunc-go-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction for 2023 – Can LUNC Go to $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-for-2023-can-lunc-go-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99585/246934/luncusd-2022-12-31-15-14-54.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="331559"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried Returns to Twitter, Denies Moving Funds in Wallets Associated with Alameda Research</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-returns-to-twitter-denies-moving-funds-in-wallets-associated-with-alameda-research.htm</link><description>Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried has returned to Twitter, denying allegations that he moved funds out of wallets associated with now-bankrupt trading firm Alameda Research. &lt;br /&gt;
In a response to a story that said wallets associated with Alameda transferred funds just days after Bankman-Fried was released on bail, SBF said he couldn't be moving any of those funds because he doesn't have access to them anymore. He added:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-returns-to-twitter-denies-moving-funds-in-wallets-associated-with-alameda-research.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried Returns to Twitter, Denies Moving Funds in Wallets Associated with Alameda Research&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Ftx Trial</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Alameda Research</category><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-returns-to-twitter-denies-moving-funds-in-wallets-associated-with-alameda-research.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99581/246931/sbfscreenshot-media-library-original-1535-784-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="56924"/></item><item><title>2022 Was a Year to Remember and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/2022-was-a-year-to-remember-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/2022-was-a-year-to-remember-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: 2022 Was a Year to Remember and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/2022-was-a-year-to-remember-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99401/246616/bitcoinbaddie-eth-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="406312"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried to Plead Not Guilty to Fraud Allegations on January 3rd</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-to-plead-not-guilty-to-fraud-allegations-on-january-3rd.htm</link><description>Sam Bankman-Fried, the disgraced founder of collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX, will plead not guilty to fraud and other charges against him at his upcoming arraignment. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a report from the Wall Street Journal, which cited a person familiar with the situation, Bankman-Fried is expected to enter a plea of not guilty in Manhattan on Tuesday, January 3rd. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-to-plead-not-guilty-to-fraud-allegations-on-january-3rd.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried to Plead Not Guilty to Fraud Allegations on January 3rd&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>Ftx Trial</category><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-to-plead-not-guilty-to-fraud-allegations-on-january-3rd.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99579/246924/sam-bankman-fried-media-library-original-1200-766.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="61980"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Shiba Inu? Crypto Experts Give Their 2023 SHIB Price Predictions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-crypto-experts-give-their-2023-shib-price-predictions.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-crypto-experts-give-their-2023-shib-price-predictions.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Shiba Inu? Crypto Experts Give Their 2023 SHIB Price Predictions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>CCHG</category><category>C+Charge</category><category>FightOut</category><category>FGHT</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-shiba-inu-crypto-experts-give-their-2023-shib-price-predictions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99566/246895/shiba-inu.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="237592"/></item><item><title>Get a Head Start on the Competition with This New Crypto Platform – Don't Miss Out on the Presale</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/get-head-start-competition-with-new-crypto-platform-dont-miss-out-presale.htm</link><description>All sorts of people in the crypto space have made huge profits recently, despite the bear market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Those who were able to make profitable trades, such as shorting FTT at $20-22 before its collapse to $2 in the space of 48 hours, were able to make huge profits.  &lt;br /&gt;
Dash 2 Trade is a platform that provides traders with all of the insights that they need in order to be able to most effectively navigate the markets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/get-head-start-competition-with-new-crypto-platform-dont-miss-out-presale.htm"&gt;Read More: Get a Head Start on the Competition with This New Crypto Platform – Don't Miss Out on the Presale&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/get-head-start-competition-with-new-crypto-platform-dont-miss-out-presale.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99549/246878/dash-2-trade-handels-und-analyseplattform-fuer-kryptowaehrungen-und-nfts-sowie-presales-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2728285"/></item><item><title>Crypto Analysts Believe These Altcoins Have the Most Potential for Growth in 2023 - Find Out Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-analysts-believe-these-altcoins-have-the-most-potential-for-growth-in-2023-find-out-why-2.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
2023 is just around the corner, and many crypto investors have been reorganizing their portfolios to focus on assets that can deliver gains in the new year. Some new digital assets have the most potential for growth in the coming year.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this article, we will take a quick look at them....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-analysts-believe-these-altcoins-have-the-most-potential-for-growth-in-2023-find-out-why-2.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Analysts Believe These Altcoins Have the Most Potential for Growth in 2023 - Find Out Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-analysts-believe-these-altcoins-have-the-most-potential-for-growth-in-2023-find-out-why-2.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99544/246867/9d5ea3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="368040"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 30 December – FGHT, BIT, D2T, TON, CCHG</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-30-december-fght-bit-d2t-ton-cchg.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-30-december-fght-bit-d2t-ton-cchg.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 30 December – FGHT, BIT, D2T, TON, CCHG&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>FGHT</category><category>FightOut</category><category>C-Charge</category><category>CCGH</category><category>TON</category><category>BIT</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-30-december-fght-bit-d2t-ton-cchg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99550/246865/best-crypto-30-dec.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="259529"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Prediction as SOL Dips Below $10 Before Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Comes to the Rescue – Here's What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-dips-below-10-before-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-comes-rescue-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Solana's price has been experiencing a drop in value due to concerns that Sam Bankman-Fried and venture capital firms may sell their tokens. This has caused SOL's price to fall below $10 for the first time in over a year and a half. However, the price may be seeing a recovery due to positive comments from Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin, who praised the Solana network for its development progress and thriving ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-dips-below-10-before-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-comes-rescue-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Prediction as SOL Dips Below $10 Before Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Comes to the Rescue – Here's What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-dips-below-10-before-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-comes-rescue-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99546/246857/solusd-2022-12-30-18-17-16.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="390700"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: FTX-owned Liquid to Start Refunding Customers in February, The Bahamas SEC Holds $3.5M of FTX Assets</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ftx-owned-liquid-to-start-refunding-customers-in-february-the-bahamas-sec-holds-35m-of-ftx-assets.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ftx-owned-liquid-to-start-refunding-customers-in-february-the-bahamas-sec-holds-35m-of-ftx-assets.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: FTX-owned Liquid to Start Refunding Customers in February, The Bahamas SEC Holds $3.5M of FTX Assets&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Exchange</category><category>FTX</category><category>Japan</category><category>Bahamas</category><category>Legal</category><category>Cardano</category><category>DeFi</category><category>DEX</category><category>Investment</category><category>Career</category><category>Bitfarms</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Tether</category><category>Community</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ftx-owned-liquid-to-start-refunding-customers-in-february-the-bahamas-sec-holds-35m-of-ftx-assets.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99510/246805/adobestock-syda-productions-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="86667"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried Met with Senior Biden Aide Prior to FTX Collapse – What Did They Discuss?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-met-with-senior-biden-aide-prior-to-ftx-collapse-what-did-they-discuss.htm</link><description>Disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried met with senior officials at the White House on at least four occasions prior to the collapse of FTX, White House visitor logs have revealed. &lt;br /&gt;
The last of the four meetings was reportedly held on September 8 between Sam Bankman-Fried – better known as SBF – and Steve Ricchetti, a senior adviser to President Joe Biden. The last meeting has not been publicly known until now....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-met-with-senior-biden-aide-prior-to-ftx-collapse-what-did-they-discuss.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried Met with Senior Biden Aide Prior to FTX Collapse – What Did They Discuss?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-met-with-senior-biden-aide-prior-to-ftx-collapse-what-did-they-discuss.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99525/246822/sbf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="109069"/></item><item><title>Expert Predicts Further Crypto Adoption in Russia – For These Reasons</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-predicts-further-crypto-adoption-russia-for-these-reasons.htm</link><description>International sanctions are driving crypto adoption in Russia, a crypto expert has stated. And, the analyst claims, they will likely spur some further growth in the sector. &lt;br /&gt;
The claims were made by Yuri Myshinsky, Chairman of the Board of the Digital Transformation Association, and reported by Podmoskovye Segodnya. &lt;br /&gt;
Myshinsky noted that “historically,” Russia’s “relationship with cryptocurrencies” was somewhat “contradictory.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-predicts-further-crypto-adoption-russia-for-these-reasons.htm"&gt;Read More: Expert Predicts Further Crypto Adoption in Russia – For These Reasons&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-predicts-further-crypto-adoption-russia-for-these-reasons.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99498/246796/adobestock-506752259.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3063541"/></item><item><title>Binance Coin Price Prediction as German Car Manufacturer BMW Partners with BNB Chain – BNB to the Moon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-as-german-car-manufacturer-bmw-partners-with-bnb-chain-bnb-moon.htm</link><description>Binance Coin, the native token of the popular cryptocurrency exchange, has seen a downturn in price in recent weeks. However, it has recovered slightly, climbing 11% since December 17th. Currently trading at $244, the token may see further gains if it can break through the 50-day Exponential Moving Average at $245.8.  &lt;br /&gt;
A green candle on the four-hour chart may indicate a potential 7.35% breakout from a triangle pattern....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-as-german-car-manufacturer-bmw-partners-with-bnb-chain-bnb-moon.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Coin Price Prediction as German Car Manufacturer BMW Partners with BNB Chain – BNB to the Moon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-as-german-car-manufacturer-bmw-partners-with-bnb-chain-bnb-moon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99499/246799/bnbusd-2022-12-30-13-53-18.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="371120"/></item><item><title>Chinese Gov’t to Unveil Its Version of an ‘NFT’ Marketplace</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-govt-unveil-its-version-of-an-nft-marketplace.htm</link><description>The Chinese government has announced plans to launch its own version of a state-backed “non-fungible token (NFT)” marketplace. But Beijing won’t be using blockchain to power its platform. And it wants to do away with crypto as the marketplace’s currency – in favor of fiat....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-govt-unveil-its-version-of-an-nft-marketplace.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Gov’t to Unveil Its Version of an ‘NFT’ Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>China</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-govt-unveil-its-version-of-an-nft-marketplace.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99490/246772/adobestock-442214332.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2947046"/></item><item><title>Central Bank Digital Currency: Turkey's Central Bank Conducts First Transactions of Digital Lira – Will Other Countries Follow Suit?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/central-bank-digital-currency-turkeys-central-bank-conducts-first-transactions-of-digital-lira-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm</link><description>The Central Bank of the Republic of Turkey (CBRT) has completed the first trial of its central bank digital currency (CBDC), the Digital Turkish Lira.  &lt;br /&gt;
The country's central bank issued a press release on December 29, stating that, &lt;br /&gt;
"In the scope of the first-phase studies of the Digital Turkish Lira Project, conducted under the leadership of the [CBRT], the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network were executed successfully." ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/central-bank-digital-currency-turkeys-central-bank-conducts-first-transactions-of-digital-lira-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm"&gt;Read More: Central Bank Digital Currency: Turkey's Central Bank Conducts First Transactions of Digital Lira – Will Other Countries Follow Suit?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Turkey</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Banking</category><category>Inflation</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/central-bank-digital-currency-turkeys-central-bank-conducts-first-transactions-of-digital-lira-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99464/246770/adobestock-doganmesut-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="121289"/></item><item><title>Shark Tank Star Kevin O’Leary’s Twitter Account Hacked, Starts Promoting Crypto Scam – Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shark-tank-star-kevin-olearys-twitter-account-hacked-starts-promoting-crypto-scam-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Shark Tank star Kevin O’Leary’s Twitter account was hacked on Thursday and started promoting a crypto giveaway scam. &lt;br /&gt;
The famed investor's Twitter account, which is followed by more than 982,000 users, sent out multiple tweets about a giveaway of 5,000 BTC and 15,000 ETH, with an accompanying image featuring O'Leary himself....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shark-tank-star-kevin-olearys-twitter-account-hacked-starts-promoting-crypto-scam-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Shark Tank Star Kevin O’Leary’s Twitter Account Hacked, Starts Promoting Crypto Scam – Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Kevin O'Leary</category><category>Scam</category><category>Giveaways</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shark-tank-star-kevin-olearys-twitter-account-hacked-starts-promoting-crypto-scam-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99482/246763/107163293-16705077171670507714-27034701265-1080pnbcnews-media-library-original-750-422.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="36325"/></item></channel></rss>
