<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Stellar Price Prediction as XLM Blasts Up 30% in 7 Days – Can XLM Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/stellar-price-prediction-as-xlm-blasts-up-30-7-days-can-xlm-reach-1.htm</link><description>The Stellar price has dipped by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, yet its current level of $0.128569 represents an impressive 30% gain in the last 30 days. &lt;br /&gt;
As a cryptocurrency that also targets cross-border payments, XLM has benefitted from Ripple's success in its case with the SEC, with the altcoin joining XRP in the past few days to decisively outperform the wider market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/stellar-price-prediction-as-xlm-blasts-up-30-7-days-can-xlm-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Stellar Price Prediction as XLM Blasts Up 30% in 7 Days – Can XLM Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/stellar-price-prediction-as-xlm-blasts-up-30-7-days-can-xlm-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119803/318243/stellar-price-prediction-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1102045"/></item><item><title>Investigation Reveals Bitcoin's Creator Satoshi Nakamoto Could Be a Group, Not an Individual</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/investigation-reveals-bitcoins-creator-satoshi-nakamoto-could-group-not-an-individual.htm</link><description>The identity of Satoshi Nakamoto, the enigmatic creator of Bitcoin (BTC), has been a subject of intense curiosity and speculation since the advent of the leading cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
While many envision a single genius behind its inception, there is growing evidence to suggest that Nakamoto may actually be a collective entity. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/investigation-reveals-bitcoins-creator-satoshi-nakamoto-could-group-not-an-individual.htm"&gt;Read More: Investigation Reveals Bitcoin's Creator Satoshi Nakamoto Could Be a Group, Not an Individual&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Satoshi Nakamoto</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/investigation-reveals-bitcoins-creator-satoshi-nakamoto-could-group-not-an-individual.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119807/318233/satoshi-media-library-ori.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="30507"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Central Bank Digital Currency Raises Alarm as Developer Uncovers Fund Freezing Feature</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-central-bank-digital-currency-raises-alarm-as-developer-uncovers-fund-freezing-feature.htm</link><description>A blockchain developer has found a code in Brazilian central bank-backed digital currency (CBDC) that would allow the government to freeze accounts or even drain them at will.  &lt;br /&gt;
Founder of Web3 consulting company Iora Labs and blockchain developer Pedro Magalhaes took to social media to reveal his findings in the Brazilian CBDC pilot. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-central-bank-digital-currency-raises-alarm-as-developer-uncovers-fund-freezing-feature.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Central Bank Digital Currency Raises Alarm as Developer Uncovers Fund Freezing Feature&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Digital fiat</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-central-bank-digital-currency-raises-alarm-as-developer-uncovers-fund-freezing-feature.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119802/318230/brazil-digital-currency-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="148180"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Ripple CEO Sees Long Appeal Process for SEC in Lawsuit – Will the Decision be Overturned?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-sees-long-appeal-process-for-sec-lawsuit-will-decision-overturned.htm</link><description>The XRP price has gained by 4% in the past 24 hours, with the coin's move to $0.748896 representing a 60% gain in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
This market-trouncing surge follows Ripple's success in its long-running legal battle with the SEC, with the presiding judge issuing a ruling last week which sided with the cryptocurreny firm on a significant number of counts....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-sees-long-appeal-process-for-sec-lawsuit-will-decision-overturned.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Ripple CEO Sees Long Appeal Process for SEC in Lawsuit – Will the Decision be Overturned?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-sees-long-appeal-process-for-sec-lawsuit-will-decision-overturned.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119799/318229/xrp-price-prediction-as-r.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="985516"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy XRP? XRP Price Nearly Doubles in 7 Days and Launchpad XYZ Just Raised $1.1 Million – What Does it Do?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-xrp-xrp-price-nearly-doubles-7-days-launchpad-xyz-just-raised-11-million-what-does-it-do.htm</link><description>After years of hard-fought legal struggle against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Ripple emerged victorious on July 13, following District Judge Torres' ruling that XRP token sales were not investment contracts (securities). &lt;br /&gt;
The highly anticipated judgement catalysed explosive price action across markets, as XRP holders were vindicated after months, and in some cases years, of cautiously-optimistic stacking....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-xrp-xrp-price-nearly-doubles-7-days-launchpad-xyz-just-raised-11-million-what-does-it-do.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy XRP? XRP Price Nearly Doubles in 7 Days and Launchpad XYZ Just Raised $1.1 Million – What Does it Do?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-xrp-xrp-price-nearly-doubles-7-days-launchpad-xyz-just-raised-11-million-what-does-it-do.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119795/318226/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1002384"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Ripple's Legal Win and Global Interest Shape the Market</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-ripples-legal-win-global-interest-shape-market-1.htm</link><description>Bitcoin price is currently trading at around $30,300, showing less than 0.50% surge during the Asian session on Monday. The recent favorable decision in the SEC vs. Ripple case has impacted the price, bringing it back to the level seen last Thursday. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a former SEC official expresses skepticism about the ruling on XRP, stating that "the decision rests on shaky ground" and anticipates a potential reversal in the future....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-ripples-legal-win-global-interest-shape-market-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Ripple's Legal Win and Global Interest Shape the Market&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-ripples-legal-win-global-interest-shape-market-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119786/318203/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1473618"/></item><item><title>China’s Changzhou to Give Away Digital Yuan Tokens, Coupons Worth $700k</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-changzhou-give-away-digital-yuan-tokens-coupons-worth-700k.htm</link><description>The city of Changzhou, China, is set to give away $700,000 worth of digital yuan tokens and coupons before the year is out, as the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) pilot continues. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Changzhou Evening News (via JSChina), the city is hoping to boost CBDC spending during an upcoming citywide shopping festival by distributing e-CNY in “lucky red [digital] envelopes.” &lt;br /&gt;
Red is a symbol of good fortune in China....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-changzhou-give-away-digital-yuan-tokens-coupons-worth-700k.htm"&gt;Read More: China’s Changzhou to Give Away Digital Yuan Tokens, Coupons Worth $700k&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-changzhou-give-away-digital-yuan-tokens-coupons-worth-700k.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119767/318181/adobestock-529912803.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1014896"/></item><item><title>10 Meme Coin Price Predictions for 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/10-meme-coin-price-predictions-for-2023.htm</link><description>2023 has been a blockbuster year for blue-chip cryptocurrencies. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) is up a staggering 80% year-to-date. &lt;br /&gt;
Ether (ETH) is up 58% over the same time period. &lt;br /&gt;
But the picture has been more mixed for meme coins. &lt;br /&gt;
Some have done very well, but others have struggled, suggesting risk appetite remains cautious and animal spirits are yet to fully return to the crypto space, despite the strong performance of the major coins....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/10-meme-coin-price-predictions-for-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: 10 Meme Coin Price Predictions for 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>DOGE</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Floki</category><category>Shitcoins</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/10-meme-coin-price-predictions-for-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119701/318070/meme-coin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1736527"/></item><item><title>Ripple’s Victory in Court Drives up Crypto Trading Volumes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-victory-court-drives-up-crypto-trading-volumes.htm</link><description>Ripple's win against the US Securities and Exchange Commission has boosted crypto trading volumes across spot exchanges. &lt;br /&gt;
Spot trading volumes on crypto exchanges surged to $16.56 billion on Friday from Wednesday's $12.74 billion, a growth of around 30% in just two days, according to The Block's data dashboard....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-victory-court-drives-up-crypto-trading-volumes.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple’s Victory in Court Drives up Crypto Trading Volumes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-victory-court-drives-up-crypto-trading-volumes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119762/318173/adobestock-photo-gonzo-1-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="64141"/></item><item><title>ARK Invest Bets Big on Meta Platforms and Robinhood, Reduces Coinbase Position</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-bets-big-meta-platforms-robinhood-reduces-coinbase-position.htm</link><description>Investment management firm ARK Invest has started accumulating Meta and Robinhood shares while selling more Coinbase shares.  &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, the company offloaded 478,356 Coinbase shares valued at $53 million as the crypto exchange’s stock prices reached a 52-week high....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-bets-big-meta-platforms-robinhood-reduces-coinbase-position.htm"&gt;Read More: ARK Invest Bets Big on Meta Platforms and Robinhood, Reduces Coinbase Position&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Robinhood</category><category>Meta</category><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-bets-big-meta-platforms-robinhood-reduces-coinbase-position.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119756/318146/adobestock-wirestock-1-me.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="42420"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Falls Back Down to $30,000 Support – Where is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-falls-back-down-30000-support-where-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price has encountered a setback as it falls back down to the key support level of $30,000. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $30,330.  &lt;br /&gt;
Recent news surrounding the cryptocurrency market includes a Coinbase user's claim of account closure by Bank of America due to Bitcoin transactions, drawing attention to potential challenges faced by banks in accommodating digital assets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-falls-back-down-30000-support-where-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Falls Back Down to $30,000 Support – Where is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-falls-back-down-30000-support-where-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119747/318135/16.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="526491"/></item><item><title>Jay-Z's Roc Nation and Puma Collaborate on NFT-Enhanced Sneakers</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jay-zs-roc-nation-and-puma-collaborate-on-nft-enhanced-sneakers.htm</link><description>Jay-Z's Roc Nation and Puma have joined forces to create a new sneaker collection that incorporates non-fungible tokens (NFTs). &lt;br /&gt;
The entertainment agency and the apparel giant have partnered with Legitimate, a startup that bridges the gap between physical and digital realms using its proprietary "LGT Tag" technology, to launch the RS-XL Mixtape sneaker collection, according to a Friday press release. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jay-zs-roc-nation-and-puma-collaborate-on-nft-enhanced-sneakers.htm"&gt;Read More: Jay-Z's Roc Nation and Puma Collaborate on NFT-Enhanced Sneakers&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><category>Puma</category><category>Jay-Z</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jay-zs-roc-nation-and-puma-collaborate-on-nft-enhanced-sneakers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119728/318115/pexels-ashutosh-sonwani-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="133238"/></item><item><title>Last Chance to Get Involved in 2023’s Best Meme Coin Presale – Thug Life Token Raises $1.8 Million, About to Sell Out</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/last-chance-get-involved-2023s-best-meme-coin-presale-thug-life-token-raises-18-million-about-sell-out.htm</link><description>Saturday, 15th July - Meme coin degens hunting for the next small-cap crypto gem to explode are quickly running out of time to get involved in the Thug Life Token presale, which analysts have hailed as one of 2023’s best meme coin presale opportunities. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite only launching the presale just over two weeks ago, Thug Life Token has now raised a staggering $1.8 million via the sale of $THUG....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/last-chance-get-involved-2023s-best-meme-coin-presale-thug-life-token-raises-18-million-about-sell-out.htm"&gt;Read More: Last Chance to Get Involved in 2023’s Best Meme Coin Presale – Thug Life Token Raises $1.8 Million, About to Sell Out&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Thug Life Token</category><category>THUG</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/last-chance-get-involved-2023s-best-meme-coin-presale-thug-life-token-raises-18-million-about-sell-out.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119733/318126/thug-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="605331"/></item><item><title>Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Sells $53 Million Coinbase Shares Amid Record Highs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-53-million-coinbase-shares-amid-record-highs.htm</link><description>Cathie Wood’s Ark Invest sold 478,356 Coinbase shares valued at $53 million on Friday as the crypto exchange’s stock prices reached a 52-week high.  &lt;br /&gt;
This is the second time Cathie Wood-led investment management firm offloaded Coinbase shares within a week. &lt;br /&gt;
As reported earlier, Ark Invest sold 135,152 Coinbase shares worth $12 million on July 11 from the Ark Innovation ETF. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-53-million-coinbase-shares-amid-record-highs.htm"&gt;Read More: Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Sells $53 Million Coinbase Shares Amid Record Highs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Cathie Wood</category><category>Meta</category><category>ARK Invest</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-53-million-coinbase-shares-amid-record-highs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119727/318125/cathie-wood.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="112103"/></item><item><title>WALTER2.0 Coin Rockets Up 30,000% But Crypto Experts Are Accumulating These Other Coins Instead - Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/walter2-coin-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-experts-are-accumulating-these-other-coins-instead-heres-why.htm</link><description>Newly launched cryptocurrency project, WALTER2.0, has quickly generated substantial profits for its early backers.  &lt;br /&gt;
In just 24 hours, the digital asset has experienced an astonishing surge of 30,000%, creating numerous millionaires. &lt;br /&gt;
However, this remarkable ascent has been marred by concerns raised by the DEXTools launchpad, which has labeled WALTER2.0 as a potential honeypot scam. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/walter2-coin-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-experts-are-accumulating-these-other-coins-instead-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: WALTER2.0 Coin Rockets Up 30,000% But Crypto Experts Are Accumulating These Other Coins Instead - Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/walter2-coin-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-experts-are-accumulating-these-other-coins-instead-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119726/318113/walter2-0-usd-uni-dextool.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="192716"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Pauses Staking Services in Several US States Amid SEC Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-pauses-staking-services-several-us-states-amid-sec-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Coinbase, the US-based cryptocurrency exchange, has temporarily paused its staking services in four states in response to legal proceedings from Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). &lt;br /&gt;
In a blog post on July 14, Coinbase announced that it was temporarily suspending its retail staking service in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-pauses-staking-services-several-us-states-amid-sec-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Pauses Staking Services in Several US States Amid SEC Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Security</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-pauses-staking-services-several-us-states-amid-sec-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119718/318096/adobestock-rafael-henriqu.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="59595"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Ripple Plummets 20% From Recent Top – Is The Selling Done Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-plummets-20-from-recent-top-selling-done-now.htm</link><description>The XRP price has experienced a significant downturn, with Ripple's native cryptocurrency plummeting by 20% from its recent peak.  &lt;br /&gt;
At the time of writing, the live XRP price stands at $0.723937, reflecting the extent of the decline.  &lt;br /&gt;
The recent surge in value, amounting to an impressive gain of approximately 100%, has occurred amid the ongoing legal dispute between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-plummets-20-from-recent-top-selling-done-now.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Ripple Plummets 20% From Recent Top – Is The Selling Done Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-plummets-20-from-recent-top-selling-done-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119709/318094/xrp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="271124"/></item><item><title>Mashinky’s Arrests, Coinbase’s Messages, Google Play’s NFTs, ETF Optimisms and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/mashinkys-arrests-coinbases-messages-google-plays-nfts-etf-optimisms-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/mashinkys-arrests-coinbases-messages-google-plays-nfts-etf-optimisms-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Mashinky’s Arrests, Coinbase’s Messages, Google Play’s NFTs, ETF Optimisms and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/mashinkys-arrests-coinbases-messages-google-plays-nfts-etf-optimisms-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119610/317905/title.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="185757"/></item><item><title>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Highlights Rising Crypto Demand from Gold Investors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-highlights-rising-crypto-demand-from-gold-investors.htm</link><description>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink has expressed optimism about the rising demand for cryptocurrencies among gold investors.  &lt;br /&gt;
In an interview with CNBC following the release of BlackRock's second-quarter earnings report, Fink stated that "more and more" gold investors have been inquiring about the role of cryptocurrencies over the past five years. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-highlights-rising-crypto-demand-from-gold-investors.htm"&gt;Read More: BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Highlights Rising Crypto Demand from Gold Investors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>Larry Fink</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-highlights-rising-crypto-demand-from-gold-investors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119715/318091/a08fe9ae12-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="112684"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Markets Suddenly Sell Off – Where is the Next Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-markets-suddenly-sell-off-where-next-target.htm</link><description>In a surprising turn of events, the cryptocurrency market witnessed a sudden sell-off, causing Bitcoin price to plummet by more than 3% from its previous level of $31,750 to $30,290.  &lt;br /&gt;
The rapid decline has caught many investors off guard and left them wondering about the next target for Bitcoin's price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-markets-suddenly-sell-off-where-next-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Markets Suddenly Sell Off – Where is the Next Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-markets-suddenly-sell-off-where-next-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119708/318089/15.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="526283"/></item></channel></rss>
