<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Square Enix Resolves to Continue with Web3, Blockchain Gaming Drive</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/square-enix-resolves-continue-with-web3-blockchain-gaming-drive.htm</link><description>The Japanese gaming giant Square Enix has reasserted its commitment to blockchain gaming, announcing that it will continue to develop blockchain, Web3, and NFT games in the next 12 months. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm, which created the Final Fantasy series, issued an end-of-fiscal year statement this month. &lt;br /&gt;
Square Enix has faced a furious backlash from many gaming communities for its blockchain pivot, which it first unveiled in early 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/square-enix-resolves-continue-with-web3-blockchain-gaming-drive.htm"&gt;Read More: Square Enix Resolves to Continue with Web3, Blockchain Gaming Drive&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Gaming</category><category>NFT</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/square-enix-resolves-continue-with-web3-blockchain-gaming-drive.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114234/276100/sq-enix.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="320744"/></item><item><title>US Lawmakers Reintroduce Securities Clarity Act Which Coins New Term</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-reintroduce-securities-clarity-act-coins-new-term.htm</link><description>US lawmakers introduced a bill on Thursday that aims to clarify how digital assets are labeled, in part through a new term coined an “investment contract asset.” &lt;br /&gt;
Reps. Tom Emmer, R-Minn., and Darren Soto, D-Fla., reintroduced the Securities Clarity Act, with backing from crypto advocacy groups in Washington D.C. &lt;br /&gt;
Emmer first introduced the bill in 2020, which would define an “investment contract asset” as distinct from the securities offering it was a part of....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-reintroduce-securities-clarity-act-coins-new-term.htm"&gt;Read More: US Lawmakers Reintroduce Securities Clarity Act Which Coins New Term&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-reintroduce-securities-clarity-act-coins-new-term.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114320/276223/washington-dc-g95abe2efb-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="439490"/></item><item><title>Ripple's $250 Million Acquisition of Swiss Blockchain Firm Metaco Marks Expansion into Tokenized Assets</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-250-million-acquisition-of-swiss-blockchain-firm-metaco-marks-expansion-into-tokenized-assets.htm</link><description>The American fintech Ripple has acquired the Switzerland-based blockchain firm Metaco for $250 million, marking its first entry into the asset tokenization field. &lt;br /&gt;
The acquisition was announced by Ripple on Wednesday, with the firm saying it expects the deal to help it expand its enterprise offerings, particularly in international markets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-250-million-acquisition-of-swiss-blockchain-firm-metaco-marks-expansion-into-tokenized-assets.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple's $250 Million Acquisition of Swiss Blockchain Firm Metaco Marks Expansion into Tokenized Assets&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ripple</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-250-million-acquisition-of-swiss-blockchain-firm-metaco-marks-expansion-into-tokenized-assets.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114319/276222/ripple-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="122365"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Reaches New All-Time High – BTC Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bitcoin-mining-difficulty-reaches-new-all-time-high-btc-adoption-on-the-rise.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin mining difficulty hits an unprecedented high, the cryptocurrency's future price trajectory comes into focus.  &lt;br /&gt;
The rising complexity of mining operations indicates a robust network and heightened interest in Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
With mining becoming increasingly challenging, it begs the question: Is this surge in difficulty a precursor to a potential rise in Bitcoin adoption? ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bitcoin-mining-difficulty-reaches-new-all-time-high-btc-adoption-on-the-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Reaches New All-Time High – BTC Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bitcoin-mining-difficulty-reaches-new-all-time-high-btc-adoption-on-the-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114316/276221/18-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481749"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 18 May – Decentraland, Axie Infinity, XRP</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-18-may-decentraland-axie-infinity-xrp.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price has once again dipped below $27,000, indicating a slight selloff in the broader cryptocurrency market. &lt;br /&gt;
At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at $26,632 and experiencing a loss of 2.83% so far today. &lt;br /&gt;
Other major cryptocurrencies, such as Ethereum (ETH) and Binance Coin (BNB), are also experiencing a decline, with losses of 1.94% and 1.64%, respectively....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-18-may-decentraland-axie-infinity-xrp.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 18 May – Decentraland, Axie Infinity, XRP&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>MANA</category><category>Sponge</category><category>AXS</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>XRP</category><category>YPRED</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Decentraland</category><category>Axie Infinity</category><category>Axie Shards</category><category>Ripple</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Cryptocurrency Market</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-18-may-decentraland-axie-infinity-xrp.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114312/276202/best-crypto-18-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="387224"/></item><item><title>Chamber of Digital Commerce Pens Call to Action for US Congress To Pass Crypto Legislation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chamber-of-digital-commerce-pens-call-action-for-us-congress-pass-crypto-legislation.htm</link><description>The Chamber of Digital Commerce is calling on the US Congress to get it together and pass legislation for digital assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The advocacy group with members such as Binance, Circle, Fidelity Investments and others, say they want lawmakers to organize a “Digital Asset and Blockchain Technology Solarium Commission” to do just that....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chamber-of-digital-commerce-pens-call-action-for-us-congress-pass-crypto-legislation.htm"&gt;Read More: Chamber of Digital Commerce Pens Call to Action for US Congress To Pass Crypto Legislation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Chamber of Digital Commerce</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chamber-of-digital-commerce-pens-call-action-for-us-congress-pass-crypto-legislation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114314/276208/adobestock-230599906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="533273"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as $1 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying Before the Halving?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-1-billion-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-before-halving.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC) is on course for its first red day in five as the broader cryptocurrency market experiences a dip as US yields and the US dollar gain in wake of strong US data releases that push back against US recession bets, and after commentary from Fed speakers puts in doubt the idea that the central bank is done hiking interest rates....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-1-billion-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-before-halving.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as $1 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying Before the Halving?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-1-billion-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-before-halving.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114315/276207/ltc-2.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2108527"/></item><item><title>DeFi Needs to Be Simpler for Wider Adoption, Uniswap Survey Suggests</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-needs-simpler-for-wider-adoption-uniswap-survey-suggests.htm</link><description>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols should be simplified for users if adoption is to grow, a survey from the team behind the Uniswap decentralized exchange (DEX) has suggested. &lt;br /&gt;
In a report that summarized the survey results, Uniswap called DeFi an “objectively simpler, more accessible tech stack for financial markets.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-needs-simpler-for-wider-adoption-uniswap-survey-suggests.htm"&gt;Read More: DeFi Needs to Be Simpler for Wider Adoption, Uniswap Survey Suggests&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-needs-simpler-for-wider-adoption-uniswap-survey-suggests.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114313/276205/uniswap-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="83205"/></item><item><title>5 Best Crypto Shitcoins to Buy Now that Andrew Tate Might Endorse – COPIUM, LADYS, AI, PEPE, SPONGE</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-crypto-shitcoins-buy-now-that-andrew-tate-might-endorse-copium-ladys-ai-pepe-sponge.htm</link><description>Controversial mega influencer Andrew Tate is pumping the meme coin mania that has taken over cryptocurrency markets in recent weeks, created significant congestion on major blockchains like Bitcoin and Ethereum and given rise to a new wave of popular meme coins including Pepe (PEPE). &lt;br /&gt;
Tate just announced via Twitter that, on the 1st of June, he will endorse a “shitcoin” and “send it to the fucking moon”....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-crypto-shitcoins-buy-now-that-andrew-tate-might-endorse-copium-ladys-ai-pepe-sponge.htm"&gt;Read More: 5 Best Crypto Shitcoins to Buy Now that Andrew Tate Might Endorse – COPIUM, LADYS, AI, PEPE, SPONGE&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shitcoin</category><category>Andrew Tate</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>AI</category><category>Sponge</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-crypto-shitcoins-buy-now-that-andrew-tate-might-endorse-copium-ladys-ai-pepe-sponge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114311/276201/andrew-tate.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="220399"/></item><item><title>Whampoa Group Private Family Office to Open Digital Bank in Bahrain – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/whampoa-group-private-family-office-open-digital-bank-bahrain-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Singapore-based investment firm Whampoa Group aims to open a digital bank in Bahrain to offer payment and settlement services for crypto firms.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent statement, Whampoa Group said it plans to set up the bank, which will provide banking services as well as the trading, custody, and asset management of digital tokens, by the end of the year, according to a report by Bloomberg. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/whampoa-group-private-family-office-open-digital-bank-bahrain-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Whampoa Group Private Family Office to Open Digital Bank in Bahrain – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Whampoa Group</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Bahrain</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/whampoa-group-private-family-office-open-digital-bank-bahrain-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114288/276177/international-ge7df2327c-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="209810"/></item><item><title>Lawmakers Reveal Differences on Stablecoin Bills in House Hearing — Will They Find Consensus?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lawmakers-reveal-differences-stablecoin-bills-house-hearing-will-they-find-consensus.htm</link><description>House Democrats and Republicans are seemingly divided on how to regulate stablecoins but are finding consensus that some form of legislation is needed. &lt;br /&gt;
House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick McHenry, R-N.C., and former chair of that committee Rep. Maxine Waters, D-Calif., worked together on a bill last year, but ahead of a hearing on Thursday, two stablecoin bills had emerged.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lawmakers-reveal-differences-stablecoin-bills-house-hearing-will-they-find-consensus.htm"&gt;Read More: Lawmakers Reveal Differences on Stablecoin Bills in House Hearing — Will They Find Consensus?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Regulation</category><category>House Financial Services</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lawmakers-reveal-differences-stablecoin-bills-house-hearing-will-they-find-consensus.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114310/276200/screen-shot-2023-05-18-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1204254"/></item><item><title>FATF President Calls on G-7 To Take the Lead To Regulate Crypto Ahead of Japan Summit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fatf-president-calls-on-g-7-to-take-the-lead-to-regulate-crypto-ahead-of-japan-summit.htm</link><description>The president of a global money laundering and terrorist financing watchdog is calling on the G-7 to put an end to “lawless spaces” and to take the lead to regulate cryptocurrencies. &lt;br /&gt;
Financial Action Task Force President Raja Kumar called on the finance ministers from some of the world’s seven most influential economies to implement recommendations from the FATF, which include going after money laundering and terrorism financing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fatf-president-calls-on-g-7-to-take-the-lead-to-regulate-crypto-ahead-of-japan-summit.htm"&gt;Read More: FATF President Calls on G-7 To Take the Lead To Regulate Crypto Ahead of Japan Summit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FATF</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fatf-president-calls-on-g-7-to-take-the-lead-to-regulate-crypto-ahead-of-japan-summit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114294/276181/adobestock-281047255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="199679"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Binance Faces Issues in Australia &amp; Joins Hands with TradingView, Ripple Reveals a CBDC Platform, Montenegro Prosecutors Appeal Do Kwon &amp; Han Chang-Joon's Bail Terms</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-faces-issues-in-australia-joins-hands-with-tradingview-ripple-reveals-a-cbdc-platform-montenegro-prosecutors-appeal-do-kwon-han-chang-joons-bail-terms.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-faces-issues-in-australia-joins-hands-with-tradingview-ripple-reveals-a-cbdc-platform-montenegro-prosecutors-appeal-do-kwon-han-chang-joons-bail-terms.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Binance Faces Issues in Australia &amp; Joins Hands with TradingView, Ripple Reveals a CBDC Platform, Montenegro Prosecutors Appeal Do Kwon &amp; Han Chang-Joon's Bail Terms&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Australia</category><category>Binance</category><category>Banking</category><category>Investing</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Payment</category><category>Ripple</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Montenegro</category><category>Terra</category><category>Wells Fargo</category><category>Legal</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>ChainLink</category><category>Do Kwon</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-faces-issues-in-australia-joins-hands-with-tradingview-ripple-reveals-a-cbdc-platform-montenegro-prosecutors-appeal-do-kwon-han-chang-joons-bail-terms.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114265/276161/adobestock-iryna-budanova-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="49519"/></item><item><title>Chinese State-Owned Greenland Eyes Hong Kong Virtual Asset Trading License</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-state-owned-greenland-eyes-hong-kong-virtual-asset-trading-license.htm</link><description>Chinese state-owned real estate firm Greenland Holdings has expressed interest in joining Hong Kong's digital assets hub. &lt;br /&gt;
A May 17 report by South China Morning Post (SCMP) revealed that Greenland is creating a new unit to acquire virtual assets trading licenses in Hong Kong. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm’s fintech unit already has a digital banking license in Singapore and “is ready to step into Hong Kong," James Gend Jing, Greenland Financial Technology Group, said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-state-owned-greenland-eyes-hong-kong-virtual-asset-trading-license.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese State-Owned Greenland Eyes Hong Kong Virtual Asset Trading License&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-state-owned-greenland-eyes-hong-kong-virtual-asset-trading-license.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114273/276153/pexels-burak-the-weekende.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99985"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Tokens Built on Dogecoin Blockchain Reach All-Time High – Can DOGE Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-tokens-built-on-dogecoin-blockchain-reach-all-time-high-can-doge-reach-1.htm</link><description>The price of Dogecoin (DOGE) has risen by 2% in the past 24 hours, rising to $0.074565 amid a similar gain for the cryptocurrency market as a whole. &lt;br /&gt;
DOGE's current price means that it has gained by 3.5% in the past week, with the meme token down by 20% in the last 30 days but up by 6% since the beginning of the year. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-tokens-built-on-dogecoin-blockchain-reach-all-time-high-can-doge-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as Tokens Built on Dogecoin Blockchain Reach All-Time High – Can DOGE Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-tokens-built-on-dogecoin-blockchain-reach-all-time-high-can-doge-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114257/276152/dogecoin-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1258334"/></item><item><title>LayerZero and Immunefi Announce Record $15 Million Crypto Bug Bounty Program</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/layerzero-immunefi-announce-record-15-million-crypto-bug-bounty-program.htm</link><description>LayerZero Labs, the development firm behind cross-chain messaging platform LayerZero, has announced a record-high $15 million bug bounty in partnership with the crypto-focused bug bounty platform Immunefi. &lt;br /&gt;
The huge bug bounty will be paid out to so-called white hat hackers who can identify vulnerabilities in the LayerZero protocol, TechCrunch reported on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/layerzero-immunefi-announce-record-15-million-crypto-bug-bounty-program.htm"&gt;Read More: LayerZero and Immunefi Announce Record $15 Million Crypto Bug Bounty Program&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>LayerZero</category><category>Immunefi</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/layerzero-immunefi-announce-record-15-million-crypto-bug-bounty-program.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114271/276151/adobestock-192869451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="567204"/></item><item><title>Crypto Bankruptcies Continue to Hit the Market – What's at Stake for Your Crypto?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-bankruptcies-continue-hit-market-whats-at-stake-for-crypto.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency industry has witnessed a concerning pattern of prominent platforms and institutions facing financial difficulties and collapsing. Voyager and Bittrex are the latest additions to this trend. &lt;br /&gt;
The series of bankruptcy filings has created uncertainty and losses for investors, raising questions about the long-term sustainability of the digital finance sphere and the regulatory environment surrounding it....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-bankruptcies-continue-hit-market-whats-at-stake-for-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Bankruptcies Continue to Hit the Market – What's at Stake for Your Crypto?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-bankruptcies-continue-hit-market-whats-at-stake-for-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114266/276146/voyager-and-bittrexrs-rec.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="310525"/></item><item><title>This Viral AI Memecoin’s Presale is Fast Selling Out With $9 Million Raised – The Next Dogecoin?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/viral-ai-memecoins-presale-fast-selling-out-with-9-million-raised-next-dogecoin.htm</link><description>Viral artificial intelligence (AI) meme coin AiDoge’s presale continues to sell out rapidly, with fundraising efforts recently scorching past the $9 million mark, despite the presale having only launched a few weeks ago. &lt;br /&gt;
AiDoge, which observers say sits at the intersection between the meme and artificial intelligence worlds thanks to its innovative AI-powered meme generation tool, has been raising funds at a pace of about $500,000 per day in the past two weeks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/viral-ai-memecoins-presale-fast-selling-out-with-9-million-raised-next-dogecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: This Viral AI Memecoin’s Presale is Fast Selling Out With $9 Million Raised – The Next Dogecoin?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/viral-ai-memecoins-presale-fast-selling-out-with-9-million-raised-next-dogecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114249/276117/unnamed-44.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1420540"/></item><item><title>Pakistan Finance Minister Says Country Will Never Legalize Crypto, Cites FATF Regulations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pakistan-finance-minister-says-country-will-never-legalize-crypto-cites-fatf-regulations.htm</link><description>Pakistan Finance Minister has said the country will not legalize crypto trading, citing regulations by the Financial Action Task Force (FATF). &lt;br /&gt;
On Wednesday, Pakistan Minister of State for Finance Aisha Ghaus said the government cannot permit crypto trading because of the country's recent exit from the FATF grey list. &lt;br /&gt;
“Permission to trade in cryptocurrency cannot be granted,” she stated during a session of the Senate Standing Committee on Finance and Revenue. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pakistan-finance-minister-says-country-will-never-legalize-crypto-cites-fatf-regulations.htm"&gt;Read More: Pakistan Finance Minister Says Country Will Never Legalize Crypto, Cites FATF Regulations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pakistan</category><category>Regulation</category><category>FATF</category><category>IMF</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pakistan-finance-minister-says-country-will-never-legalize-crypto-cites-fatf-regulations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114253/276120/pakistan-g5728faf47-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="475139"/></item><item><title>Crypto.com Expands Pay Service, Adds Support for MATIC, USDC, and DAI</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocom-expands-pay-service-adds-support-for-matic-usdc-dai.htm</link><description>Crypto.com, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, has revealed significant upgrades to its payment services, introducing new features and expanding the range of supported coins. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the exchange, this development aims to enhance users' experience, allowing them to purchase more cryptocurrencies with credit or debit cards. &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, Crypto.com integrated a DeFi Wallet into its Crypto.com Pay in January to allow users securely and seamlessly buy crypto with their fiat cards. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocom-expands-pay-service-adds-support-for-matic-usdc-dai.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto.com Expands Pay Service, Adds Support for MATIC, USDC, and DAI&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocom-expands-pay-service-adds-support-for-matic-usdc-dai.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114259/276166/screenshot-2023-05-18-194710.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="243301"/></item></channel></rss>
