<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 04:28:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi’s 7th PrimeVote finishes with MinePlex (XFI) Coming out on Top]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/huobis-7th-primevote-finishes-with-mineplex-xfi-coming-out-on-top</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Tokenization_1692129345ek3oWlc32N.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Tokenization_1692129345ek3oWlc32N.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Tokenization_1692129345ek3oWlc32N.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:59:33 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/huobis-7th-primevote-finishes-with-mineplex-xfi-coming-out-on-top</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Crypto Exchange Huobi announced that the 7th round of Huobi's PrimeVote event is finished. In this round, a total of 12 projects competed for the listing, accumulating 226,040,064 votes in the form of "Rockets". After two rounds of intense voting, MinePlex (XFI) emerged as the winner, garnering a total of 208,172,999 "Rockets". XFI will soon get listed on Huobi for trading.</p><p>In the final round of voting, XFI secured the win by amassing 208,172,999 "Rockets". XDAO secured the second position with 11,355,497 "Rockets" while AD and INS captured the third and fourth positions with 4,130,180 "Rockets" and 2,381,388 "Rockets" respectively. Huobi's official data reveals that participants casted a total of 226,040,064 "Rockets" with 5,176 individuals taking part. Notably, the "Rockets" used for voting witnessed a substantial 78% upswing compared to the previous round. Additionally, the 8th round of Huobi's PrimeVote event will carry on its worldwide search for outstanding projects by encouraging their participation in this vote-to-list event. The rules of the 8th PrimeVote will stay the same&nbsp; with "rockets" as the favored voting tool.</p><p>Vote for projects with "Rockets" and win limited edition NFTs</p><p>The "Rocket Plan" is Huobi's newest endeavor aimed at enriching user engagement and experience. Rockets refer to the USDT equivalent of your average assets on Huobi over a 30-day period. 1 USDT equals to 1 Rocket. The Rocket value represents an integer without decimal places.</p><p>The number of "Rockets" a user holds is determined by the balance of their assets. With an increased possession of "Rockets," users can wield more influence in the PrimeVote event, major platform decisions, new token airdrops, and other scenarios where "Rockets" come into play. This grants them a stronger voice and a larger share of rewards. To increase their Rocket values, users can improve their asset balances by making deposits and purchasing quality assets like BTC, ETH, HT, etc. Moreover, using "Rockets" to vote will not cause users' asset balance to be locked.</p><p>"Rockets" are users' tickets to take part in the PrimeVote events and also give participants a chance to mint limited edition NFTs in Huobi's Mars Program that offers $6 million worth of space travel.</p><p>Based on Huobi's official announcement, a total of 12 projects were shortlisted in the 7th round of the PrimeVote event. As of August 9 202313:00 (UTC), EML and XDAO emerged as top performers in Group A while XFI and AD took the lead in Group B. These projects have advanced to the final voting stage. Following two rounds of preliminary and final voting, MinePlex (XFI) has stood out as the favored pick among the community by winning the championship of this event with a notable 208,172,999 "Rockets". MinePlex (XFI) represents an innovative CrossFi initiative by integrating the stability and liquidity of traditional financial instruments with the security and transparency embedded in blockchain technology. To realize this vision, the team is crafting a distinct blockchain v1.0 featuring the LPoS consensus algorithm. The MinePlex 2.0 blockchain adopts the DPoS consensus protocol.</p><p>Huobi prioritize users and persistent crypto listings with community votes</p><p>Huobi remains committed to upholding the principle of impartial listing and respects the choices of all users. It aims to establish a digital asset trading platform that is compliant, secure, and transparent. It returns the listing right to community users by allowing them to decide which tokens can be traded on Huobi. Launching PrimeVote not only identifies the most popular tokens and ensures listing quality but also maximizes the transparency and fairness of the listing process.</p><p>To date, Huobi has successfully conducted seven rounds of the PrimeVote event by establishing a unique method for token listing. Looking ahead, Huobi will further refine event rules and introduce innovative features.</p><p></p><p>About Huobi&nbsp;</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p>Company Website</p><p>https://www.huobi.com</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Crypto Exchange Huobi announced that the 7th round of Huobi's PrimeVote event is finished. In this round, a total of 12 projects competed for the listing, accumulating 226,040,064 votes in the form of "Rockets". After two rounds of intense voting, MinePlex (XFI) emerged as the winner, garnering a total of 208,172,999 "Rockets". XFI will soon get listed on Huobi for trading.</p><p>In the final round of voting, XFI secured the win by amassing 208,172,999 "Rockets". XDAO secured the second position with 11,355,497 "Rockets" while AD and INS captured the third and fourth positions with 4,130,180 "Rockets" and 2,381,388 "Rockets" respectively. Huobi's official data reveals that participants casted a total of 226,040,064 "Rockets" with 5,176 individuals taking part. Notably, the "Rockets" used for voting witnessed a substantial 78% upswing compared to the previous round. Additionally, the 8th round of Huobi's PrimeVote event will carry on its worldwide search for outstanding projects by encouraging their participation in this vote-to-list event. The rules of the 8th PrimeVote will stay the same&nbsp; with "rockets" as the favored voting tool.</p><p>Vote for projects with "Rockets" and win limited edition NFTs</p><p>The "Rocket Plan" is Huobi's newest endeavor aimed at enriching user engagement and experience. Rockets refer to the USDT equivalent of your average assets on Huobi over a 30-day period. 1 USDT equals to 1 Rocket. The Rocket value represents an integer without decimal places.</p><p>The number of "Rockets" a user holds is determined by the balance of their assets. With an increased possession of "Rockets," users can wield more influence in the PrimeVote event, major platform decisions, new token airdrops, and other scenarios where "Rockets" come into play. This grants them a stronger voice and a larger share of rewards. To increase their Rocket values, users can improve their asset balances by making deposits and purchasing quality assets like BTC, ETH, HT, etc. Moreover, using "Rockets" to vote will not cause users' asset balance to be locked.</p><p>"Rockets" are users' tickets to take part in the PrimeVote events and also give participants a chance to mint limited edition NFTs in Huobi's Mars Program that offers $6 million worth of space travel.</p><p>Based on Huobi's official announcement, a total of 12 projects were shortlisted in the 7th round of the PrimeVote event. As of August 9 202313:00 (UTC), EML and XDAO emerged as top performers in Group A while XFI and AD took the lead in Group B. These projects have advanced to the final voting stage. Following two rounds of preliminary and final voting, MinePlex (XFI) has stood out as the favored pick among the community by winning the championship of this event with a notable 208,172,999 "Rockets". MinePlex (XFI) represents an innovative CrossFi initiative by integrating the stability and liquidity of traditional financial instruments with the security and transparency embedded in blockchain technology. To realize this vision, the team is crafting a distinct blockchain v1.0 featuring the LPoS consensus algorithm. The MinePlex 2.0 blockchain adopts the DPoS consensus protocol.</p><p>Huobi prioritize users and persistent crypto listings with community votes</p><p>Huobi remains committed to upholding the principle of impartial listing and respects the choices of all users. It aims to establish a digital asset trading platform that is compliant, secure, and transparent. It returns the listing right to community users by allowing them to decide which tokens can be traded on Huobi. Launching PrimeVote not only identifies the most popular tokens and ensures listing quality but also maximizes the transparency and fairness of the listing process.</p><p>To date, Huobi has successfully conducted seven rounds of the PrimeVote event by establishing a unique method for token listing. Looking ahead, Huobi will further refine event rules and introduce innovative features.</p><p></p><p>About Huobi&nbsp;</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p>Company Website</p><p>https://www.huobi.com</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Navigating the Best PR Agencies in the Blockchain Realm]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/navigating-the-best-pr-agencies-in-the-blockchain-realm</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-14.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-14.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-14.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 18:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/navigating-the-best-pr-agencies-in-the-blockchain-realm</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The enduring enigma around the inability of most contemporary crypto enterprises to surpass their competitors endures due to a fundamental overlook in understanding the importance of cryptocurrency marketing agencies. It is high time we acknowledged the crucial significance of crypto marketing agencies, whose function is essential in promoting innovation and engaging the intended audience.</p>
<p class="s5">Ensuring the dissemination of a project's narrative to the appropriate audience is of similar significance compared to creating a compelling whitepaper and roadmap. This means achieving success is contingent upon these fundamental principles: Building a project that solves a problem and comprehending the intricate mechanics of marketing.</p>
<p class="s5">To establish a connection between technological expertise and successful marketing strategies, companies need to understand cryptocurrency marketing agencies' significant contribution to every crypto project's success. In this article, we'd look at key crypto marketing firms that have proved reliable over the years in the crypto space.</p>
Crypto Marketing Agencies With Proven Track Records
IdolMe Agency
<p class="s5">Empowering tech and crypto companies since 2013, IdolMe Agency stands as an influential PR and marketing lab. The team's expertise unlocks early-stage project potential, propelling crypto businesses into market leaders. Also, their services encompass analytics, brand promotion, AMA sessions, and influence marketing across various social networks.</p>
<p class="s5">IdolMe Agency understands that tailored strategies for startups and corporations reflect a deep understanding of this fast-evolving industry. The team engages in unique content strategies that range from op-eds to social media posts, cultivating strong project communities. They also engage in vast influencer and media contacts that ensure features and releases resonate with clients' target audiences.</p>
Coinband
<p class="s5">Coinband is a leading marketing agency for Web3 &amp; Crypto &amp; NFT projects. The company has cutting-edge client-side expertise to create better solutions for their client's marketing challenges. Their client gets access to the best financial and crypto media and influencers. The team engages in best practices in content management and the web3 community to enable their clients to have a complete marketing solution.</p>
<p class="s5">Over the past year, the team has worked with projects such as ByBit, OKX, NEAR, ChainGPT, and LayerAI and ranked among the best crypto marketing companies. By working with Coinband, clients can access 400+ Crypto &amp; Finance media outlets and exclusive publishing opportunities.</p>
Blockfluence
<p class="s5">Blockfluence, accessible via blockfluence.io, is a premier agency specializing in crypto marketing and press services. Catering to the unique demands of the cryptocurrency world, they extend their expertise to crypto projects, ensuring they gain the visibility and traction they deserve.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, Blockfluence strongly emphasizes personal branding, recognizing the importance of positioning founders and thought leaders at the forefront of the crypto movement. With a blend of strategic marketing campaigns, impactful press releases, and bespoke branding solutions, Blockfluence is the trusted partner for crypto innovators seeking to establish a formidable presence in the competitive digital domain.</p>
CTRL-PR
<p class="s5">CTRL-PR gets your story out there. The firm is a PR Agency specializing in developing modern and innovative PR solutions for startup businesses worldwide. CTRL-PR offers success-based, convenient, and cost-effective media and PR services. CTRL-PR specializes in content marketing, press releases, editorial media placements, tech PR, crypto PR, success-based PR, and SEO.</p>
<p class="s5">With over 100+ effective marketing campaigns, the team assists companies in expanding their global presence by connecting them with influential media outlets and KOLs. They are passionate about creating a difference for clients and helping crypto, fintech, NFTs, and Blockchain ventures to establish strong audience relationships.&nbsp;</p>
FINPR Agency&nbsp;
<p class="s5">FINPR Agency is counted amongst the top Dubai-based crypto marketing firms, owing to its profoundly experienced team. Although located in the Middle East, FINPR covers the whole world, especially the United States, Europe, Asia Pacific, and (of course) MENA.</p>
<p class="s5">Projects and firms prefer FINPR Agency due to its ever-expanding range of services, including; Crypto PR, Influencer marketing, Crypto Advertising, Community management, Crypto SEO, Marketing strategy creation, Crypto exchange listings, and Crypto copywriting.</p>
Final Thoughts
<p class="s5">In the world of cryptocurrency, there's a puzzle we need help figuring out: why do so many new crypto businesses struggle to do better than their rivals? The answer might be that they're not paying enough attention to something important &ndash; companies that help promote cryptocurrencies; crypto marketing agencies.</p>
<p class="s5">It's time we realize how crucial these agencies are. They're like the people who tell others about a new story or idea. It's not enough to make something cool &ndash; you have to help people understand why it's cool, too. Success comes from knowing how the market works and being creative. Companies must connect their technical skills with marketing. That's where crypto marketing agencies come in. They're like friends who make sure everyone knows about the cool thing you made.</p>
<p class="s10">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The enduring enigma around the inability of most contemporary crypto enterprises to surpass their competitors endures due to a fundamental overlook in understanding the importance of cryptocurrency marketing agencies. It is high time we acknowledged the crucial significance of crypto marketing agencies, whose function is essential in promoting innovation and engaging the intended audience.</p>
<p class="s5">Ensuring the dissemination of a project's narrative to the appropriate audience is of similar significance compared to creating a compelling whitepaper and roadmap. This means achieving success is contingent upon these fundamental principles: Building a project that solves a problem and comprehending the intricate mechanics of marketing.</p>
<p class="s5">To establish a connection between technological expertise and successful marketing strategies, companies need to understand cryptocurrency marketing agencies' significant contribution to every crypto project's success. In this article, we'd look at key crypto marketing firms that have proved reliable over the years in the crypto space.</p>
Crypto Marketing Agencies With Proven Track Records
IdolMe Agency
<p class="s5">Empowering tech and crypto companies since 2013, IdolMe Agency stands as an influential PR and marketing lab. The team's expertise unlocks early-stage project potential, propelling crypto businesses into market leaders. Also, their services encompass analytics, brand promotion, AMA sessions, and influence marketing across various social networks.</p>
<p class="s5">IdolMe Agency understands that tailored strategies for startups and corporations reflect a deep understanding of this fast-evolving industry. The team engages in unique content strategies that range from op-eds to social media posts, cultivating strong project communities. They also engage in vast influencer and media contacts that ensure features and releases resonate with clients' target audiences.</p>
Coinband
<p class="s5">Coinband is a leading marketing agency for Web3 &amp; Crypto &amp; NFT projects. The company has cutting-edge client-side expertise to create better solutions for their client's marketing challenges. Their client gets access to the best financial and crypto media and influencers. The team engages in best practices in content management and the web3 community to enable their clients to have a complete marketing solution.</p>
<p class="s5">Over the past year, the team has worked with projects such as ByBit, OKX, NEAR, ChainGPT, and LayerAI and ranked among the best crypto marketing companies. By working with Coinband, clients can access 400+ Crypto &amp; Finance media outlets and exclusive publishing opportunities.</p>
Blockfluence
<p class="s5">Blockfluence, accessible via blockfluence.io, is a premier agency specializing in crypto marketing and press services. Catering to the unique demands of the cryptocurrency world, they extend their expertise to crypto projects, ensuring they gain the visibility and traction they deserve.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, Blockfluence strongly emphasizes personal branding, recognizing the importance of positioning founders and thought leaders at the forefront of the crypto movement. With a blend of strategic marketing campaigns, impactful press releases, and bespoke branding solutions, Blockfluence is the trusted partner for crypto innovators seeking to establish a formidable presence in the competitive digital domain.</p>
CTRL-PR
<p class="s5">CTRL-PR gets your story out there. The firm is a PR Agency specializing in developing modern and innovative PR solutions for startup businesses worldwide. CTRL-PR offers success-based, convenient, and cost-effective media and PR services. CTRL-PR specializes in content marketing, press releases, editorial media placements, tech PR, crypto PR, success-based PR, and SEO.</p>
<p class="s5">With over 100+ effective marketing campaigns, the team assists companies in expanding their global presence by connecting them with influential media outlets and KOLs. They are passionate about creating a difference for clients and helping crypto, fintech, NFTs, and Blockchain ventures to establish strong audience relationships.&nbsp;</p>
FINPR Agency&nbsp;
<p class="s5">FINPR Agency is counted amongst the top Dubai-based crypto marketing firms, owing to its profoundly experienced team. Although located in the Middle East, FINPR covers the whole world, especially the United States, Europe, Asia Pacific, and (of course) MENA.</p>
<p class="s5">Projects and firms prefer FINPR Agency due to its ever-expanding range of services, including; Crypto PR, Influencer marketing, Crypto Advertising, Community management, Crypto SEO, Marketing strategy creation, Crypto exchange listings, and Crypto copywriting.</p>
Final Thoughts
<p class="s5">In the world of cryptocurrency, there's a puzzle we need help figuring out: why do so many new crypto businesses struggle to do better than their rivals? The answer might be that they're not paying enough attention to something important &ndash; companies that help promote cryptocurrencies; crypto marketing agencies.</p>
<p class="s5">It's time we realize how crucial these agencies are. They're like the people who tell others about a new story or idea. It's not enough to make something cool &ndash; you have to help people understand why it's cool, too. Success comes from knowing how the market works and being creative. Companies must connect their technical skills with marketing. That's where crypto marketing agencies come in. They're like friends who make sure everyone knows about the cool thing you made.</p>
<p class="s10">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Enters Canada: Unlocking New Crypto Frontier]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/coinbase-enters-canada-unlocking-new-crypto-frontier</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/coinbase-enters-canada-unlocking-new-crypto-frontier</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has announced its official entry into the Canadian market in a strategic move that involved the integration of Interac payment rails.&nbsp;</p>
Expanding Horizons: Canada as a Crypto Hub
<p>On Monday, Coinbase executives Nana Murugesan and newly-appointed Lucas Matheson penned a joint announcement declaring Coinbase's decision to venture into Canada's crypto landscape.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The statement also addressed the various factors why Canada was chosen as the next Coinbase outpost, calling it the world's third-most crypto-aware nation, with a thriving local tech ecosystem that firmly positions it as a potential global leader in the crypto-economy. The duo pulled up the Ontario Securities Commission's survey highlights, which revealed that over 30% of Canadians are gearing up to explore crypto assets within the year.</p>
Pioneering Innovations for Canadians
<p>According to the statement, Coinbase will be presenting a slew of innovative offerings to cater to the Canadian market. The integration of Interac payment rails takes center stage as it would enable Canadian users to effortlessly deposit and withdraw funds (CAD) to and from their Coinbase wallets in an attempt to make the crypto experience more accessible to Canadians.</p>
<p>They also revealed the launch of Coinbase One, which is being touted to feature benefits like a 30-day trial period, zero trading fees, enhanced staking rewards, and priority support.&nbsp;</p>
Coinbase Appoints New Canada Director
<p>In March 2023, Coinbase appointed Lucas Matheson as the Country Director for Canada. Matheson, who has experience leading operation and financial teams, will be focusing on Coinbase&rsquo;s offerings for Canadians by working with partners, government, and regulators.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the regulatory front, the company has also signed an Enhanced Pre-Registration Undertaking in order to highlight its dedication to regulatory compliance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The firm has almost 200 full-time employees at the Canadian tech hub, thus making the most of local talent and fostering a user-centric platform tailored to Canadian citizens.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
Other Crypto Firms In Canada
<p>Other leading crypto firms have also turned to Canada, especially in the wake of growing regulatory uncertainty in the United States. Crypto exchange Kraken has demonstrated its commitment to Canada's financial sector by signing a pre-registration undertaking (PRU) with the Ontario Securities Commission.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, a few of them, like Binance and ByBit, have had to wrap up their Canada operations, citing an unfavorable regulatory climate in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In summary, Coinbase's official launch in Canada, backed by Interac payment integration, Coinbase One, and a strong commitment to local engagement, ushers in a new chapter in Canada's crypto journey. This move is a testament to Coinbase's unwavering dedication to fostering financial empowerment through innovative crypto solutions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has announced its official entry into the Canadian market in a strategic move that involved the integration of Interac payment rails.&nbsp;</p>
Expanding Horizons: Canada as a Crypto Hub
<p>On Monday, Coinbase executives Nana Murugesan and newly-appointed Lucas Matheson penned a joint announcement declaring Coinbase's decision to venture into Canada's crypto landscape.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The statement also addressed the various factors why Canada was chosen as the next Coinbase outpost, calling it the world's third-most crypto-aware nation, with a thriving local tech ecosystem that firmly positions it as a potential global leader in the crypto-economy. The duo pulled up the Ontario Securities Commission's survey highlights, which revealed that over 30% of Canadians are gearing up to explore crypto assets within the year.</p>
Pioneering Innovations for Canadians
<p>According to the statement, Coinbase will be presenting a slew of innovative offerings to cater to the Canadian market. The integration of Interac payment rails takes center stage as it would enable Canadian users to effortlessly deposit and withdraw funds (CAD) to and from their Coinbase wallets in an attempt to make the crypto experience more accessible to Canadians.</p>
<p>They also revealed the launch of Coinbase One, which is being touted to feature benefits like a 30-day trial period, zero trading fees, enhanced staking rewards, and priority support.&nbsp;</p>
Coinbase Appoints New Canada Director
<p>In March 2023, Coinbase appointed Lucas Matheson as the Country Director for Canada. Matheson, who has experience leading operation and financial teams, will be focusing on Coinbase&rsquo;s offerings for Canadians by working with partners, government, and regulators.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the regulatory front, the company has also signed an Enhanced Pre-Registration Undertaking in order to highlight its dedication to regulatory compliance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The firm has almost 200 full-time employees at the Canadian tech hub, thus making the most of local talent and fostering a user-centric platform tailored to Canadian citizens.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
Other Crypto Firms In Canada
<p>Other leading crypto firms have also turned to Canada, especially in the wake of growing regulatory uncertainty in the United States. Crypto exchange Kraken has demonstrated its commitment to Canada's financial sector by signing a pre-registration undertaking (PRU) with the Ontario Securities Commission.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, a few of them, like Binance and ByBit, have had to wrap up their Canada operations, citing an unfavorable regulatory climate in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In summary, Coinbase's official launch in Canada, backed by Interac payment integration, Coinbase One, and a strong commitment to local engagement, ushers in a new chapter in Canada's crypto journey. This move is a testament to Coinbase's unwavering dedication to fostering financial empowerment through innovative crypto solutions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Sideways After 29228 - 16 August 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-sideways-after-29228-16-august-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-sideways-after-29228-16-august-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Sideways After 29228 Bids:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) was more volatile early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 29369.12 level, representing the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29072.96 to 29665.27.&nbsp; &nbsp;After steadily climbing to the 29665 area and reversing lower, BTC/USD appreciated from the 29227.79 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the appreciating range from 28850 to 29462.90.&nbsp;&nbsp; Technical trading was recently evident when buying pressure strengthened around the 28754 area, a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure around the 29526 and 29344 areas.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 27991.29 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 15460 to 31862.21.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional areas of technical support and potential buying pressure in these appreciating ranges include the 27466, 27166, 26428, 26272, and 25715 areas.</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 28213, 28137, 27979, 27757, 27430, 27409, 27338, 27312, 27246, 26501, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29298.07 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29368.57.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Sideways After 29228 Bids:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) was more volatile early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 29369.12 level, representing the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29072.96 to 29665.27.&nbsp; &nbsp;After steadily climbing to the 29665 area and reversing lower, BTC/USD appreciated from the 29227.79 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the appreciating range from 28850 to 29462.90.&nbsp;&nbsp; Technical trading was recently evident when buying pressure strengthened around the 28754 area, a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure around the 29526 and 29344 areas.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 27991.29 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 15460 to 31862.21.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional areas of technical support and potential buying pressure in these appreciating ranges include the 27466, 27166, 26428, 26272, and 25715 areas.</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 28213, 28137, 27979, 27757, 27430, 27409, 27338, 27312, 27246, 26501, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29298.07 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29368.57.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Vs Solana? Analysts Choose Everlodge]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/polygon-matic-vs-solana-analysts-choose-everlodge</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-15-at-154230.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-15-at-154230.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-15-at-154230.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/polygon-matic-vs-solana-analysts-choose-everlodge</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon and Solana are two of DeFi&rsquo;s most popular altcoins. In 2023, both projects have grown their ecosystems, with Solana taking a slight lead over Polygon in terms of market cap. Now, however, a new cryptocurrency could outperform both.</p>
<p>Everlodge is a new DeFi project set to release in 2023. It has revolutionary utility and could offer returns of 280% during its presale. Here&rsquo;s why analysts are choosing Everlodge over Polygon and Solana.</p>
<p class="s6">Find Out How To Buy Everlodge (ELDG)</p>
Everlodge Brings Travel Properties To Web3 
<p>Everlodge is a DeFi property marketplace designed for luxury villas, vacation homes, and hotels. Its marketplace lets individuals buy, sell and invest in fractional real estate on the blockchain. To achieve this, a property is minted into an NFT and fractionalized.</p>
<p>For example, A $2 million luxury villa in Spain could be fractionalized into 20 fragments. Each can then be purchased or sold for $200,000, reducing the amount an investor needs for their investment.</p>
<p>Everlodge will also offer a launchpad designed for property developers. This launchpad will let developers raise capital from the Everlodge community to kick-start developments. Investors will then profit from getting involved in developments early to maximize their returns.</p>
<p>In addition to its launchpad and property marketplace, Everlodge will offer an exclusive rewards club. As part of the rewards club, investors will earn free nightly stays across properties throughout the Everlodge ecosystem. Several tiers will be available and will determine the properties and number of stays an individual gets. Members aren&rsquo;t obliged to use this timehowever. Instead, it can be sold on third-party platforms such as Airbnb to generate another income source.</p>
<p>Investors who co-own properties will be able to use their NFT as collateral to obtain other short term loans. This will give them access to more capital to quickly scale their property portfolio.</p>
<p>ELDG tokens will be used throughout the Everlodge ecosystem. They will grant holders a number of benefits such as staking bonuses, discounts on property and free stays at properties. Tokens will start at $0.01 when the Everlodge presale begins, and are expected to hit $0.035 before tokens are launched on mainstream exchanges.</p>
Experts Predict That Solana Will Pass $30 
<p>Solana&rsquo;s total value locked has consistently increased since the start of 2023. Over the last month, Solana&rsquo;s TVL has stayed above $1 billion. This indicates that confidence in Solana is starting to build following the project's crash in June.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Solana&rsquo;s value has also increased. In the last 30 days, Solana has increased in value by 22.44%. At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $23.59. Given its steady increase, experts believe that Solana will pass $30 in August.</p>
Confidence In Polygon Remains High Despite POL Proposal
<p>Polygon&rsquo;s price increases slowed over the last week after Polygon founders proposed an upgrade to Polygon's native token. This proposal has caused Polygon to decrease in value by 2.24%, andcreated confusion throughout the Polygon community.</p>
<p>The development team has proposed replacing MATIC tokens with POL. This new token would be used throughout the Polygon network, though investors are questioning why the upgrade needs to be made.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, confidence in Polygon continues to rise. PancakeSwap recently launched its v3 on the Polygon zkEVM Mainnet Beta, which is a huge win for the Polygon ecosystem.</p>
<p>Currently trading at $0.6897, analysts believe that Polygon will increase to $1 by the end of the year. Despite this increase, experts still predict that Everlodge will be a more profitable investment.</p>
<p class="s12">Find out more about the Everlodge (ELDG) Presale</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://www.everlodge.io/</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram: https://t.me/everlodge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon and Solana are two of DeFi&rsquo;s most popular altcoins. In 2023, both projects have grown their ecosystems, with Solana taking a slight lead over Polygon in terms of market cap. Now, however, a new cryptocurrency could outperform both.</p>
<p>Everlodge is a new DeFi project set to release in 2023. It has revolutionary utility and could offer returns of 280% during its presale. Here&rsquo;s why analysts are choosing Everlodge over Polygon and Solana.</p>
<p class="s6">Find Out How To Buy Everlodge (ELDG)</p>
Everlodge Brings Travel Properties To Web3 
<p>Everlodge is a DeFi property marketplace designed for luxury villas, vacation homes, and hotels. Its marketplace lets individuals buy, sell and invest in fractional real estate on the blockchain. To achieve this, a property is minted into an NFT and fractionalized.</p>
<p>For example, A $2 million luxury villa in Spain could be fractionalized into 20 fragments. Each can then be purchased or sold for $200,000, reducing the amount an investor needs for their investment.</p>
<p>Everlodge will also offer a launchpad designed for property developers. This launchpad will let developers raise capital from the Everlodge community to kick-start developments. Investors will then profit from getting involved in developments early to maximize their returns.</p>
<p>In addition to its launchpad and property marketplace, Everlodge will offer an exclusive rewards club. As part of the rewards club, investors will earn free nightly stays across properties throughout the Everlodge ecosystem. Several tiers will be available and will determine the properties and number of stays an individual gets. Members aren&rsquo;t obliged to use this timehowever. Instead, it can be sold on third-party platforms such as Airbnb to generate another income source.</p>
<p>Investors who co-own properties will be able to use their NFT as collateral to obtain other short term loans. This will give them access to more capital to quickly scale their property portfolio.</p>
<p>ELDG tokens will be used throughout the Everlodge ecosystem. They will grant holders a number of benefits such as staking bonuses, discounts on property and free stays at properties. Tokens will start at $0.01 when the Everlodge presale begins, and are expected to hit $0.035 before tokens are launched on mainstream exchanges.</p>
Experts Predict That Solana Will Pass $30 
<p>Solana&rsquo;s total value locked has consistently increased since the start of 2023. Over the last month, Solana&rsquo;s TVL has stayed above $1 billion. This indicates that confidence in Solana is starting to build following the project's crash in June.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Solana&rsquo;s value has also increased. In the last 30 days, Solana has increased in value by 22.44%. At the time of writing, SOL was trading at $23.59. Given its steady increase, experts believe that Solana will pass $30 in August.</p>
Confidence In Polygon Remains High Despite POL Proposal
<p>Polygon&rsquo;s price increases slowed over the last week after Polygon founders proposed an upgrade to Polygon's native token. This proposal has caused Polygon to decrease in value by 2.24%, andcreated confusion throughout the Polygon community.</p>
<p>The development team has proposed replacing MATIC tokens with POL. This new token would be used throughout the Polygon network, though investors are questioning why the upgrade needs to be made.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, confidence in Polygon continues to rise. PancakeSwap recently launched its v3 on the Polygon zkEVM Mainnet Beta, which is a huge win for the Polygon ecosystem.</p>
<p>Currently trading at $0.6897, analysts believe that Polygon will increase to $1 by the end of the year. Despite this increase, experts still predict that Everlodge will be a more profitable investment.</p>
<p class="s12">Find out more about the Everlodge (ELDG) Presale</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://www.everlodge.io/</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram: https://t.me/everlodge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[As Shiba Inu (SHIB) Dogecoin (DOGE) Waver, Pomerdoge (DOGE)'s Presale Becomes the New Memecoin Magnet]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/as-shiba-inu-shib-dogecoin-doge-waver-pomerdoge-doges-presale-becomes-the-new-memecoin-magnet</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-15-at-153655.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-15-at-153655.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-15-at-153655.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/as-shiba-inu-shib-dogecoin-doge-waver-pomerdoge-doges-presale-becomes-the-new-memecoin-magnet</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Amidst the wavering performance of well-known Memecoins such as Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE), Pomerdoge (POMD) emerges as a fresh attraction. Currently, in its presale phase, Pomerdoge is quickly becoming the new memeCoin magnet, demonstrating the unending appetite for new ventures in the dynamic cryptocurrency market. Let's take a closer look.</p>
<p>Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</p>
Pomerdoge (DOGE): Early Adopters and The Race to Buy POMD
<p class="s5">Pomerdoge is breaking new ground in the meme cryptocurrency arena, coupling the allure of meme culture with a dynamic play-to-earn gaming environment and a sound token structure. Although it bears some resemblance to Shiba Inu as an Ethereum-based meme coin, Pomerdoge's appeal lies in its unique offerings.</p>
<p class="s5">At the heart of Pomerdoge's distinctiveness is an integrated ecosystem, featuring an engaging P2E gaming platform and a bustling marketplace called Pomerplace. The gaming platform enables players from across the globe to compete and earn rewards, while Pomerplace provides a vibrant hub for trading in-game assets.</p>
<p class="s5">The driving force behind this multifaceted universe is the POMD token. Not just a means of exchange, POMD unlocks various rewards and special functionalities within the platform, which promotes user loyalty and sustainable growth for the project.</p>
<p class="s5">Financial pundits are forecasting an astonishing 5,000% surge in Pomerdoge's value come 2024. This is, in part, due to the current low price of $0.07 during the first phase of the presale.</p>
<p class="s5">By joining the presale, early adopters can cement their position in what promises to be an exciting new chapter in the world of meme cryptocurrencies. More than 100 million POMDtokens have already been purchased, and the number is increasing daily.</p>
Pitting Shiba Inu (SHIB)'s Limited Utility Against Pomerdoge(POMD)'s Offerings
<p class="s5">Shiba Inu burst onto the cryptocurrency scene with a bang as it tried to topple Dogecoin as the biggest meme coin. Shiba Inu has been a wild ride since then, with its value shooting up and crashing back down multiple times in the span of a few months.</p>
<p class="s5">Shiba Inu is now trading 88% below its all-time high at just $0.00001030. The euphoria and frenzy that once surrounded Shiba Inu seem to have dimmed, primarily because its intrinsic value appeared limited. Shiba Inu lacked a clear utility beyond being just a meme, rendering it no different from Dogecoin.</p>
<p class="s5">This is in stark contrast to Pomerdoge, which offers both a meme coin and an array of practical uses. As the Shiba Inu craze subsides, many investors are turning their attention towards Pomerdoge &mdash; a new and exciting project that offers investors the best of both worlds.</p>
Dogecoin (DOGE): Analyzing the Shift in Investor Interest
<p class="s5">The crypto realm is currently under a bearish spell, and Dogecoin is taking the brunt of it. Dogecoin is now a whopping 90% under its 2021 peak of $0.79, with a 2% decline in the last 24 hours alone.</p>
<p class="s5">Dogecoin may not tout cutting-edge technology, but it boasts a position within the top 20 coins on CoinMarketCap, largely thanks to its humorous origin and loyal following of supporters.</p>
<p class="s5">However, this lack of utility limits just how high Dogecoin can go. Analysts predict that Dogecon will continue to range in the tight trading window of $0.050 to $0.010 in the near term. It seems Dogecoin might have to wait in the wings for the next altcoin surge to steal the spotlight.</p>
<p class="s5">In comparison, Pomerdoge is now emerging as the new shining star within meme coins. As evidenced by the sale of 100 million tokens already, Pomerdoge is not affected by the current bearish market trends that have weighed down on Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.</p>
Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today
<p class="s13">Website: https://pomerdoge.com/</p>
<p class="s13">Telegram Community: https://t.me/pomerdoge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Amidst the wavering performance of well-known Memecoins such as Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE), Pomerdoge (POMD) emerges as a fresh attraction. Currently, in its presale phase, Pomerdoge is quickly becoming the new memeCoin magnet, demonstrating the unending appetite for new ventures in the dynamic cryptocurrency market. Let's take a closer look.</p>
<p>Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</p>
Pomerdoge (DOGE): Early Adopters and The Race to Buy POMD
<p class="s5">Pomerdoge is breaking new ground in the meme cryptocurrency arena, coupling the allure of meme culture with a dynamic play-to-earn gaming environment and a sound token structure. Although it bears some resemblance to Shiba Inu as an Ethereum-based meme coin, Pomerdoge's appeal lies in its unique offerings.</p>
<p class="s5">At the heart of Pomerdoge's distinctiveness is an integrated ecosystem, featuring an engaging P2E gaming platform and a bustling marketplace called Pomerplace. The gaming platform enables players from across the globe to compete and earn rewards, while Pomerplace provides a vibrant hub for trading in-game assets.</p>
<p class="s5">The driving force behind this multifaceted universe is the POMD token. Not just a means of exchange, POMD unlocks various rewards and special functionalities within the platform, which promotes user loyalty and sustainable growth for the project.</p>
<p class="s5">Financial pundits are forecasting an astonishing 5,000% surge in Pomerdoge's value come 2024. This is, in part, due to the current low price of $0.07 during the first phase of the presale.</p>
<p class="s5">By joining the presale, early adopters can cement their position in what promises to be an exciting new chapter in the world of meme cryptocurrencies. More than 100 million POMDtokens have already been purchased, and the number is increasing daily.</p>
Pitting Shiba Inu (SHIB)'s Limited Utility Against Pomerdoge(POMD)'s Offerings
<p class="s5">Shiba Inu burst onto the cryptocurrency scene with a bang as it tried to topple Dogecoin as the biggest meme coin. Shiba Inu has been a wild ride since then, with its value shooting up and crashing back down multiple times in the span of a few months.</p>
<p class="s5">Shiba Inu is now trading 88% below its all-time high at just $0.00001030. The euphoria and frenzy that once surrounded Shiba Inu seem to have dimmed, primarily because its intrinsic value appeared limited. Shiba Inu lacked a clear utility beyond being just a meme, rendering it no different from Dogecoin.</p>
<p class="s5">This is in stark contrast to Pomerdoge, which offers both a meme coin and an array of practical uses. As the Shiba Inu craze subsides, many investors are turning their attention towards Pomerdoge &mdash; a new and exciting project that offers investors the best of both worlds.</p>
Dogecoin (DOGE): Analyzing the Shift in Investor Interest
<p class="s5">The crypto realm is currently under a bearish spell, and Dogecoin is taking the brunt of it. Dogecoin is now a whopping 90% under its 2021 peak of $0.79, with a 2% decline in the last 24 hours alone.</p>
<p class="s5">Dogecoin may not tout cutting-edge technology, but it boasts a position within the top 20 coins on CoinMarketCap, largely thanks to its humorous origin and loyal following of supporters.</p>
<p class="s5">However, this lack of utility limits just how high Dogecoin can go. Analysts predict that Dogecon will continue to range in the tight trading window of $0.050 to $0.010 in the near term. It seems Dogecoin might have to wait in the wings for the next altcoin surge to steal the spotlight.</p>
<p class="s5">In comparison, Pomerdoge is now emerging as the new shining star within meme coins. As evidenced by the sale of 100 million tokens already, Pomerdoge is not affected by the current bearish market trends that have weighed down on Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.</p>
Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today
<p class="s13">Website: https://pomerdoge.com/</p>
<p class="s13">Telegram Community: https://t.me/pomerdoge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SBF Charged With Using Stolen Funds For Political Donations]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sbf-charged-with-using-stolen-funds-for-political-donations</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-rugpull-link-h-compressed.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-rugpull-link-h-compressed.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-rugpull-link-h-compressed.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sbf-charged-with-using-stolen-funds-for-political-donations</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried is in the news once again after a recent development revealed that he had allegedly used stolen customer funds to donate over $100 million to political campaigns.&nbsp;</p>
FTX Founder's Troubles Deepen
<p>Federal prosecutors have filed a fresh indictment against Bankman-Fried, charging him with seven counts of conspiracy and fraud related to the collapse of his crypto exchange. According to the indictment, Bankman-Fried contributed over $100 million of funds stolen from customer accounts on the FTX exchange to donate to political campaigns in the run-up to the 2022 U.S. midterm elections to influence softer crypto legislations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The former CEO of the defunct crypto exchange is already under legal scrutiny over charges of pilfering billions in FTX customer funds to offset losses at Alameda Research, his crypto-focused hedge fund.&nbsp;</p>
Political Leanings And Opaque Donations
<p>The 31-year-old entrepreneur, who previously pleaded not guilty to the initial charges, is now confronted with new allegations that he misappropriated customer funds for political donations.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried reportedly made substantial political donations in 2022, with a CBS News analysis suggesting the figure exceeded $40 million. Although the majority of these contributions were made to Democratic candidates and causes, he stated that Bankman-Fried had also supported Republicans through undisclosed "dark" donations.</p>
Lobbying Efforts And Hidden Agendas
<p>The indictment highlights Bankman-Fried's alleged use of FTX's influence and connections to push for cryptocurrency-friendly regulations. He purportedly directed fellow FTX executives to make donations aimed at circumventing contribution limits, with the goal of supporting legislation that would enable FTX to continue accepting customer deposits and growing its operations.</p>
<p>The indictment claims that Bankman-Fried orchestrated the donations in a covert manner, transferring funds from FTX's sister trading firm, Alameda, to the personal bank accounts of FTX executives. These executives would then make donations under their own names, evading restrictions on certain political contributions and enhancing FTX's political clout.</p>
Legal Maneuvering And Upcoming Trial
<p>While prosecutors initially charged Bankman-Fried with violating U.S. campaign finance laws, they later dropped this charge in light of the Bahamas' refusal to extradite him on that basis. Despite this setback, prosecutors have indicated their intention to file a new indictment that would clarify the allegations of an illegal campaign finance scheme as part of the broader fraud and money laundering charges.</p>
<p>U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan ordered Bankman-Fried's incarceration prior to his scheduled trial on October 2. The decision was made based on probable cause to believe that he tampered with witnesses on two occasions. Previously confined to his parents' home in Palo Alto, California, on a $250 million bond, Bankman-Fried now faces a more restrictive situation in the lead-up to his trial.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried is in the news once again after a recent development revealed that he had allegedly used stolen customer funds to donate over $100 million to political campaigns.&nbsp;</p>
FTX Founder's Troubles Deepen
<p>Federal prosecutors have filed a fresh indictment against Bankman-Fried, charging him with seven counts of conspiracy and fraud related to the collapse of his crypto exchange. According to the indictment, Bankman-Fried contributed over $100 million of funds stolen from customer accounts on the FTX exchange to donate to political campaigns in the run-up to the 2022 U.S. midterm elections to influence softer crypto legislations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The former CEO of the defunct crypto exchange is already under legal scrutiny over charges of pilfering billions in FTX customer funds to offset losses at Alameda Research, his crypto-focused hedge fund.&nbsp;</p>
Political Leanings And Opaque Donations
<p>The 31-year-old entrepreneur, who previously pleaded not guilty to the initial charges, is now confronted with new allegations that he misappropriated customer funds for political donations.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried reportedly made substantial political donations in 2022, with a CBS News analysis suggesting the figure exceeded $40 million. Although the majority of these contributions were made to Democratic candidates and causes, he stated that Bankman-Fried had also supported Republicans through undisclosed "dark" donations.</p>
Lobbying Efforts And Hidden Agendas
<p>The indictment highlights Bankman-Fried's alleged use of FTX's influence and connections to push for cryptocurrency-friendly regulations. He purportedly directed fellow FTX executives to make donations aimed at circumventing contribution limits, with the goal of supporting legislation that would enable FTX to continue accepting customer deposits and growing its operations.</p>
<p>The indictment claims that Bankman-Fried orchestrated the donations in a covert manner, transferring funds from FTX's sister trading firm, Alameda, to the personal bank accounts of FTX executives. These executives would then make donations under their own names, evading restrictions on certain political contributions and enhancing FTX's political clout.</p>
Legal Maneuvering And Upcoming Trial
<p>While prosecutors initially charged Bankman-Fried with violating U.S. campaign finance laws, they later dropped this charge in light of the Bahamas' refusal to extradite him on that basis. Despite this setback, prosecutors have indicated their intention to file a new indictment that would clarify the allegations of an illegal campaign finance scheme as part of the broader fraud and money laundering charges.</p>
<p>U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan ordered Bankman-Fried's incarceration prior to his scheduled trial on October 2. The decision was made based on probable cause to believe that he tampered with witnesses on two occasions. Previously confined to his parents' home in Palo Alto, California, on a $250 million bond, Bankman-Fried now faces a more restrictive situation in the lead-up to his trial.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Prime Trust Files for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/prime-trust-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/prime-trust-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/prime-trust-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/prime-trust-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/prime-trust-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency custodian Prime Trust and some affiliates filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy on Monday. </p>
<p>Las Vegas-based cryptocurrency custodian Prime Trust filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy earlier this week after Nevada regulators placed it into receivership in June.</p>
Prime Trust Records Significant Deficit on Its Books
<p>Nevada&rsquo;s Financial Institutions Division (NFID) placed crypto custodian Prime Trust into receivership, took control of the business, and froze its operations and businesses. Regulators decided to step in after it determined the company was insolvent and could not serve its customers.</p>
<p>Prime Trust said in a filing that it has between 25,000 to 50,000 creditors and estimates its liabilities to be between $100 million and $500 million. The firm added its assets are worth $50 million to $100 million.</p>
<p>The Chapter 11 filing indicates John Guedry, the former president of the Bank of Nevada, will act as a receiver and lead the restructuring committee. Judge Susan Johnson of the Eighth Judicial Court of the State of Nevada will oversee the bankruptcy proceedings. Prime Trust will continue in their role as &ldquo;debtors-in-possession&rdquo; under the court&rsquo;s jurisdiction.</p>
<p>In a press release announcing its bankruptcy, Prime Trust said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Company, under the supervision and direction of the Special Committee, continues to manage their businesses as &ldquo;debtors-in-possession&rdquo; under the jurisdiction of the Bankruptcy Court and in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Bankruptcy Code and orders of the Bankruptcy Court.&rdquo;</p>

<p>It added,</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Company intends to file a number of motions with the Bankruptcy Court designed to facilitate the Company&rsquo;s orderly evaluation of all strategic alternatives, including potentially a sale of the Company&rsquo;s assets and operations as a going concern.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Regulators claim Prime Trust misused customer funds to pay withdrawals since December 2021 after the firm lost access to several customer crypto wallets.</p>
<p>Prime&rsquo;s voluntary bankruptcy filing comes as no surprise. In a press statement, the NFID commented on its decision to place the firm under receivership:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Nevada Financial Institutions Division (&ldquo;NFID&rdquo;) was actively monitoring the solvency of Prime Trust, LLC (&ldquo;Prime&rdquo;) in anticipation of a potential acquisition or merger.&nbsp;Ultimately, Prime failed to safeguard assets under its custody and cannot meet all client withdrawals. As such, Prime has breached its fiduciary duties to its clients, in violation of Nevada trust laws. NFID&rsquo;s primary objective is to preserve any enterprise value remaining in Prime for the benefit of Prime&rsquo;s clients.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Several of the company&rsquo;s affiliates, including Prime Core Technologies Inc., Prime Trust, LLC, Prime IRA LLC and Prime Digital LLC, also filed for bankruptcy relief.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency custodian Prime Trust and some affiliates filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy on Monday. </p>
<p>Las Vegas-based cryptocurrency custodian Prime Trust filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy earlier this week after Nevada regulators placed it into receivership in June.</p>
Prime Trust Records Significant Deficit on Its Books
<p>Nevada&rsquo;s Financial Institutions Division (NFID) placed crypto custodian Prime Trust into receivership, took control of the business, and froze its operations and businesses. Regulators decided to step in after it determined the company was insolvent and could not serve its customers.</p>
<p>Prime Trust said in a filing that it has between 25,000 to 50,000 creditors and estimates its liabilities to be between $100 million and $500 million. The firm added its assets are worth $50 million to $100 million.</p>
<p>The Chapter 11 filing indicates John Guedry, the former president of the Bank of Nevada, will act as a receiver and lead the restructuring committee. Judge Susan Johnson of the Eighth Judicial Court of the State of Nevada will oversee the bankruptcy proceedings. Prime Trust will continue in their role as &ldquo;debtors-in-possession&rdquo; under the court&rsquo;s jurisdiction.</p>
<p>In a press release announcing its bankruptcy, Prime Trust said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Company, under the supervision and direction of the Special Committee, continues to manage their businesses as &ldquo;debtors-in-possession&rdquo; under the jurisdiction of the Bankruptcy Court and in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Bankruptcy Code and orders of the Bankruptcy Court.&rdquo;</p>

<p>It added,</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Company intends to file a number of motions with the Bankruptcy Court designed to facilitate the Company&rsquo;s orderly evaluation of all strategic alternatives, including potentially a sale of the Company&rsquo;s assets and operations as a going concern.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Regulators claim Prime Trust misused customer funds to pay withdrawals since December 2021 after the firm lost access to several customer crypto wallets.</p>
<p>Prime&rsquo;s voluntary bankruptcy filing comes as no surprise. In a press statement, the NFID commented on its decision to place the firm under receivership:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Nevada Financial Institutions Division (&ldquo;NFID&rdquo;) was actively monitoring the solvency of Prime Trust, LLC (&ldquo;Prime&rdquo;) in anticipation of a potential acquisition or merger.&nbsp;Ultimately, Prime failed to safeguard assets under its custody and cannot meet all client withdrawals. As such, Prime has breached its fiduciary duties to its clients, in violation of Nevada trust laws. NFID&rsquo;s primary objective is to preserve any enterprise value remaining in Prime for the benefit of Prime&rsquo;s clients.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Several of the company&rsquo;s affiliates, including Prime Core Technologies Inc., Prime Trust, LLC, Prime IRA LLC and Prime Digital LLC, also filed for bankruptcy relief.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Singapore Releases Revised Regulatory Framework For Stablecoins]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/singapore-releases-revised-regulatory-framework-for-stablecoins</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/singapore-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/singapore-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/singapore-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/singapore-releases-revised-regulatory-framework-for-stablecoins</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore&rsquo;s central bank has announced the release of a revised regulatory framework to ensure stability for single-currency stablecoins regulated in the city-state.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The framework outlines requirements that issuers need to meet to be deemed as regulated by the monetary authority of Singapore.&nbsp;</p>
Better Regulatory Clarity&nbsp;
<p>The revised framework was announced on the 15th of August and is primarily aimed at non-bank issued stablecoins that are pegged to the value of the Singapore Dollar, or G10 currencies, including the British Pound, Euro, and the United States Dollar, and whose circulation is greater than 5 million Singapore Dollars. The Monetary Authority of Singapore stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Stablecoins are digital payment tokens designed to maintain a constant value against one or more specified fiat currencies. When well-regulated to preserve such value stability, stablecoins can serve as a trusted medium of exchange to support innovation, including the &ldquo;on-chain&rdquo; purchase and sale of digital assets. MAS&rsquo; stablecoin regulatory framework will apply to single-currency stablecoins (SCS) pegged to the Singapore Dollar or any G10 currency that is issued in Singapore.&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to the Singapore central bank&rsquo;s financial supervision deputy managing director, Ho Hern Shin, the framework helps to establish and facilitate stablecoin use as a credible digital medium of exchange and a bridge between the traditional and digital currency ecosystems. Shin also urged stablecoin issuers to prepare for compliance if they wished for their stablecoin to be labeled as regulated by the Monetary Authority of Singapore.&nbsp;</p>
Details Of The Framework&nbsp;
<p>The revised regulatory framework lists several requirements for stablecoin issuers. These include redemption timelines, reserve management, disclosures, and capital requirements. According to the MAS, reserve assets will be subject to requirements depending on their valuation, composition, custody, and audit. Stablecoin issuers will also have to maintain a minimum base capital and liquid assets to stave off any risk of insolvency. Stablecoin issuers will also be required to return the par value of the stablecoins to holders within five business days following a redemption request.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore also observed that only those issuers who could fulfill the revised requirements could apply to be regulated by the MAS. According to the country&rsquo;s central bank, this label would help distinguish regulated stablecoins from non-regulated ones in the market. It also warned that those representing a token or stablecoin to be certified by the Monetary Authority of Singapore would also be subject to penalties defined in the new framework. The penalties include prison time, fines, as well as the addition on an alert list.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Penny Chai, VP of Business Development for Sumsub in APAC, reiterates the importance of crypto businesses prioritizing AML compliance processes:</p>
<p>"Singapore's aim to establish comprehensive regulations for stablecoins is a significant step towards fostering a secure and transparent digital currency environment - the move sets a noteworthy example for other jurisdictions. Stablecoins have surpassed $100 billion in market value, according to&nbsp;recent reports, therefore the need for regulatory clarity is paramount as the market continues to grow.Failing to adhere to this regulation could potentially result in fraudulent activities due to the inability to identify suspicious users, leading to financial penalties and substantial reputational harm for cryptocurrency businesses operating in Singapore and broader markets, APAC and further beyond. Companies must prioritise establishing crypto transaction monitoring tools and comprehensive AML compliance and verification procedures, both during the onboarding process and beyond."</p>
Attempts At Regulating Stablecoins
<p>The revised framework takes into account feedback from a public consultation held in October 2022. However, the MAS will still need to hold consultations, while parliament would need to pass amendments to enforce the revised framework. The MAS highlighted the risks involved in investing in crypto last year following the collapse of the TerraUSD (UST) and Luna tokens. The United States is also looking to pass regulations regarding stablecoins. The United States House Financial Services Committee had recently proposed a bill that would establish a federal regulatory framework.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The bill proposes that the United States Federal Reserve draw up requirements for the issuance of stablecoins while maintaining the authority of state regulators. The bill was modified after several democrats raised concerns that stablecoin issuers could simply bypass stricter federal oversight by opting to be regulated by state regulatory authorities.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore&rsquo;s central bank has announced the release of a revised regulatory framework to ensure stability for single-currency stablecoins regulated in the city-state.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The framework outlines requirements that issuers need to meet to be deemed as regulated by the monetary authority of Singapore.&nbsp;</p>
Better Regulatory Clarity&nbsp;
<p>The revised framework was announced on the 15th of August and is primarily aimed at non-bank issued stablecoins that are pegged to the value of the Singapore Dollar, or G10 currencies, including the British Pound, Euro, and the United States Dollar, and whose circulation is greater than 5 million Singapore Dollars. The Monetary Authority of Singapore stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Stablecoins are digital payment tokens designed to maintain a constant value against one or more specified fiat currencies. When well-regulated to preserve such value stability, stablecoins can serve as a trusted medium of exchange to support innovation, including the &ldquo;on-chain&rdquo; purchase and sale of digital assets. MAS&rsquo; stablecoin regulatory framework will apply to single-currency stablecoins (SCS) pegged to the Singapore Dollar or any G10 currency that is issued in Singapore.&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to the Singapore central bank&rsquo;s financial supervision deputy managing director, Ho Hern Shin, the framework helps to establish and facilitate stablecoin use as a credible digital medium of exchange and a bridge between the traditional and digital currency ecosystems. Shin also urged stablecoin issuers to prepare for compliance if they wished for their stablecoin to be labeled as regulated by the Monetary Authority of Singapore.&nbsp;</p>
Details Of The Framework&nbsp;
<p>The revised regulatory framework lists several requirements for stablecoin issuers. These include redemption timelines, reserve management, disclosures, and capital requirements. According to the MAS, reserve assets will be subject to requirements depending on their valuation, composition, custody, and audit. Stablecoin issuers will also have to maintain a minimum base capital and liquid assets to stave off any risk of insolvency. Stablecoin issuers will also be required to return the par value of the stablecoins to holders within five business days following a redemption request.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore also observed that only those issuers who could fulfill the revised requirements could apply to be regulated by the MAS. According to the country&rsquo;s central bank, this label would help distinguish regulated stablecoins from non-regulated ones in the market. It also warned that those representing a token or stablecoin to be certified by the Monetary Authority of Singapore would also be subject to penalties defined in the new framework. The penalties include prison time, fines, as well as the addition on an alert list.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Penny Chai, VP of Business Development for Sumsub in APAC, reiterates the importance of crypto businesses prioritizing AML compliance processes:</p>
<p>"Singapore's aim to establish comprehensive regulations for stablecoins is a significant step towards fostering a secure and transparent digital currency environment - the move sets a noteworthy example for other jurisdictions. Stablecoins have surpassed $100 billion in market value, according to&nbsp;recent reports, therefore the need for regulatory clarity is paramount as the market continues to grow.Failing to adhere to this regulation could potentially result in fraudulent activities due to the inability to identify suspicious users, leading to financial penalties and substantial reputational harm for cryptocurrency businesses operating in Singapore and broader markets, APAC and further beyond. Companies must prioritise establishing crypto transaction monitoring tools and comprehensive AML compliance and verification procedures, both during the onboarding process and beyond."</p>
Attempts At Regulating Stablecoins
<p>The revised framework takes into account feedback from a public consultation held in October 2022. However, the MAS will still need to hold consultations, while parliament would need to pass amendments to enforce the revised framework. The MAS highlighted the risks involved in investing in crypto last year following the collapse of the TerraUSD (UST) and Luna tokens. The United States is also looking to pass regulations regarding stablecoins. The United States House Financial Services Committee had recently proposed a bill that would establish a federal regulatory framework.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The bill proposes that the United States Federal Reserve draw up requirements for the issuance of stablecoins while maintaining the authority of state regulators. The bill was modified after several democrats raised concerns that stablecoin issuers could simply bypass stricter federal oversight by opting to be regulated by state regulatory authorities.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celsius Sends Bankruptcy Plan for Creditor Approval]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/celsius-sends-bankruptcy-plan-for-creditor-approval</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cel-4.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cel-4.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cel-4.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/celsius-sends-bankruptcy-plan-for-creditor-approval</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius received permission to seek creditor approval for its proposed bankruptcy plan. </p>
<p>According to reports by Bloomberg and Reuters, bankrupt cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network was granted permission by a US bankruptcy judge to send its proposed bankruptcy plan to its creditors. Celsius&rsquo; proposed strategy will see it exit Chapter 11 bankruptcy as an entity its creditors own.</p>
Creditors Have Sufficient Information to Vote on Bankruptcy Plan
<p>On Monday, during a US Bankruptcy Court hearing in Manhattan, Judge Martin Glenn approved Celsius&rsquo;s disclosure agreement and solicitation material, noting the firm had provided creditors with enough information to vote on its bankruptcy proposal.</p>
<p>Celsius filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in 2022, leaving customers with uncertainty over the outcome of their funds. The firm reached two settlements in July which will allow the lender to exit bankruptcy proceedings and return customer assets. In addition to its proposed bankruptcy plan, a confirmation hearing is scheduled for October to deal with Celsius&rsquo; reorganization plan. If all goes well, customers may see disbursements of their assets before the end of the year.</p>
<p>When Celsius filed for bankruptcy, it had 600,000 customers who invested around $4.4 billion in interest-bearing Celsius accounts.</p>
Fahrenheit Group to Take Control of Remaining Business Lines
<p>Under Celsius&rsquo; bankruptcy plan, retail customers will receive some crypto deposits, and the Fahrenheit Group will take over the lender remaining business line, including bitcoin mining and staking. The Fahrenheit consortium recently won the bid to acquire Celsius.</p>
<p>The lender suggests that most of its customers with interest-bearing Earn accounts will receive a 67% recovery. The recovery will consist of the return of liquid crypto assets such as Bitcoin and Ether, equity shares in the new entity, and proceeds from the litigation against Celsius&rsquo; founder Alex Mashinsky and other executives.</p>
<p>Mashinsky was arrested and sued by US regulators and charged with seven counts of securities, commodities, and wire fraud, as well as a conspiracy charge to manipulate the lender&rsquo;s native token, $CEL.</p>
<p>During an appearance in federal court, Mashinsky pleaded not guilty to the charges against him.</p>
<p>The lender&rsquo;s creditors have until September 20 to submit votes on the proposal.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius received permission to seek creditor approval for its proposed bankruptcy plan. </p>
<p>According to reports by Bloomberg and Reuters, bankrupt cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network was granted permission by a US bankruptcy judge to send its proposed bankruptcy plan to its creditors. Celsius&rsquo; proposed strategy will see it exit Chapter 11 bankruptcy as an entity its creditors own.</p>
Creditors Have Sufficient Information to Vote on Bankruptcy Plan
<p>On Monday, during a US Bankruptcy Court hearing in Manhattan, Judge Martin Glenn approved Celsius&rsquo;s disclosure agreement and solicitation material, noting the firm had provided creditors with enough information to vote on its bankruptcy proposal.</p>
<p>Celsius filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in 2022, leaving customers with uncertainty over the outcome of their funds. The firm reached two settlements in July which will allow the lender to exit bankruptcy proceedings and return customer assets. In addition to its proposed bankruptcy plan, a confirmation hearing is scheduled for October to deal with Celsius&rsquo; reorganization plan. If all goes well, customers may see disbursements of their assets before the end of the year.</p>
<p>When Celsius filed for bankruptcy, it had 600,000 customers who invested around $4.4 billion in interest-bearing Celsius accounts.</p>
Fahrenheit Group to Take Control of Remaining Business Lines
<p>Under Celsius&rsquo; bankruptcy plan, retail customers will receive some crypto deposits, and the Fahrenheit Group will take over the lender remaining business line, including bitcoin mining and staking. The Fahrenheit consortium recently won the bid to acquire Celsius.</p>
<p>The lender suggests that most of its customers with interest-bearing Earn accounts will receive a 67% recovery. The recovery will consist of the return of liquid crypto assets such as Bitcoin and Ether, equity shares in the new entity, and proceeds from the litigation against Celsius&rsquo; founder Alex Mashinsky and other executives.</p>
<p>Mashinsky was arrested and sued by US regulators and charged with seven counts of securities, commodities, and wire fraud, as well as a conspiracy charge to manipulate the lender&rsquo;s native token, $CEL.</p>
<p>During an appearance in federal court, Mashinsky pleaded not guilty to the charges against him.</p>
<p>The lender&rsquo;s creditors have until September 20 to submit votes on the proposal.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Takes Action Against UK Company Over Audit]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-takes-action-against-uk-company-over-audit</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-takes-action-against-uk-company-over-audit</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC has taken decisive action against Crowe U.K. LLP, a pro-crypto London-based audit firm over the auditing of music streaming service Akazoo.</p>
<p>The firm's CEO, Nigel Bostock, and senior auditor, Matthew Stallabrass, who advocate for wider crypto adoption, have also been implicated for their roles in a flawed audit of the music streaming entity, Akazoo Limited. All parties involved have opted for a settlement with the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
Akazoo revenue overstated
<p>Diving into the details, the SEC's findings reveal that Crowe U.K. had given Akazoo's 2018 financial statements a clean bill of health. However, post Akazoo's public debut in 2019 through a merger with a special purpose acquisition entity, discrepancies emerged.</p>
<p>Akazoo's 2018 financial records boasted a whopping $120 million in revenue, a figure that was later debunked, revealing only trivial revenue figures. The SEC's probe highlighted that Crowe U.K.'s audit team lacked the requisite experience and training in Public Company Accounting Oversight Board (PCAOB) standards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The oversight became evident when the team missed glaring warning signs, such as accepting fabricated agreements and dubious confirmation letters from Akazoo without the necessary scrutiny.&nbsp;</p>
Failings and penalties
<p>The SEC's findings also spotlighted the roles of Bostock and Stallabrass. Bostock, as the lead for the Akazoo audit, was found lacking in his supervisory duties, documentation, and professional care. On the other hand, Stallabrass, responsible for reviewing the audit's quality, failed to conduct a comprehensive review.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Eric Werner, the Regional Director of the Fort Worth Regional Office, commented on the situation, emphasising the role of Crowe U.K. in lending an unwarranted legitimacy to Akazoo, facilitating its entry into the public trading arena. He stressed the SEC's commitment to holding such gatekeepers accountable to prevent financial deceptions from infiltrating public markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the settlement, without admitting to any wrongdoing, Crowe U.K., Bostock, and Stallabrass have agreed to pay penalties amounting to $750,000, $25,000, and $10,000, respectively. They've also committed to refraining from any future violations related to the Exchange Act and Regulation S-X. Additionally, Crowe U.K. will voluntarily withdraw its PCAOB registration and introduce measures concerning new client acquisitions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Both Bostock and Stallabrass face suspensions from practising before the SEC as accountants, with potential reinstatements after five and two years, respectively.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC has taken decisive action against Crowe U.K. LLP, a pro-crypto London-based audit firm over the auditing of music streaming service Akazoo.</p>
<p>The firm's CEO, Nigel Bostock, and senior auditor, Matthew Stallabrass, who advocate for wider crypto adoption, have also been implicated for their roles in a flawed audit of the music streaming entity, Akazoo Limited. All parties involved have opted for a settlement with the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
Akazoo revenue overstated
<p>Diving into the details, the SEC's findings reveal that Crowe U.K. had given Akazoo's 2018 financial statements a clean bill of health. However, post Akazoo's public debut in 2019 through a merger with a special purpose acquisition entity, discrepancies emerged.</p>
<p>Akazoo's 2018 financial records boasted a whopping $120 million in revenue, a figure that was later debunked, revealing only trivial revenue figures. The SEC's probe highlighted that Crowe U.K.'s audit team lacked the requisite experience and training in Public Company Accounting Oversight Board (PCAOB) standards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The oversight became evident when the team missed glaring warning signs, such as accepting fabricated agreements and dubious confirmation letters from Akazoo without the necessary scrutiny.&nbsp;</p>
Failings and penalties
<p>The SEC's findings also spotlighted the roles of Bostock and Stallabrass. Bostock, as the lead for the Akazoo audit, was found lacking in his supervisory duties, documentation, and professional care. On the other hand, Stallabrass, responsible for reviewing the audit's quality, failed to conduct a comprehensive review.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Eric Werner, the Regional Director of the Fort Worth Regional Office, commented on the situation, emphasising the role of Crowe U.K. in lending an unwarranted legitimacy to Akazoo, facilitating its entry into the public trading arena. He stressed the SEC's commitment to holding such gatekeepers accountable to prevent financial deceptions from infiltrating public markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the settlement, without admitting to any wrongdoing, Crowe U.K., Bostock, and Stallabrass have agreed to pay penalties amounting to $750,000, $25,000, and $10,000, respectively. They've also committed to refraining from any future violations related to the Exchange Act and Regulation S-X. Additionally, Crowe U.K. will voluntarily withdraw its PCAOB registration and introduce measures concerning new client acquisitions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Both Bostock and Stallabrass face suspensions from practising before the SEC as accountants, with potential reinstatements after five and two years, respectively.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[FDIC report includes crypto as banking risk]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/fdic-report-includes-crypto-as-banking-risk</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fdic-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fdic-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fdic-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:00:16 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/fdic-report-includes-crypto-as-banking-risk</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation has included crypto in its annual risk review for the first time, stating that crypto presents key risks and that it needs closer supervision.</p>
FDIC seeks more control over crypto companies
<p>The crypto industry may not be entirely happy with being closely supervised by the likes of the FDIC given that it came about as an alternative to a slow-moving banking system that does not provide a helpful service to clients.</p>
<p>Be that as it may, the FDIC has the reins of power and will do what it will do in order to try and bring crypto under the control of regulators that are regulating on behalf of the incumbent system.</p>
<p>Banks are already working with crypto institutions, and others are contemplating such a move. Therefore, in collaboration with its fellow federal banking entities the FDIC has stated in its report that it is ready to delve further into how banks are getting involved in crypto, and with this knowledge provide full supervisory guidance.</p>
Perceived risks to banks
<p>In its report the FDIC talks of the &ldquo;dynamic nature of crypto-assets&rdquo;, and their &ldquo;rapid pace of innovation&rdquo;. The main risks for the banking sector, as perceived by the FDIC is the possibility of &ldquo;contagion&rdquo; which could spread over into banks with exposure to the sector, and also the &ldquo;run risk&rdquo; for banks that hold stablecoin reserves.</p>
<p>The report went on to specify that all FDIC supervised banks must notify the agency of any crypto related activities that they have or that they are planning to engage in. Examples were then given of firms that had made misleading claims as to the eligibility of FDIC insurance for certain crypto-assets. The report ended with what the authors saw as &ldquo;heightened liquidity risks&rdquo; due to what they saw as the &ldquo;unpredictability&rdquo; of deposit inflows and outflows.</p>
Opinion
<p>The FDIC is an organisation staffed by those from the existing financial system, and therefore it is biassed towards the protection of the banks within that system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There is no conversation as to how more failing banks might impact any crypto companies that are dealing with them, or how obliging crypto companies, or the banks that seek to deal with them, to jump through ever more complex regulatory hoops, might end up squashing the dynamism and innovation of crypto.</p>
<p>The FDIC is there to insure the funds of bank customers should their bank fail. However, without the money to guarantee the savings of the clients of more than one or two big banks should they fail - it might be asked: what is the point of this organisation anyway?</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation has included crypto in its annual risk review for the first time, stating that crypto presents key risks and that it needs closer supervision.</p>
FDIC seeks more control over crypto companies
<p>The crypto industry may not be entirely happy with being closely supervised by the likes of the FDIC given that it came about as an alternative to a slow-moving banking system that does not provide a helpful service to clients.</p>
<p>Be that as it may, the FDIC has the reins of power and will do what it will do in order to try and bring crypto under the control of regulators that are regulating on behalf of the incumbent system.</p>
<p>Banks are already working with crypto institutions, and others are contemplating such a move. Therefore, in collaboration with its fellow federal banking entities the FDIC has stated in its report that it is ready to delve further into how banks are getting involved in crypto, and with this knowledge provide full supervisory guidance.</p>
Perceived risks to banks
<p>In its report the FDIC talks of the &ldquo;dynamic nature of crypto-assets&rdquo;, and their &ldquo;rapid pace of innovation&rdquo;. The main risks for the banking sector, as perceived by the FDIC is the possibility of &ldquo;contagion&rdquo; which could spread over into banks with exposure to the sector, and also the &ldquo;run risk&rdquo; for banks that hold stablecoin reserves.</p>
<p>The report went on to specify that all FDIC supervised banks must notify the agency of any crypto related activities that they have or that they are planning to engage in. Examples were then given of firms that had made misleading claims as to the eligibility of FDIC insurance for certain crypto-assets. The report ended with what the authors saw as &ldquo;heightened liquidity risks&rdquo; due to what they saw as the &ldquo;unpredictability&rdquo; of deposit inflows and outflows.</p>
Opinion
<p>The FDIC is an organisation staffed by those from the existing financial system, and therefore it is biassed towards the protection of the banks within that system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There is no conversation as to how more failing banks might impact any crypto companies that are dealing with them, or how obliging crypto companies, or the banks that seek to deal with them, to jump through ever more complex regulatory hoops, might end up squashing the dynamism and innovation of crypto.</p>
<p>The FDIC is there to insure the funds of bank customers should their bank fail. However, without the money to guarantee the savings of the clients of more than one or two big banks should they fail - it might be asked: what is the point of this organisation anyway?</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[RocketSwap Outlines Emergency Plan Following $865,000 Exploit]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/rocketswap-outlines-emergency-plan-following-865000-exploit</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/rocketswap-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/rocketswap-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/rocketswap-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/rocketswap-outlines-emergency-plan-following-865000-exploit</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Base project RocketSwap has shared an emergency plan with users as it looks to recover from a brute force hack that saw the protocol lose around 471 ETH, valued at around $865,000, on the 14th of August.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The team behind the project also plans on reaching out to the hacker.&nbsp;</p>
The Emergency Plan&nbsp;
<p>The team at RocketSwap explained in a post on X on the 15th of August, stating that they planned to redeploy a new farm contract, following which it would be open-sourced on-chain. The team stated that they would also be relinquishing mining rights, mostly of RCKT, and also reach out to the hackers in an attempt to negotiate a return of the stolen assets, This approach was taken by Curve, and several other decentralized protocols following the Curve exploit.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The emergency programme agreed upon by the team is as follows. We plan to redeploy a new farm contract by dropping the proxy contract and open-sourcing it on-chain. The new farm will advance the production reduction plan by 0.075 per block. The team relinquishes minting rights and retains only low-risk rights to allocate new pools. Locked initial liquidity and 80k tokens will be extended for 1 year. The team will continue to roll out LaunchPad, with further updates planned. Telegram groups will be reopened after stabilization. Call on hackers to return assets to victims.&rdquo;</p>

The RocketSwap Hack&nbsp;
<p>On the 14th of April, a hacker managed to steal around 471 ETH, bridging it from Base to Ethereum. The activity was flagged by blockchain security firm PeckShield. The hacker then created 90 trillion LoveRCKT tokens before transferring them to Uniswap, along with 400 of the 471 ETH initially stolen. PeckShield detailed the hack in a post on X, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;#PeckShieldAlert The @RocketSwap_Labs exploiter has grabbed ~471 $ETH and bridged them from #Base to #Ethereum, and then created the token $LoveRCKT, the exploiter already supplied 90T $LoveRCKT and 400 $ETH to #Uniswap.&rdquo;</p>

<p>RocketSwap eventually confirmed the news on the same day, with PeckShield and another blockchain security firm, CertiK, providing additional details about the hack a few hours later. The attack was attributed to a brute force attack on RocketSwap&rsquo;s server, with the protocol stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As a result of the team&rsquo;s investigation, We are sorry to inform you that the team needed to use offline signatures when deploying the launchpad and put the private keys on the server. A brute force hack of the server was detected, and due to the proxy contract used for the farm contract, there were multiple high-risk permissions that led to the transfer of the farm&rsquo;s assets. We shut down the farm to prevent further damage. The team is currently working on an emergency plan, and the Telegram group has been banned for the time being. The loss of farm assets is only a concern, DEX is not affected in any way.&rdquo;</p>

Growing Headaches On Base&nbsp;
<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s layer-2 blockchain Base has faced several issues since commencing operations. LeetSwap, a leading decentralized exchange on the Base blockchain, suspended trading operations after flagging a security vulnerability in their factory, leading to the suspicion of compromised pool liquidity. The pause was done so that the team could investigate the issue further. PeckShield reported that around 340 ETH was exploited from liquidity pairs on Base, showing the gravity of the prevailing situation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Prior to the pause in trading by LeetSwap, the BALD memecoin suffered a significant drop in value. The crash occurred after the token&rsquo;s developer withdrew 6800 ETH, valued at around $12.5 million, from the liquidity pools on LeetSwap, raising several eyebrows and compounding the list of issues faced by LeetSwap. Furthermore, Coinbase is also dealing with its own set of regulatory challenges after finding itself as a target of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The Securities and Exchange Commission has ordered Coinbase to stop all crypto trading, except for that of Bitcoin. When Coinbase questioned the decision made by the regulatory body, Coinbase filed a lawsuit against the exchange.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Base project RocketSwap has shared an emergency plan with users as it looks to recover from a brute force hack that saw the protocol lose around 471 ETH, valued at around $865,000, on the 14th of August.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The team behind the project also plans on reaching out to the hacker.&nbsp;</p>
The Emergency Plan&nbsp;
<p>The team at RocketSwap explained in a post on X on the 15th of August, stating that they planned to redeploy a new farm contract, following which it would be open-sourced on-chain. The team stated that they would also be relinquishing mining rights, mostly of RCKT, and also reach out to the hackers in an attempt to negotiate a return of the stolen assets, This approach was taken by Curve, and several other decentralized protocols following the Curve exploit.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The emergency programme agreed upon by the team is as follows. We plan to redeploy a new farm contract by dropping the proxy contract and open-sourcing it on-chain. The new farm will advance the production reduction plan by 0.075 per block. The team relinquishes minting rights and retains only low-risk rights to allocate new pools. Locked initial liquidity and 80k tokens will be extended for 1 year. The team will continue to roll out LaunchPad, with further updates planned. Telegram groups will be reopened after stabilization. Call on hackers to return assets to victims.&rdquo;</p>

The RocketSwap Hack&nbsp;
<p>On the 14th of April, a hacker managed to steal around 471 ETH, bridging it from Base to Ethereum. The activity was flagged by blockchain security firm PeckShield. The hacker then created 90 trillion LoveRCKT tokens before transferring them to Uniswap, along with 400 of the 471 ETH initially stolen. PeckShield detailed the hack in a post on X, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;#PeckShieldAlert The @RocketSwap_Labs exploiter has grabbed ~471 $ETH and bridged them from #Base to #Ethereum, and then created the token $LoveRCKT, the exploiter already supplied 90T $LoveRCKT and 400 $ETH to #Uniswap.&rdquo;</p>

<p>RocketSwap eventually confirmed the news on the same day, with PeckShield and another blockchain security firm, CertiK, providing additional details about the hack a few hours later. The attack was attributed to a brute force attack on RocketSwap&rsquo;s server, with the protocol stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As a result of the team&rsquo;s investigation, We are sorry to inform you that the team needed to use offline signatures when deploying the launchpad and put the private keys on the server. A brute force hack of the server was detected, and due to the proxy contract used for the farm contract, there were multiple high-risk permissions that led to the transfer of the farm&rsquo;s assets. We shut down the farm to prevent further damage. The team is currently working on an emergency plan, and the Telegram group has been banned for the time being. The loss of farm assets is only a concern, DEX is not affected in any way.&rdquo;</p>

Growing Headaches On Base&nbsp;
<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s layer-2 blockchain Base has faced several issues since commencing operations. LeetSwap, a leading decentralized exchange on the Base blockchain, suspended trading operations after flagging a security vulnerability in their factory, leading to the suspicion of compromised pool liquidity. The pause was done so that the team could investigate the issue further. PeckShield reported that around 340 ETH was exploited from liquidity pairs on Base, showing the gravity of the prevailing situation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Prior to the pause in trading by LeetSwap, the BALD memecoin suffered a significant drop in value. The crash occurred after the token&rsquo;s developer withdrew 6800 ETH, valued at around $12.5 million, from the liquidity pools on LeetSwap, raising several eyebrows and compounding the list of issues faced by LeetSwap. Furthermore, Coinbase is also dealing with its own set of regulatory challenges after finding itself as a target of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The Securities and Exchange Commission has ordered Coinbase to stop all crypto trading, except for that of Bitcoin. When Coinbase questioned the decision made by the regulatory body, Coinbase filed a lawsuit against the exchange.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Go!Labs Empowers Global Change Through AI-Powered Engagement and Community Challenges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/golabs-empowers-global-change-through-ai-powered-engagement-and-community-challenges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image_91_1692046478F1KGlLRtJf.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image_91_1692046478F1KGlLRtJf.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image_91_1692046478F1KGlLRtJf.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 23:03:05 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/golabs-empowers-global-change-through-ai-powered-engagement-and-community-challenges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 14th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The Go! Initiative stands at the forefront of AI-powered weekly global competitions, poised to drive substantial global impact. Leveraging advanced AI technology, their weekly global competitions transcend traditional boundaries, uniting a diverse global community in a shared pursuit of positive change. Each week, participants are presented with captivating challenges that encourage social, environmental, and personal betterment. Through these dynamic competitions, Go! not only showcases the transformative potential of AI but also empowers individuals worldwide to contribute to meaningful causes, fostering a collective movement toward a brighter and more sustainable future.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Dive right into the future of engaging impact experiences. One can kickstart their journey on Twitter and further immerse in the ecosystem by engaging in conversations on Discord. The experience isn&rsquo;t just pioneering an impact revolution; it&rsquo;s shaping the next era of Web3, intertwining thrilling real-life experiences with significant global impact in the multi-billion-dollar ESG market.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Fueled by the convergence of blockchain, generative AI, and an AI Copilot, Go! offers an immersive on-chain experience, backed by RWA (Real-World Assets). These assets guarantee tangible and verifiable value to every in-game achievement and token, transforming virtual wins into real-world impacts.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">SmartChain: The Web3 System supporting Go!</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Developed by Go! Labs, SmartChain integrates Layer 1 AI-optimized zkEVM tech, paving the way for a more performant and eco-efficient system. This results in superior on-chain experiences, minimized gas fees, and a sustainable ecosystem. The introduction of DePIN ensures that user interactions are not just fast, but also secure, private, and tailored, revolutionizing the blockchain realm.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Engage, Earn &amp; Empower</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Harness the Potential of AI: Through an innovative AI Copilot, participants are guided toward meaningful interactions that lead to remarkable rewards. By delving into genuine engagements, individuals can unlock unique experiences that empower them on a global scale.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Community-Centric Challenges and Recognition: The platform offers community-centered challenges that resonate with participants' shared values. As contributors distinguish themselves through impactful actions, they gain access to exclusive $HLTHY tokens, solidifying their role as catalysts for positive change. The engagement journey not only fosters growth but also fosters a tangible impact backed by Real-World Assets (RWA), aligning personal achievements with a greater purpose.</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">Validators and Shaping the Web3 Future</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Go! Labs is also scouting for skilled validators for SmartChain. If you&rsquo;re equipped to influence the future of blockchain and Web3, dive into the tech specifics, onboarding processes, and research documents here. Visit https://goplatform.io to learn more.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Join, Play, Transform</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Embark on a journey that fuses global health, impact, and next-gen Web3 tech with Go! Stay updated on Twitter and partake in weekly global health competitions on their Discord under &ldquo;Events.&rdquo;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Go! Labs</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Go! Labs is a group of experienced industry professionals working towards improving the quality of life on a global scale. Supported by notable industry VCs with an established distribution network and a solid user base, Go! Labs are working on financial inclusion, data monetization, climate concerns, healthcare revolution, and web3 innovation. To learn more about Go! Labs and their work, visit https://www.goplatform.io/.</p>ContactGo! Labs TeamGo! Labshello@goplatform.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, August 14th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The Go! Initiative stands at the forefront of AI-powered weekly global competitions, poised to drive substantial global impact. Leveraging advanced AI technology, their weekly global competitions transcend traditional boundaries, uniting a diverse global community in a shared pursuit of positive change. Each week, participants are presented with captivating challenges that encourage social, environmental, and personal betterment. Through these dynamic competitions, Go! not only showcases the transformative potential of AI but also empowers individuals worldwide to contribute to meaningful causes, fostering a collective movement toward a brighter and more sustainable future.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Dive right into the future of engaging impact experiences. One can kickstart their journey on Twitter and further immerse in the ecosystem by engaging in conversations on Discord. The experience isn&rsquo;t just pioneering an impact revolution; it&rsquo;s shaping the next era of Web3, intertwining thrilling real-life experiences with significant global impact in the multi-billion-dollar ESG market.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Fueled by the convergence of blockchain, generative AI, and an AI Copilot, Go! offers an immersive on-chain experience, backed by RWA (Real-World Assets). These assets guarantee tangible and verifiable value to every in-game achievement and token, transforming virtual wins into real-world impacts.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">SmartChain: The Web3 System supporting Go!</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Developed by Go! Labs, SmartChain integrates Layer 1 AI-optimized zkEVM tech, paving the way for a more performant and eco-efficient system. This results in superior on-chain experiences, minimized gas fees, and a sustainable ecosystem. The introduction of DePIN ensures that user interactions are not just fast, but also secure, private, and tailored, revolutionizing the blockchain realm.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Engage, Earn &amp; Empower</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Harness the Potential of AI: Through an innovative AI Copilot, participants are guided toward meaningful interactions that lead to remarkable rewards. By delving into genuine engagements, individuals can unlock unique experiences that empower them on a global scale.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Community-Centric Challenges and Recognition: The platform offers community-centered challenges that resonate with participants' shared values. As contributors distinguish themselves through impactful actions, they gain access to exclusive $HLTHY tokens, solidifying their role as catalysts for positive change. The engagement journey not only fosters growth but also fosters a tangible impact backed by Real-World Assets (RWA), aligning personal achievements with a greater purpose.</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">Validators and Shaping the Web3 Future</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Go! Labs is also scouting for skilled validators for SmartChain. If you&rsquo;re equipped to influence the future of blockchain and Web3, dive into the tech specifics, onboarding processes, and research documents here. Visit https://goplatform.io to learn more.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Join, Play, Transform</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Embark on a journey that fuses global health, impact, and next-gen Web3 tech with Go! Stay updated on Twitter and partake in weekly global health competitions on their Discord under &ldquo;Events.&rdquo;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Go! Labs</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Go! Labs is a group of experienced industry professionals working towards improving the quality of life on a global scale. Supported by notable industry VCs with an established distribution network and a solid user base, Go! Labs are working on financial inclusion, data monetization, climate concerns, healthcare revolution, and web3 innovation. To learn more about Go! Labs and their work, visit https://www.goplatform.io/.</p>ContactGo! Labs TeamGo! Labshello@goplatform.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coca-Cola Unveils New Masterpiece NFTs on Base Blockchain]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/coca-cola-unveils-new-masterpiece-nfts-on-base-blockchain</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coca-cola-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coca-cola-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coca-cola-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/coca-cola-unveils-new-masterpiece-nfts-on-base-blockchain</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Coca-Cola has launched its new exclusive NFT collection on Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer-2 network during the &ldquo;Onchain Summer&rdquo; festival.</p>
Coca-Cola&rsquo;s Masterpiece Campaign
<p>On Sunday, August 13, one of the most recognizable consumer brands in the world, Coca-Cola, revealed its new non-fungible tokens (NFT) collection on Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer-2 blockchain called &ldquo;Base&rdquo;.</p>
<p>The collection is a part of Coca-Cola's global &ldquo;Masterpiece&rdquo; campaign which was partially created by the brand&rsquo;s AI platform known as &ldquo;Real Magic&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;&lsquo;Masterpiece&rsquo; is not a story in which Coke appears&hellip; Coke is the story,&rdquo; commented Pratik Thakar, Global Head of Creative Strategy and Integrated Content for Coca‑Cola. &ldquo;True to the spirit of the brand&mdash;and not unlike the way a synchronized supply chain collaborates to seamlessly deliver ice-cold Coca‑Cola to consumers at just the right time&mdash;a diverse collection of artwork spanning multiple genres, geographies and generations comes together to uplift a slumping teenager. Creating human connection and bringing enchantment to everyday moments is what &lsquo;Real Magic&rsquo; is all about.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Masterpiece NFT collection showcases the artwork featured in the brand&rsquo;s campaign, including Andy Warhol&rsquo;s iconic 1962 Coca‑Cola painting, classical pieces of timeless artists such as Edvard Munch&rsquo;s &ldquo;The Scream&rdquo; and Johannes Vermeer&rsquo;s &ldquo;Girl with a Pearl Earring,&rdquo;, as well as works of emerging artists such as Aket, Fatma Ramadan, and Vikram Kushwah.</p>
Coinbase&rsquo;s Onchain Summer
<p>Coca-Cola&rsquo;s new NFT collection has been offered for a limited time and presented as a part of the Coinbase&rsquo;s Onchain Summer event:</p>

<p>&ldquo;@CocaCola is bringing their Global Masterpiece campaign onchain with iconic works from leading artists,&rdquo; Coinbase announced on X, formerly known as Twitter.</p>

<p>Onchain Summer is Coinbase's month-long celebration of its Layer-2 Blochcian Base which became available to the general public on August 9. Each day, the festival offers numerous onchain mints, stories, and activities related to art, culture, music, gaming, and more. Coca-Cola is undoubtedly the most recognizable brand presented on the list of Base&rsquo;s partners so far.</p>
Coca-Cola and NFTs
<p>This is not the first time the world-renowned soft drinks brand has ventured into the NFT space. Back in 2021, Coca-Cola auctioned off exclusive NFT collectibles with the aim of raising funds for Special Olympics International. At that time, the first Coca-Cola&rsquo;s NFT loot box was sold as a single asset for over $575,000.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coca-Cola&rsquo;s engagement with NFTs is meaningful for the whole cryptocurrency industry. As one of the largest global consumer brands, Coca-Cola could introduce many of its customers to the world of digital art and Web3. Besides, the beverage giant will likely play a big role in promoting Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer-2 network Base.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coca-Cola has launched its new exclusive NFT collection on Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer-2 network during the &ldquo;Onchain Summer&rdquo; festival.</p>
Coca-Cola&rsquo;s Masterpiece Campaign
<p>On Sunday, August 13, one of the most recognizable consumer brands in the world, Coca-Cola, revealed its new non-fungible tokens (NFT) collection on Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer-2 blockchain called &ldquo;Base&rdquo;.</p>
<p>The collection is a part of Coca-Cola's global &ldquo;Masterpiece&rdquo; campaign which was partially created by the brand&rsquo;s AI platform known as &ldquo;Real Magic&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;&lsquo;Masterpiece&rsquo; is not a story in which Coke appears&hellip; Coke is the story,&rdquo; commented Pratik Thakar, Global Head of Creative Strategy and Integrated Content for Coca‑Cola. &ldquo;True to the spirit of the brand&mdash;and not unlike the way a synchronized supply chain collaborates to seamlessly deliver ice-cold Coca‑Cola to consumers at just the right time&mdash;a diverse collection of artwork spanning multiple genres, geographies and generations comes together to uplift a slumping teenager. Creating human connection and bringing enchantment to everyday moments is what &lsquo;Real Magic&rsquo; is all about.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Masterpiece NFT collection showcases the artwork featured in the brand&rsquo;s campaign, including Andy Warhol&rsquo;s iconic 1962 Coca‑Cola painting, classical pieces of timeless artists such as Edvard Munch&rsquo;s &ldquo;The Scream&rdquo; and Johannes Vermeer&rsquo;s &ldquo;Girl with a Pearl Earring,&rdquo;, as well as works of emerging artists such as Aket, Fatma Ramadan, and Vikram Kushwah.</p>
Coinbase&rsquo;s Onchain Summer
<p>Coca-Cola&rsquo;s new NFT collection has been offered for a limited time and presented as a part of the Coinbase&rsquo;s Onchain Summer event:</p>

<p>&ldquo;@CocaCola is bringing their Global Masterpiece campaign onchain with iconic works from leading artists,&rdquo; Coinbase announced on X, formerly known as Twitter.</p>

<p>Onchain Summer is Coinbase's month-long celebration of its Layer-2 Blochcian Base which became available to the general public on August 9. Each day, the festival offers numerous onchain mints, stories, and activities related to art, culture, music, gaming, and more. Coca-Cola is undoubtedly the most recognizable brand presented on the list of Base&rsquo;s partners so far.</p>
Coca-Cola and NFTs
<p>This is not the first time the world-renowned soft drinks brand has ventured into the NFT space. Back in 2021, Coca-Cola auctioned off exclusive NFT collectibles with the aim of raising funds for Special Olympics International. At that time, the first Coca-Cola&rsquo;s NFT loot box was sold as a single asset for over $575,000.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coca-Cola&rsquo;s engagement with NFTs is meaningful for the whole cryptocurrency industry. As one of the largest global consumer brands, Coca-Cola could introduce many of its customers to the world of digital art and Web3. Besides, the beverage giant will likely play a big role in promoting Coinbase&rsquo;s Layer-2 network Base.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Singapore Red Cross To Accept Donations in Crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/singapore-red-cross-to-accept-donations-in-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/red-cross.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/red-cross.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/red-cross.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:53:11 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/singapore-red-cross-to-accept-donations-in-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Humanitarian aid organisation Singapore Red Cross announced it will now accept donations in the form of cryptocurrencies. Donors can contribute in Bitcoin, Ether, Tether and USD Coin. </p>
<p>The Singapore Red Cross recently announced that it will now accept donations in cryptocurrencies via a partnership with Triple-A.</p>
Singapore Red Cross Enables Anonymous Crypto Donations
<p>In an effort to secure contributions from a whole new generation, the Singapore Red Cross entered into a partnership with Triple-A to enable the option of anonymous crypto donations. According to a press release, the organisation accepts Bitcoin, Ether, Tether and USD Coin.</p>
<p>The Singapore Red Cross explained:</p>

<p>&lsquo;Powered by Triple-A, payment is compatible with all wallets and provides locked-in exchange rates. You can pre-define an amount (in fiat) that you would like to give and the system will automatically do the conversion for you.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Triple-A is the first crypto payment gateway licensed by the Monetary Authority of Singapore. The platform was sanctioned as a Digital Payment Token Provider by the MAS in November 2021.</p>
<p>Secretary general and CEO of the Singapore Red Cross, Benjamin William, commented:</p>

<p>&ldquo;By accepting digital currencies, we open our doors to a new segment of donors who are tech-savvy and wish to make a difference through their digital assets.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Enabling cryptocurrency donations also opens more opportunities for the new generation of donors who are&nbsp;au fait&nbsp;with digital currencies to consider philanthropy and helping the vulnerable.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Donors can contribute with the four above tokens or donate via a separate solution from a Binance digital wallet.</p>
<p>Currently, crypto donations are not tax deductible.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Humanitarian aid organisation Singapore Red Cross announced it will now accept donations in the form of cryptocurrencies. Donors can contribute in Bitcoin, Ether, Tether and USD Coin. </p>
<p>The Singapore Red Cross recently announced that it will now accept donations in cryptocurrencies via a partnership with Triple-A.</p>
Singapore Red Cross Enables Anonymous Crypto Donations
<p>In an effort to secure contributions from a whole new generation, the Singapore Red Cross entered into a partnership with Triple-A to enable the option of anonymous crypto donations. According to a press release, the organisation accepts Bitcoin, Ether, Tether and USD Coin.</p>
<p>The Singapore Red Cross explained:</p>

<p>&lsquo;Powered by Triple-A, payment is compatible with all wallets and provides locked-in exchange rates. You can pre-define an amount (in fiat) that you would like to give and the system will automatically do the conversion for you.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Triple-A is the first crypto payment gateway licensed by the Monetary Authority of Singapore. The platform was sanctioned as a Digital Payment Token Provider by the MAS in November 2021.</p>
<p>Secretary general and CEO of the Singapore Red Cross, Benjamin William, commented:</p>

<p>&ldquo;By accepting digital currencies, we open our doors to a new segment of donors who are tech-savvy and wish to make a difference through their digital assets.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Enabling cryptocurrency donations also opens more opportunities for the new generation of donors who are&nbsp;au fait&nbsp;with digital currencies to consider philanthropy and helping the vulnerable.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Donors can contribute with the four above tokens or donate via a separate solution from a Binance digital wallet.</p>
<p>Currently, crypto donations are not tax deductible.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Former US President Donald Trump Holds Around $500K Of ETH]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/former-us-president-donald-trump-holds-around-500k-of-eth</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/trump-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/trump-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/trump-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/former-us-president-donald-trump-holds-around-500k-of-eth</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Former United States President Donald Trump&rsquo;s latest public financial disclosure has revealed that he owns around $250,000 to $500,000 worth of Ethereum (ETH).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Trump had recently launched an exclusive non-fungible token (NFT) collection after leaving the White House in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
Trump Holds Considerable ETH&nbsp;
<p>The financial disclosure was filed with the Office of Government Ethics and outlined Trump&rsquo;s various assets and sources of income. Eagle-eyed observers noticed a section that mentioned a &ldquo;cryptocurrency wallet Ethereum&rdquo; on the second to last entry on the 82-page form. According to the information in the financial disclosure, the wallet held an estimated $250,000 to $500,000 worth of ETH. It is believed that the contents of the cryptocurrency wallet are linked with the NFT collection launched by Trump in December 2022.&nbsp;</p>
The Trump NFTs&nbsp;
<p>The former president launched his NFT collection in December 2022 after weeks of speculation regarding his &ldquo;special announcement.&rdquo; Many believed the announcement would be naming a running mate for his presidential campaign. However, Mr. Trump announced the launch of his exclusive NFT collection instead. The collection features the former president in several avatars, including a Nascar driver and an astronaut. At the time of the launch, Mr Trump had stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;These limited edition cards feature amazing ART of my Life &amp; Career. It would make a great Christmas gift. Don&rsquo;t Wait. They will be gone; I believe, very quickly!&rdquo;</p>

<p>He had also posted a clip that featured an animated version of himself standing in front of the Trump Tower, with lasers shooting out of his eyes. The NFT collection was described as similar to baseball cards but far more exciting and priced at $99 each. Buyers of the collection will also be able to enter a sweepstake and have a chance at winning a gala dinner or a game of golf with Mr. Trump. However, the move was roundly criticized on social media, with several high-profile Republicans speaking out.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following her husband&rsquo;s footsteps, the former first lady also launched an NFT collection only a couple of months after the former president&rsquo;s NFT collection. Each NFT in the Melania Trump collection is priced at $50. The collection consisted of seven designs, with a total of 3500 NFTs. The former first lady had stated at the time of launch,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The 1776 Collection of artwork draws inspiration from several iconic landmarks of our nation, which I had the privilege of visiting during the time I served as first lady. Each piece provides a view into our nation&rsquo;s history, culture, and patriotism. I am proud to celebrate our great nation and remain inspired by the words contained within the Declaration of Independence.&rdquo;</p>

Past Skepticism Of Crypto&nbsp;
<p>The disclosure that the former president owns a considerable amount of ETH is interesting, especially when you consider how skeptical he had been about crypto in the past. Back in 2019, Trump had stated that he was not a fan of Bitcoin and described it as &ldquo;not money&rdquo; with its valuation based on thin air.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am not a fan of Bitcoin and other Cryptocurrencies, which are not money, and whose value is highly volatile and based on thin air. Unregulated Crypto Assets can facilitate unlawful behavior, including drug trade and other illegal activity....&rdquo;</p>

<p>Trump reiterated these views in a 2021 interview, once again highlighting his opposition to the crypto ecosystem and digital assets. He stated that he was quite wary of digital assets such as Bitcoin because they were a threat to the dollar. He even called the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency a scam, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bitcoin just seems like a scam&hellip;I don&rsquo;t like it because it is another currency competing against the dollar. Essentially it&rsquo;s a currency competing against the dollar. I want the dollar to be the currency of the world. That is what I have always said.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former United States President Donald Trump&rsquo;s latest public financial disclosure has revealed that he owns around $250,000 to $500,000 worth of Ethereum (ETH).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Trump had recently launched an exclusive non-fungible token (NFT) collection after leaving the White House in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
Trump Holds Considerable ETH&nbsp;
<p>The financial disclosure was filed with the Office of Government Ethics and outlined Trump&rsquo;s various assets and sources of income. Eagle-eyed observers noticed a section that mentioned a &ldquo;cryptocurrency wallet Ethereum&rdquo; on the second to last entry on the 82-page form. According to the information in the financial disclosure, the wallet held an estimated $250,000 to $500,000 worth of ETH. It is believed that the contents of the cryptocurrency wallet are linked with the NFT collection launched by Trump in December 2022.&nbsp;</p>
The Trump NFTs&nbsp;
<p>The former president launched his NFT collection in December 2022 after weeks of speculation regarding his &ldquo;special announcement.&rdquo; Many believed the announcement would be naming a running mate for his presidential campaign. However, Mr. Trump announced the launch of his exclusive NFT collection instead. The collection features the former president in several avatars, including a Nascar driver and an astronaut. At the time of the launch, Mr Trump had stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;These limited edition cards feature amazing ART of my Life &amp; Career. It would make a great Christmas gift. Don&rsquo;t Wait. They will be gone; I believe, very quickly!&rdquo;</p>

<p>He had also posted a clip that featured an animated version of himself standing in front of the Trump Tower, with lasers shooting out of his eyes. The NFT collection was described as similar to baseball cards but far more exciting and priced at $99 each. Buyers of the collection will also be able to enter a sweepstake and have a chance at winning a gala dinner or a game of golf with Mr. Trump. However, the move was roundly criticized on social media, with several high-profile Republicans speaking out.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following her husband&rsquo;s footsteps, the former first lady also launched an NFT collection only a couple of months after the former president&rsquo;s NFT collection. Each NFT in the Melania Trump collection is priced at $50. The collection consisted of seven designs, with a total of 3500 NFTs. The former first lady had stated at the time of launch,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The 1776 Collection of artwork draws inspiration from several iconic landmarks of our nation, which I had the privilege of visiting during the time I served as first lady. Each piece provides a view into our nation&rsquo;s history, culture, and patriotism. I am proud to celebrate our great nation and remain inspired by the words contained within the Declaration of Independence.&rdquo;</p>

Past Skepticism Of Crypto&nbsp;
<p>The disclosure that the former president owns a considerable amount of ETH is interesting, especially when you consider how skeptical he had been about crypto in the past. Back in 2019, Trump had stated that he was not a fan of Bitcoin and described it as &ldquo;not money&rdquo; with its valuation based on thin air.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am not a fan of Bitcoin and other Cryptocurrencies, which are not money, and whose value is highly volatile and based on thin air. Unregulated Crypto Assets can facilitate unlawful behavior, including drug trade and other illegal activity....&rdquo;</p>

<p>Trump reiterated these views in a 2021 interview, once again highlighting his opposition to the crypto ecosystem and digital assets. He stated that he was quite wary of digital assets such as Bitcoin because they were a threat to the dollar. He even called the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency a scam, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bitcoin just seems like a scam&hellip;I don&rsquo;t like it because it is another currency competing against the dollar. Essentially it&rsquo;s a currency competing against the dollar. I want the dollar to be the currency of the world. That is what I have always said.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Caught Between Levels - 15 August 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-caught-between-levels-15-august-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-14-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-14-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-14-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-caught-between-levels-15-august-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Volatility Favoring Downside:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 15 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) experienced elevated downside risk early in the Asian session as the pair depreciated to the 29072.96 area after selling pressure expanded around the 29447.60 area, representing another failed test of the 76.4% retracement of the depreciating range from 30350.70 to 26501.59.&nbsp;&nbsp; This interday high also represented a test of the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 28660.53 to 30222, while the move to multi-session lows around the 29072 area represented a test of the 76.4% retracement of the same appreciating. &nbsp;Technical trading was recently evident when buying pressure strengthened around the 28754 area, a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure around the 29526 and 29344 areas.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 27991.29 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 15460 to 31862.21.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional areas of technical support and potential buying pressure in these appreciating ranges include the 27466, 27166, 26428, 26272, and 25715 areas.</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 28213, 28137, 27979, 27757, 27430, 27409, 27338, 27312, 27246, 26501, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29347.27 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29346.47.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Volatility Favoring Downside:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 15 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) experienced elevated downside risk early in the Asian session as the pair depreciated to the 29072.96 area after selling pressure expanded around the 29447.60 area, representing another failed test of the 76.4% retracement of the depreciating range from 30350.70 to 26501.59.&nbsp;&nbsp; This interday high also represented a test of the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 28660.53 to 30222, while the move to multi-session lows around the 29072 area represented a test of the 76.4% retracement of the same appreciating. &nbsp;Technical trading was recently evident when buying pressure strengthened around the 28754 area, a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure around the 29526 and 29344 areas.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 27991.29 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 15460 to 31862.21.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional areas of technical support and potential buying pressure in these appreciating ranges include the 27466, 27166, 26428, 26272, and 25715 areas.</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 28213, 28137, 27979, 27757, 27430, 27409, 27338, 27312, 27246, 26501, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29347.27 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29346.47.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uniswap Fires Developer At The Heart Of FrensTech Rug Pull]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/uniswap-fires-developer-at-the-heart-of-frenstech-rug-pull</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/uniswap-fires-developer-at-the-heart-of-frenstech-rug-pull</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Prominent decentralized exchange Uniswap has confirmed that it has fired a prominent developer over his involvement in a $25,000 memecoin rug pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The developer in question, AzFlin, or Allen Lin, orchestrated a rug pull hours after initiating the deployment of the FrensTech meme coin.&nbsp;</p>
Uniswap Moves To Fire AzFlin
<p>Allen Lin, the Uniswap developer at the center of the storm surrounding the FrensTech meme coin rug pull, has lost his job at Uniswap. The sacking was confirmed in a post on X by Uniswap founder Hayden Adams, with Uniswap moving quickly to distance themselves from the actions of their former employee.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Wanted to let people know this person is no longer with the company. Not behavior we support or condone.&rdquo;</p>

<p>AzFlin lost his job at the decentralized exchange following the FrensTech meme coin rug pull that saw investors lose 14 ETH, valued at around $25,900. The meme coin was launched on the social platform of the Coinbase Layer-2 base program, friend.tech.&nbsp;</p>
How The Rug Pull Was Orchestrated&nbsp;
<p>A pseudo-anonymous user on X going by the name UniswapVillain initially made the Uniswap community aware of the fact that AzFlin had rug-pulled a meme coin project just hours after creating it. UniswapVillain noted that AzFlin initiated the rug pull by withdrawing support that was previously added to enable the trading of the FRENs token. Once the project had accumulated 14 ETH in fees, AzFlin removed liquidity and pocketed all the funds collected by the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The rug pull was orchestrated via the Hop Protocol, a decentralized bridge that allows users to transfer tokens between different blockchains. Furthermore, UniswapVillain added that the developer did not just remove liquidity from the project and meme coin. He also sold all the coins from which he had withdrawn the liquidity. He also added that the situation was particularly concerning, given AzFlin&rsquo;s association with Uniswap, one of the most prominent decentralized exchanges.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Frenstech (@FrensTech) $FRENS was deployed a few hours ago by the dev, @AzFlina Uniswap employee. One hour and four minutes ago, he effectively rugged the project, moving 14 ETH off of Base chain through HOP. Multiple people have confirmed he is the dev, and there were numerous early Uniswap employee followers on Twitter. He removed liquidity he added from fees and pocketed 14 ETH of fees. He sold the tokens he removed from liquidity even. This is wild to me that someone who is doxxed and works for Uniswap would do this.&rdquo;</p>

AzFlin Calls Sacking Net Neutral&nbsp;
<p>An unremorseful AzFlin called his sacking &ldquo;net neutral,&rdquo; boasting that he had gained 600 new followers and the status of a crypto villain on X. While people have wondered why someone who is doxxed and works for Uniswap would do this, AzFlin has remained unrepentant. The bad actor simply gave an update about losing their job on Twitter.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Got fired from UniSwap but gained new followers and Crypto Twitter villain status.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also changed his bio on X, adding the words AzFlin &ldquo;Unemployment arc&rdquo; and further commented on the issue:</p>

<p>"To those who think I rugged 14E: that came from dev taxes. It belonged to me. I know whatever I say, the low IQ CT narrative has already been spun. I will not comment further on this anymore, everything is on chain.&rdquo;</p>

The Growing Menace Of Rug Pulls&nbsp;
<p>Rug pulls have become increasingly common in the crypto space in recent times, primarily impacting newer tokens and decentralized exchanges. This comes against the backdrop of major cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum making record price moments that are not actionable, leaving investors desperate for a hefty profit. This is why traders should not buy into the hype of new projects and tokens pushed by influencers. Instead, they must do their own research and invest in reputable projects.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent decentralized exchange Uniswap has confirmed that it has fired a prominent developer over his involvement in a $25,000 memecoin rug pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The developer in question, AzFlin, or Allen Lin, orchestrated a rug pull hours after initiating the deployment of the FrensTech meme coin.&nbsp;</p>
Uniswap Moves To Fire AzFlin
<p>Allen Lin, the Uniswap developer at the center of the storm surrounding the FrensTech meme coin rug pull, has lost his job at Uniswap. The sacking was confirmed in a post on X by Uniswap founder Hayden Adams, with Uniswap moving quickly to distance themselves from the actions of their former employee.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Wanted to let people know this person is no longer with the company. Not behavior we support or condone.&rdquo;</p>

<p>AzFlin lost his job at the decentralized exchange following the FrensTech meme coin rug pull that saw investors lose 14 ETH, valued at around $25,900. The meme coin was launched on the social platform of the Coinbase Layer-2 base program, friend.tech.&nbsp;</p>
How The Rug Pull Was Orchestrated&nbsp;
<p>A pseudo-anonymous user on X going by the name UniswapVillain initially made the Uniswap community aware of the fact that AzFlin had rug-pulled a meme coin project just hours after creating it. UniswapVillain noted that AzFlin initiated the rug pull by withdrawing support that was previously added to enable the trading of the FRENs token. Once the project had accumulated 14 ETH in fees, AzFlin removed liquidity and pocketed all the funds collected by the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The rug pull was orchestrated via the Hop Protocol, a decentralized bridge that allows users to transfer tokens between different blockchains. Furthermore, UniswapVillain added that the developer did not just remove liquidity from the project and meme coin. He also sold all the coins from which he had withdrawn the liquidity. He also added that the situation was particularly concerning, given AzFlin&rsquo;s association with Uniswap, one of the most prominent decentralized exchanges.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Frenstech (@FrensTech) $FRENS was deployed a few hours ago by the dev, @AzFlina Uniswap employee. One hour and four minutes ago, he effectively rugged the project, moving 14 ETH off of Base chain through HOP. Multiple people have confirmed he is the dev, and there were numerous early Uniswap employee followers on Twitter. He removed liquidity he added from fees and pocketed 14 ETH of fees. He sold the tokens he removed from liquidity even. This is wild to me that someone who is doxxed and works for Uniswap would do this.&rdquo;</p>

AzFlin Calls Sacking Net Neutral&nbsp;
<p>An unremorseful AzFlin called his sacking &ldquo;net neutral,&rdquo; boasting that he had gained 600 new followers and the status of a crypto villain on X. While people have wondered why someone who is doxxed and works for Uniswap would do this, AzFlin has remained unrepentant. The bad actor simply gave an update about losing their job on Twitter.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Got fired from UniSwap but gained new followers and Crypto Twitter villain status.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also changed his bio on X, adding the words AzFlin &ldquo;Unemployment arc&rdquo; and further commented on the issue:</p>

<p>"To those who think I rugged 14E: that came from dev taxes. It belonged to me. I know whatever I say, the low IQ CT narrative has already been spun. I will not comment further on this anymore, everything is on chain.&rdquo;</p>

The Growing Menace Of Rug Pulls&nbsp;
<p>Rug pulls have become increasingly common in the crypto space in recent times, primarily impacting newer tokens and decentralized exchanges. This comes against the backdrop of major cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum making record price moments that are not actionable, leaving investors desperate for a hefty profit. This is why traders should not buy into the hype of new projects and tokens pushed by influencers. Instead, they must do their own research and invest in reputable projects.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Affyn Backs Singapore Government Initiative During F1 Singapore ]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/affyn-backs-singapore-government-initiative-during-f1-singapore</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-2-16.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-2-16.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-2-16.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/affyn-backs-singapore-government-initiative-during-f1-singapore</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Singapore-based Web 3 gaming firm Affyn is set to participate in the annual Grand Prix Season Singapore (GPSS), a 10-day event supported by the Singapore Tourism Board that culminates during the&nbsp; Formula 1 Singapore Grand Prix weekend. According to the team statement, Affyn entered a strategic partnership with GPSS to present a metaverse event to the fans of the Grand Prix.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;"We are proud to partner with GPSS as it underlines Affyn&rsquo;s intent to bolster Government initiatives and bring Web 3.0 development to the next level,&rdquo; said Affyn CEO Lucaz Lee. &ldquo;As the only official Web 3.0 company partnering with GPSS, an event supported by STB, it is an incredible opportunity to drive awareness of developments in the industry.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The event, titled &lsquo;Web 3.0 | Art Meets Metaverse&rsquo;,&nbsp; is set to run on Saturday, 16th September 2023, at Suntec City&rsquo;s Synthesis from 1 PM to 4 PM (local time). The event will include NFT exhibitions from artists around Singapore, a celebrity-hosted panel talk show and experiential zones that allow guests to delve into the metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With Singapore rising as a crypto hub in the East, the involvement of crypto in such a global sporting event blends well in maintaining its verve as the leading crypto hub in Asia. The event aims to educate non-crypto fans on the developments of the metaverse in the art world, dive into discussions on the state of the metaverse industry, interact during the exhibition and learn from experts via their talk shows. In addition, attendees can interact and share with other enthusiasts and dive into how blockchain and the metaverse affect art in the real world today.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In other news, Affyn-based gaming title Nexus World Land City will be launching its third wave of land parcels starting August 23.&nbsp; Players will have the chance to claim their land parcels in eight cities, including Amsterdam, Barcelona, Dubai, Kuala Lumpur, Madrid, Manilla, Sydney, and Zurich.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto companies&rsquo; relationship with F1 extends
<p>Despite the recent departures of FTX and Tezos, who sponsored the Mercedes-AMG Petronas F1 Team and Scuderia AlphaTauri, respectively, crypto partnerships with F1 teams have grown, as evidenced by Affyn&rsquo;s Singapore GP event. Earlier this year, British F1 team Williams Racing entered a strategic partnership with Kraken Exchange to launch a competition to see NFTs showcased around this year's Singapore GP.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Other crypto partners in F1 include Bybit, sponsoring Redbull Racing Team in a $150 million deal and Stake.com, an Alfa Romeo Formula One Team sponsor.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Singapore-based Web 3 gaming firm Affyn is set to participate in the annual Grand Prix Season Singapore (GPSS), a 10-day event supported by the Singapore Tourism Board that culminates during the&nbsp; Formula 1 Singapore Grand Prix weekend. According to the team statement, Affyn entered a strategic partnership with GPSS to present a metaverse event to the fans of the Grand Prix.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;"We are proud to partner with GPSS as it underlines Affyn&rsquo;s intent to bolster Government initiatives and bring Web 3.0 development to the next level,&rdquo; said Affyn CEO Lucaz Lee. &ldquo;As the only official Web 3.0 company partnering with GPSS, an event supported by STB, it is an incredible opportunity to drive awareness of developments in the industry.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The event, titled &lsquo;Web 3.0 | Art Meets Metaverse&rsquo;,&nbsp; is set to run on Saturday, 16th September 2023, at Suntec City&rsquo;s Synthesis from 1 PM to 4 PM (local time). The event will include NFT exhibitions from artists around Singapore, a celebrity-hosted panel talk show and experiential zones that allow guests to delve into the metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With Singapore rising as a crypto hub in the East, the involvement of crypto in such a global sporting event blends well in maintaining its verve as the leading crypto hub in Asia. The event aims to educate non-crypto fans on the developments of the metaverse in the art world, dive into discussions on the state of the metaverse industry, interact during the exhibition and learn from experts via their talk shows. In addition, attendees can interact and share with other enthusiasts and dive into how blockchain and the metaverse affect art in the real world today.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In other news, Affyn-based gaming title Nexus World Land City will be launching its third wave of land parcels starting August 23.&nbsp; Players will have the chance to claim their land parcels in eight cities, including Amsterdam, Barcelona, Dubai, Kuala Lumpur, Madrid, Manilla, Sydney, and Zurich.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto companies&rsquo; relationship with F1 extends
<p>Despite the recent departures of FTX and Tezos, who sponsored the Mercedes-AMG Petronas F1 Team and Scuderia AlphaTauri, respectively, crypto partnerships with F1 teams have grown, as evidenced by Affyn&rsquo;s Singapore GP event. Earlier this year, British F1 team Williams Racing entered a strategic partnership with Kraken Exchange to launch a competition to see NFTs showcased around this year's Singapore GP.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Other crypto partners in F1 include Bybit, sponsoring Redbull Racing Team in a $150 million deal and Stake.com, an Alfa Romeo Formula One Team sponsor.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
