<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Up 1.5% as Market Focus Shifts to June CPI and PPI Readings</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-up-15-as-market-focus-shifts-to-june-cpi-and-ppi-readings.htm</link><description>Bitcoin price is trading at $30,492 in today's market, marking an over 1% rise on Tuesday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency market continues to draw attention as Gary Gensler, the chair of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), faces criticism from a Ripple attorney, who refers to him as a "bad faith regulator" following the SEC's acceptance of Grayscale's Bitcoin Futures Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-up-15-as-market-focus-shifts-to-june-cpi-and-ppi-readings.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Up 1.5% as Market Focus Shifts to June CPI and PPI Readings&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-up-15-as-market-focus-shifts-to-june-cpi-and-ppi-readings.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119259/317203/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1662397"/></item><item><title>Litecoin's Strong Performance Before 'Halvening' Fuels Optimism for Bitcoin Rally</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoins-strong-performance-before-halvening-fuels-optimism-for-bitcoin-rally.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) investors are closely watching the performance of Litecoin (LTC), another proof-of-work token, as the flagship cryptocurrency gears up for its upcoming "halvening" event.  &lt;br /&gt;
The term "halvening" refers to the protocol-backed reduction in rewards for miners who successfully solve puzzles and add blocks to proof-of-work tokens like Litecoin and Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoins-strong-performance-before-halvening-fuels-optimism-for-bitcoin-rally.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin's Strong Performance Before 'Halvening' Fuels Optimism for Bitcoin Rally&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>Litecoin price</category><category>Halving</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoins-strong-performance-before-halvening-fuels-optimism-for-bitcoin-rally.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119277/317236/ltc-media-library-origina.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="201632"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Builds Strong Support at $1,800 Level – When is the Next Leg Up?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-builds-strong-support-at-1800-level-when-next-leg-up.htm</link><description>The Ethereum price has risen by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, with its move to $1,881 coming as the wider cryptocurrency market also sees a modest gain today. &lt;br /&gt;
ETH is now down by 3.5% in the past week but up by 7% in the last 30 days, with the altcoin holding firmly above the $1,800 support level in the face of recent market-wide losses....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-builds-strong-support-at-1800-level-when-next-leg-up.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Builds Strong Support at $1,800 Level – When is the Next Leg Up?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-builds-strong-support-at-1800-level-when-next-leg-up.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119271/317228/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1375174"/></item><item><title>Dubai Virtual Assets Regulator Imposes Enforcement Action Against Crypto Exchange BitOasis</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-virtual-assets-regulator-imposes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-exchange-bitoasis.htm</link><description>Dubai-based cryptocurrency exchange BitOasis, which received a minimum viable product (MVP) operational license from the UAE’s crypto regulator in April, is now facing enforcement actions from the authority. &lt;br /&gt;
Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) issued a market alert on July 10, indicating that BitOasis’ conditional MVP license has been suspended as the firm failed to meet mandated conditions set forth by the regulator....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-virtual-assets-regulator-imposes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-exchange-bitoasis.htm"&gt;Read More: Dubai Virtual Assets Regulator Imposes Enforcement Action Against Crypto Exchange BitOasis&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-virtual-assets-regulator-imposes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-exchange-bitoasis.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119269/317219/buildings-1839726-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="188449"/></item><item><title>South Korean Pop Star Says He Lost ‘$77,000’ on Crypto Investment</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-pop-star-say-he-lost-77000-crypto-investment.htm</link><description>Seo Chul-goo (aka Xitsuh), a South Korean pop star, rapper, and TV personality, says he “lost” up to $77,000 on bad crypto investments.  &lt;br /&gt;
The star and his fiancee Lee Young-joo appeared on the E Channel TV talk show “Love of a Lifetime” (literal translation), where he discussed his precarious financial situation.  &lt;br /&gt;
TVDaily quoted Lee as saying,...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-pop-star-say-he-lost-77000-crypto-investment.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Pop Star Says He Lost ‘$77,000’ on Crypto Investment&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Celebrities</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-pop-star-say-he-lost-77000-crypto-investment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119224/317130/eer1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="559283"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Police to Auction Assets Seized from Suspected Crypto Fraudsters</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-auction-assets-seized-from-suspected-crypto-fraudsters.htm</link><description>Police in Brazil have announced plans to auction off assets seized from Trust Investing, a suspected crypto-themed financial pyramid operator. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Portal do Bitcoin, a Federal Court in Campo Grande granted the authorities the right to auction off “seven luxury cars,” including armored vehicles. &lt;br /&gt;
The assets are valued at just under $288,000 and comprise BMWs, a Land Rover, and Porsches, as well as trucks and other cars....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-auction-assets-seized-from-suspected-crypto-fraudsters.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Police to Auction Assets Seized from Suspected Crypto Fraudsters&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Fraud</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-auction-assets-seized-from-suspected-crypto-fraudsters.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119095/316920/adobestock-193294139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="535660"/></item><item><title>DeFi Platform Arcadia Finance Falls Victim to $455K Hack on Ethereum and Optimism</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-falls-victim-455k-hack-ethereum-optimism.htm</link><description>Arcadia Finance has joined the growing list of DeFi protocols to lose funds in hack exploitation. The hackers leveraged a code vulnerability to siphon about $455,000 from the protocol’s Ethereum and Optimism vaults. &lt;br /&gt;
Blockchain sleuth PeckShield alerted about Arcadia’s exploitation in a July 9 tweet. In the tweet, PeckShield also highlighted the cause of the attack....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-falls-victim-455k-hack-ethereum-optimism.htm"&gt;Read More: DeFi Platform Arcadia Finance Falls Victim to $455K Hack on Ethereum and Optimism&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-falls-victim-455k-hack-ethereum-optimism.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119240/317175/computer-g1b843fd86-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="176673"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs Co-founder Faces Legal Proceedings: Trial Preparations Underway</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-faces-legal-proceedings-trial-preparations-underway.htm</link><description>Source: UDC / YouTube &lt;br /&gt;
Legal proceedings have been initiated against Shin Hyun-Seong, also known as Daniel Shin, concerning charges concerning alleged illicit profits from the sale of Terra (LUNA) tokens. &lt;br /&gt;
The co-founder of Terraform Labs, Daniel Shin, was indicted in South Korea on April 25 in connection with the collapse of Terra and Luna cryptocurrencies. Shin, along with co-founder Do Kwon, established Terraform Labs in 2018. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-faces-legal-proceedings-trial-preparations-underway.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs Co-founder Faces Legal Proceedings: Trial Preparations Underway&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Terra</category><category>Terra Luna</category><category>Terra Classic (LUNC)</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-faces-legal-proceedings-trial-preparations-underway.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119239/317185/screenshot-2023-07-11-010312.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="220288"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 10, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-1-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Woonen (WOOO) &lt;br /&gt;
BinanceRemoved Trading Pairs:POWR/BUSDQKC/BUSDSC/BUSDSTEEM/BUSD...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 10, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Trading</category><category>Exchange</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119210/317075/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Wobbles at $30,000 Support – Is a Larger Sell Off on the Way?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-wobbles-at-30000-support-is-larger-sell-off-way.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price is currently teetering around the crucial $30,000 support level, raising concerns about the possibility of a more significant sell-off. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency's stability at this critical juncture has attracted considerable attention among traders and investors, as they closely monitor its next move. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-wobbles-at-30000-support-is-larger-sell-off-way.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Wobbles at $30,000 Support – Is a Larger Sell Off on the Way?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-wobbles-at-30000-support-is-larger-sell-off-way.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119228/317154/10.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482367"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin's Optimism Fades as Turmoil and Interest Rates Present Challenges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoins-optimism-fades-as-turmoil-interest-rates-present-challenges.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) fell lower over the course of last week, as optimism faded among market participants in the face of potentially higher interest rates in the US. &lt;br /&gt;
The price of the number one cryptocurrency have largely been in an uptrend since news broke that the world’s largest asset manager BlackRock had filed to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the US....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoins-optimism-fades-as-turmoil-interest-rates-present-challenges.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin's Optimism Fades as Turmoil and Interest Rates Present Challenges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoins-optimism-fades-as-turmoil-interest-rates-present-challenges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119209/317076/bull-and-bear.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="164591"/></item><item><title>Volatility Shares Co-Founder: Spot Bitcoin ETF Will Attract New Investors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/volatility-shares-co-founder-spot-bitcoin-etf-will-attract-new-investors.htm</link><description>A spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded-funds (ETF) could mark a new phase of institutional investors entering the crypto market. &lt;br /&gt;
Justin Young, co-founder and president of Volatility Shares, has said that investors seeking exposure to Bitcoin are searching for the "easiest and most regulated way" to invest, adding that a spot ETF may be the most effective means of achieving this. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/volatility-shares-co-founder-spot-bitcoin-etf-will-attract-new-investors.htm"&gt;Read More: Volatility Shares Co-Founder: Spot Bitcoin ETF Will Attract New Investors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Bitcoin ETF</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/volatility-shares-co-founder-spot-bitcoin-etf-will-attract-new-investors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119220/317118/7391ce01e2-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96291"/></item><item><title>European Union's MiCA Legislation and its Impact on Stablecoin Adoption: Lawyers Raise Concerns</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/european-unions-mica-legislation-its-impact-stablecoin-adoption-lawyers-raise-concerns.htm</link><description>The European Union's Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) legislation, enacted on May 31, has generated praise and concerns within the crypto industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
While hailed as a groundbreaking regulatory framework for cryptocurrencies, there is growing apprehension regarding one particular aspect: the imposition of a daily transaction cap on private stablecoins....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/european-unions-mica-legislation-its-impact-stablecoin-adoption-lawyers-raise-concerns.htm"&gt;Read More: European Union's MiCA Legislation and its Impact on Stablecoin Adoption: Lawyers Raise Concerns&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>MiCA</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/european-unions-mica-legislation-its-impact-stablecoin-adoption-lawyers-raise-concerns.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119222/317126/adobestock-458520299-preview-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="417629"/></item><item><title>Binance Facilitates Crypto Deals for Indians in Rupees</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-facilitates-crypto-deals-for-indians-rupees.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange by market cap, is reportedly attracting traders in India, allowing them to buy and sell cryptos in Indian rupees. &lt;br /&gt;
The fund transfers are carried out from local bank accounts or services like Google Pay or by accepting cash....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-facilitates-crypto-deals-for-indians-rupees.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Facilitates Crypto Deals for Indians in Rupees&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-facilitates-crypto-deals-for-indians-rupees.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119214/317080/pexels-sohel-patel-68912.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1408597"/></item><item><title>Homer Simpson Meme Coin Pumps Up 30,000% But Experts Say it is a Scam While New Meme Coin Wall Street Memes Just Raised $13.9 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/homer-simpson-meme-coin-pumps-up-30000-but-experts-say-it-scam-while-new-meme-coin-wall-street-memes-just-raised-139-million.htm</link><description>Up over 30,000% in the past 24 hours, a new $HOMER token is the biggest crypto gainer today - however, according to DEXTools' audit, has a blacklist function. &lt;br /&gt;
That means some wallet addresses might not be able to trade normally, DEXTools explains. &lt;br /&gt;
As a result, some crypto experts are warning that the token could be a scam. &lt;br /&gt;
$HOMER was last trading around $0.000003, up around 3000x versus its levels this time one day ago in the $0.000000001 area....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/homer-simpson-meme-coin-pumps-up-30000-but-experts-say-it-scam-while-new-meme-coin-wall-street-memes-just-raised-139-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Homer Simpson Meme Coin Pumps Up 30,000% But Experts Say it is a Scam While New Meme Coin Wall Street Memes Just Raised $13.9 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Meme coin</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/homer-simpson-meme-coin-pumps-up-30000-but-experts-say-it-scam-while-new-meme-coin-wall-street-memes-just-raised-139-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119221/317121/wsm-web.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="698751"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 10 July – Compound, Maker, Cosmos Hub</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-july-compound-maker-cosmos-hub.htm</link><description>Crypto markets are mostly flat in a quiet start to the trading week. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last going sideways just to the north of the $30,000 level, while ether (ETH) was last going sideways just above $1,850. &lt;br /&gt;
Total cryptocurrency market cap was broadly unchanged on Monday around $1.18 trillion, as traders await key US inflation data on Wednesday that could impact expectations for Fed tightening in the coming quarters and thus trigger volatility....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-july-compound-maker-cosmos-hub.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 10 July – Compound, Maker, Cosmos Hub&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cosmos</category><category>ATOM</category><category>Compound</category><category>COMP</category><category>Maker</category><category>MKR</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-july-compound-maker-cosmos-hub.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119219/317104/bc10j.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="335873"/></item><item><title>Web3 AI-Intelligence Platform yPredict’s Product Rollout Going From Strength to Strength as $YPRED Presale Surges Towards $3 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-ai-intelligence-platform-ypredicts-product-rollout-going-from-strength-to-strength-as-ypred-presale-surges-towards-3-million.htm</link><description>Monday 10 July - Industry-leading AI-powered web3 market intelligence platform yPredict’s product rollout is going from strength to strength. &lt;br /&gt;
yPredict recently launched the platform’s first AI-powered tool, its Backlink Estimator. &lt;br /&gt;
The free preview of the tool was a remarkable success, receiving over 5,000 requests in the first 24 hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-ai-intelligence-platform-ypredicts-product-rollout-going-from-strength-to-strength-as-ypred-presale-surges-towards-3-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 AI-Intelligence Platform yPredict’s Product Rollout Going From Strength to Strength as $YPRED Presale Surges Towards $3 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-ai-intelligence-platform-ypredicts-product-rollout-going-from-strength-to-strength-as-ypred-presale-surges-towards-3-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119213/317081/ypred-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="468570"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Prediction as $400 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-400-million-trading-volume-comes-time-buy.htm</link><description>Despite nearly $400 million in trading volumes coming in on Monday as per CoinGecko, Solana (SOL) is down just over 1.0% on the day. &lt;br /&gt;
SOL/USD was last trading around $21 per token, nearly 7% lower versus weekend highs in the $22.50 area. &lt;br /&gt;
Solana, the cryptocurrency that powers the high-performance, smart-contract-enabled Solana layer-1 blockchain, found strong resistance at its early June highs over the weekend, hence the recent retracement....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-400-million-trading-volume-comes-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Prediction as $400 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-400-million-trading-volume-comes-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119212/317077/sol-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="588589"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: BIS Presents Seven-Point Plan to Prevent CBDC Cyber Attacks, Multiple Scam Warnings Are Issued, Preliminary Hearing for Terraform Co-Founder Daniel Shin Held on Monday</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bis-presents-seven-point-plan-to-prevent-cbdc-cyber-attacks-multiple-scam-warnings-are-issued-preliminary-hearing-for-terraform-co-founder-daniel-shin-held-on-monday.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bis-presents-seven-point-plan-to-prevent-cbdc-cyber-attacks-multiple-scam-warnings-are-issued-preliminary-hearing-for-terraform-co-founder-daniel-shin-held-on-monday.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: BIS Presents Seven-Point Plan to Prevent CBDC Cyber Attacks, Multiple Scam Warnings Are Issued, Preliminary Hearing for Terraform Co-Founder Daniel Shin Held on Monday&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>BIS</category><category>Hack</category><category>Scam</category><category>Fraud</category><category>ATM</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Arbitrum</category><category>USDC</category><category>Tether</category><category>USDT</category><category>Terra</category><category>Legal</category><category>Binance</category><category>DeFi</category><category>1Inch</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bis-presents-seven-point-plan-to-prevent-cbdc-cyber-attacks-multiple-scam-warnings-are-issued-preliminary-hearing-for-terraform-co-founder-daniel-shin-held-on-monday.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119169/317031/adobestock-jeromemaurice-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="287086"/></item><item><title>Decentralized Fiverr and Upwork Alternative Secures $1.5 Million in Presale Funding – Next Big Thing?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-alternative-secures-15-million-presale-funding-next-big-thing.htm</link><description>DeeLance is making waves in the crypto space as its native token, $DLANCE, has reached a significant milestone of $1.5 million in presale funding. &lt;br /&gt;
This remarkable achievement has garnered attention from retail and institutional investors, who are drawn to its potential as the next crypto asset to hit a moonshot in the coming days.  &lt;br /&gt;
The freelance marketplace is saturated with Web2-powered recruitment platforms like Fiverr and Upwork....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-alternative-secures-15-million-presale-funding-next-big-thing.htm"&gt;Read More: Decentralized Fiverr and Upwork Alternative Secures $1.5 Million in Presale Funding – Next Big Thing?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-alternative-secures-15-million-presale-funding-next-big-thing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119204/317061/deelance.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="190343"/></item></channel></rss>
