<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:50:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ripple (XRP) Rival Stellar (XLM) Becomes Minority Investor in MoneyGram</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-rival-stellar-xlm-becomes-minority-investor-in-moneygram/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stellar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266743</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/moneygram_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/moneygram_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SDF's commercial partnership with MoneyGram officially began in 2021.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Stellar Development Foundation (SDF) &#8211; the organization behind the Stellar network that facilitates cross-border transactions &#8211; announced becoming a minority investor in payments giant MoneyGram International.</p>
<p>The latest investment is the first of its kind made from SDF&#8217;s treasury which includes a position on MGI&#8217;s Board of Directors. Denelle Dixon, SDF CEO and Executive Director, will occupy that role, according to the official announcement.</p>
<h2>Stellar x MoneyGram</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://stellar.org/blog/sdfs-investment-in-moneygram-international" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">investment</a> was sourced from SDF&#8217;s internal cash reserve, Dixon said in a statement. This cash reserve is designated to support the operations of the non-profit organization rather than the Enterprize Fund, which targets investments in startups and emerging businesses.</p>
<p>The exec mentioned that the investment is expected to position SDF as a crucial player aiding MoneyGram in expanding its digital business, exploring blockchain technology, and contributing to the many other ways the fintech company allows consumers and businesses to transfer and manage money in nearly every country across the globe.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This is an exciting time for SDF and MGI, and I believe the opportunities will only grow. Continuing to build strong partnerships with organizations across the payments space puts SDF one step closer to achieving our mission of creating equitable access to financial services.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>MoneyGram and SDF&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stellar-lumens-xlm-spikes-12-after-news-of-a-partnership-between-moneygram-and-the-stellar-foundation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnership</a> dates back to October 2021, when the two joined forces to settle transactions with USDC stablecoin for instant and cheaper transactions.</p>
<h2>Bidding Ripple Adieu</h2>
<p>The payments firm previously partnered with Stellar&#8217;s direct competitor to leverage the RippleNet as part of the exchange settlements process for international remittances. MoneyGram also received financial incentives in the form of XRP in exchange for giving Ripple an equity stake in the company.</p>
<p>MoneyGram, however, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-and-moneygram-part-ways-amid-sec-litigation-while-xrp-eyes-0-50/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">severed its ties</a> with Ripple in March 2021, a few months after the SEC slapped the blockchain firm with a lawsuit over XRP. At that time, Ripple maintained that the decision to part ways was mutual and hinted at a potential rekindling once the legal spat was over.</p>
<p>While Ripple secured a partial victory against the SEC this year, MoneyGram has not yet revisited the idea of reinstating the partnership. With SDF, on the other hand, the payment company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/moneygram-to-partner-with-stellar-to-provide-stablecoin-remittances/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to offer stablecoin remittances last year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-rival-stellar-xlm-becomes-minority-investor-in-moneygram/" rel="nofollow">Ripple (XRP) Rival Stellar (XLM) Becomes Minority Investor in MoneyGram</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Team Announces Launch Of Shibarium Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shib-team-announces-launch-of-shibarium-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266984</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/shibainu_downtrend_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/shibainu_downtrend_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Shibarium mainnet is now live and ready for users and developers alike.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Wednesday, Shiba Inu (SHIB) developers appeared on stage at the Blockchain Futurist Conference in Toronto to discuss the “End Game” for Shibarium – the meme token’s metaverse and NFT-oriented layer 2 blockchain.</p>
<p>The team said that the Shibarium mainnet has gone live, allowing developers to begin building apps on the blockchain.</p>
<ul>
<li>The ecosystem will include “Shibdentities,” a proof of personhood solution that lets users retain control of their data and privacy.</li>
<li>Shibdentities can be used to create digital wills, which transfer assets to another user’s wallet after one person’s death is confirmed.</li>
<li>“We are building a decentralized, autonomous, digital nation state,” said the team during its keynote presentation.</li>
<li>Regarding the Shibarium metaverse, the ecosystem will feature “seamless transactions” and its “Shiboshi” NFTs.</li>
<li>Shibarium will also use an “super app” called the ShibaHub – a common location for accessing a users’ favorite dapps.</li>
<li>Like many layer 2 solutions, “Shibarium” aims to address the scaling issues and transaction costs that plague Ethereum’s base layer.</li>
<li>Until now, details about Shibarium’s technical development have been largely a mystery.</li>
<li>However, lead developer Shytoshi Kusama has provided many hints about what features it will include, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-pumps-after-lead-developer-shares-shibarium-update-details/" data-wpel-link="internal">real-world asset authentication</a>.</li>
<li>SHIB is currently the 13th largest crypto by market cap.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-team-announces-launch-of-shibarium-mainnet/" rel="nofollow">SHIB Team Announces Launch Of Shibarium Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Exec Calls for Tighter Regulations Against Crypto Firms Counterfeiting U.S. Dollars</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circle-exec-calls-for-tighter-regulations-against-crypto-firms-counterfeiting-u-s-dollars/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266818</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/circle_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/circle_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Disparte called for relevant federal legislation around stablecoins to protect consumers and prevent investors from companies with fake USD.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dante Disparte, the chief strategy officer and head of global policy of the second-largest stablecoin issuer Circle, has blasted crypto firms that create counterfeits of the U.S. dollar.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-15/circle-criticizes-crypto-firms-that-counterfeit-us-dollars" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, Disparte called for relevant federal legislation around stablecoins to protect consumers and prevent investors from companies with fake USD.</p>
<h2>Circle CSO Criticizes Firms That Counterfeit USD</h2>
<p>Disparte said the several bank failures in the U.S. earlier this year drove investors into unsafe and opaque crypto assets overseas, showing the need for sound monetary policy in the United States. He questioned the ability of any company to forge the USD using cryptographic methods, insisting that setting relevant rules would maintain transparency and ensure investor safety.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Candidly, should anyone anywhere be able to counterfeit U.S. dollar using cryptographic methods, or should there be a rule-set around competing with digital dollars on the internet where the safety and soundness and monetary policy of the United States is respected?” &#8211; he asked.</p></blockquote>
<p>Disparte’s remarks come as Circle’s USD Coin (USDC) sees a slump in its market dominance. The stablecoin, once favored by institutions, was negatively affected by its exposure to the now-bankrupt Silicon Valley Bank and worldwide regulatory scrutiny on crypto assets.</p>
<p>USDC’s supply has declined by more than 50% since June 2022, from $56 billion to around $26 billion. This has also affected its market share, which has dwindled significantly within the same period, while Tether – the largest stablecoin by market cap – continues to gain dominance.</p>
<h2>Circle Faces International Markets</h2>
<p>While USDC’s numbers are declining, Circle has disclosed its intention to face international crypto markets with Asia as the focus. In June, the company’s co-founder and CEO Jeremy Allaire <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-pays-close-attention-to-hong-kongs-crypto-policies-ceo-allaire-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> Circle is closely observing the regulatory developments in Hong Kong as the city aims to establish itself as a significant center for digital markets and stablecoins.</p>
<p>Most recently, Allaire <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-jeremy-allaire-estimates-majority-of-usdc-adoption-originates-beyond-us-borders/" data-wpel-link="internal">estimated</a> that 70% of USDC adoption originates from non-U.S. regions, with Asia, Latin America, and Africa leading the pace. However, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-will-become-a-highly-competitive-market-once-it-embraces-crypto-circle-ceo-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">believes</a> the U.S. will become a highly competitive market once its regulators embrace the crypto industry.</p>
<p>In the meantime, Circle and Tether are facing competition from newly issued stablecoins like that of digital payments giant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" data-wpel-link="internal">PayPal Holdings</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-exec-calls-for-tighter-regulations-against-crypto-firms-counterfeiting-u-s-dollars/" rel="nofollow">Circle Exec Calls for Tighter Regulations Against Crypto Firms Counterfeiting U.S. Dollars</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump&#8217;s True Crypto Holdings Are Worth Millions, New Filings Show</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/trumps-true-crypto-holdings-are-worth-millions-new-filings-show/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Donald Trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266976</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/donald_trump_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/donald_trump_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The former President’s reported crypto holdings have shot up to nearly $3 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated filings show that former President Donald Trump owns $2.8 million worth of cryptocurrency in his Ethereum wallet – a far higher amount than disclosures from earlier this month appeared to suggest.</p>
<p>The disclosures paint a different picture of Trump’s views on crypto than his public pronouncements about the asset class would seem to suggest.</p>
<h2>Trumps Crypto and NFT Earnings</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://www.citizensforethics.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Disclosure-Report-Part-38-14-23.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">submitted</a> to the Office of Government Ethics, entry 24 under Trump’s “Employment Assets and Income and Retirement Accounts” lists a series of items related to crypto and NFTs.</p>
<p>The item is titled “CIC Digital LLC (License fees for NFTs)” and is subdivided into three parts: One of those parts included his Ethereum crypto wallet, which contained $2,806,341 in assets at disclosure time.</p>
<p>Another part – listed as “License agreement with NFT INT, LLC” – related to Trump’s earnings from a non-fungible token (NFT) collection he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-reportedly-earned-up-to-1-million-from-his-latest-nft-collection/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> as part of his relaunched election campaign to return to the White House in 2024. This amount totaled $4,866,832.</p>
<p>The first installment of the collection performed well, even surging after Trump’s first indictment in early April. However, it crashed later that month when he announced the launch of a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-donald-trump-nfts-to-hit-the-market-again-but-heres-the-catch/" data-wpel-link="internal">second batch</a> of NFTs on Polygon.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, Trump’s OGE financial disclosure documents <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-holds-between-250k-and-500k-worth-of-eth/" data-wpel-link="internal">stated</a> that he owned between $250,000 and $500,000 in his ETH wallet. This wallet was also connected to his NFT collection.</p>
<p>Trump’s wife Melania has also dabbled in NFT sales, launching an <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/melania-trump-launches-an-nft-and-blockchain-venture-based-on-solana/" data-wpel-link="internal">NFT venture</a> on Solana in 2021 featuring digital and physical art. Part of the proceeds were used to raise money for children aging out of the foster care system.</p>
<p>Melania also announced a set of 10,000 official NFTs celebrating Trump on President’s Day last year, meant to highlight “iconic” moments of the Trump administration.</p>
<h2>Trump’s Past Claims About Crypto</h2>
<p>In July 2021, Trump told Fox Business that he thought Bitcoin looks like a “scam” and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-bitcoin-looks-like-a-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">criticized</a> it for competing with the US dollar.</p>
<p>“I want the dollar to be the currency of the world. That’s what I’ve always said,&#8221; he said at the time.</p>
<p>That being the case, Trump was more recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-bail-release-trump-predicts-the-us-dollar-will-lose-global-dominance/" data-wpel-link="internal">bearish</a> on the U.S. dollar’s status under the Biden administration, warning that its devaluation would lead to its loss of world reserve status.</p>
<p>Unlike Trump, the current Republican party is largely <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/republicans-blast-white-house-for-failure-to-compromise-on-stablecoin-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">supportive</a> of crypto, with several members of the party pushing for legislation to create a welcoming regulatory framework for the industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/trumps-true-crypto-holdings-are-worth-millions-new-filings-show/" rel="nofollow">Trump&#8217;s True Crypto Holdings Are Worth Millions, New Filings Show</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Layer-2 Solution Base&#8217;s Second-Largest DEX Eliminates Vulnerabilities After Exploit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-layer-2-solution-bases-second-largest-dex-eliminates-vulnerabilities-after-exploit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 20:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266529</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hack_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hack_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The team has eliminated the loophole, according to the latest update. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second-largest decentralized exchange on the newly released Base blockchain &#8211; RocketSwap &#8211; announced eliminating any existing high risks and vulnerabilities a day after sustaining a &#8220;brute force hack of the server&#8221; where the platform stored its private keys.</p>
<p>The RocketSwap team confirmed relinquishing minting rights, which is part of its recovery plan. In a new update, the protocol said it has retained only low-risk rights to allocate new pools. The locked initial liquidity and 80k tokens, on the other hand, have been extended for 1 year.</p>
<ul>
<li>On August 14th, hackers stole $865,000 or 471 Ether from RocketSwap and bridged it from Base to Ethereum, which was <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1691268504396374016" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">flagged</a> by blockchain security expert, PeckShield.</li>
<li>The entity behind the attack then generated 90 trillion tokens named &#8220;LoveRCKT&#8221; and proceeded to move them to Uniswap, along with 400 ETH.</li>
<li>The platform&#8217;s official <a href="https://twitter.com/RocketSwap_Labs/status/1691398314795929601" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> on the attack read,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;A brute force hack of the server was detected. Due to the proxy contract linked to our farm contract, multiple high-risk permissions became vulnerable. This resulted in the unauthorized transfer of the farm’s assets. Immediate steps were taken to shut down the farm and halt further potential risks.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The breach prompted RocketSwap to redeploy a new farm contract by dropping the proxy contract and open-sourcing it on-chain. As part of the emergency program, the DEX announced a new farm in a bid to advance the production reduction plan by 0.075 per block.</li>
<li>Among other things, RocketSwap also revealed its intention to call on the hackers to return the assets.</li>
<li>This was the second project on Coinbase-incubated layer 2 solutions, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-base-notches-4th-rank-in-daily-tps-among-layer-2-solutions-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Base,</a> to have suffered an attack.</li>
<li>Earlier this month, another DEX on Base called LeetSwap was drained off 342.5 ETH.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-layer-2-solution-bases-second-largest-dex-eliminates-vulnerabilities-after-exploit/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Layer-2 Solution Base&#8217;s Second-Largest DEX Eliminates Vulnerabilities After Exploit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal UK To Pause Crypto Purchases Until Early 2024</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-uk-to-pause-crypto-purchases-until-early-2024/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266964</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/PayPalUK.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/PayPalUK.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PayPal needs time to come into compliance with new standards established by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PayPal announced that it will temporarily suspend crypto purchases on its platform for its U.K. based users beginning in October.</p>
<p>The move comes in response to evolving regulatory guidelines provided by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) – Britain’s chief market regulator.</p>
<h2>PayPal Pauses Crypto Buys</h2>
<p>Per an <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Crib_/status/1691661748359614481" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">email</a> received by certain U.K. users on Wednesday, the suspension will take effect on October 1, and is expected to last until early 2024.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Your crypto remains safe,” clarified the company. “You can keep it on our platform at no charge. You can also sell your crypto at any time.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">PayPal will &#39;pause&#39; crypto purchases in UK <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1ec-1f1e7.png" alt="🇬🇧" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/NPkj7F61cC" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/NPkj7F61cC</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Crypto Crib (@Crypto_Crib_) <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Crib_/status/1691661748359614481?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>PayPal <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypals-u-k-customers-can-now-buy-sell-and-hold-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">enabled</a> crypto services for U.K. customers in September 2021, allowing them to buy, sell, and hold crypto. This followed its initial launch in the United States as early as October 2020.</p>
<p>To this day, supported assets are limited to Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Bitcoin Cash (BCH), and Litecoin (LTC). In Q1, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-holds-1-billion-in-crypto-on-balance-sheet-records-show/" data-wpel-link="internal">held</a> over $1 billion worth of these assets on its balance sheet o behalf of customers.</p>
<p>Though its crypto business model may seem simple, the FCA now requires crypto firms to “implement additional steps before customers can purchase crypto.” PayPal said it works closely with regulators to ensure that it stays compliant wherever it operates.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We apologize for the inconvenience,” said the company. “We will let you know when we have implemented the required changes to the crypto experience.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Compared to the United States, crypto companies have praised U.K. regulators and policymakers for embracing crypto, and helping provide a clear pathway to industry compliance.</p>
<p>In late June, the nation passed a bill <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-passes-bill-establishing-crypto-and-stablecoins-as-regulated-financial-activities/" data-wpel-link="internal">establishing</a> crypto and stablecoin businesses as within the regulatory perimeter, while giving the FCA authority to create a clear regulatory framework for the sector.</p>
<p>Last month, the FCA published <a href="https://www.fca.org.uk/publication/guidance-consultation/gc23-2.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">guidelines</a> claiming that crypto memes could potentially amount to criminal offenses if they did not comply with existing financial promotion laws.</p>
<h2>PayPal’s Stablecoin Startup</h2>
<p>PayPal’s latest foray into the crypto industry is an attempt to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> its own stablecoin, which will be pegged to the U.S. dollar.</p>
<p>Announced last week, PYUSD will be based on Ethereum and will be backed by cash, U.S. T-bills, and other cash equivalents. While currently only usable in crypto and Web 3-related activities, PayPal plans to popularize it for lost-cost transfers between users and merchants worldwide.</p>
<p>Shortly after the announcement, PayPal CEO Dan Schulman <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-week-following-stablecoin-introduction-paypal-appoints-new-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that he will step down from his position in late September.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-uk-to-pause-crypto-purchases-until-early-2024/" rel="nofollow">PayPal UK To Pause Crypto Purchases Until Early 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CFTC is Doing SEC&#8217;s Real Job on Crypto According to XRP Decision</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-is-doing-secs-real-job-on-crypto-according-to-xrp-decision/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266328</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cftc.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cftc.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC is seeking to appeal the Ripple ruling, while applications for a Bitcoin ETF are piling up. It seems the CFTC is doing the actual securities enforcement.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is leaving securities enforcement up to the CFTC when it comes to cryptocurrency. While the commission rushes ahead of Congress to write the entire federal crypto policy by lawsuit, the CFTC is going for more clear-cut violations.</p>
<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission took the lead late last week and filed charges of securities fraud against a cryptocurrency business in Florida. It <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8766-23" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed the</a> charges in the U.S. District Court for the Middle District of Florida.</p>
<h2>CFTC Charges Florida Residents for Crypto Scam</h2>
<p>The CFTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-people-charged-for-allgedly-defrauding-investors-in-crypto-and-precious-metal-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal">charged</a> four individuals in three states and their unregistered entity &#8220;Fundsz&#8221; with allegations of securities fraud Friday:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The complaint charges them with fraudulent solicitation from clients to purportedly trade in cryptocurrencies and precious metals.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The commission&#8217;s Director of Enforcement, Ian McGinley, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The CFTC continues to root out individuals who defraud customers in the cryptocurrency and precious metals markets.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>But the allegations faced by defendants in this case are actually within the purview of the SEC, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-cto-david-schwartz-breaks-down-howey-test-following-sec-appeal/" data-wpel-link="internal">according</a> to the Howey test in the recent Ripple court case.</p>
<h2>Commodity Futures Doing SEC&#8217;s Job</h2>
<p>This case is kind of like what <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-closer-look-at-what-sam-bankman-fried-is-accused-of-exactly/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried</a> is in trouble for with the law. It&#8217;s not that they the defendants were selling Fugazi and claiming it&#8217;s Rolex. It&#8217;s that they were selling Rolex and claiming it&#8217;s a really great Fugazi.</p>
<p>But it&#8217;s not so great when people lose their money to something they thought was less risky during a 75% Bitcoin price plunge.</p>
<p>These are clear cut allegations of selling unregistered and unregulated securities. It&#8217;s the sort of thing the SEC could actually be effective at enforcing.</p>
<p>McGinley warns crypto investors seeking online brokerages and crypto exchanges:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Though the products fraudsters purport to trade and their methods of attracting victims—in this case through social media—may have changed, the old adage ‘if something sounds too good to be true, it probably is’ remains as valid as ever.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>That advice is just as good for considering a rare <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-judge-crypto-is-baseball-cards-not-stocks/" data-wpel-link="internal">baseball card purchase</a> as a high flying stock buy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-is-doing-secs-real-job-on-crypto-according-to-xrp-decision/" rel="nofollow">CFTC is Doing SEC&#8217;s Real Job on Crypto According to XRP Decision</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bittrex CEO Cautions Against Celebratory Stance Following $24 Million SEC Settlement</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-ceo-cautions-against-celebratory-stance-following-24-million-sec-settlement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266867</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bittrex_US.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bittrex_US.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While Bittrex Global remains exempt from any financial obligation, its US division has agreed to pay a $24 million settlement with the SEC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bittrex reached a $24 million settlement with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Under this arrangement, Bittrex and Bittrex Global have settled with the federal regulator, agreeing to make payments totaling $14.4 million for disgorgement (repayment of unjust profits), $4 million for prejudgment interest, and $5.6 million in civil penalties to resolve the legal conflict.</p>
<p>Even though both parties were able to avoid the effort and cost of litigation, Bittrex CEO Oliver Linch said that &#8220;now is not the time for a victory lap.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Bittrex&#8217;s Statement After $24M Settlement</h2>
<p>While Bittrex&#8217;s US arm agreed to pay $24 million in the settlement, it will refrain from acknowledging or refuting the accusations and is also restricted from issuing any public communication that could imply the absence of a factual foundation for the SEC&#8217;s allegations.</p>
<p>Deeming the resolution to be a quick one, considering pending lawsuits against Binance, Coinbase, etc., Bittrex&#8217;s boss Linch said in a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230816932630/en/Bittrex-Global-Reaches-Successful-Settlement-with-the-SEC" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are delighted that a settlement on these terms has been quickly reached. While it is good news for Bittrex Global, now is not the time for a victory lap. Instead, with this matter behind us, we can concentrate on building our vision for the future of crypto, as a regulated, mature, and sophisticated part of the wider financial ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Linch asserted that Bittrex Global dedicated significant resources to ensure that they do not accept US customers. The exec went on to state that the company solely caters to clients and provides services exclusively outside the US.</p>
<p>He further added that Bittrex Global is a non-US-regulated digital assets exchange that market participants around the world should engage with &#8220;who are increasingly wary of having any connection to the United States given its regulatory uncertainty.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Lawsuit and Subsequent Backlash</h2>
<p>In an April filing, the SEC alleged that Bittrex&#8217;s US arm and its co-founder and former CEO, William Shihara, were involved in operating an unregistered national securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency. The financial regulator also initiated a distinct enforcement action against Bittrex Global for its management of a shared order book in conjunction with Bittrex.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange filed for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-bittrex-files-for-us-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy</a> in Delaware on May 8th, months after announcing it would shut down its operations in the country and weeks after being <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-receives-wells-notice-from-sec-for-violating-investor-protection-laws/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> by the SEC. The regulatory authority&#8217;s enforcement actions <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paradigm-criticizes-secs-actions-against-bittrex-in-new-amicus-brief-filing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">prompted</a> severe backlash from industry players.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-ceo-cautions-against-celebratory-stance-following-24-million-sec-settlement/" rel="nofollow">Bittrex CEO Cautions Against Celebratory Stance Following $24 Million SEC Settlement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Linera Blockchain Raises Additional $6M for Innovative Microchain Design Evolving from Meta’s Novi Research</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/linera-blockchain-raises-additional-6m-for-innovative-microchain-design-evolving-from-metas-novi-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266891</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-16_10-51-58_1692172380cppCtNUOYH.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-16_10-51-58_1692172380cppCtNUOYH.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; San Francisco, USA, August 16th, 2023] Linera reaches a total of $12M in seed funding. The new round of funding was led by Borderless Capital with contributions from a16z crypto, Laser Digital Ventures, Matrixport, Flow Traders, GSR Markets, and more Linera, the first blockchain network scalable via microchains, has successfully closed an [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; San Francisco, USA, August 16th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Linera reaches a total of $12M in seed funding. The new round of funding was led by Borderless Capital with contributions from a16z crypto, Laser Digital Ventures, Matrixport, Flow Traders, GSR Markets, and more</p>
<p><a href="https://linera.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Linera</a>, the first blockchain network scalable via microchains, has successfully closed an additional $6M round, led by Borderless Capital. Founded by Mathieu Baudet, former Meta researcher on the Novi digital payments wallet and a cryptographic protocols specialist, Linera&#8217;s pioneering technology aims to bring web2 scalability to web3 applications by introducing an unlimited number of user chains powered by an elastically scalable network.</p>
<p>Linera has now secured a total of $12M in seed funding, with the most recent $6 million follow-on investment round led by Borderless Capital. Notable participants include Laser Digital Ventures, DFG, Cadenza, Block1, Eterna Capital, MH Ventures, Matrixport, L2IV, ArkStream, Flow Traders, GSR Markets, and Open Web Collective (OWC), alongside continued support from a16z crypto, Tribe Capital, and Cygni Capital, who participated in the initial seed round.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Among new web3 architectures emerging like the move away from a single monolithic blockchain, Linera’s microchains are a completely new and necessary evolution. Further, Linera’s capacity for linear scaling is designed to support millions and conceivably billions of simultaneous transactions. And, while unprecedented, this kind of performance and reliability is essential for web3 to actually scale applications like payments, messaging, trading, AI, and more to billions of users around the world,&#8221; <strong>said Alpen Sheth, Senior Partner at Borderless Capital. </strong></p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Linera has made significant progress since we led their initial seed round last year, and we&#8217;re excited to expand our support for the project. Mathieu and the Linera team have designed a truly innovative multi-chain architecture that unlocks a broader design space for developers and their end users. We can&#8217;t wait to see how the ecosystem takes shape and the utilities it enables as Linera advances into the devnet and testnet phases,&#8221;<strong> said Ali Yahya, General Partner at a16z crypto.</strong></p></blockquote>
<p>Linera recently made its initial software development kit (SDK) available for testing, targeting Rust developers. Thanks to the new funding, Linera will be expanding the team, launching a devnet and a testnet for the protocol and fostering a strategic presence in the APAC region while continuing to grow their developer academy.</p>
<h2>From Microchains to Mass-Scalable Applications</h2>
<p>The competition for blockspace in traditional Layer 1 blockchains, coupled with limited production rates and block sizes, creates a bottleneck during traffic peaks, leaving users outpriced or delayed, rendering the infrastructure effectively unavailable.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’ve taken a step back to completely redesign a blockchain infrastructure that scales from the start,” <strong>said Mathieu Baudet, founder and CEO of Linera.</strong> “Linera’s unique multi-chain architecture ensures predictable performance, responsiveness, and robust security at Internet scale.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Linera empowers developers to create high-speed web3 applications used by a large number of active users in parallel, revolutionizing decentralized infrastructure for a variety of use cases, including retail payments, gaming micro-payments, messaging, proprietary trading, and blockchain bridges.</p>
<p>The Linera system scales by adding chains, not by increasing the size or the production rate of blocks. Its groundbreaking microchain model grants each individual user their own lightweight chains, which integrate into browser extensions or mobile devices for streamlined web3 app interactions within their wallets. During times of high demand, Linera&#8217;s validators expand dynamically like elastic web services.</p>
<p>Linera&#8217;s innovative design is rooted in the expertise that Mathieu Baudet acquired at Meta while contributing to the Libra (now Diem) blockchain and co-authoring the academic paper &#8220;FastPay&#8221;, which laid the foundations for the Linera protocol. Bernadette Cay, Linera&#8217;s COO, brings extensive experience in launching products from Google and MoPub, the mobile ad exchange acquired by Twitter.</p>
<h2>About Linera</h2>
<p>Linera is the first low-latency blockchain designed to scale elastically like web2 applications. Founded by Mathieu Baudet, a former Meta Novi engineer and researcher, with a PhD in cryptographic protocols, Linera revolutionizes blockchain scalability by introducing microchains, removing mempools, and minimizing validator interactions. Linera optimizes performance for web3 applications used by a large number of active users in parallel, enabling unprecedented horizontal scalability for use cases such as retail payments, gaming micro-payments, messaging, proprietary trading, and blockchain bridges.</p>
<p>Join us in creating the next generation of high-performance decentralized applications. Learn more at <a href="https://linera.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">linera.io</a></p>
<h2>About Borderless</h2>
<p>Borderless is a leading investment management firm focused on Web3 technology, dedicated to supporting the next generation of innovators who are driving the development of groundbreaking technologies that will enable the creation of value without borders. Borderless comprises a team of builders, partners, and investors who adopt a long-term perspective and strive to unleash the full potential of open, community-driven networks. Since 2018, Borderless has made 200+ investments across infrastructure, business applications, and nascent cryptographic protocols, and has played an integral role in the development of some of the most significant and innovative Web3 communities.</p>
<p>For more information, please visit their website at <a href="https://www.borderlesscapital.io/." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">borderlesscapital.io</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/linera-blockchain-raises-additional-6m-for-innovative-microchain-design-evolving-from-metas-novi-research/" rel="nofollow">Linera Blockchain Raises Additional $6M for Innovative Microchain Design Evolving from Meta’s Novi Research</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Short&#8217;s Michael Burry Bets Big on Stock Crash: Will Bitcoin Follow?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/big-shorts-michael-burry-bets-big-on-stock-crash-will-bitcoin-follow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266630</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Michael_Burry.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Michael_Burry.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Christian Bale might have a new movie contract soon.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Burry, one of the Tradfi banking industry&#8217;s most notorious bears, just put a $1.6 billion hit out on the U.S. stock market. What happens to bitcoin while the grownups are fighting?</p>
<p>The Scion Capital founder, who famously shorted mortgage-backed securities before the 2007 housing crisis, just gave the stock market a $1.6 billion shove of puts in SPY and QQQ!</p>
<h2>Michael Burry Bets $1.6B on Stock Market Crash</h2>
<p>Steve Anderson <a href="https://www.tipranks.com/news/the-big-short-redux-michael-burry-shorts-market-big" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">writes at</a> TipRanks:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Michael Burry made a name for himself by shorting the market to the point where they made a movie about him called &#8216;The Big Short.&#8217; But is he preparing for a time when lightning will strike twice?&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>During the U.S. subprime mortgage crisis, big bets against Wall Street&#8217;s housing market earned Burry $100 million in personal profit. His big contrarian trade made some $700 million in profits for his clients.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/big-shorts-michael-burry-says-he-was-wrong-to-say-sell/" data-wpel-link="internal">flipped bullish</a> and bought a bunch of finance stocks, but the market wizard behind Scion Capital is apparently very certain of a near-term stock market crash.</p>
<p>The sheer percentage of his portfolio Burry has devoted to this trade shows far more conviction than his long positions in banks earlier this year.</p>
<h2>How Would a Stock Market Crash Affect BTC?</h2>
<p>What could it mean for bitcoin&#8217;s price?</p>
<p>Stocks and bitcoin have followed <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-correlation-with-us-equities-at-2-year-low-potential-bullish-signal/" data-wpel-link="internal">various correlation</a> regimes, but it&#8217;s clear there&#8217;s some correlation. An event as massive as one Burry&#8217;s trade anticipates would be so global it would undoubtedly impact <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC</a>.</p>
<p>Most likely, a sell-off would ensue on the net as investors go for cash to make up for equities losses or go bargain hunting for stocks. But it could result in a rocketing resurgence of bitcoin&#8217;s price when stocks recover.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/BTC-USD/history?period1=1577836800&amp;period2=1609372800&amp;interval=1d&amp;filter=history&amp;frequency=1d&amp;includeAdjustedClose=true" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">what happened in</a> 2020, when gains on Wall Street were matched by bitcoin gains, only with massive leverage in the percentages.</p>
<p>While the market does digest news faster than ever, Scion&#8217;s big short is no cause for immediate alarm. It took years for the housing market to unwind, so a bear market as bad as Burry is predicting could be some time off yet. Additionally, he has had quite a few wrong predictions in the past.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/big-shorts-michael-burry-bets-big-on-stock-crash-will-bitcoin-follow/" rel="nofollow">Big Short&#8217;s Michael Burry Bets Big on Stock Crash: Will Bitcoin Follow?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
