<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Republican Tim Scott Announces His Run for President — How Could That Affect Crypto?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/republican-tim-scott-announces-his-run-for-president-how-could-that-affect-crypto.htm</link><description>Republican Sen. Tim Scott, who could be an influential player in the cryptocurrency industry, announced his run for US president on Monday. &lt;br /&gt;
The South Carolina lawmaker formally announced his run on Twitter as a crowd gathered in Charleston, South Carolina.  &lt;br /&gt;
Scott joins other candidates, including former President Donald Trump....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/republican-tim-scott-announces-his-run-for-president-how-could-that-affect-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Republican Tim Scott Announces His Run for President — How Could That Affect Crypto?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Tim Scott</category><category>Senate Banking</category><category>Presidential campaign</category><category>Biden</category><category>Trump</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/republican-tim-scott-announces-his-run-for-president-how-could-that-affect-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114635/276710/screen-shot-2023-05-22-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="609605"/></item><item><title>Ukraine’s Anti-corruption Bureau Unveils Plan to Fight ‘Crypto Corruption’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ukraines-anti-corruption-bureau-unveils-plan-to-fight-crypto-corruption.htm</link><description>Ukraine’s anti-corruption bureau has stated that it is probing the crypto sector to unmask money launderers. &lt;br /&gt;
In an official National Anti-corruption Bureau of Ukraine (NABU) release, the regulator said that it was teaming up with the United States Embassy for the drive. &lt;br /&gt;
The NABU said that its efforts would be “financially supported” by the US State Department’s Bureau of International Narcotics and Law Enforcement Affairs....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ukraines-anti-corruption-bureau-unveils-plan-to-fight-crypto-corruption.htm"&gt;Read More: Ukraine’s Anti-corruption Bureau Unveils Plan to Fight ‘Crypto Corruption’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ukraine</category><category>Corruption</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ukraines-anti-corruption-bureau-unveils-plan-to-fight-crypto-corruption.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114551/276568/adobestock-495573016.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="801643"/></item><item><title>BlockFi Sent Out Reorganization Plan ‘Prematurely,’ Court Orders Them Withdrawn</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-sent-out-reorganization-plan-prematurely-court-orders-them-withdrawn.htm</link><description>Bankruptcy cryptocurrency lender BlockFi took back statements it made earlier this month about a plan to reorganize which it said was done “prematurely.” &lt;br /&gt;
BlockFi released a “corrective letter to creditors” on Friday, directed by the court, asking them to disregard certain statements posted to the court docket, on its website and on Twitter. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-sent-out-reorganization-plan-prematurely-court-orders-them-withdrawn.htm"&gt;Read More: BlockFi Sent Out Reorganization Plan ‘Prematurely,’ Court Orders Them Withdrawn&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-sent-out-reorganization-plan-prematurely-court-orders-them-withdrawn.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114629/276704/pexels-ekaterina-bolovtso.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="114986"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 22 May – Render, Copium, Tron, AiDoge.com, Apecoin, Sponge, Ecoterra</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-22-may-render-copium-tron-aidogecom-apecoin-sponge-ecoterra.htm</link><description>With the crypto markets seeing less trading volume, Bitcoin's price fluctuations have mellowed lately. &lt;br /&gt;
However, on-chain data shows that long-term Bitcoin holders are continuing to hold on to their positions. &lt;br /&gt;
As a result, Bitcoin is presently trading within a tight price range. Given this, what are the best cryptos to buy now? &lt;br /&gt;
Typically a very volatile asset, Bitcoin's weekly price has stayed within a tight 4% range....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-22-may-render-copium-tron-aidogecom-apecoin-sponge-ecoterra.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 22 May – Render, Copium, Tron, AiDoge.com, Apecoin, Sponge, Ecoterra&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Render</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>Tron</category><category>AiDoge.com</category><category>ApeCoin</category><category>Sponge</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>RNDR</category><category>TRX</category><category>APE</category><category>AI</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-22-may-render-copium-tron-aidogecom-apecoin-sponge-ecoterra.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114636/276712/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>LUNC Burn Didn't Help Terra Classic Price, New Crypto Coin Burns 30% of Token Supply</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lunc-burn-cant-help-terra-luna-classic-price-new-crypto-coin-burns-30-of-token-supply.htm</link><description>The Terra Classic (LUNC) price has been in a downtrend throughout 2023 despite the LUNC coin burn, its total supply still 5.87 trillion tokens.  &lt;br /&gt;
New cryptocurrency Copium is burning 30% of its supply, aiming to achieve what the former Terra LUNA hasn't. Since the announcement of its token burn, the $COPIUM price has risen over 100%. &lt;br /&gt;
The meme coin has a total supply of 1 billion, so 300 million tokens will be burned....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lunc-burn-cant-help-terra-luna-classic-price-new-crypto-coin-burns-30-of-token-supply.htm"&gt;Read More: LUNC Burn Didn't Help Terra Classic Price, New Crypto Coin Burns 30% of Token Supply&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lunc-burn-cant-help-terra-luna-classic-price-new-crypto-coin-burns-30-of-token-supply.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114634/276709/copium-token-supply-burn.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="159094"/></item><item><title>TORN Price gets Lift After Tornado Cash Attacker Proposes to Reverse Governance Attack</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/torn-price-gets-lift-after-tornado-cash-attacker-proposes-reverse-governance-attack.htm</link><description>The price of crypto mixer Tornado Cash’s governance token TORN saw a strong recovery after the hackers behind a recent attack on the protocol appeared to offer to reverse the attack. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a post published in Tornado Cash’s governance forum by a user named Tornadosaurus-Hex, the attacker has posted “a new proposal to restore the state of Governance” on Tornado Cash....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/torn-price-gets-lift-after-tornado-cash-attacker-proposes-reverse-governance-attack.htm"&gt;Read More: TORN Price gets Lift After Tornado Cash Attacker Proposes to Reverse Governance Attack&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Tornado Cash</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/torn-price-gets-lift-after-tornado-cash-attacker-proposes-reverse-governance-attack.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114630/276707/tornado-cash.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="73171"/></item><item><title>In SEC emails, Ripple's XRP Still Doesn't Meet SEC's Security Standards</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-emails-ripples-xrp-still-doesnt-meet-secs-security-standards.htm</link><description>XRP, the cryptocurrency once issued by US fintech firm Ripple, has never fully met the Security and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) definition of a security, a citation from what some believe is an SEC email suggests....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-emails-ripples-xrp-still-doesnt-meet-secs-security-standards.htm"&gt;Read More: In SEC emails, Ripple's XRP Still Doesn't Meet SEC's Security Standards&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ripple</category><category>XRP</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-emails-ripples-xrp-still-doesnt-meet-secs-security-standards.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114625/276702/xrp.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1343801"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Debt Default Looms – Is BTC a Safe Haven?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-debt-default-looms-btc-safe-haven.htm</link><description>As the possibility of a US debt default looms, the Bitcoin price prediction gains increased attention.  &lt;br /&gt;
With the potential turmoil in the financial markets, investors are looking for safe-haven assets to protect their wealth.  &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin, as a decentralized and borderless digital currency, has been hailed by some as a potential store of value during uncertain times. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-debt-default-looms-btc-safe-haven.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Debt Default Looms – Is BTC a Safe Haven?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-debt-default-looms-btc-safe-haven.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114572/276599/22-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482636"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: May 22, 2023 - $RFD, $GEN, $BOB</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-may-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-may-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: May 22, 2023 - $RFD, $GEN, $BOB&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Trading</category><category>Exchange</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-may-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114585/276602/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Exchange Launches Crypto TV Campaign in Washington DC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-coinbase-launches-tv-campaign-washington-dc.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase is honing in on Washington DC with a new TV campaign set to launch this week promoting the future of crypto amid its own fight with US regulators. &lt;br /&gt;
In a black and white and almost two-minute long video, CEO Brian Armstrong lays out the benefits of crypto and calls out its “naive view.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-coinbase-launches-tv-campaign-washington-dc.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Exchange Launches Crypto TV Campaign in Washington DC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Brian Armstrong</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-coinbase-launches-tv-campaign-washington-dc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114622/276698/brian-armstrong-coinbase-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115644"/></item><item><title>Nevada Man Faces Time Behind Bars for Alleged Role in CoinDeal Scam</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nevada-man-faces-time-behind-bars-for-alleged-role-coindeal-scam.htm</link><description>The US Department of Justice (DOJ) has charged a Nevada man for his role in the multi-million-dollar CoinDeal investment scheme. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent press release, the DOJ said Bryan Lee conspired with CoinDeal leader Neil Chandran to defraud 10,000 investors out of $45 million. &lt;br /&gt;
The Nevada resident reportedly misled customers to invest in companies controlled by Chandran by claiming that they were about to be acquired by buyers with deep pockets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nevada-man-faces-time-behind-bars-for-alleged-role-coindeal-scam.htm"&gt;Read More: Nevada Man Faces Time Behind Bars for Alleged Role in CoinDeal Scam&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Nevada</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Scam</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nevada-man-faces-time-behind-bars-for-alleged-role-coindeal-scam.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114607/276645/129071560e.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96241"/></item><item><title>PSYOP Token Investors Lose Half Their Funds After ‘Scam' – Here’s Three Coins You Can Trust</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-investors-lose-half-their-funds-after-scam-heres-three-coins-you-can-trust.htm</link><description>Presale investors in Ben.eth’s unorthodox launch of the PSYOP meme coin appear to have lost out big time, with some losing half of their funds and others dubbing the token launch a “scam”. &lt;br /&gt;
On-chain analytics Twitter account @lookonchain examined the airdrops received by some of the PSYOP presale’s biggest investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-investors-lose-half-their-funds-after-scam-heres-three-coins-you-can-trust.htm"&gt;Read More: PSYOP Token Investors Lose Half Their Funds After ‘Scam' – Here’s Three Coins You Can Trust&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>PSYOP</category><category>Presale</category><category>Crypto Scam</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-investors-lose-half-their-funds-after-scam-heres-three-coins-you-can-trust.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114620/276697/ben-eth.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="378561"/></item><item><title>VanEck CEO Says “No Chance” on the Future of a Spot Bitcoin ETF in the US</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/vaneck-ceo-says-no-chance-future-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-us.htm</link><description>A bitcoin-spot exchange traded fund may not be in the cards for investors any time soon, VanEck CEO Jan van Eck alluded to last week.  &lt;br /&gt;
During the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami last week, Van Eck was asked what the likelihood of a spot bitcoin ETF in the US.  &lt;br /&gt;
His response was “no chance.” &lt;br /&gt;
Firms have been vying for a spot bitcoin ETF for years to no avail. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/vaneck-ceo-says-no-chance-future-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-us.htm"&gt;Read More: VanEck CEO Says “No Chance” on the Future of a Spot Bitcoin ETF in the US&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>VanEck</category><category>Etf Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/vaneck-ceo-says-no-chance-future-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114619/276694/pexels-pixabay-315788.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="211502"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as 21.5 Trillion SHIB Bought Last Week  – Can SHIB Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-215-trillion-shib-bought-last-week-can-shib-reach-1.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the Ethereum-based ERC-20 Shiba Inu dog-inspired meme coin at the heart of Shiba Inu’s web3 ecosystem, has seen choppy price action on Monday. &lt;br /&gt;
SHIB at one point rallied as high as the $0.000009 level once again, but has since fallen back to the $0.0000087 area, where it still trades higher by about 3% on the day. &lt;br /&gt;
Large buyers could be spurring the rebound....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-215-trillion-shib-bought-last-week-can-shib-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as 21.5 Trillion SHIB Bought Last Week  – Can SHIB Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-215-trillion-shib-bought-last-week-can-shib-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114616/276673/shib.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="701497"/></item><item><title>Terra Classic Price Prediction - Is LUNC Dead, Two Experts Predict 'Zero'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-price-prediction-is-lunc-dead-experts-predict-zero.htm</link><description>The day the Terra Classic price (LUNC) hit its 2022 top, two of the best crypto traders correctly predicted the bull run was over. &lt;br /&gt;
That was September 8th, when the LUNC price reached $0.000593 on Binance, and by mid October LUNC was trading over 50% lower, below the $0.0003 support level. &lt;br /&gt;
Update May 2023 - since writing this post, the Terra Classic price has dropped 75% further....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-price-prediction-is-lunc-dead-experts-predict-zero.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Classic Price Prediction - Is LUNC Dead, Two Experts Predict 'Zero'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-price-prediction-is-lunc-dead-experts-predict-zero.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/91040/227937/terra-classic-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="89451"/></item><item><title>New Religious Cryptos Pump - Are They Scams? God, Mary, Baby Jesus Coins Top Crypto Gainers Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-religious-cryptos-pumping-god-mary-baby-jesus-coins-top-crypto-gainers-today-dextools.htm</link><description>Three new meme coins with a religious theme were listed on Uniswap today, May 22nd - $GOD, $MARY and $BABYJESUS - making the top crypto gainers list on DEXTools. &lt;br /&gt;
Each has a low DEXTscore and some warnings under the contract details section of their DEXTools links - exercise caution when buying new DEX coins. &lt;br /&gt;
Jesus Coin (JESUS), launched last month, is also among the top trending cryptocurrency assets today on CoinMarketCap....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-religious-cryptos-pumping-god-mary-baby-jesus-coins-top-crypto-gainers-today-dextools.htm"&gt;Read More: New Religious Cryptos Pump - Are They Scams? God, Mary, Baby Jesus Coins Top Crypto Gainers Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-religious-cryptos-pumping-god-mary-baby-jesus-coins-top-crypto-gainers-today-dextools.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114601/276635/god-crypto-mary-baby-jesu.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="148880"/></item><item><title>Saudi Pepe Price Jumps 85% in 24 Hours as yPredict Rockets to $1.4m</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/saudi-pepe-price-jumps-100-24-hours-as-ypredict-rockets-14m.htm</link><description>The Saudi Pepe (SAUDIPEPE) price is up big in the last 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
The meme coin, which claims on its website to be the Arabic version of the popular Pepe meme coin and “Pepe’s best friend”, was last trading in the $0.00017s across Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs), up around 85% in the last 24 hours versus Sunday’s lows under $0.00010....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/saudi-pepe-price-jumps-100-24-hours-as-ypredict-rockets-14m.htm"&gt;Read More: Saudi Pepe Price Jumps 85% in 24 Hours as yPredict Rockets to $1.4m&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Saudi Pepe</category><category>SAUDIPEPE</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/saudi-pepe-price-jumps-100-24-hours-as-ypredict-rockets-14m.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114612/276659/ypred-presale.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="56765"/></item><item><title>Lido Proposes to Staking the Lido Protocol Token to Boost Utility and Sustainability</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lido-proposes-staking-lido-protocol-token-boost-utility-sustainability.htm</link><description>The Ethereum staking provider Lido has proposed a staking mechanism for its native LDO token in an effort to boost the utility and financial sustainability of the token. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the proposal, posted on Lido’s governance forum on May 17, the staking program will enable token holders to stake LDO in exchange for a share – worth approximately 20-50% – of Lido’s future earnings. &lt;br /&gt;
The proposal is written by a Lido community member who goes by the name Lidomaxi....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lido-proposes-staking-lido-protocol-token-boost-utility-sustainability.htm"&gt;Read More: Lido Proposes to Staking the Lido Protocol Token to Boost Utility and Sustainability&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Lido</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lido-proposes-staking-lido-protocol-token-boost-utility-sustainability.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114605/276657/lido.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="172085"/></item><item><title>Pepe Coin Price Gains Are Fragile But AiDoge.com Pumps to $11m For Its Meme Generator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-gains-are-fragile-but-aidogecom-pumps-11m-for-its-meme-generator.htm</link><description>As meme coins increasingly take main stage and become catalysts for the current memecoin season, PepeCoin ($PEPE) has become a skyrocket contender in the market. &lt;br /&gt;
Today's live price stands at $0.0414467, with a 24-hour trading volume of $651,993.92 USD. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite a decline of -3.26% in the last 24 hours, PepeCoin has displayed potential for a price rally, hinting at a bullish breakout from its wedge pattern....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-gains-are-fragile-but-aidogecom-pumps-11m-for-its-meme-generator.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin Price Gains Are Fragile But AiDoge.com Pumps to $11m For Its Meme Generator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-gains-are-fragile-but-aidogecom-pumps-11m-for-its-meme-generator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114594/276654/thumbnail-341910282-25731.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="80439"/></item><item><title>Malaysia Regulator Orders Crypto Exchange Huobi Global Limited To Stop Operations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/malaysia-regulator-orders-crypto-exchange-huobi-global-limited-stop-operations.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi Global Limited has to stop operations in Malaysia after its regulator found it was operating without being registered.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Securities Commission Malaysia on Monday said the exchange has to disable its website and mobile apps on platforms including the Apple Store and Google Play, according to a press release. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/malaysia-regulator-orders-crypto-exchange-huobi-global-limited-stop-operations.htm"&gt;Read More: Malaysia Regulator Orders Crypto Exchange Huobi Global Limited To Stop Operations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Huobi Global</category><category>Malaysia</category><category>Cryptocurrency Exchanges</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Bittrex</category><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/malaysia-regulator-orders-crypto-exchange-huobi-global-limited-stop-operations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114604/276644/adobestock-92828366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="420491"/></item></channel></rss>
