<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 21:47:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Funds Soak In $27 Million Inflows Following Positive Inflation Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-funds-soak-in-27-million-inflows-following-positive-inflation-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 22:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266413</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_cover-8.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_cover-8.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Two specific funds were responsible for most inflows: Canada’s Purpose Bitcoin ETF, and Switzerland’s 21Shares AG.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto fund inflows are running positive again after a three-week lull period, with the vast majority of capital rushing into Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<p>The renewed interest follows the release of inflation figures for July, which came in slightly better than expectations.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Funds Back In Profit</h2>
<p>According to CoinShares’ weekly digital asset flows <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-144-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-7d29c8c04df5" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, inflows to crypto funds totaled $28.5 million last week, with $27 million heading into Bitcoin. This follows a three-week period in which Bitcoin experienced $144 million in net outflows.</p>
<p>Other digital assets including Ether (ETH) and XRP also scored inflows last week of $2.5 million and $0.5 million respectively. The latter is now on its sixteenth week of consecutive inflows, with assets under management rising by 127% since the year began.</p>
<p>“We believe the improved sentiment is due to the recent US inflation data, which was slightly below expectations, signifying that a September rate hike is less likely,” CoinShares wrote.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and other digital assets fell consistently last year as the Federal Reserve embarked on the fastest rate hiking cycle in history, in order to quell record-high inflation.</p>
<p>With CPI <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-unfazed-as-cpi-for-july-increases-by-0-2-mom/" data-wpel-link="internal">back down</a> to 3.2% year over year, the Fed’s hiking cycle may finally have peaked, potentially marking a good time to invest. According to CME FedWatch Tool, the market i pricing in an 88% chance that the Fed will keep rates flat at 5.25% at its next September meeting.</p>
<h2>ETF Excitement</h2>
<p>The Bank of Canada – which closely tracks the decisions of the Federal Reserve – is also expected to keep its rate flat at 5% until the end of the year. CoinShares’ report noted that most crypto inflows last week ($24 million) went to Canada’s Purpose ETF, the world’s first Bitcoin spot ETF.</p>
<p>The only other country to see substantial inflows was Switzerland, at $7.9 million.</p>
<p>Excitement over a potential U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF began growing in June after BlackRock filed for the product, followed by Fidelity and others. The hype not only sent BTC above $30,000 but led to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-investment-products-attract-highest-inflows-since-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">multiple weeks of inflows</a> to Bitcoin funds totaling $742 million.</p>
<p>ETF analysts at Bloomberg currently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloomberg-boosts-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval-odds-to-65-heres-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">assign</a> a 65% likelihood of a Bitcoin spot ETF being approved in 2023.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-funds-soak-in-27-million-inflows-following-positive-inflation-data/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Funds Soak In $27 Million Inflows Following Positive Inflation Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Supporter Javier Milei Wins Primary Presidential Elections in Argentina</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-supporter-javier-milei-wins-primary-presidential-elections-in-argentina/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 21:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266160</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the results, the bitcoin-loving far-right candidate has the best chance to become Argentina's next president.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Javier Milei &#8211; a 52-year-old Argentine politician, businessman, and economist &#8211; collected the most votes in the country&#8217;s primary presidential elections. The leader of the political coalition La Libertad Avanza (Freedom Advances) is a keen advocate of bitcoin and a fierce opponent of the central bank.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He has also gained popularity due to a crypto scandal involving the dubious digital asset platform called CoinX. Milei advertised the entity on his Instagram account in December 2021, whereas the Argentine authorities halted its activities a few months later, claiming it had no legal permission to operate inside the country&#8217;s borders.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">High Chances to Become President</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Arguably the most eccentric presidential candidate in Argentina &#8211; Javier Milei &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2023-argentina-election/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">amassed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> over 7 million votes (over 31.5% of the overall support) in the open primaries, held approximately two months before the general election. The center-right political coalition Together for Change (which has still not outlined its nominees) ranked second.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that Milei has won a decisive victory in almost every Argentine region apart from the capital Buenos Aires, where Utility for the Homeland (the party behind the current President Alberto Fernandez) got the majority of the votes. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Serving as the next political leader of the South American nation sounds like a tough job considering the triple-digit inflation, the increasing poverty line, and the overall economic downfall that has spread throughout the region. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Milei has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/alexstanczyk/status/1611010925401903104?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1611010925401903104%7Ctwgr%5E7939f4de0f665cb171542fe3fd7e358d9cf07d63%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fcointelegraph.com%2Fnews%2Fbitcoiner-javier-milei-wins-argentina-presidential-primary" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">opposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the controversial policies conducted by the central bank, calling the financial institution a &#8220;scam.&#8221; He also displayed himself as a proponent of bitcoin, arguing that Argentina could solve some of its issues by opening its arms toward it:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The point is that the first thing we have to understand is that the central bank is a scam. It is a mechanism by which politicians cheat to the good people with the inflationary tax. What bitcoin is representing is the return of money to its original creator: the private sector&#8230;</span></p>
<p>Bitcoin has an algorithm that one day it will reach a certain amount, and there is no more, and it can compete with other currencies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_266209" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266209" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266209" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei.webp" alt="Javier Milei" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei.webp 770w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei-300x200.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei-768x512.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Javier-Milei-50x33.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266209" class="wp-caption-text">Javier Milei, Source: Al Jazeera</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Argentines seem to have had enough of their financial problems and are willing to give a chance to the peculiar Milei, whose nickname is &#8220;el Peluca&#8221; (the Wig) because of his bizarre hairstyle. In fact, many locals have already </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/argentines-embrace-crypto-following-resignation-of-economy-minister/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hopped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on the cryptocurrency bandwagon, converting their depreciating pesos into BTC or USDT to preserve their net worths from the unrelenting inflation. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Scandal Involving Milei</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides his positive comments on bitcoin, the far-right presidential candidate made the headlines last summer when a group of harmed CoinX investors </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/argentina-presidential-candidate-sued-for-promoting-a-crypto-ponzi-scheme/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> him for promoting a fraudulent cryptocurrency project.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The individuals maintained that they parted with around $300,000 after Milei advertised the platform on his Instagram account, thus prompting them to invest. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CoinX promised significant returns for its users and claimed it had gathered a team of professionals to give customers the best advice. However, Argentina&#8217;s National Securities Commission (CNV) terminated its operations since it lacked the necessary authorization to provide services in the country.</span></p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of CNN</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-supporter-javier-milei-wins-primary-presidential-elections-in-argentina/" rel="nofollow">BTC Supporter Javier Milei Wins Primary Presidential Elections in Argentina</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lelantus Spark: Redefining Blockchain Privacy</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lelantus-spark-redefining-blockchain-privacy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 20:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266290</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin network is designed to foster some level of anonymity, allowing users to perform transactions globally without revealing their true identity. Despite this, the blockchain network is not private, as transactions are publicly open to everyone. Anyone can also identify the total Bitcoin holdings of any wallet address. Like the Bitcoin protocol, most blockchains [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bitcoin network is designed to foster some level of anonymity, allowing users to perform transactions globally without revealing their true identity. Despite this, the blockchain network is not private, as transactions are publicly open to everyone. Anyone can also identify the total Bitcoin holdings of any wallet address.</p>
<p>Like the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-for-beginners/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin protoco</a>l, most blockchains today are public. This means that transactions and other on-chain data that should otherwise be private easily become public knowledge.</p>
<p>Blockchain project Firo introduces a solution to fix this problem. Through its new privacy protocol dubbed Lelantus Spark, the company aims to solve the issue of private on-chain transactions.</p>
<h2>Introducing Lelantus Spark</h2>
<p>Lelantus Spark (also called Spark) is a privacy protocol developed by Firo developers. Firo (formerly known as Zcoin) is a blockchain project that uses cryptography to build a private ecosystem for its users.</p>
<p>The Lelantus Spark project has <a href="https://firo.org/2021/08/24/presenting-lelantus-spark.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">been in the works</a> since August 2021. It came as part of further development of the project’s Lelantus v1/v2 protocol. Combining existing key features in the former protocol and adding new features to the new protocol, Lelantus Spark is positioned at the forefront of privacy protocols deployed on the blockchain. These privacy-preserving features include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Spark addresses</li>
<li>Multisignature operations</li>
<li>View keys</li>
<li>Modular design</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Spark Addresses</strong></h3>
<p>The Spark address is a stealth address that masks a user’s public key by using cryptography to generate a one-time wallet address. Anyone can send crypto assets like Firo from transparent addresses to Spark addresses. With the Spark addresses, users can conceal their total holdings in the wallet and details about the transactions they make, such as the amount, time of the transaction, and history of the flow of the transferred asset.</p>
<p>Most public blockchains have an explorer that allows anyone to view the transferred amount and time of the transaction. In Lelantus v1, users need to manually anonymize any funds received.</p>
<p>However, Lelantus Spark uses Spark addresses to bolster anonymity with ease. This feature ensures that third parties cannot identify the sender or receiver of a cryptocurrency without using additional external information.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-162868" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1.jpg" alt="firo_cover1" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/firo_cover1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h3><strong>Multisignature Operations</strong></h3>
<p>Multisignature operations enable several trustless entities to cooperatively generate, receive, and sign transactions tied to a multisig address.</p>
<p>Lelantus Spark supports multi-signature operations through a modified Chaum-Pedersen discrete logarithm zero-knowledge proof. Decentralized exchanges and custodians are beneficiaries of the multi-signature operation. It can also be used in cases where more than one party is needed to approve a transaction.</p>
<h3><strong>View Keys</strong></h3>
<p>A view key is a valuable feature that allows wallet owners and creators of stealth addresses to willingly grant third parties access to see incoming and/or outgoing transactions to/from their wallet addresses without the ability to spend those funds</p>
<p>The feature is useful for accounting, auditing, and benefactor purposes. Offloaded scan services can also be used on online and mobile wallets.</p>
<h3><strong>Modular Design</strong></h3>
<p>Lelantus Spark’s dynamic design allows it to use several layers of privacy, relying on well-established cryptographic time-tested building blocks. These include Pedersen commitments, range proofs, zero-knowledge proofs, and discrete logarithm equality proofs that enable straightforward security analysis without needing trusted setup processes.</p>
<h2>Lelantus Spark Goes Live on Testnet</h2>
<p>In mid-July 2023, Firo announced its plan to launch the Lelantus Spark testnet after undergoing a series of cryptographic and implementation audits.</p>
<p>The testnet will allow public users to test the protocol in a safe and controlled ecosystem before it gets deployed on the mainnet. During this period, the developer team will gather data and feedback that will be used to make necessary adjustments to the protocol to make it as secure, private, and user-friendly as possible.</p>
<p>The Lelantus Spark testnet was <a href="https://firo.org/2023/07/31/lelantus-spark-testnet-launched.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">launched</a> on July 31st. Participants in the testnet will be offered incentives for engaging in the project’s bug bounty program and mainnet Firo token rewards incentives. There will also be other fun quizzes that will bring the Spark community members together.</p>
<h2>Final Thoughts</h2>
<p>Firo’s Lelantus Spark highlights the company’s commitment to bringing its privacy-loving users to more secure and private mediums of funds transfer. The project achieves this by building new tools and modifying existing ones to maintain a private blockchain experience.</p>
<p>As the protocol progresses from testnet to mainnet, Spark grounds itself as a haven from public blockchain networks that litter the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lelantus-spark-redefining-blockchain-privacy/" rel="nofollow">Lelantus Spark: Redefining Blockchain Privacy</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Asked X Follower &#8216;Choose New Bill&#8217; and Half the Replies Were Crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-asked-x-follower-choose-new-bill-and-half-the-replies-were-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266008</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Fidelity.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Fidelity.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto community was quick to intercept Fidelity's latest question to its X followers.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity recently asked its X followers to choose a new bill denomination. Two hours later, more than half the answers were cryptocurrencies. It&#8217;s another sign of crypto&#8217;s ascendance in the global economy.</p>
<p>The trillion-dollar multinational finance company wanted to know what new bill denomination their social media followers would come up with:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">You get to choose a new bill denomination (don&#8217;t ask, just roll with it). What are you choosing, and why?</p>
<p>— Fidelity Investments (@Fidelity) <a href="https://twitter.com/Fidelity/status/1690015270117560320?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>It must have been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/margot-robbie-says-bitcoin-has-ken-energy-as-quip-appears-canonical-to-barbie-film/" data-wpel-link="internal">such Kens</a> replying. Within two hours, more than half the answers were about crypto.</p>
<h2>&#8216;$BTC, and #DOGECOIN, and $Sats&#8230;&#8217; oh my!</h2>
<p>BTC and SATS were among the top replies in the resulting tweet thread. Moreover, someone was relegated to the &#8220;offensive content&#8221; link at the bottom of the mentions for spamming Fidelity&#8217;s post with too many Dogecoin replies.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, someone with the display name of Lee answered, &#8220;If you’re asking about dollars, it’s zero. That’s ultimately what they’re worth,&#8221; and signed the terse missive &#8220;#Bitcoin.&#8221;</p>
<p>Although there were the Tradfi answers Fidelity probably expected as well as crypto answers &#8211; like a $200 bill or $1,000 bill. But most of those answers dogged the Fed for inflation.</p>
<p>It may be telling that the inflationary answers like those examples outnumbered the ones given in 1990s prices like: &#8220;$25. A multiple of the $50 bill just makes things easier.&#8221;</p>
<p>Although someone with a winky Guy Fawkes mask profile pic did say we&#8217;ll need a trillion-dollar bill soon.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">$5 trillion.<br />
We&#8217;ll need a bill worth more than the $1 trillion platinum coin the Treasury wants to mint.</p>
<p>— Joel Jorgensen (@JoelJorgensen) <a href="https://twitter.com/JoelJorgensen/status/1690052723821944849?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>But that wasn&#8217;t exactly a joke or satire. Some have <a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/01/19/1149924318/would-a-trillion-dollar-coin-buy-time-to-resolve-the-debt-ceiling-debate" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">seriously pitched</a> minting a trillion-dollar U.S. coin. That would, of course, devalue the dollar <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/40-yearr-high-inflation-surged-another-100bps-in-june-tailwind-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">even more</a> to pay off the national debt.</p>
<h2>A &#8216;Normie&#8217; Pitches Smart Contracts to Fidelity on X</h2>
<p>One of the answers to Fidelity&#8217;s conversation prompt, a $69-dollar-bill, was very nerdy even for finance discussions. It was most likely a joke about asymptotic functions and simple fractions.</p>
<p>The replier&#8217;s display name was set to &#8220;Crypto Patriot.&#8221; Blockchain investors and engineers encounter this figure frequently as a result of the work they do with basic math and computers all day.</p>
<p>But another funny answer for a new denomination, whether the replier knows it or not, is something that&#8217;s actually possible in blockchain with smart contracts: &#8220;$12 tip included.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">You get to choose a new bill denomination (don&#8217;t ask, just roll with it). What are you choosing, and why?</p>
<p>— Fidelity Investments (@Fidelity) <a href="https://twitter.com/Fidelity/status/1690015270117560320?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Fidelity is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-vaneck-invesco-amend-bitcoin-spot-etf-filings-following-secs-warning-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">currently awaiting</a> regulatory approval for a spot BTC ETF. The company began to roll out its current menu of BTC and ETH brokerage, custody, and trading services in 2018.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-asked-x-follower-choose-new-bill-and-half-the-replies-were-crypto/" rel="nofollow">Fidelity Asked X Follower &#8216;Choose New Bill&#8217; and Half the Replies Were Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Won&#8217;t Joe Rogan Host A Bitcoin-Focused Podcast? (Op-Ed)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-wont-joe-rogan-host-a-bitcoin-focused-podcast-op-ed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266395</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/JoeRogan1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/JoeRogan1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It's not because he’s not interested – he just doesn’t want more controversy.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Famous podcast host and MMA commentator, Joe Rogan, is no stranger to Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<p>Having mentioned it in numerous conversations already, both he and his guests have praised the asset before for its absolute scarcity and freedom-focused properties, while contrasting it against the controlling nature of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/joe-rogan-and-post-malone-raised-concerns-of-a-potential-launch-of-cbdc-in-america/" data-wpel-link="internal">Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs)</a>. He’s even <a href="https://ca.news.yahoo.com/joe-rogan-reportedly-accepts-100-181807503.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">accepted</a> BTC as payment for one of his comedy shows.</p>
<p>That said, the podcaster’s remarks on Bitcoin are often only in passing. Despite popular demand, he seemingly neglects to host any experts on his show to explain its benefits at length, or to answer common questions about the technology – which he’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/joe-rogan-i-have-a-lot-of-hope-for-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">confessed</a> to not understanding very well.</p>
<p>What might be keeping Rogan from hosting Bitcoin-dedicated podcasts with experts in the field? To answer, let’s examine his only historical exception to the rule so far.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265642" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265642" style="width: 960px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Joe-Rogan.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-265642 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Joe-Rogan.webp" alt="" width="960" height="768" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Joe-Rogan.webp 960w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Joe-Rogan-300x240.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Joe-Rogan-768x614.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Joe-Rogan-50x40.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265642" class="wp-caption-text">Joe Rogan.</figcaption></figure>
<h2>The Andreas Episodes</h2>
<p>Rogan has hosted at least three podcasts focused on Bitcoin so far – all with the popular blockchain expert and author, Andreas Antonopolous.</p>
<p>In the most recent of those interviews, the men talked about Bitcoin’s place in hyperinflationary environments, its lack of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-wood-explains-how-bitcoin-can-reach-1-5-million-by-2030/" data-wpel-link="internal">counterparty risk</a>, the implications of a cashless society, and so on.</p>
<p>That discussion, however, was in 2016 – when Bitcoin’s price was still below $1000, and corporate adoption of crypto was a fraction of today’s. Even then, Rogan was giving Bitcoin a fair shake, and exposing his audience to the idea.</p>
<p>While Antonopolous has mostly stepped out of the spotlight since that time, a slew of new corporate and intellectual voices have stepped in to advocate for Bitcoin and digital assets at large. Yet this rise to prominence may be exactly why Rogan has sidestepped the topic entirely.</p>
<h2>The Rise of Altcoins</h2>
<p>Back in 2016, Bitcoin also consumed nearly the entire crypto market. According to <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/symbols/BTC.D/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">TradingView</a>, the asset’s market dominance was above 95% at the time.</p>
<p>Today, that figure has shrunk to 50%. Other major digital assets now breathe the same air as Bitcoin, including smart contract platforms like Ethereum (ETH), stablecoins like Tether (USDT), and non-fungible token (NFT) collections.</p>
<p>Like Bitcoin, Rogan has mentioned these alternative assets in more recent conversations – but he’s not quite the same fan.</p>
<blockquote><p>“It’s a weird hustle,” he said about NFTs in 2021. “I think it’s like a cryptocurrency hustle. It doesn’t make any sense to me… I can have that photo and I can have it on my phone.”</p></blockquote>
<p>On other occasions, Rogan has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YeTw9WuvxJk&amp;ab_channel=SwanBitcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">admitted</a> to having “a little bit of Bitcoin,” and acknowledged it as “semi-tangible,” while expressing confusion over the thousands of other cryptos and tokens, such as Dogecoin (DOGE).</p>
<p>While no hardened expert, Rogan’s reservations about some cryptos compared to others reflects disagreements within the crypto industry as well. To this day, community leaders continue to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/whats-better-than-bitcoin-jack-dorsey-to-coinbase-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">dispute</a> the role of other crypto compared to Bitcoin regarding value storage, transactions, scaling, DeFi, and other roles.</p>
<h2>Political Implications</h2>
<p>As a host, launching a Bitcoin-focused episode in this climate creates complications and controversy that weren’t present when he discussed the topic years ago.</p>
<p>For example, by hosting a podcast with self-proclaimed “Bitcoin maximalist” and billionaire <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-thinks-the-sec-crackdown-could-boost-bitcoins-dominance-to-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">Michael Saylor</a>, Rogan might be labelled a maximalist himself, and be subject to all the criticism that comes with that. Similar events have occurred in the past in the realm of politics, where Rogan has been labelled “<a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/joe-rogan-is-mainstreaming-right-wing-misinformation" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">far right</a>” for hosting conservative voices like <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jordan-peterson-bitcoin-is-the-only-alternative-to-a-cbdc/" data-wpel-link="internal">Jordan Peterson</a> and Ben Shapiro on his show.</p>
<p>In fact, we’ve already seen another podcaster face the same fate. After hosting Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin on his show years ago, Lex Friedman has since been pressured into hosting dissenting voices from across the space. Some of these guests have included Michael Saylor, Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson, Bitcoin Standard author Saifedean Ammous, and others.</p>
<p>However, in hosting such guests, Friedman has found himself further embroiled in online drama, which has even prompted him to release <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yB5WGV4zlgw&amp;ab_channel=LexClips" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">video messages</a> directly criticizing Bitcoiners for their “style of discourse”</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Given Rogan’s history with controversy already, and the example set by Friedman, its likely the podcaster is attempting to entirely sidestep this conflict before entering it.</p>
<p>Though Rogan appears to hold more pro-Bitcoin opinions on the subject right now, expressing these in the form of a dedicated podcast could invite backlash from rivalling communities that he may not like. He may then feel compelled to invite altcoin supporters (ex. Vitalik, Hoskinson, etc) to create a “balance” of voices – whether or not he’s actually interested in doing so.</p>
<p>Bitcoin expert Jimmy Song put it succinctly in a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/jimmysong/status/1689421114953342976" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Twitter post</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The controversy will remain on Bitcoin versus altcoins and that&#8217;s not something he&#8217;ll be able to avoid. He needs more conviction before he&#8217;ll talk about it on his show and that&#8217;s not something he has yet.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Until Rogan cares enough to enter the flames of that controversy, it&#8217;s likely best not to pester him further for a Saylor episode anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-wont-joe-rogan-host-a-bitcoin-focused-podcast-op-ed/" rel="nofollow">Why Won&#8217;t Joe Rogan Host A Bitcoin-Focused Podcast? (Op-Ed)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pepe Coin Price Dips, But Wall Street Memes Nears $24 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-price-dips-but-wall-street-memes-nears-24-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266382</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pepe_wsm_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pepe_wsm_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto market continues to struggle, with Bitcoin trading sideways near the $29,300 price level and major altcoins like Ethereum and Solana adopting a slightly bearish stance. The bull rally in major meme coins has come to a halt as well &#8211; both Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are seeing selling pressure in the daily time [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market continues to struggle, with Bitcoin trading sideways near the $29,300 price level and major altcoins like Ethereum and Solana adopting a slightly bearish stance.</p>
<p>The bull rally in major meme coins has come to a halt as well &#8211; both Dogecoin and Shiba Inu are seeing selling pressure in the daily time frame, correcting 2.2% and 1% respectively.</p>
<p>Pepe coin has also been unable to carry its bullish momentum and is facing a crucial resistance at $0.14. Nevertheless, experts believe that Pepe coin is poised to continue its positive trajectory and can regain its $1 billion market capitalization.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the new meme token Wall Street Memes is displaying huge potential, with it now very closely to hitting the $24 million milestone in its ongoing ICO.</p>
<h2><strong>Is The Pepe Rally Over As It Turns Bearish?</strong></h2>
<p>After a high-flying 22% pump, Pepe coin is currently stuck at the $0.0000014 price mark and has also seen a marginal 0.5% correction over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266385" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-18.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="305" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-18.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-18-300x152.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-18-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Despite an explosive 40% surge in its 24-hour trading volume, the token continues to hover near the $550 million market capitalization.</p>
<p><a href="https://in.tradingview.com/symbols/PEPEUSDT/technicals/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">TradingView</a>, a technical analysis platform, continues to give a Buy signal to Pepe coin in the daily time frame. However, it would need to breach its 50-day Simple Moving Average and 100-day Exponential Moving Average at $0.00000144 to see any further bullish continuation.</p>
<p>It is also at risk of falling below its 50-day Exponential Moving Average at $0.00000138, which can lead to more downward movement.</p>
<p>Popular crypto trader <a href="https://twitter.com/MTI_Trading/status/1691020503677382656?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">@MTI_Trading</a> is also dubious about whether Pepe would be able to flip a crucial resistance at $0.00000146.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the meme coin rally may face obstacles from the broader crypto market, as ex-SEC official John Reed Stark believes that the US Securities and Exchange Commission will likely <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1690707913789112320?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Etweet" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reject all the Bitcoin spot trading applications</a>. The SEC has already delayed their decision on ARK investment’s application and experts believe that other applications will likely go the same route.</p>
<p>The latest Bitcoin and crypto bull run was a result of major TradFi institutions like BlackRock applying for BTC spot trading options. A rejection from the SEC can see major crypto assets retrace their entire pump and enter deeply bearish territory.</p>
<p>The history of the crypto market also proves this assessment. In 2018, Bitcoin and major altcoins saw a sharp decline after the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/winklevoss-twins-bitcoin-etf-rejected-by-sec.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">SEC rejected the Gemini exchange’s</a> BTC spot trading request.</p>
<p>However, other experts are much more bullish on the token. Popular analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoKaleo/status/1690703555819175937?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">@CryptoKaleo</a>, who has close to 600K followers on Twitter, has revealed that the Pepe breakout is just starting and the token will soon regain its $1 billion market capitalization.</p>
<h2><strong>Wall Street Memes Token Set to Hit $24 Million Mark In Presale &#8211; Next 10x Meme Coin?</strong></h2>
<p>While major meme coins struggle, the <a href="https://bs_73dffd2a.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=pepe-coin-price-dips-but-wall-street-memes-nears-24-million" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes token</a> has quickly emerged as a popular choice for traders after its impressive presale performance. The token has already raised close to $24 million in its ICO in less than 3 months, with one presale stage still remaining.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266384" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-18.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="295" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-18.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-18-300x147.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-18-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Even whales are lining up to the presale, with one such investor making a cumulative investment of over $1 million in $WSM.</p>
<p>The token has its origins in the legendary Wall Street Bets Reddit community that inspired the historic GameStop short-squeeze. $WSM is looking to make a similar breakthrough in the crypto market, targeting a $1 billion market capitalization after its launch.</p>
<p>The meme coin continues to get strong community backing, thanks to the global brand value of the Wall Street Memes group. The group boasts of a million-strong internet army and farms over 40 million impressions monthly across its social media pages.</p>
<p>The developer team behind the token has a strong track record of launching successful Web3 projects &#8211; its Wall St Bulls NFT collection drew enormous hype and sold out in less than 32 minutes, netting a cool $2.5 million.</p>
<p>Interested investors can head to the Wall Street Memes presale and purchase the token through bank cards or by swapping ETH, BNB or USDT tokens.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_73dffd2a.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=pepe-coin-price-dips-but-wall-street-memes-nears-24-million" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-price-dips-but-wall-street-memes-nears-24-million/" rel="nofollow">Pepe Coin Price Dips, But Wall Street Memes Nears $24 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here is When the Fed Will Start Cutting Interest Rates According to Goldman Sachs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-when-the-fed-will-start-cutting-interest-rates-according-to-goldman-sachs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266225</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Federal_Reserve.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Federal_Reserve.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[“We are penciling in 25 basis points of cuts per quarter but are uncertain about the pace," the Goldman Sachs' economists said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jan Hatzius and David Mericle &#8211; economists at the banking giant Goldman Sachs &#8211; predicted that the US Federal Reserve will start lowering interest rates from the second quarter of 2024. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Many experts have previously suggested that such a pivot could boost investor interest in risk-on assets, including stocks, commodities, and cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Still Uncertain About the Pace</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/goldman-pencils-in-first-fed-rate-cut-for-second-quarter-of-2024-1.1958486" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Hatzius and Mericle, the US central bank &#8211; the Federal Reserve &#8211; will start a gradual reduction of interest rates from the end of June next year. They are still unsure about the declining temp, highlighting 25 basis points of cuts per quarter as the most possible scenario.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“The cuts in our forecast are driven by this desire to normalize the funds rate from a restrictive level once inflation is closer to target,” they stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The economists also believe the Fed will not increase the rates during its next FOMC meeting in September and conclude that “the core inflation trend has slowed enough to make a final hike unnecessary&#8221; in November.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Normalization is not a particularly urgent motivation for cutting, and for that reason, we also see a significant risk that the FOMC will instead hold steady.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Goldman Sachs&#8217; financial experts believe the Fed will continue dropping the interest rates until reaching a 3-3.25% benchmark. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Federal Reserve has launched quite an aggressive strategy ever since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic, aiming to reduce the disaster&#8217;s short-term devastating economic effect by printing colossal money and raising interest rates. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It lifted the benchmark 11 times between March 2020 and July 2023, hampering the interest in riskier assets, such as cryptocurrencies. Some believe one of the contributing factors for the digital asset market to flourish again will be the end of that policy. The CEO of Galaxy Digital &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-04-06/novogratz-says-bitcoin-will-go-to-the-moon-once-fed-pauses?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=bd&amp;cmpId=google&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall&amp;in_source=embedded-checkout-banner" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mike Novogratz</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8211; and the founder of SkyBridge Capital &#8211; Anthony Scaramucci &#8211; are some examples. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">What About an Earlier Pivot?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tom Lee – Managing Partner and the Head of Research at Fundstrat Global Advisors &#8211; also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fed-most-likely-wont-raise-interest-rates-anymore-tom-lee/" data-wpel-link="internal">thinks</a> the Fed will start cutting interest rates in 2024. Unlike Goldman Sachs&#8217; economists, though, he forecasted that this could happen from Q1:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“Most people believe it’s the second half because the Fed doesn’t want to tighten rates, but if inflation’s falling, they have to cut rates. Otherwise, it’s actually stricting the economy more.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-when-the-fed-will-start-cutting-interest-rates-according-to-goldman-sachs/" rel="nofollow">Here is When the Fed Will Start Cutting Interest Rates According to Goldman Sachs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) Could be Poised for a Bull Rally, Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-could-be-poised-for-a-bull-rally-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266281</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Cardano_Green.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Cardano_Green.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Large ADA holders remain unfazed by underwhelming price performance.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano remained locked in a narrow trading range lately with no volatility in sight. Over the past month, ADA was down by approximately 20%, trading at $0.29 as of now. While this trend has caused increasing frustration among market observers, ADA whales and sharks continued to be resilient.</p>
<p>In fact, this cohort of holders has continued to fill their bags with ADA tokens despite the stagnant price action.</p>
<h2>ADA Whales Show Resilience</h2>
<p>According to Santiment&#8217;s latest analysis, Cardano&#8217;s trader sentiment hasn&#8217;t fared well owing to the 35% decline in the crypto-asset&#8217;s market cap.</p>
<p>However, ADA sharks and whales have remained undeterred. The count of addresses on Cardano with over 100k ADA has rebounded to its peak level since April 2022. In a recent update, the blockchain intelligence platform <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1690983240730054656" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweeted</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Trader sentiment toward Cardano continues to be low as its market cap is down 35% since topping 4 months ago. However, the sharks &amp; whales haven&#8217;t been as deterred as one may think. There are now 25,294 wallets with 100K+ $ADA, the most in 16 months.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bull Run Soon?</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-whales-accumulate-heavily-below-0-30-details/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">accumulation</a> trend typically depicts a bullish momentum in the offing. The similar sentiment was echoed by another prominent analyst, Ali, who drew <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1690986678519832577" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">parallels</a> to a similar period of stagnancy between 2018 and 2020. During that phase, ADA&#8217;s price appeared to have oscillated between $0.10 and $0.028 for a total of 665 days.</p>
<p>The accumulation ended with a bull run of over 2,985%.</p>
<p>In the current scenario, the analyst observed that ADA has been trapped in the $0.46 to $0.24 range for 329 days already. If history is to repeat itself, the crypto-asset could potentially break free around February 2024, as per Ali&#8217;s estimation.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The key takeaway? Patience often pays in the crypto market, and those willing to wait will be rewarded.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Even as ADA failed to perform, the Cardano ecosystem, as a whole, was reported to have grown significantly. This is evident from a recent Messari <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-records-impressive-49-qoq-growth-in-dapp-transactions-10-rise-in-tvl-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> that revealed an increase of 8.5% in Cardano&#8217;s average transaction in Q2 as compared to the previous quarter, going from $0.117 to $0.126. Moreover, the average daily transactions also grew by nearly 2% QoQ from 67,500 to 68,800.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-could-be-poised-for-a-bull-rally-heres-why/" rel="nofollow">Cardano (ADA) Could be Poised for a Bull Rally, Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Bears Target $28.5K as Price Unable to Push $30K: Bitcoin Price Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-bears-target-28-5k-as-price-unable-to-push-30k-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266300</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price movement has remained stagnant after being rejected from the critical resistance zone at $30,000. However, it is currently consolidating near a pivotal support area, which includes both the 100-day moving average and the lower boundary of a multi-month ascending channel. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart The daily chart analysis shows that [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price movement has remained stagnant after being rejected from the critical resistance zone at $30,000. However, it is currently consolidating near a pivotal support area, which includes both the 100-day moving average and the lower boundary of a multi-month ascending channel.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The daily chart analysis shows that the price entered a slight corrective phase at the beginning of July, marked by diminished volatility and subdued price fluctuations.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, BTC is gradually approaching a substantial support range comprising the 100-day moving average, positioned at $28,544, and the lower threshold of the ascending channel, situated at around $28,500. This particular price range holds significant importance as robust support that could potentially prevent additional declines.</p>
<p>However, the current price action within this pivotal support area suggests the prevalence of market indecision, evident from the formation of small and directionless candles. Consequently, if the price receives support and witnesses strengthened buying pressure, market participants could anticipate a decisive reversal in price.</p>
<p>Conversely, in the absence of such support, the price might breach the mentioned support levels, subsequently triggering a cascade effect toward the noteworthy support zone at $25,000.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266304" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266304" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266304 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1408231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Dailuy-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266304" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, it is observable that the price appears to be constrained within a static range, oscillating between the resistance at $30,000 and the minor support at $28,000. At present, Bitcoin is consolidating close to the critical 0.5 Fibonacci retracement level, displaying efforts to avoid a downward breach.</p>
<p>Considering the likelihood of the price undergoing a temporary corrective phase, it is reasonable to regard the price range marked by the 0.5 and 0.618 Fibonacci retracement levels as the most probable target for this movement. Therefore, a positive response within this defined range could potentially pave the way for a fresh upward trend, propelling the price toward the significant resistance level at $30,000.</p>
<p>However, in the event that the price breaks below the range outlined by the 0.5 and 0.618 Fibonacci levels, it may provoke an impulsive plunge toward the support region around the $25K mark.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266303" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266303" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266303 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1408232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266303" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2><strong>Sentiment Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/tradingrage?lang=en" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3><strong>Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Index</strong></h3>
<p>Although Bitcoin&#8217;s price has remained relatively stable, there are significant developments taking place behind the scenes. The Bitcoin Coinbase premium index measures the percentage difference between Coinbase Pro price (USD pair) and Binance price(USDT pair). Positive premium values indicate stronger buying pressure by US investors in Coinbase, while negative values suggest selling pressure by Americans.</p>
<p>US investors include financial institutions and wealthy individuals interested in the crypto market. Therefore, analyzing their behavior can provide valuable insight.</p>
<p>As the chart depicts, this metric has been showing negative values over the past few weeks, pointing to the fact that American investors are selling their BTC. If this pattern continues and the market fails to break above $30K, the price might reverse to the downside in the short term due to excess supply.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266302" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266302" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266302 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_coinbase_premium_1408231" width="2560" height="1613" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-1536x968.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-2048x1291.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Aug-14-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266302" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-bears-target-28-5k-as-price-unable-to-push-30k-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Bears Target $28.5K as Price Unable to Push $30K: Bitcoin Price Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside The Horrible New York Jail Where SBF is Held Ahead of His Trial</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/inside-the-horrible-new-york-jail-where-sbf-is-held-ahead-of-his-trial/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 13:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266261</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn.1-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn.1-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lawyers have complained about overflowing toilets, plastic in inmates’ meals, and contaminated water, amongst other horrific living conditions at the MDC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After Judge Lewis Kaplan of the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York revoked Sam Bankman-Fried’s (SBF) bail on Friday, August 11, the former CEO and disgraced founder of the bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX has spent three nights at the Metropolitan Detention Center, Brooklyn (MDC Brooklyn).</p>
<p>Unfortunately for SBF, MDC Brooklyn is considered one of the worst prisons in New York City and is infamous for its horrible conditions and inmate maltreatment. Judge Kaplan acknowledged that the detention center “is not on anybody’s list of five-star facilities.”</p>
<h2>SBF Detained at MDC Brooklyn</h2>
<p>Federal prosecutors <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/doj-wants-sbf-detained-and-his-bail-revoked-following-witness-tampering-efforts/" data-wpel-link="internal">sought</a> to reverse SBF’s $250 million bail in July after he attempted to tamper with witnesses. At the time of the request, the FTX founder was under <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">house arrest</a> at his parent’s $4 million home in Palo Alto, California.</p>
<p>The Department of Justice pushed to revoke the bail because SBF’s activities, including using a virtual private network to conceal his internet activities, violated his bail conditions. The 31-year-old former CEO also reached out to FTX’s general counsel, suggesting that they become resourceful to each other.</p>
<p>To crown it all, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/caroline-ellison-felt-unsuited-to-run-alameda-amid-sbf-relationship-drama/" data-wpel-link="internal">leaked</a> the private writings of Caroline Ellison, his ex-girlfriend and former CEO of FTX sister trading firm Alameda Research, to a New York Times reporter. As per the Justice Department’s accusations, SBF attempted to cast Ellison in a negative light to make her look like a jilted lover, thereby discrediting her as a witness in his upcoming trial.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266311" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266311" style="width: 650px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-266311" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn.jpg" alt="MDC Brooklyn. Source: News.Com.Au" width="650" height="366" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn.jpg 650w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/MDC-Brooklyn-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266311" class="wp-caption-text">MDC Brooklyn. Source: News.Com.Au</figcaption></figure>
<h2>One of the Worst Prisons in NYC</h2>
<p>Following the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">hearing </a>Friday, SBF was moved to MDC Brooklyn, a U.S. federal administrative detention facility housing both male and female prisoners of all security levels. Originally built to accommodate 1,000 inmates, the center houses more than 1,600 prisoners.</p>
<p>Lawyers have complained about overflowing toilets, plastic in inmates’ meals, and contaminated water, amongst other horrific living conditions at the MDC. On one occasion during winter in 2019, inmates suffered days without heat, electricity, and hot meals due to a power outage. Prisoners who <a href="https://theintercept.com/2019/02/16/metropolitan-detention-center-mdc-brooklyn-jail/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">protested</a> the conditions were pepper sprayed, thrown in solitary confinement, and had their toilets shut down.</p>
<p>The MDC has held high-profile individuals like American singer cum convicted sex offender R. Kelly, child sex trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell, and American rapper Fetty Wap.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, SBF’s lawyers disclosed their intent to appeal Judge Kaplan’s decision.</p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of The Intercept</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/inside-the-horrible-new-york-jail-where-sbf-is-held-ahead-of-his-trial/" rel="nofollow">Inside The Horrible New York Jail Where SBF is Held Ahead of His Trial</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
