<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:02:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Invest Offloads Over $88M Worth Coinbase&#8217;s COIN Shares in 2 Weeks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-invest-offloads-over-88m-worth-coinbases-coin-shares-in-2-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261133</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ark_invest.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ark_invest.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase is expected to release its Q2 earnings early next month.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investors are closely monitoring Coinbase&#8217;s earning reports as shares of the crypto giant COIN are up more than 214% YTD. The fresh boost was provided after the crypto exchange reached an agreement with Cboe&#8217;s BZX Exchange to maintain a surveillance-sharing agreement for five of its spot Bitcoin ETF applications.</p>
<p>As a result, funds associated with Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Investment have rushed to profit from the stock upsurge.</p>
<h2>ARK Invest Offloads COIN</h2>
<p>The investment fund led by Bitcoin bull Cathie Wood had acquired a significant amount of Coinbase shares during the bear market. While Wood is still optimistic about Coinbase in light of a court ruling against the SEC and favor of Ripple&#8217;s XRP, ARK Invest has offloaded $88.5 million worth of COIN shares in the past two weeks.</p>
<p>On July 11, the investment firm sold off $12 million worth of COIN shares just as the stock climbed near a one-year high. Nearly $50.5 million worth of shares, representing 485,000 COIN, were sold on July 14th across three different funds. Three of ARK Investment&#8217;s ETFs cashed in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coin-shares-climb-10-after-cboe-included-coinbase-in-amended-btc-etf-applications/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">COIN&#8217;s recent rally</a>, selling a total of 248,838 shares, worth $26.3 million, based on Monday’s <a href="https://www.google.com/finance/quote/COIN:NASDAQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">closing price</a> of $105.5.</p>
<p>Following a rough start, Coinbase reported a net loss of $79 million in Q1 this year, down from $430 million lost during the same period last year. In a shareholder letter, Coinbase said it was a &#8220;turning point” in building a more efficient and financially disciplined company.</p>
<p>Industry players are turning increasingly bullish on Coinbase as shares of COIN witnessed a turnaround despite the crypto exchange receiving a Wells notice in March and being hammered by a lawsuit from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission in June.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange is expected to release its Q2 earnings early next month.</p>
<h2>Relocating Capital to &#8216;Laggards&#8217;</h2>
<p>The recent moves by ARK Invest are unusual as it made a series of buys of Coinbase&#8217;s stock during crypto winter. However, Wood attributed the sales to simple profit-taking. In a recent Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-07-17/cathie-wood-on-ark-fund-flows-coinbase-ai-investments-video" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">interview</a>, the exec said that the investment firm is instead looking to relocate &#8220;capital to perhaps some laggards.&#8221; She added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Flows are coming back. One of the reasons, ARKK established a base over the last year and it has been trading up and down through that base. I think a lot of investors and more who are technically oriented are looking now at a breakout in our strategy. We&#8217;ll see if it continues. We have enjoyed positive inflows in July, which have cut in half the outflows.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Besides COIN, ARK has also offloaded Tesla (TSLA) shares worth $13 million and instead purchased additional shares of Meta Platforms (META) and Robinhood (HOOD).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-invest-offloads-over-88m-worth-coinbases-coin-shares-in-2-weeks/" rel="nofollow">Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Invest Offloads Over $88M Worth Coinbase&#8217;s COIN Shares in 2 Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink’s Cross-Chain Protocol Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chainlinks-cross-chain-protocol-goes-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261145</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Chainlink.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Chainlink.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The firm behind LINK hopes to close the gap between traditional banks using their oracle system and other blockchains.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink, a leading project focusing on the use of oracles to bring real-world data onto the blockchain and use it for business purposes, has been working on a way to bring its hard-earned, reputable data to partnered projects for quite some time now.</p>
<p>After a long wait, the devs at Chainlink announced the launch of CCIP, the Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol.</p>
<p>For now, CCIP is available on the mainnets of target protocols only in an invitation-based early access system – but not for long.</p>
<h2>Testnet Availability Coming Soon</h2>
<p>CCIPs mainnet launch on the Ethereum, Polygon, Avalanche, and Optimism blockchains is already in use by the teams at Synthetix and BGD Labs, who are using the Chainlink network to get around the limitations of traditional cross-chain bridges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ The Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP) has officially launched on Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon mainnets.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LinkTheWorld?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#LinkTheWorld</a> <a href="https://t.co/SdLVyaapg3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/SdLVyaapg3</a></p>
<p>— Chainlink (@chainlink) <a href="https://twitter.com/chainlink/status/1680970793331613697?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>For non-partnered projects, CCIP will be made available on the testnets of these blockchains on the 20th of July. In the meantime, devs looking to integrate their dApps with Chainlink can sign up for early access and get vetted on the project&#8217;s website.</p>
<h2>Setting New Standards</h2>
<p>According to Chainlink co-founder and acting CEO Sergey Nazarov, the project hopes that CCIP will become the new gold standard for cross-chain interoperability. In a press release celebrating the launch, he likened CCIP to the TCP/IP standard that made the Internet as we know it possible.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Just like key standards such as TCP/IP remade a fragmented early internet into the single global internet we all know and use today, we are making CCIP to connect the fragmented public blockchain landscape and the growing bank chain ecosystem into a single Internet of Contracts.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Nazarov also <a href="https://blog.chain.link/ccip-mainnet-early-access/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stressed</a> that he and his team hope that other devs will find ways to improve the infrastructure he and his team built.</p>
<p>In order to facilitate further development of the protocol, Chainlink gives developers the option to build their own cross-chain solutions on top of CCIP using Arbitrary Messaging and Simplified Token Transfers – both of which will be backed up by the data that has so far enabled over $8 trillion worth of value to be moved on-chain.</p>
<p>Devs who use CCIP will also benefit from the Active Risk Management Network (ARM), a lightweight, independent network created specifically to add an extra layer of security to CCIP.</p>
<blockquote><p>“ARM is a separate, independent network that continually monitors and validates the behavior of the primary CCIP network, providing an additional layer of security by independently verifying cross-chain operations. The ARM Network utilizes a separate, minimal Rust implementation of the Chainlink node software.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The surprise announcement prompted an increase in the market value of LINK. The price of Chainlink’s proprietary token has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainlink-jumps-7-on-cross-chain-news-bitcoin-slipped-to-18-day-low-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">risen</a> by over 6% within the past 24 hours, according to CoinGecko, compounding a steady increase in value over the past month.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainlinks-cross-chain-protocol-goes-live/" rel="nofollow">Chainlink’s Cross-Chain Protocol Goes Live</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stake-to-Earn BTC20 Token Presale Goes Live, Aims to Repeat Bitcoin Bull Run</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stake-to-earn-btc20-token-presale-goes-live-aims-to-repeat-bitcoin-bull-run/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261152</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc20_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc20_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In an ambitious move, the new crypto project BTC20 ($BTC20) has embarked on its token presale, aiming to recreate the early days of Bitcoin. Hosted on the Ethereum blockchain, BTC20 ($BTC20) will boast a unique stake-to-earn setup that provides passive income potential for all token holders. Not only that, but BTC20’s green approach and potential [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an ambitious move, the new crypto project BTC20 ($BTC20) has embarked on its token presale, aiming to recreate the early days of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Hosted on the Ethereum blockchain, <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=stake-to-earn-btc20-token-presale-goes-live-aims-to-repeat-bitcoin-bull-run" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BTC20 ($BTC20)</a> will boast a unique stake-to-earn setup that provides passive income potential for all token holders.</p>
<p>Not only that, but BTC20’s green approach and potential for decentralized application (dApp) integration set it apart from most other new projects in the crowded crypto market.</p>
<h2>Fair $BTC20 Presale Distribution Fosters Strong Community Engagement</h2>
<p>BTC20&#8217;s exciting launch strategy pays homage to Bitcoin, aiming to give investors a taste of the original coin&#8217;s historic gains.</p>
<p>The developers have just launched a presale phase to kickstart the project, aiming to recreate the enthusiasm of Bitcoin&#8217;s early days, when its price eventually reached $1.</p>
<p>Initially, 3 million $BTC20 tokens will be available in the presale, with the soft cap set at $3 million.</p>
<p>Investors can purchase $BTC20 for just $1 per token – and once the soft cap has been hit, the development team intends to provide an &#8220;oversupply&#8221; of 3.05 million $BTC20.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-20.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261157" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-20.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="271" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-20.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-20-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-20-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This will take the total presale allocation to 6.05 million $BTC20, mirroring an early stage of Bitcoin&#8217;s circulating supply.</p>
<p>Per BTC20’s <a href="https://btc20.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, any unsold presale tokens will be added to the staking rewards pool, increasing earning potential for early adopters.</p>
<p>Through this setup, BTC20&#8217;s thoughtfully-designed presale pays homage to Bitcoin&#8217;s history while prioritizing community engagement.</p>
<p>With this approach, the developers aim to foster organic growth through this presale, ensuring that every investor has a stake in the project’s future success.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=stake-to-earn-btc20-token-presale-goes-live-aims-to-repeat-bitcoin-bull-run" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit BTC20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Eco-Friendly Staking Setup Incentivizes Long-Term $BTC20 Holding</h2>
<p>At the core of the BTC20 project lies an innovative staking system that allows token holders to generate a passive income stream.</p>
<p>Leveraging a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus protocol, this setup is designed to be highly energy-efficient relative to Bitcoin&#8217;s Proof-of-Work (PoW) setup.</p>
<p>According to a report by <a href="https://content.ftserussell.com/sites/default/files/education_proof_of_stake_paper_v6_0.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">FTSE Russell</a>, PoS systems consume over 99% less energy than PoW systems – making them much more eco-friendly.</p>
<p>Following BTC20’s presale, 14.95 million $BTC20 tokens will be locked into a staking contract.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-20.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261156" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-20.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="253" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-20.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-20-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-20-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Users who decide to stake their $BTC20 will receive a share of these rewards each time a new block is validated on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>Importantly, the more tokens a user stakes, the higher the percentage of rewards they&#8217;ll earn, incentivizing long-term participation in the project.</p>
<p>Not only that, but users don’t require any expensive mining equipment or computing hardware to benefit from BTC20’s stake-to-earn protocol, making it much more accessible than Bitcoin’s mining setup.</p>
<p>As such, BTC20 holders can earn recurring rewards while supporting a green blockchain ecosystem – a factor that’s contributing to the growing buzz around the project.</p>
<h2>Leveraging Ethereum Powers BTC20 Excitement</h2>
<p>By building on Ethereum’s blockchain infrastructure, <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=stake-to-earn-btc20-token-presale-goes-live-aims-to-repeat-bitcoin-bull-run" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BTC20</a> unlocks an array of benefits unavailable to the original Bitcoin.</p>
<p>For example, integration with widely-used Ethereum wallets like MetaMask provides increased accessibility for crypto investors.</p>
<p>It also provides scope for $BTC20 to be integrated into thousands of dApps built on the Ethereum blockchain, leading to new and exciting use cases.</p>
<p>Moreover, BTC20&#8217;s stake-to-earn protocol would not be possible using the original Bitcoin protocol, adding another layer of innovation that makes the project stand out.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-13.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261155" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-13.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="173" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-13.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-13-300x86.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-13-50x14.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>These factors have combined to help create a palpable buzz around BTC20, even though it is still in the early stages of its life cycle.</p>
<p>BTC20’s <a href="https://twitter.com/BTC20Token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter page</a> and <a href="https://t.me/BTC20Token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a> have welcomed an influx of new members, with investors eager to learn more about the development team&#8217;s ambitions.</p>
<p>Not only that, but crypto influencers have also begun taking note of BTC20’s potential – with leading YouTuber Jacob Bury <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xy26n_e2pus&amp;ab_channel=JacobCryptoBury" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">stating</a> that it could be a “10x potential Bitcoin alternative”.</p>
<p>This early excitement highlights BTC20’s appeal, validating its ambitious vision for the future.</p>
<p>With the presale now underway, the stage is set for major growth as the crypto community gets on board with this promising new ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=stake-to-earn-btc20-token-presale-goes-live-aims-to-repeat-bitcoin-bull-run" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit BTC20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stake-to-earn-btc20-token-presale-goes-live-aims-to-repeat-bitcoin-bull-run/" rel="nofollow">Stake-to-Earn BTC20 Token Presale Goes Live, Aims to Repeat Bitcoin Bull Run</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink Jumps 7% on Cross-Chain News, Bitcoin Slipped to 18-Day Low (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chainlink-jumps-7-on-cross-chain-news-bitcoin-slipped-to-18-day-low-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LINKUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261137</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Red_Mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Red_Mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[LINK is among the few exceptions today in the green.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price took another turn for the worse in the past 24 hours as the asset fell to an 18-day low of $29,650.</p>
<p>Most altcoins have also turned red, with ETH close to breaking below $1,900. SOL has dumped the most from the larger caps.</p>
<h2>BTC Dips Below $30K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin went on a massive roller-coaster at the end of last week when it pumped from just over $30,000 to $31,800 to register its highest price tag in over a year. This came following Ripple&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/history-in-the-making-with-ripple-scoring-massive-win-in-court-in-xrp-security-case-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">court win</a> over the SEC.</p>
<p>However, the primary cryptocurrency failed there and nosedived on the following day back down to $30,000. The bulls managed to recover a few hundred dollars by the time the weekend had arrived.</p>
<p>As with most previous ones, this past weekend was also uneventful, and BTC spent it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-bitcoin-btc-defends-30k-cardano-ada-drops-4-daily/" data-wpel-link="internal">stuck</a> at $30,300. Monday didn&#8217;t <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/1inch-skyrockets-45-daily-bitcoin-stagnates-above-30k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">provide</a> any different scenarios either, and it was only during the early trading hours of Tuesday when bitcoin finally made a move.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t a positive one, though, as BTC slumped to $29,650 (on Bitstamp) for the first time since June 30. It has managed to recover most of the losses, but it is still shaky above $30,000.</p>
<p>Its market cap has declined to under $585 billion, and its dominance over the alts is slightly up to 48.6%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261138" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261138" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-261138" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-17-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261138" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LINK Defies the Marke Sentiment</h2>
<p>Most altcoins were also calmer during the weekend, but the landscape now is slightly more painful. Ethereum is close to dropping below $1,900 after a 1.4% decline on a daily scale. Ripple and Binance Coin, which exchanged places last week, are down by 0.5% to $0.74 and $242, respectively.</p>
<p>Cardano, Dogecoin, Polkadot, Polygon, Avalanche, and Litecoin have all dropped by between 2-4% in a day. Solana, though, has dumped the most from the larger-cap alts, having lost 6.5% of value. As a result, SOL struggles at $25.</p>
<p>Chainlink is the only notable exception from the top 50 alts. On the news of its cross-chain protocol going live, LINK has soared by 6% and trades above $7.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has lost just over $10 billion in a day and sits inches above $1.2 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261139" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261139" style="width: 1876px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-261139" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1876" height="841" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12.jpg 1876w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12-1024x459.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12-768x344.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12-1536x689.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-12-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1876px) 100vw, 1876px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261139" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainlink-jumps-7-on-cross-chain-news-bitcoin-slipped-to-18-day-low-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Chainlink Jumps 7% on Cross-Chain News, Bitcoin Slipped to 18-Day Low (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>LFG Market Integrates Portal to Offer Trustless Cross-Chain Ordinals Trading</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lfg-market-integrates-portal-to-offer-trustless-cross-chain-ordinals-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261070</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Hero_Image_-_LFG_Integration_PR_2_-_1200x720_1689611787lB1OQHMyxb.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Hero_Image_-_LFG_Integration_PR_2_-_1200x720_1689611787lB1OQHMyxb.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE San Francisco, US, July 17th, 2023] Portal, a self-hosted wallet and true cross-chain Layer-2 DEX built on Bitcoin is thrilled to announce that LFG Market, a marketplace for Ordinal NFTs and Bitcoin-based BRC-20 tokens, has chosen to integrate the Portal DEX protocol to offer users cross-chain trading of Ordinals and BRC-20 tokens. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE San Francisco, US, July 17th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://portaldefi.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Portal</a>, a self-hosted wallet and true cross-chain Layer-2 DEX built on Bitcoin is thrilled to announce that <a href="https://www.lfg.cash/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">LFG Market</a>, a marketplace for Ordinal NFTs and Bitcoin-based BRC-20 tokens, has chosen to integrate the Portal DEX protocol to offer users cross-chain trading of Ordinals and BRC-20 tokens. The integration of Portal DEX will make cross-chain transactions between Bitcoin and other digital assets fast, secure, and private.</p>
<p>With this, LFG users will be able to purchase the Ordinal NFTs and BRC-20 tokens using assets from other chains, such as Ethereum, without bridges or custodians. Utilizing Portal’s “cross-chain Atomic Swaps” technology for payments in any NFT marketplace is a monumental “first” in the NFT ecosystem.</p>
<blockquote><p>“LFG is looking for solutions that allow ETH and other NFT collectors seamless access to Ordinal trading, and we found Portal to be the best solution available. So it makes total sense to integrate Portal’s DEX protocol,” said LFG Market Co-founder Jason Rosenstein.</p></blockquote>
<p>The creation of Ordinal inscriptions on the Bitcoin blockchain has led to over $210 million in Ordinals trading volume, according to the latest quarterly report by <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-volume-hits-210-million-in-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DappRadar</a>. With DEXes gaining a <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/231675/crypto-traders-flock-to-dexes-amid-memecoin-mania." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stronger foothold</a> in the crypto industry, the interest in NFTs on Bitcoin is only expected to shoot up in the future. According to Nansen, 4% of the US population owns an NFT; but it was almost non-existent on Bitcoin until the Ordinals revolution in 2023.</p>
<p>For Ordinals to truly take off as the value layer for data and information, cross-chain solutions are needed to bring the much bigger non-Bitcoin NFT audiences from across the blockchain space to access Bitcoin Ordinals with security and trust-minimization. Whether it’s Eth NFT fans or Solana NFT fans, there still is no ability to exchange their treasured NFTs in a trust-minimized way across chains. “Bridge” solutions and wrappers are cumbersome, often custodial, and highly vulnerable to security threats.</p>
<p>Portal’s “cross-chain Atomic Swaps” functionality being built into LFG Market and other DEXes allows for stablecoin payments – that today only exist on EVM-compatible chains – seamless access to Bitcoin BRC-20 and Ordinal purchases.</p>
<p>While the LFG Market currently accepts payments only in BTC, other tokens such as ETH, USDC, USDT, and even tokens on Layer 2 EVMs like Arbitrum and others will be accepted after integrating the Portal DEX protocol. Since Portal’s Atomic Swaps operate at Layer 2 without bridging, it is both the safest and least-expensive way to trade cross-chain. Portal is working on supporting as many compatible blockchains, wallets, and DeFi apps as possible.</p>
<p>Portal CEO Chandra Duggirala said, “Based on our research, we know that marketplace and DEX operators value UX and liquidity. We&#8217;ve worked tirelessly to ensure that our infrastructure integrates smoothly with their existing setups, minimizing engineering overhead, while cross-chain liquidity aggregation helps them increase volumes and offer more assets and features to their users.”</p>
<p>Portal believes that blockchains are “specialized” and that each chain is optimized to do one thing, at the expense of other tradeoffs. Bitcoin is purpose-designed to be sound, peer-to-peer money with superior censorship resistance. Ethereum, on the other hand, was designed for composable utility. By enabling seamless swapping of assets between incompatible chains, Portal helps aggregate liquidity across many chains, ending the fragmentation problem and helping marketplaces like LFG and others grow their user bases and value propositions.</p>
<h2>About LFG Market</h2>
<p>LFG’s mission is to create a platform that simplifies and enhances the trading process of Ordinals and BRC-20 tokens. LFG is a seamless and efficient trading environment that enriches the digital asset ecosystem and facilitates novel financial interactions on top of Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>About Portal</h2>
<p>Portal is building the cross-chain DEX protocol and ecosystem tools to help DEXes and users seamlessly own, exchange and contract across blockchains while minimizing custodial risk. With Portal, DeFi becomes a service that anyone can provide, maintaining anonymity within open, transparent markets with a security model as robust as Bitcoin mining.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lfg-market-integrates-portal-to-offer-trustless-cross-chain-ordinals-trading/" rel="nofollow">LFG Market Integrates Portal to Offer Trustless Cross-Chain Ordinals Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stuttering SEC Chair Gary Gensler ‘Disappointed’ at Ripple Victory</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stuttering-sec-chair-gary-gensler-disappointed-at-ripple-victory/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261112</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SEC chair Gary Gensler has spoken out for the first time since Ripple’s landmark partial victory against the regulator last week, and he’s not happy.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 17, Gary Gensler said he was “disappointed” with the judge’s ruling that Ripple’s XRP token was not a security when it was sold to retail investors on exchanges.</p>
<p>The ruling was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-is-a-win-for-the-entire-crypto-space-says-brad-garlinghouse/" data-wpel-link="internal">celebrated</a> as good news for the wider crypto industry and retail investors, but Gensler doesn’t agree.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />BREAKING: <a href="https://twitter.com/GaryGensler?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@GaryGensler</a> addresses the <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Ripple</a> Summary Judgment decision for the first time since last week’s ruling:</p>
<p>“…And while we’re disappointed on what they said about retail investors, we&#8217;re still looking at it, and assessing that.”</p>
<p>— Eleanor Terrett (@EleanorTerrett) <a href="https://twitter.com/EleanorTerrett/status/1680997005944934401?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Crackdown on Crypto Will Continue</h2>
<p>However, Gensler said he was “pleased” about the decision recognizing the “protection of institutional investors” before adding:</p>
<blockquote><p>“While disappointed on what they said about retail investors, we’re still looking at it and assessing that opinion.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The speech was stuttered, and Gensler appeared simply lost for words at times. The fragmented comments came at an event at the National Press Club on July 17.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, he added that the war on crypto will continue despite this loss.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re going to continue to try to bring firms that may not be in compliance into compliance — without prejudging any one of them — and try to ensure that we protect the investing public,”</p></blockquote>
<p>The ruling that XRP sales to retail traders did not constitute securities transactions is good news for other crypto assets that Gensler and crew alleged were investment contracts.</p>
<p>In 2020, the SEC accused Ripple of illegally raising $1.3 billion through an unregistered securities sale of XRP. However, Judge Analisa Torres of the Southern District of New York ruled that XRP was not a security in the secondary market sale.</p>
<p>She said Ripple’s algorithmic sales system for XRP on exchanges and trading platforms was not a securities offering (which is similar to a stock offering). Buyers “could not have known if their payments of money went to Ripple,” she said.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Outlook</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">XRP prices</a> skyrocketed more than 80% late last week but have settled in the mid-$0.70 area. The token has lost 2.5% on the day, however, in a fall to $0.738 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>XRP hit its highest level since March 2022 but remains down 78% from its 2018 all-time high of $3.40.</p>
<p>The ruling also boosted several other crypto assets, including Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-stellar-lumens-price-rally-cools-off-but-ypredict-is-rising/" data-wpel-link="internal">Stellar Lumens</a> (XLM). All of these have also been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-does-ripples-victory-over-sec-mean-for-sol-ada-and-other-alleged-security-tokens/" data-wpel-link="internal">labeled securities</a> by the SEC.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stuttering-sec-chair-gary-gensler-disappointed-at-ripple-victory/" rel="nofollow">Stuttering SEC Chair Gary Gensler ‘Disappointed’ at Ripple Victory</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Successfully Integrates Bitcoin on Lightning Network, Enabling Deposits and Withdrawals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-successfully-integrates-bitcoin-on-lightning-network-enabling-deposits-and-withdrawals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260916</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Lightning Network enable faster, cheaper, and more scalable transactions by allowing users to create off-chain transaction channels.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Binance announced it has completed the integration of Bitcoin on the Lightning Network (LN).</p>
<p>The move will enable Binance users to leverage the scaling solution for Bitcoin deposits and withdrawals. When depositing BTC, users will have the additional option of &#8220;BTC-Lightning&#8221; alongside the standard choices of Bitcoin, BEP20, SegWit, and others.</p>
<ul>
<li>With the latest <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-completes-integration-of-bitcoin-btc-on-lightning-network-opens-deposits-and-withdrawals-eefbfae2c0ae472d9e1e36f1a30bf340?ref=AZTKZ9XS&amp;utm_source=BinanceTwitter&amp;utm_medium=GlobalSocial&amp;utm_campaign=GlobalSocial" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">integration</a>, Binance now stands alongside other prominent players such as Kraken, OKX, Bitfinex, and River Financial to adopt the layer 2 scaling solution.</li>
<li>Binance initially indicated its intention to integrate the Lightning Network in May, prompted by the temporary suspension of BTC withdrawals due to an influx of pending transactions <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">caused</a> by the significant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-75-of-daily-bitcoin-on-chain-transactions-used-taproot-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">upsurge</a> in BTC network gas fees.</li>
<li>In June, the crypto exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/keep-building-binance-starts-running-bitcoin-lightning-network-nodes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">began</a> running multiple nodes on the Lightning Network in a bid to enable cheaper BTC deposits and withdrawals on its platform.</li>
<li>After a slow start, LN&#8217;s adoption was boosted by several notable partners, including the decentralized social media platform Nostr.</li>
<li>LN&#8217;s capacity surpassed an all-time high of 5,000 BTC earlier this year.</li>
<li>A recent <a href="https://valkyrieinvest.com/daily-market-brief/the-valkyrie-market-brief-02-06-23/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by Valkyrie Investments stated that the adoption of the Lightning Network is rapidly gaining momentum in emerging markets such as South America and Africa, largely driven by the initiatives of the LN mobile payment application Strike.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, the company behind LN &#8211; Lightning Labs &#8211; recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-unveils-toolkit-to-enable-ai-transact-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">released</a> a new toolkit that assists AI applications such as OpenAI’s ChatGPT to interact with the Bitcoin network to send, receive, and hold the crypto-asset</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-successfully-integrates-bitcoin-on-lightning-network-enabling-deposits-and-withdrawals/" rel="nofollow">Binance Successfully Integrates Bitcoin on Lightning Network, Enabling Deposits and Withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Burned Investor Accused of Kidnapping and Assaulting Ontario&#8217;s &#8216;Crypto King&#8217; (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/burned-investor-accused-of-kidnapping-and-assaulting-ontarios-crypto-king-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260942</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Jail.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Jail.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Akil Heywood has also purportedly threatened a bankruptcy trustee Rob Stelzer to force him to pay $2 million in digital currencies. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Canadian law enforcement agents have reportedly arrested the 39-year-old Akil Heywood over allegations that he kidnapped, threatened, and beat Aiden Pleterski in December 2022. The latter supposedly orchestrated a crypto scam, draining over $40 million from investors. Records show that Heywood invested $740,000 with Pleterski, making him one of the countless victims.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The alleged fraudster apologized in a recent video, vowing to &#8220;live on the bare minimum&#8221; to repay the conned investors.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Brutal Way to Get Revenge?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/investor-lost-money-among-5-men-charged-kidnapping-ontario-crypto-king-1.6907548" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by CBC, Heywood is among the five people facing charges connected to the kidnapping and assault of the self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto King&#8221; Aiden Pleterski at the end of last year. The former was supposedly one of the individuals lured into a cryptocurrency scheme run by the latter and served as an inspector in the case&#8217;s bankruptcy proceedings.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I&#8217;ve never seen a bankruptcy proceeding where an inspector is charged in a kidnapping and a forcible confinement related to recovering money in a bankruptcy,&#8221; said fraud recovery lawyer Norman Groot.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A spokesperson for Grant Thornton informed that Heywood resigned as an inspector on July 7. Apart from the alleged kidnapping, the 39-year-old Chairman of Atlantic Mas Camp supposedly threatened a bankruptcy trustee Rob Stelzer to induce him to pay $2 million in cryptocurrency (a sum much higher than the $740,000 he lost investing with the &#8220;Crypto King&#8221;). While the investigation is ongoing, the Canadian authorities have released Heywood on bail. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pleterski&#8217;s lawyer &#8211; Micheal Simaan &#8211; said his client &#8220;is grateful for the work of the Toronto Police in apprehending those involved in his kidnapping and assault.&#8221;  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that Pleterski warned about Heywood&#8217;s aggressive behavior two weeks before the abduction. He said during an interview that the accused kidnapper &#8220;is still, by the way, uttering threats, and very dangerous, violent threats, to me over Instagram comment sections and text messages.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The four other men accused of Pleterski&#8217;s kidnapping face additional charges, such as pointing a firearm at him. None of the claims have so far been tested in court. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">From a &#8216;Crypto King&#8217; to a Man Begging for Forgiveness</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides informing about the kidnapping and the related suspects, the media outlet <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/player/play/2245735491709" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">published</a> a video showing how Pleterski regrets the losses he caused to the investors. The visibly beaten man explained that he started dealing with digital currencies in 2020, whereas, in the following months, he offered his services to family, friends, and other individuals. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">And while the scheme worked perfectly during the crypto bull market, &#8220;everything went downhill&#8221; when prices started nosediving. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;When the crypto market started to tank in November of 2021, I should have been honest with everybody. I lost enough to where my debts outweighed my assets … I lost close to $45 million strictly alone in the crypto market within one month,&#8221; Pleterski said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a bankruptcy report seen by CBC, the &#8220;Crypto King&#8221; used only $670,700 of the aforementioned sum as intended, whereas he spent approximately $16 million to fund his lavish lifestyle (going on vacations, renting private jets, and purchasing luxurious cars). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pleterski admitted employing some investor deposits toward car payments, food expenses, and house settlements. He said he felt &#8220;very humiliated&#8221; and &#8220;embarrassed,&#8221; promising to work around the clock to reimburse victims:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I&#8217;m going to do it before I go and buy myself another car before I go and buy myself another watch before I go and buy myself expensive clothing or anything. I&#8217;m going to live on the bare minimum until every last soul is paid back.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, Pleterski&#8217;s lawyer claimed that the information from the video should not be taken for granted as his client might have been forced to say those things by his kidnappers. Moreover, the alleged crypto scammer has insisted he is innocent. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/burned-investor-accused-of-kidnapping-and-assaulting-ontarios-crypto-king-report/" rel="nofollow">Burned Investor Accused of Kidnapping and Assaulting Ontario&#8217;s &#8216;Crypto King&#8217; (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aave&#8217;s Lens Protocol V2 Introduces New Features to its Web3 Social App</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/aaves-lens-protocol-v2-introduces-new-features-to-its-web3-social-app/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260952</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LENS_protocol.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/LENS_protocol.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lens Protocol's latest version has introduced a blocking feature for its users. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aave Companies announced the launch of the second iteration of Lens Protocol on July 17th, designed to serve as a social layer for Web3. The new version aims to bring even greater control to builders and integrators as well as people exploring Web3-powered experiences.</p>
<p>The first version of Lens Protocol was purposely built and launched without a user interface. The V2, on the other hand, comes with a codebase that&#8217;s entirely rewritten, refactored, and optimized.</p>
<h2>Lens V2: Spotlight on Monetization</h2>
<p>The main goal of such a move is to allow easy composability and configurability that delivers an improved user experience, support new social use cases, and shared monetization opportunities that benefit all Web3 social networking stakeholders be it users, creatives, applications, and algorithms, not just individually but collectively as a ecosystem.</p>
<p>The monetization layer now expands to encompass all Web3 applications and profiles, creating opportunities among individuals, applications, algorithms, and protocols. Users, applications, and algorithms are now integral components of the monetization chain, allowing them to mutually reward and incentivize collaborative work, fostering the spirit of collaboration within web3.</p>
<p>Following the development, Stani Kulechov, Founder of Lens Protocol, commented,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Lens Protocol V2 takes decentralized social media and monetization opportunities to a new level. Providing maximum flexibility for builders, V2 enables new types of social engagements and monetization relationships, where all stakeholders can share in the value of social networks – both individually and collectively as an ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Other Features</h2>
<p>In terms of new features, V2 will introduce &#8216;open actions&#8217; that seek to enable developers to deploy new activities on Lens, expanding the different ways that people can interact with content and creators in Web3. These actions can be integrated into both existing and future consumer-facing applications.</p>
<p>Lens Protocol V2 adopts an open model, rewarding valuable actions at each stage of the value chain to establish a sustainable ecosystem for content creators, applications, algorithms, and even external protocols.</p>
<p>The latest iteration has also implemented a new standard known as ERC-6551 for user profiles. This standard allows Lens profiles to possess their own wallets, housing ERC-721 tokens and other non-fungible tokens (NFTs). Consequently, ERC-6551-powered Lens profiles enable NFTs the capability to execute actions.</p>
<p>In a bid to ensure trust and security, V2 will let users block a profile from commenting, mirroring, collecting, or conducting any open action.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aaves-lens-protocol-v2-introduces-new-features-to-its-web3-social-app/" rel="nofollow">Aave&#8217;s Lens Protocol V2 Introduces New Features to its Web3 Social App</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana And Cardano Prices Slide But Launchpad XYZ Raises $1 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/solana-and-cardano-prices-slide-but-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261050</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/launchpad_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/launchpad_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Major altcoins saw another strong correction as the global crypto market cap shrank by 0.5% over the past day. Solana plunged 4% over the past 24 hours, while Cardano fell close to 2% over the same period. The crypto market is facing a choppy week ahead as the threat of an SEC appeal against the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Major altcoins saw another strong correction as the global crypto market cap shrank by 0.5% over the past day. Solana plunged 4% over the past 24 hours, while Cardano fell close to 2% over the same period.</p>
<p>The crypto market is facing a choppy week ahead as the threat of an SEC appeal against the recent Ripple ruling becomes more likely.</p>
<p>Despite the bearish conditions, several tokens remain bullish due to their high utility. Launchpad XYZ is one such project that has recently surpassed the $1 million mark in its ongoing presale.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261052" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-12.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="307" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-12.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-12-300x153.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-12-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<h2><strong>Solana and Cardano Plummet As Ripple’s Post-Win Enthusiasm Dampens</strong></h2>
<p>Ripple’s landmark win against the SEC provided a strong bullish boost to the entire crypto market.</p>
<p>In a watershed ruling, district judge Analisa Torres stated that Ripple’s programmatic sales of XRP tokens did not meet the criteria set by the Howey test and thus did not make the token a security.</p>
<p>The decision resulted in a close to 100% surge for XRP, with the token trading as high as $0.95 at one point &#8211; it has since corrected to $0.738.</p>
<p>The ruling also resulted in double-digit pumps in other major altcoins that have been labelled as securities in the SEC’s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>Solana in particular reached its highest price mark since the disastrous FTX bankruptcy in November of last year. The token is currently trading at $26.9 and is up 30% over the past week, bringing its total gains to 70% over the last month.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261053" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-19.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="329" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-19.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-19-300x164.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-19-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Similarly, Cardano is also up 10% in the weekly time frame as the ADA token is trading at $0.31.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261054" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-19.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="333" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-19.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-19-300x166.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-19-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Cardano and Solana’s surge can be attributed to the widespread belief that Ripple’s victory will make it easier for other tokens to prove their non-security status. Expert crypto analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/thecryptolark/status/1679602044473311236?s=46" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Lark Davis</a> believes that if XRP is not a security, then most other major altcoins aren’t as well.</p>
<p>However, several legal experts now believe that this celebration may have been premature. Both ConsenSys lawyer Bill Hughes and litigator Bryan Jacotout are of the opinion that the <a href="https://twitter.com/bryanjacoutot/status/1679539619312853028?s=46" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">SEC will likely appeal the district court’s ruling</a>.</p>
<p>Other experts are also noting that the recent ruling did find that <a href="https://twitter.com/jvallee2000/status/1679978131908890626?s=46" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ripple violated the Securities Act</a> when they sold the tokens to institutional investors.</p>
<p>Even in the case of programmatic sales, Ripple won because Judge Torres factored in the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-07-13/what-does-ripple-xrp-ruling-in-sec-case-mean-for-crypto" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">lack of mainstream knowledge</a> of the crypto market in the early days of XRP. Several other newer tokens may not receive such a benefit of the doubt.</p>
<h2><strong>Which Tokens Can Outperform The Crypto Market?</strong></h2>
<p>The crypto market remains in the doldrums, and an SEC appeal can result in strong downward pressure.</p>
<p>Investors are now looking for presale tokens that can display bullish price surges despite the bearish sentiment. Launchpad XYZ is emerging as a top contender it has raised over $1.1m and continues to rise.</p>
<h2><strong>New Web3 Portal Launchpad XYZ Turns Heads as Token Nears $1.5 Million</strong></h2>
<p>The crypto market is extremely volatile and can be overwhelming for newbies and natives alike. However, the <a href="https://bs_010f7b2f.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=solana-and-cardano-prices-slide-but-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-million" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ</a> ecosystem is offering a suite of powerful trading products that can help users combat the complexities of the market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261055" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-15.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="359" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-15.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-15-300x179.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-15-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Investors have been quick to recognize the project’s high real-world utility as it has already raised $1.1 million in the presale and is well on its way to hitting the $1.5 million mark.</p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ is carefully designed to help users succeed in crypto trading while also offering them maximum learning opportunities. For example, the Terminal Edge platform will help them gain valuable market insights with the help of sentiment analysis and the latest crypto news. Beginners can also get to know the trading setup of other expert traders.</p>
<p>Similarly, the Launchpad Quotient will make sure users do not miss out on the next big investment opportunity by ranking crypto assets across 400 data points.</p>
<p>The all-in-one Web3 portal also offers other tools such as its own Web3 wallet, premium NFT marketplace, a decentralized exchange, a sophisticated Terminal trading engine, etc.</p>
<p>The $LPX token is currently priced at $0.0445 but will surge significantly to $0.0565 at listing. Investors can purchase the token through bank cards or by swapping ETH or USDT tokens.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_010f7b2f.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=solana-and-cardano-prices-slide-but-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-million" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-and-cardano-prices-slide-but-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-million/" rel="nofollow">Solana And Cardano Prices Slide But Launchpad XYZ Raises $1 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
