<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:20:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bybit and Franck Muller Watches Announce Exciting Co-Branding Partnership</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-and-franck-muller-watches-announce-exciting-co-branding-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254946</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screen_7-_1200x720_cm_HD_16863198557PpVux2yRq.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screen_7-_1200x720_cm_HD_16863198557PpVux2yRq.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 13th, 2023] Bybit, the world’s third most visited crypto exchange, is pleased to announce its collaboration with Swiss luxury watch manufacturer Franck Muller. Together, they will create shared campaigns which showcase the synergy between Bybit&#8217;s cutting-edge technology and Franck Muller&#8217;s timeless craftsmanship. Bybit and Franck Muller will introduce [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 13th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Bybit, the world’s third most visited crypto exchange, is pleased to announce its collaboration with Swiss luxury watch manufacturer <a href="https://franckmullerencrypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Franck Muller</a>. Together, they will create shared campaigns which showcase the synergy between Bybit&#8217;s cutting-edge technology and Franck Muller&#8217;s timeless craftsmanship.</p>
<p>Bybit and Franck Muller will introduce a co-branded card, which will benefit the clients of both companies. The card will offer customers a payment solution for the Franck Muller website, as well as access to exclusive discounts when used at participating retailers. It will also feature an eye-catching design that reflects the spirit of both companies.</p>
<p>Franck Muller will also launch an exclusive game that offers an immersive experience for watch enthusiasts and gaming aficionados alike. Bybit will help develop a collection of NFTs featuring iconic figures and weapons from the game and offer weekly prizes for top scorers.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We are excited about our collaboration with Franck Muller, a brand whose values of meticulous craftsmanship and timeless design are closely aligned with our own,” said Ben Zhou, co-founder and CEO of Bybit. “Through this partnership, we aim to create an unforgettable experience for our users, combining cutting-edge technology with the sophistication of Franck Muller&#8217;s luxury watches.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re confident that the co-branded card and the exclusive game will be highly sought after by our customers and watch enthusiasts alike. We believe this partnership is a great way for us to further expand our reach and show our appreciation for our user base of 15 million people worldwide.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Managing Director of Franck Muller, Erol Baliyan said: “As the first luxury watch company in the world to embrace cryptocurrencies, we are thrilled to announce this exciting collaboration between Franck Muller and Bybit, a leading and admired cryptocurrency exchange.</p>
<p>We share the same passion for innovation, and together, we aim to revolutionize the way people perceive and engage with both cryptocurrencies and luxury in the digital and physical space, creating a truly unique and unforgettable customer experience for our valuable clientele. This unprecedented collaboration opens up a world of possibilities, fusing the beauty of traditional craftsmanship with the limitless potential of the blockchain era.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>About Franck Muller</h2>
<p><a href="https://franckmullerencrypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Franck Muller</a> is a Swiss luxury watch manufacturer famous for its watches which are one of the finest and most complicated in the world. It is the first luxury watch company to embrace cryptocurrencies and constantly brings its innovation through its own exclusive game experiences and unique timepieces.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-and-franck-muller-watches-announce-exciting-co-branding-partnership/" rel="nofollow">Bybit and Franck Muller Watches Announce Exciting Co-Branding Partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Highly Anticipated Chancer Crypto Presale Officially Launches Today</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/highly-anticipated-chancer-crypto-presale-officially-launches-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254952</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/gold-challenge-comp_1372_1686580560dLoepWAWIW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/gold-challenge-comp_1372_1686580560dLoepWAWIW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, June 13th, 2023] Chancer, one of the most exciting new Web3 projects of 2023, has officially launched its crypto presale today, 13th June. The project aims to disrupt the betting industry by removing the ‘house’ from the picture and putting the markets firmly back in the hands of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, June 13th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Chancer, one of the most exciting new Web3 projects of 2023, has officially launched its crypto presale today, 13th June. The project aims to disrupt the betting industry by removing the ‘house’ from the picture and putting the markets firmly back in the hands of the bettors, allowing users to create their own betting markets, set their own odds, and create their own rules.</p>
<p><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=chainwire&amp;utm_term=stage1_announcement&amp;utm_content=launch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Chancer</a> is the world’s first decentralized predictive markets app — something co-founders and brothers Adam and Paul Kelbie believe will dramatically change how people bet and, ultimately, put the fun back into betting.</p>
<p>Chancer positions itself as a betting facilitator, not a betting house, allowing users to create peer-to-peer (P2P) bets. These can be small, friendly bets amongst a small group of people, or huge, viral bets such as predicting the Champions League final result or who will win Best Director at the Oscars, in which masses of people can participate. Chancer doesn’t limit people to sport betting; bets can be made on any prediction or event, a stark contrast from most bookmakers. Its inherent appeal lies in the fact that users are in complete control of their bets and won’t lose to a traditional bookmaker who stacks the odds against them.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’re confident that we can change the way betting and gambling works,” said Adam Kelbie, CEO of Chancer. “The next few months are going to be very exciting, and we’re thrilled that we can offer a new cryptocurrency in such a competitive market. We’re doing something no one else has done, disrupting an industry that has had the odds stacked against consumers since it began. It won’t be easy, but we’re ready for the fight.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>How CHANCER Works</h2>
<p>All bets and payouts are made in Chancer’s native token, ‘CHANCER,’ which can then be traded with stablecoins like USDT. The online betting and gambling industry is huge, standing at approximately $64 billion (as of 2022), and Chancer aims to take advantage of that and claim a dominant position within the space.</p>
<p>The CHANCER token will be launched on the BSC Blockchain and is now available during its presale, which comprises 12 stages in total. The token is now available at a price of $0.010 during stage one of the presale and will eventually rise to $0.021 by stage 12, an increase of 70% from the initial price in the first tranche of the presale.</p>
<h2>Revolutionizing Betting Industry with Future-Forward Capabilities</h2>
<p>As outlined in the <a href="https://chancer.com/whitepaper.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">whitepaper</a>, the project has a well-planned roadmap outlining a variety of product use cases to draw different types of investor interest. <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=chainwire&amp;utm_term=stage1_announcement&amp;utm_content=launch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Chancer</a> also aims to achieve and maintain true decentralization. To do this, Chancer will have a proof of stake consensus mechanism so that no single party can take control of the network. Quadratic governance will hand decision-making over to the platform’s users.</p>
<p>For full transparency, Chancer’s source code will remain open. This also means that anyone is welcome to review, contribute, and propose changes in how the platform works with the assurance that they will be listened to.</p>
<p>Uniquely, Chancer will be channeled by the real-time communication capability of Google’s WebRTC to live stream events to its community.</p>
<p>Chancer believes in rewarding its users and will therefore offer CHANCER tokens simply for using the platform, as well as providing a Share2Earn scheme, staking, and discounted fees for those who create and participate in the market, making it cost-effective for those who use the platform frequently. Another way to earn a passive income via Chancer is to become a node validator.</p>
<h2>About Chancer</h2>
<p>Chancer is set to develop the world’s first decentralized social predictive markets platform. This will allow Chancer token holders to create, participate in, and profit from their very own predictive markets based on their interests, expertise, and social opportunities.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=chainwire&amp;utm_term=stage1_announcement&amp;utm_content=launch" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">project</a> intends to disrupt the global gambling and betting market by ‘removing the house’ and taking a slice of the market share as it garners attention by challenging the traditional bookmaking and betting business model.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/highly-anticipated-chancer-crypto-presale-officially-launches-today/" rel="nofollow">Highly Anticipated Chancer Crypto Presale Officially Launches Today</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Mid-Year Conference: Building a Web3 Finance Hub in the Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-mid-year-conference-building-a-web3-finance-hub-in-the-metaverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254921</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a48e96c9-b8ca-432d-8e50-13d5afba060a_1686593840eYgMML0FW9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/a48e96c9-b8ca-432d-8e50-13d5afba060a_1686593840eYgMML0FW9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; The Caribbean, June 12th, 2023] Recently, Huobi held its mid-year conference to review the overall progress from the first half of 2023, including a development plan for the second half of the year. H.E. Justin Sun, a member of the Huobi Advisory Board, shared his unique insights into the development of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; The Caribbean, June 12th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Recently, <a href="https://www.huobi.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Huobi</a> held its mid-year conference to review the overall progress from the first half of 2023, including a development plan for the second half of the year. H.E. Justin Sun, a member of the Huobi Advisory Board, shared his unique insights into the development of the blockchain industry.</p>
<p class="ql-align-center"><strong> </strong><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ikrkoJe-IfZTP5gbR8OKSUZrklAHXwhmSGmnogyJvMIlpcOQ50_1686593548jWXZYwI8x8.jpeg" /></p>
<h2>Becoming a Household Name</h2>
<p>Huobi and Poloniex witnessed a significant improvement in operational performance during Q2 compared to Q1 2023. This can be attributed to various factors, including the meme coin frenzy and the regulatory crackdown on other exchanges.</p>
<p>However, in terms of total on-chain assets, Huobi and Poloniex equated to $4 billion, which falls behind Binance&#8217;s $60 billion and OKX&#8217;s $10 billion.</p>
<p>Huobi stated that in the next six months, it will continue to restore its brand confidence, increase platform assets and trading volume, and achieve profitability targets. It aims to become a stronger player and a household name within the cryptocurrency exchange industry.</p>
<p>With months of cost reduction and efficiency improvement efforts, Huobi has overcome survival challenges and will make future decisions based on long-term perspectives. Huobi is committed to actively embracing the ever-changing crypto industry and prioritizing user needs. The company firmly doesn’t believe in sacrificing user interests for short-term gains. The focus will be on constantly creating value for users while achieving greater business wins.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market&#8217;s 3 Pillars: Exchange, Public Chain, and Stablecoin</h2>
<p><strong> </strong><strong> <img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ZhplANSDn_s5OXrzlubKIC1F2KIcuLzPDgsTUgMQxXGaAmRKWm_1686593548oNdc4XQshI.jpeg" /></strong></p>
<p>Sun expressed that Huobi has always been following its global compliance strategy by actively embracing regulation and exploring diverse compliance operations. Numerous crypto companies are entering the Hong Kong market because of its new regulatory rules. Huobi is gaining exposure in the Hong Kong crypto market by launching Huobi Hong Kong, which allowed registration for Hong Kong residents on June 1, 2023. Huobi is also the first exchange to become a member of the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC). Additionally, Huobi is in continuous communication with the Hong Kong government to apply for a cryptocurrency exchange license.</p>
<p>Sun analyzed that exchanges, public chains, and stablecoins will become the main core of the entire blockchain industry. These three pillars for the decentralized financial landscape will influence long-time development in the industry. Sun stated that their mission is to build a Web3 finance hub in the metaverse and give an option to people worldwide to pursue financial freedom in the metaverse. Public chains serve as the foundation for creating a financial world in the metaverse, while exchanges play a crucial role as the gatekeepers.</p>
<p>Sun believes that Huobi holds a leading position within the industry. However, in terms of integration capabilities, Huobi stands out as the sole decentralized financial ecosystem platform with a structure encompassing all three pillars mentioned earlier. The three core businesses consisting of exchanges, public chains, and stablecoins, will strive to enhance the user experience from multiple angles. It focuses on long-term industry development, covering the majority of industry traffic and building a globally influential Web3 financial hub.</p>
<h2>About Huobi</h2>
<p>Founded in 2013, <a href="https://www.huobi.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Huobi</a> has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies &#8211; &#8220;global development, technology drives development, and technology for good&#8221; &#8211; underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-mid-year-conference-building-a-web3-finance-hub-in-the-metaverse/" rel="nofollow">Huobi Mid-Year Conference: Building a Web3 Finance Hub in the Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Requests Binance Asset Freeze, Exchange Hires Former Agency Director as Lawyer (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-requests-binance-asset-freeze-exchange-hires-former-agency-director-as-lawyer-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254950</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Binance_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Binance_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC has requested an emergency freeze of all available Binance assets, which will be fought by a former agency executive.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last week, the SEC sued Binance for violations of U.S. securities laws and “years of violative conduct” that allegedly put customers&#8217; funds at risk.</p>
<p>Now, the regulatory agency wants to freeze those said funds.</p>
<h2>Complete Freeze of Assets Requested</h2>
<p>Since customers&#8217; funds are allegedly at risk, it was only convenient that a complete asset freeze be requested from the U.S. government. The <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-12/binance-us-says-asset-freeze-sought-by-sec-will-cripple-exchange" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">request</a> would target the assets of both Binance U.S. and the global exchange and would also seek to repatriate funds held abroad.</p>
<p>One unnamed former banking partner – who will cease handling deposits and withdrawals for the exchange starting on the 14th of June – even froze Binance’s assets of its their volition ever since the court case started. However, those assets will most likely be recovered by Binance once the bank closes its account.</p>
<p>The exchange has, naturally, argued against the “draconian relief sought by the SEC,” saying customer funds were perfectly safe and a freeze would do nothing but prevent Binance customers from using their funds as they did so far. Of course, a freeze would also conveniently hamper the company’s operations – and probably make its legal defense a lot harder.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Operations would quickly grind to a halt without the ability to pay employees, vendors, suppliers, and professionals or to maintain the trading platform. With a freeze of all corporate assets, banking partners would most likely cease to honor requests to transfer funds for any purpose, including customer redemptions.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance Will Be Defended by Former SEC Insider</h2>
<p>In order to fight what many see as an overreach by U.S. regulators, Binance has signed on several new <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-12/binance-us-hires-former-sec-enforcement-co-director-canellos#xj4y7vzkg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lawyers</a> from Milbank LPP.</p>
<p>One of the four freshly contracted lawyers is none other than George Canellos, a former co-director of the Securities and Exchange Commission’s enforcement division. His best-known managed cases include the SEC’s investigations into the insider trading charges leveled against Raj Rajaratnam. Prior to his stint at the agency, Canellos had served with the Major Crimes Unit of the Southern District of New York.</p>
<p>John Reed Stark, the former head of the SEC’s Office of Internet Enforcement, commented on the news. According to him, the decision to hire such a specialized lawyer indicates that Binance expects to fight serious criminal charges in a long, drawn-out court battle.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Canellos possesses a rare and remarkably special combination of skillsets &#8212; having served as both an SEC prosecutor and a DOJ prosecutor. Think Liam Neeson meets Perry Mason. Binance is clearly preparing for criminal prosecution and continuing to hire the best defense attorneys in the world.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Two other lawyers formerly served with the SDNY’s criminal division, focusing on cybercrime, terrorism, the narcotics trade, and white-collar financial crime, further substantiating Stark’s assessment of the situation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-requests-binance-asset-freeze-exchange-hires-former-agency-director-as-lawyer-report/" rel="nofollow">SEC Requests Binance Asset Freeze, Exchange Hires Former Agency Director as Lawyer (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Made it &#8216;Impossible to Know&#8217; Which Tokens Are Securities: Mark Cuban</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-made-it-impossible-to-know-which-tokens-are-securities-mark-cuban/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security Tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254789</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/MarkCuban.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/MarkCuban.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC's instruction is so unclear that even an "army of securities lawyers" could not say which crypto assets classify as securities, Cuban argued. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American businessman, philanthropist, and television personality &#8211; Mark Cuban &#8211; lambasted the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for providing misleading guidance regarding which digital currencies could categorize as securities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency has not been kind to the crypto sector and recently filed lawsuits against two of the largest exchanges &#8211; Binance and Coinbase. It also claimed that some leading digital assets, including BNB, SOL, ADA, and MATIC, operate as unregistered securities.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC Treats Crypto Differently</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The billionaire and owner of The Dallas Mavericks &#8211; Cuban &#8211; is yet another individual who believes the Commission has not done enough to properly supervise the cryptocurrency sector and determine which tokens classify as securities and which as commodities.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In one of his recent Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1667914770651987970" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">posts</a>, he claimed that the watchdog&#8217;s public statements on the matter differ from the official position on its website. Cuban added that the lengthy guidance does not give information regarding &#8220;what is or is not a security in the crypto universe.&#8221; He went further, stating one wouldn&#8217;t be able to find out the status of the different digital currencies even with &#8220;an army of securities lawyers.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American thinks the SEC has double standards when speaking of crypto and other aspects of finance. He <a href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1667153158106226692" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> last week that the Gary Gensler-spearheaded agency had called the stock loan industry &#8220;opaque&#8221; and required additional transparency. Unlike the digital asset sector, though, it did not categorize &#8220;stock loans&#8221; securities and did not file lawsuits against brokers or banks. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;They should do the same thing with crypto as an effort to determine which aspects of crypto are securities and which are not and the best way to regulate the industry and protect investors. I think their difference in approach is emblematic of their intent for one industry vs another,&#8221; he concluded.<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_56631" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-56631" style="width: 589px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a style="font-weight: bold; background-color: transparent;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-56631" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban.jpg" alt="mark-cuban" width="589" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban.jpg 1400w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban-300x204.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban-1024x695.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban-768x521.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/mark-cuban-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 589px) 100vw, 589px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-56631" class="wp-caption-text">Mark Cuban, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">The SEC&#8217;s War on Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency&#8217;s unfriendly attitude toward the industry intensified last week. For starters, it </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Binance, the CEO &#8211; Changpeng Zhao (CZ), and the American subsidiary of the company &#8211; Binance.US.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The main accusation is that the platform operated &#8220;unregistered national securities exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing agencies.&#8221; According to the regulator, Binance&#8217;s unlicensed products include certain lending offerings, a staking program, the native token BNB and a fiat-backed stablecoin BUSD. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">continued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with its harsh actions with another lawsuit against Coinbase a day later. It alleged that the latter served as a broker, national securities exchange, and clearing agency without obtaining the necessary authorization.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It also claimed that well-known cryptocurrencies such as Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC) are securities, accusing Coinbase of offering trading services with them.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Coinbase has elevated its interest in increasing its profits over investors&#8217; interests and over compliance with the law and the regulatory framework that governs the securities markets,&#8221; the Commission stated. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that Binance&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Changpeng Zhao &#8211; and Coinbase&#8217;s &#8211; Brian Armstrong &#8211; remained unfazed by the accusations. The former </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1665742100845961217" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">tweeted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his signature number &#8211; &#8220;4,&#8221; urging his followers not to trust fake news or any sort of misleading information.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For his part, Armstrong </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-welcomes-sec-legal-battle-well-get-the-job-done/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his exchange would be &#8220;proud&#8221; to represent the crypto sector in its SEC court battle, assuring &#8220;we will get the job done.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-made-it-impossible-to-know-which-tokens-are-securities-mark-cuban/" rel="nofollow">SEC Made it &#8216;Impossible to Know&#8217; Which Tokens Are Securities: Mark Cuban</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>JP Morgan Pays $290 Million Settlement For Serving Jeffrey Epstein</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jp-morgan-pays-290-million-settlement-for-serving-jeffrey-epstein/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[JP Morgan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254928</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/JPMorgan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/JPMorgan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[JP Morgan served Epstein and Epstein-related entities from January 1998 through August 2013.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">JP Morgan has agreed to pay $290 million to settle a class-action lawsuit from the victims of Jeffrey Epstein – the famous American financier and sex offender. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The plaintiffs claimed that JP Morgan laundered money and thereby enabled sex trafficking on behalf of Epstein while he was still a client of the bank.</span></p>
<h2>JP Morgan Aiding Money Laundering?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A </span><a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230612240332/en/JPMorgan-Chase-and-Jane-Doe-1-Reach-Agreement-to-Settle-Lawsuit-in-Epstein-Matter" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">joint statement</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from the largest bank in the United States and victims’ attornies said on Monday that both groups had “reached an agreement in principle to settle the putative class action lawsuit related to Jeffrey Epstein’s crimes.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The agreement is subject to court approval, and will not involve JP Morgan admitting liability in the case. “The parties believe this settlement is in the best interests of all parties, especially the survivors who were the victims of Epstein’s terrible abuse,” read the statement. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to </span><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/12/investing/jpmorgan-epstein-victims-settlement/index.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">CNN</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, David Boies – one of the victims’ attornies – said that over 100 women are expected to receive compensation for Epstein’s abuse. More victims who filed through the Epstein Victims’ Compensation program are likely to be compensated following similar settlements with two other banks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Victims&#8217; lawyers called the settlement “life-changing and historic” given how a major financial institution is participating in shutting down sex trafficking. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Money, which for far too long flowed with impunity between Jeffrey Epstein’s global sex trafficking enterprise and Wall Street’s leading banks, is decisively being used for good,” said Sigrid McCawley, managing partner at Boies Schiller Flexner.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Epstein’s victims reached a $75 million settlement deal with Deutsche Bank, with which there is expected to be an overlap with JP Morgan in the victims it helps compensate, according to Boies. </span></p>
<h2>How Does Bitcoin Compare?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin’s loudest critics often point to the blockchain as a lawless landscape enabling money laundering, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-warrens-bill-will-hurt-crypto-not-russia-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">sanctions violation</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, and terrorist financing. Last year, ex-Federal Reserve Chairman Ben Bernanke </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-has-failed-as-an-alternative-money-says-former-fed-chairman/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">claimed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Bitcoin has no underlying value besides “ransomware, or something like that.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, data from Chainalysis shows that the proportion of Bitcoin transactions being used to facilitate financial crime is falling over time. Furthermore, though illicit crypto volume appears to be </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/illicit-crypto-transactions-in-2022-surpassed-20-billion-for-the-first-time-chainalysis/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">rising</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in absolute terms, the U.S. Treasury Department has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fiat-is-far-more-common-than-bitcoin-for-money-laundering-confirms-us-treasury-department/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">confirmed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the dollar remains king when it comes to money laundering. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jp-morgan-pays-290-million-settlement-for-serving-jeffrey-epstein/" rel="nofollow">JP Morgan Pays $290 Million Settlement For Serving Jeffrey Epstein</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turkey Residents Turn to Crypto Amid Another Lira Collapse (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/turkey-residents-turn-to-crypto-amid-another-lira-collapse-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Turkey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254769</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Turkey.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Turkey.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The lira's crash and the restrictions on purchasing dollars and gold with the local currency have made USDT even more attractive to Turks.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some residents of Turkey have reportedly revived their interest in the cryptocurrency market, more specifically in the stablecoin USDT, following a new decline in their national currency and fears that severe inflation could start looming again across the country. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The downtrend of the Turkish lira (which has been evident in the past few years) intensified shortly after Recep Erdogan won the presidential elections, securing himself another five years as the political leader. He is known as a fierce critic of digital currencies, whereas his opponent Kemal Kilicdaroglu (who collected two million votes less than Erdogan) shared pro-crypto views.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Turks Turn to Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to recent Bloomberg </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/turkish-investors-looking-for-haven-turn-to-stablecoin-tether-1.1931285" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, residents of the Eurasian country have shifted their focus towards the largest stablecoin by market capitalization &#8211; USDT &#8211; at the beginning of May, ahead of the presidential elections. The interest has remained high even after their completion, which saw Erdogan </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/05/28/europe/turkey-president-runoff-polls-erdogan-intl/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">win</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by getting 52% of the votes. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One possible factor pushing the people of Turkey toward the cryptocurrency industry could be the depreciating national currency that recently hit a record low against the American dollar. Currently, 1 TRY equals $0.042, whereas it was worth approximately $0.15 at the beginning of 2020 (at the start of the global COVID-19 pandemic). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">USDT has turned into a safe haven for some locals who try to preserve their wealth amid the worrying inflationary environment. The asset maintains a consistent peg with the US dollar, and it provides a relatively safe and simple way in which Turks can join the crypto sector.</span></p>
<p>On the other hand, domestic regulators have restricted the purchase of dollars and even gold with the lira, giving crypto a more notable status. Ebru Güven &#8211; university lecturer and former banker &#8211; shed more details:</p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Investing in stablecoins allows people to keep the value of their wealth; it&#8217;s one of the ways to hold on to some value when inflation is this high. This is the only motivation for people to buy stablecoins right now.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Response From the Locals</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Concerned about the lira&#8217;s condition, some Turkish residents have distributed all their savings into the cryptocurrency market. One example is the 28-year-old graphic designer &#8211; Batuhan Basoglu &#8211; who revealed:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Just before the election, I felt the urge to convert my Turkish lira to US dollars due to the uncertainty surrounding the currency&#8217;s future. To safeguard myself against this risk, I purchased Tether.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Data <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1661781497827803136" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">presented</a> by the cryptocurrency analytics provider &#8211; Kaiko &#8211; showed that USDT trading volume on BtcTurk spiked at the end of May (when Erdogan won the Presidential elections).</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_254770" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254770" style="width: 633px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a style="font-weight: bold; background-color: transparent;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT-trading-volume.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254770" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT-trading-volume.png" alt="USDT trading volume" width="633" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT-trading-volume.png 733w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT-trading-volume-300x189.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/USDT-trading-volume-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 633px) 100vw, 633px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254770" class="wp-caption-text">USDT trading volume on BtcTurk, Source: Kaiko</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dessislava Aubert &#8211; an analyst at the company &#8211; told Bloomberg that the last time Turks were so intrigued by the stablecoin was in 2020. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It&#8217;s noticeable that despite historically low volumes, demand for stablecoins on Turkish markets has remained robust,&#8221; she added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/turkey-residents-turn-to-crypto-amid-another-lira-collapse-report/" rel="nofollow">Turkey Residents Turn to Crypto Amid Another Lira Collapse (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Circulation Hits New Peak as Confidence in Circle Continues to Shrink</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-circulation-hits-new-peak-as-confidence-in-circle-continues-to-shrink/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254767</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Circle_Tether.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Circle_Tether.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether has just notched up a new all-time high for USDT supply despite a deepening bear market and the ongoing war on crypto in the US.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The stablecoin ecosystem has also been impacted by America’s war on crypto, with a clear divergence happening between the top two issuers.</p>
<p>Tether supply has reached an all-time high of 83.36 billion USDT, according to the firm’s transparency <a href="https://tether.to/en/transparency/#usdt" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>.  Industry analyst Will Clemente commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The divergence from USDC is striking, reflecting easier access to treasuries for US-based USDC holders and regulatory uncertainty for US-based Circle.</p>
<p>What was once a competitive advantage for USDC is now the opposite,” he added.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Tether in circulation just reached an ATH of $83.35 billion</p>
<p>The divergence from USDC is striking, reflecting easier access to treasuries for US-based USDC holders &amp; regulatory uncertainty for US-based Circle. What was once a competitive advantage for USDC is now the opposite. <a href="https://t.co/OcExkpZqAW" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/OcExkpZqAW</a></p>
<p>— Will Clemente (@WClementeIII) <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1667939371054505984?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Tether Keeps Minting</h2>
<p>Circle’s USDC was once favored by institutions, but with an ongoing industry-wide crackdown, the demand for the stablecoin is dwindling.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Circle was heavily <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-usdc-outflows-surpassed-10b-since-svb-collapse-tether-dominance-rises/" data-wpel-link="internal">impacted by exposure</a> to the now-bankrupt Silicon Valley Bank. USDC de-pegged at the time in early March, causing a massive loss in confidence.</p>
<p>USDC supply has declined by almost 50% since June 2022, when it peaked at around $56 billion. As a result, its market share has also taken a hit, tanking to 22%, whilst Tether’s has increased to a commanding 64.5%.</p>
<p>The total stablecoin market capitalization is currently $129.3 billion, according to CoinGecko. It represents almost 12% of the entire cryptocurrency market capitalization though it, too, has shrunk considerably during the bear market.</p>
<p>On June 12, Glassnode reported that USDT and USDC continue to leave centralized exchanges, with both stablecoins hitting a monthly high for outflow volumes.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c8.png" alt="📈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$USDT</a> Exchange Outflow Volume (7d MA) just reached a 1-month high of 32,508,950.195 USDT</p>
<p>View metric:<a href="https://t.co/D90kNIpU2J" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/D90kNIpU2J</a> <a href="https://t.co/2XsLdprSgx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/2XsLdprSgx</a></p>
<p>— glassnode alerts (@glassnodealerts) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1667958775611895809?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The flight to safety from exchanges, especially Binance, has increased following the SEC’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-ceos-see-wealth-crushed-after-secs-twin-lawsuits/" data-wpel-link="internal">twin lawsuits</a> and enforcement action last week.</p>
<p>However, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1667554966662266883" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">cautioned</a> investors not to read too much into Binance outflow figures from analytics platforms because they use TVL (total value locked), which includes decreases in crypto asset prices.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Crypto markets have calmed over the weekend as the consolidation continues. There has been virtually no change in total capitalization over the past 24 hours, as it remains at $1.09 trillion.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC prices</a> have held steady at $25,800, while Ethereum has dipped marginally to $1,735 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Unsurprisingly, BNB has been hit the hardest, having lost 25% over the past week. Binance Coin was trading at its lowest price this year at $222, having dropped another 5% at the time of writing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-circulation-hits-new-peak-as-confidence-in-circle-continues-to-shrink/" rel="nofollow">Tether Circulation Hits New Peak as Confidence in Circle Continues to Shrink</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Coinbase and Binance Lawsuits Super Bullish for BTC and ETH (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-coinbase-and-binance-lawsuits-super-bullish-for-btc-and-eth-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254641</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bullsbears_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bullsbears_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission went ham on crypto exchanges last week by filing toothy lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase. While crypto exchanges and altcoins are in the hot seat, the regulator is leaving BTC and ETH alone, at least for now. When news of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase hit markets, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission went ham on crypto exchanges last week by filing toothy lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase. While crypto exchanges and altcoins are in the hot seat, the regulator is leaving BTC and ETH alone, at least for now.</p>
<p>When news of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase hit markets, the prices of all assets plunged across the board. BNB <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-coin-price-analysis-bnb-crashes-10-on-sec-lawsuit-is-250-in-sight/" data-wpel-link="internal">crashed 10%</a> in 24 hours. It lost another 5% on Sunday and kept dumping on Monday to a multi-month low at $223.</p>
<p>Bitcoin prices plummeted from the $27,100 handle Sunday to $25,750 Monday. But the world&#8217;s oldest and most well-capitalized cryptocurrency blockchain recovered quickly.</p>
<h2>BTC and ETH Rally with SEC&#8217;s New Suits Priced in</h2>
<p>BTC bounced back to above the $27,000 level on Tuesday, even as news of a second SEC lawsuit <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">against Coinbase</a> spread.</p>
<p>Although the agency increasing enforcement activities against the crypto industry harmed crypto prices last week, it appears BTC and ETH will emerge from the regulatory heat unscathed. Bitcoin is already up 2.75% on the five-day window, with the Binance and Coinbase lawsuits priced in.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum had a massive rally with the latest SEC news priced into the market. Ether prices on crypto exchanges jumped from $1,800 at 1:30 pm UTC Tuesday to a high of $1,890 before the session turned over. That was a cool 5% intraday gain for the second-largest crypto.</p>
<h2>SEC Leaves Bitcoin, Ether, and Ripple Alone</h2>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The SEC has named these 19 tokens as securities throughout the Binance + Coinbase filings.</p>
<p>This could have massive implications for these tokens, and the industry as a whole.</p>
<p>Some quick thoughts.<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (1/9) <a href="https://t.co/kYQTK8lvoe" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/kYQTK8lvoe</a></p>
<p>— Miles Deutscher (@milesdeutscher) <a href="https://twitter.com/milesdeutscher/status/1666644256696729600?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The legal theory of the SEC&#8217;s lawsuits against the two major crypto exchanges hinges on a 90-year-old law. The Securities Act of 1933 <a href="https://www.govinfo.gov/content/pkg/COMPS-1884/pdf/COMPS-1884.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">was</a> written to protect investors in the aftermath of the 1929 stock market crash.</p>
<p>Between the Securities Act and the &#8220;<a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/h/howey-test.asp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Howey test</a>&#8221; from a 1946 Supreme Court decision, the SEC intends to persuade U.S. courts that many cryptocurrencies offered for sale and exchange by Coinbase and Binance meet the legal definition of securities.</p>
<p>If the SEC&#8217;s theory prevails in court, then Coinbase, Binance, and any other crypto exchange would be required by the U.S. federal government to register with the agency and comply with the rules they set to protect retail investors.</p>
<p>But even in that worst case outcome of these legal battles, Bitcoin, Ethereum, and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-xrp-not-named-a-security-in-the-secs-case-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a> may emerge unscathed. The SEC didn&#8217;t bother to name them as securities in either the Binance or Coinbase lawsuit.</p>
<p>Retail investors, as well as institutions, are apt to see less risk and more upside in these cryptocurrencies as a result. The SEC&#8217;s reluctance to push its luck with these commodities is incredibly bullish for XRP, ETH, and BTC.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-coinbase-and-binance-lawsuits-super-bullish-for-btc-and-eth-opinion/" rel="nofollow">SEC Coinbase and Binance Lawsuits Super Bullish for BTC and ETH (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Did Investors React to the SEC, Binance, Coinbase Fiasco? Glassnode Reports</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-did-investors-react-to-the-sec-binance-coinbase-fiasco-glassnode-reports/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254912</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_ethereum_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_ethereum_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Coinbase experienced significantly greater withdrawals for ETH than BTC last week. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Glassnode published a report on Monday breaking down investors’ on-chain behavior after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued two of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchanges. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The report acknowledged a boost to the number of short-term crypto holders sending their balances onto exchanges. </span></p>
<h2>Exchange Deposits and Withdrawals</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The </span><a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-24-2023/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> echoed findings from </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-sees-massive-outflows-following-sec-lawsuit-data/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">last week</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> showing that Binance experienced significantly higher withdrawals immediately following the SEC’s Monday filing. The platform’s Bitcoin and Ethereum balances have fallen by 40,200 BTC (5.7%) and 324,000 ETH (7.1%) respectively over the past 7 days. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, Binance’s stablecoin balance took the biggest hit, declining by $1.6 billion (20.9%) over the past week. Since FTX’s collapse in November 2022, Binance’s stablecoin balance has fallen a whopping 75% from $26 billion to just $6.5 billion today – largely spurred by another </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-will-happen-to-binance-if-sec-manages-to-kill-busd/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">SEC crackdown</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against its Paxos-issued BUSD stablecoin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The exchange still holds some of the largest reserves of any entity on-chain, and their BTC and ETH balances are still quite substantial,” clarified Glassnode.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase – which was sued the day after Binance for multiple securities law violations – faced relatively smaller Bitcoin (BTC) withdrawals of just 2300 BTC (0.5%). However, Ethereum withdrawals were much more pronounced at 291,000 ETH (8.0%), possibly indicating heightened investor fear around the company’s staking-as-a-service product. </span></p>
<h2>Behavior By Cohort</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Investor behavior surrounding exchanges also seemed to differ by cohort: transactions of under $10 million comprised consistent withdrawals, while those over $10 million were consistent deposits, with net inflows ranging between $15 million to $30 million per day. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This suggests that very large entities (such as institutions) are more affected to a greater extent by the SEC news as compared to smaller entities,” wrote Glassnode. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Furthermore, short-term crypto holders are showing heightened activity, accounting for 76% of recent BTC deposit volume (versus the typical 60%). Such deposits accounted for 0.93% of short-term holders’ total held balances on exchanges. By contrast, long-term holders showed “no discernible reaction to the news.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Analysis from CryptoQuant </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-short-term-holders-not-willing-to-cash-out-amid-sec-fud-data/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">suggests</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that even short-term holders are reluctant to sell their coins too heavily, as the cohort is waiting for a chance to realize more profit from its purchases. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The entire crypto market slid after the SEC’s lawsuits last week, with heightened pain among coins specifically </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">targeted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by the agency’s Coinbase filing: Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC). </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-did-investors-react-to-the-sec-binance-coinbase-fiasco-glassnode-reports/" rel="nofollow">How Did Investors React to the SEC, Binance, Coinbase Fiasco? Glassnode Reports</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
