<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>US CFTC Chair Behnam, Coinbase Chief Legal Among Others To Testify at House Hearing</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-behnam-coinbase-chief-legal-among-others-testify-at-house-hearing.htm</link><description>The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission Chair Rostin Behnam, Coinbase’s Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal and a slew of former regulators are set to testify Tuesday morning in front of a US congressional committee. &lt;br /&gt;
The House Agriculture Committee will meet to discuss legislation to regulate cryptocurrencies and hear from Behnam, Grewal and former CFTC Chair Christopher Giancarlo, among others....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-behnam-coinbase-chief-legal-among-others-testify-at-house-hearing.htm"&gt;Read More: US CFTC Chair Behnam, Coinbase Chief Legal Among Others To Testify at House Hearing&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-behnam-coinbase-chief-legal-among-others-testify-at-house-hearing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115977/311596/adobestock-265746413-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="381661"/></item><item><title>Russia’s Rosbank Begins ‘Int’l Crypto Pay Pilot’ – Banks Joining Government’s Crypto Plan?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russias-rosbank-begins-intl-crypto-pay-pilot-banks-joining-governments-crypto-plan.htm</link><description>The Russian megabank Rosbank says it has launched a “cross-border crypto payments” pilot. &lt;br /&gt;
Per RBC, Rosbank has become the “first major” Russian bank to launch cross-border payments services “in cryptocurrency.” &lt;br /&gt;
The bank has teamed up with a local crypto firm named B-Crypto for its initiative. &lt;br /&gt;
B-Crypto works as an “intermediary” by “buying cryptocurrency abroad” on behalf of importers before “transferring [coins] to foreign suppliers.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russias-rosbank-begins-intl-crypto-pay-pilot-banks-joining-governments-crypto-plan.htm"&gt;Read More: Russia’s Rosbank Begins ‘Int’l Crypto Pay Pilot’ – Banks Joining Government’s Crypto Plan?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Banks</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russias-rosbank-begins-intl-crypto-pay-pilot-banks-joining-governments-crypto-plan.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115888/311415/adobestock-515107674-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="322079"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 5 June – Decentraland, Solana, The Sandbox</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-5-june-decentraland-solana-sandbox.htm</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission announced today that it has filed charges against Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, for violating federal securities laws. &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC alleges that Binance mismanaged billions of dollars of client funds and deceived regulators and investors. &lt;br /&gt;
How might this affect the selection of the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-5-june-decentraland-solana-sandbox.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 5 June – Decentraland, Solana, The Sandbox&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>WSM</category><category>MANA</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>SOL</category><category>YPRED</category><category>SAND</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>SEC</category><category>CZ</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Solana</category><category>Decentraland</category><category>Sandbox</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-5-june-decentraland-solana-sandbox.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115978/311597/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>The US SEC Sued Binance and CZ on Monday — What’s in the Complaint?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-sued-binance-cz-monday-whats-complaint.htm</link><description>A complaint by the US Securities and Exchange Commission filed against Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao unveiled a mix of stark revelations about the world’s largest crypto exchange from evading US laws to internal conversations about Binance.US.  &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC sued Binance and Changpeng Zhao, also known as CZ,  on Monday for their “blatant disregard of the federal securities laws,” along with 13 charges, including operating an unregistered exchange....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-sued-binance-cz-monday-whats-complaint.htm"&gt;Read More: The US SEC Sued Binance and CZ on Monday — What’s in the Complaint?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>SEC</category><category>Lawsuit</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-sued-binance-cz-monday-whats-complaint.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115974/311594/adobestock-456009336-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="125292"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Plunges Amid Legal Action by US SEC Against Binance and Its Founder</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-plunges-amid-legal-action-by-us-sec-against-binance.htm</link><description>In the wake of recent legal action by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, and its founder, Bitcoin has witnessed a significant plunge.  &lt;br /&gt;
This development has sent shockwaves throughout the crypto market, raising concerns and uncertainty among investors. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-plunges-amid-legal-action-by-us-sec-against-binance.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Plunges Amid Legal Action by US SEC Against Binance and Its Founder&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-plunges-amid-legal-action-by-us-sec-against-binance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115920/311523/5-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481642"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 5, 2023 - $LOVE, $SNEK, $WFAI</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-june-5-2023-love-snek-wfai.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:WHEE (WHEE)VMPX (VMPX)The Qwan (QWAN)Waifu AI (WFAI)Loyalty Labs (LOYAL)Umi's Friends (IMG)Spiral Tower (STS)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-june-5-2023-love-snek-wfai.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 5, 2023 - $LOVE, $SNEK, $WFAI&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Trading</category><category>Exchange</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-june-5-2023-love-snek-wfai.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115914/311456/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>China's Web3 Stance: A Glimpse into the Future?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-web3-stance-glimpse-into-future.htm</link><description>China's perspective on web3 has come to light through a recently released white paper that suggests China is open to incorporating web3 into its future internet. &lt;br /&gt;
In the paper, the term “Internet 3.0” is defined as a "three-dimensional space that combines virtual and real realms with a highly immersive interactive experience," and it describes a future world characterized by a high level of intelligence and an integration of the virtual and physical worlds....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-web3-stance-glimpse-into-future.htm"&gt;Read More: China's Web3 Stance: A Glimpse into the Future?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Web3</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-web3-stance-glimpse-into-future.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115957/311535/china.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="184981"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Developers Divided Over How to Deal with Meme Coin Explosion – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-developers-divided-over-how-deal-with-meme-coin-explosion-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>While many celebrate Bitcoin (BTC)’s plethora of new applications related to its new “Ordinals” protocol, developers maintaining the network’s source code are in disarray on the matter.  &lt;br /&gt;
Critics claim that new types of transactions beyond simple Bitcoin transactions are clogging the blockchain for those trying to use it for its intended purpose. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-developers-divided-over-how-deal-with-meme-coin-explosion-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Developers Divided Over How to Deal with Meme Coin Explosion – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-developers-divided-over-how-deal-with-meme-coin-explosion-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115968/311593/adobestock-438532694.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="451862"/></item><item><title>Russian Official Under Fire for Allegedly Accepting $28 Million Bitcoin Bribe</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/russian-official-under-fire-for-allegedly-accepting-28-million-bitcoin-bribe.htm</link><description>The local media outlet, Kommersant, reported details of the highest bribery case in recent years, where an officer received a bribe worth millions of dollars in Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Investigative Committee of the Russian Federation and the Prosecutor General's Office discovered the bribery incident. &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, the head of the ICR department for the Tverskoy district of Moscow, Marat Tambiev, collected bribes in Bitcoins from hackers under his investigation. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/russian-official-under-fire-for-allegedly-accepting-28-million-bitcoin-bribe.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Official Under Fire for Allegedly Accepting $28 Million Bitcoin Bribe&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/russian-official-under-fire-for-allegedly-accepting-28-million-bitcoin-bribe.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115967/311560/taxes-ga751b03b4-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="339889"/></item><item><title>Japan Blockchain Week 2023 Receives Backing from the Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/japan-blockchain-week-2023-receives-backing-from-ministry-of-economy-trade-industry.htm</link><description>The Japan Blockchain Week 2023 in Tokyo will commence on June 18 to July 9, 2023 and according to the Chainwire report, the Japanese Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry (METI) is backing this year’s edition.  &lt;br /&gt;
This development comes amid the growing need for clearer regulatory pathways for crypto and accelerated efforts to become a global digital assets hub. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/japan-blockchain-week-2023-receives-backing-from-ministry-of-economy-trade-industry.htm"&gt;Read More: Japan Blockchain Week 2023 Receives Backing from the Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/japan-blockchain-week-2023-receives-backing-from-ministry-of-economy-trade-industry.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115964/311557/blockchain-g36362107d-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="144797"/></item><item><title>Beyond Collectibles: Gary Vaynerchuk's Vision for the Future of NFTs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/beyond-collectibles-gary-vaynerchuks-vision-for-future-of-nfts.htm</link><description>Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are set to expand well beyond the digital collectibles and art pieces that they are today, according to one industry insider. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking in a recent podcast interview with TechCrunch, Gary Vaynerchuk (also known as Gary Vee), the entrepreneur behind the media company VaynerX and NFT collection VeeFriends, said that NFTs have a much broader purpose than simply being collectibles,...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/beyond-collectibles-gary-vaynerchuks-vision-for-future-of-nfts.htm"&gt;Read More: Beyond Collectibles: Gary Vaynerchuk's Vision for the Future of NFTs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/beyond-collectibles-gary-vaynerchuks-vision-for-future-of-nfts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115921/311463/nft.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="96915"/></item><item><title>Gate.io Exchange Threatens Legal Action Against Bankruptcy Rumor Spreaders</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/gateio-exchange-threatens-legal-action-against-bankruptcy-rumor-spreaders.htm</link><description>Major crypto exchange Gate.io has threatened to take legal measures against those spreading rumors of its possible bankruptcy.  &lt;br /&gt;
“Legal proceedings will be initiated against people who cause panic among investors only with rumors and gossip, without relying on any concrete source,” according to a rough translation of a June 4 Twitter announcement written in Turkish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gateio-exchange-threatens-legal-action-against-bankruptcy-rumor-spreaders.htm"&gt;Read More: Gate.io Exchange Threatens Legal Action Against Bankruptcy Rumor Spreaders&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Gate.io</category><category>Gatecoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/gateio-exchange-threatens-legal-action-against-bankruptcy-rumor-spreaders.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115966/311559/0-fwyprrfu0uibjfvv.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="19520"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Rallies 5% in a Week – Where is LTC Heading Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-rallies-5-week-where-ltc-heading-now.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC) has seen a sharp intraday drop in tandem with the broader cryptocurrency market on Monday, with sell pressure triggered by news that the SEC is suing Binance, Binance.US and the exchange’s founder Changpeng Zhou (CZ) over offering unregistered securities to the general public in the US, as well as a host of other charges. &lt;br /&gt;
LTC, the cryptocurrency that powers the payments-focused Litecoin blockchain, was last changing hands in the $88 area, down close to 7% on the day....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-rallies-5-week-where-ltc-heading-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Rallies 5% in a Week – Where is LTC Heading Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-rallies-5-week-where-ltc-heading-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115963/311556/ltc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="596536"/></item><item><title>As Apple Announces its New VR Headset This Crypto Startup is Creating a Decentralized Freelancer Ecosystem on the Metaverse – Here's How it Works</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-apple-announces-its-new-vr-headset-crypto-startup-creating-decentralized-freelancer-ecosystem-metaverse-heres-how-it-works.htm</link><description>Apple, the world’s most valuable company, is expected to announce its new virtual reality (VR) headset on Monday at the annual Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC). &lt;br /&gt;
The announcement would mark Apple’s most significant product release since the launch of the Apple Watch in 2015 and is expected to reinvigorate the VR headset industry which seems to have stalled in recent years....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/as-apple-announces-its-new-vr-headset-crypto-startup-creating-decentralized-freelancer-ecosystem-metaverse-heres-how-it-works.htm"&gt;Read More: As Apple Announces its New VR Headset This Crypto Startup is Creating a Decentralized Freelancer Ecosystem on the Metaverse – Here's How it Works&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Apple</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-apple-announces-its-new-vr-headset-crypto-startup-creating-decentralized-freelancer-ecosystem-metaverse-heres-how-it-works.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115962/311553/apple-headset.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="8327523"/></item><item><title>Crypto Prices crashing after SEC Sues Binance, These Presales Still Pumping – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-crashing-after-sec-sues-binance-these-presales-still-pumping-heres-why.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency markets just experienced a big intraday drop in response to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) revealing that it has sued Binance, its US subsidiary Binance.US and the exchange’s founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ). &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last trading close to 5% lower on the day in the $25,800 area, having just hit its lowest levels since March under $25,500. &lt;br /&gt;
Ether (ETH), meanwhile, was last down close to 4% on the day and changing hands just above $1,800....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-crashing-after-sec-sues-binance-these-presales-still-pumping-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Prices crashing after SEC Sues Binance, These Presales Still Pumping – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-crashing-after-sec-sues-binance-these-presales-still-pumping-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115958/311540/binance.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2534089"/></item><item><title>Binance Plans To Fight ‘To the Full Extent of the Law’ Following SEC Charges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-plans-fight-to-full-extent-of-law-following-sec-charges.htm</link><description>Binance said the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s 13 charges against it and its CEO Changpeng Zhao are “just another example of the Commission’s misguided and conscious refusal to provide much-needed clarity and guidance,” to the crypto industry. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-plans-fight-to-full-extent-of-law-following-sec-charges.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Plans To Fight ‘To the Full Extent of the Law’ Following SEC Charges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>CZ binance</category><category>SEC</category><category>Charges</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-plans-fight-to-full-extent-of-law-following-sec-charges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115956/311532/screen-shot-2023-06-05-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="454797"/></item><item><title>SEC Sues Binance and CZ Over 'Blatant Disregard' of Its Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-sues-binance-cz-over-blantant-disregard-of-its-rules.htm</link><description>Binance Holdings Ltd., and its US affiliates, are being charged by the US Securities and Exchange Commission for multiple offenses, months after being charged separately by another US regulator. &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC’s case stems from the defendants’ “blatant disregard of the federal securities laws,” the regulator said. &lt;br /&gt;
“In so doing, Defendants have enriched themselves by billions of U.S. dollars while placing investors’ assets at significant risk,” the SEC said in its complaint....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-sues-binance-cz-over-blantant-disregard-of-its-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Sues Binance and CZ Over 'Blatant Disregard' of Its Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Binance</category><category>CZ binance</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-sues-binance-cz-over-blantant-disregard-of-its-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115951/311529/screen-shot-2023-06-05-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="554222"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Shoots Up 5% and This AI Crypto Signals Platform Helps to Find the Next Coin to Pump – Best Low Cap Gem?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-shoots-up-5-but-lesser-known-green-coin-may-next-crypto-explode-time-buy.htm</link><description>Market traction is growing behind Solana, as months of stalemate price action have given way to an impressive +15% SOL price pump, but is it too late to buy Solana? &lt;br /&gt;
At the time of writing, Solana (SOL) is currently trading at $21.54 (24hr change -1.33%). &lt;br /&gt;
After a month of downside price action, SOL appears to be breaking to the upside from strong consolidatory footing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-shoots-up-5-but-lesser-known-green-coin-may-next-crypto-explode-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Shoots Up 5% and This AI Crypto Signals Platform Helps to Find the Next Coin to Pump – Best Low Cap Gem?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-shoots-up-5-but-lesser-known-green-coin-may-next-crypto-explode-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115932/311525/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="265845"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: JPMorgan Partners with 6 Indian Banks on Blockchain-Based Interbank Transactions, APPG Makes 53 Crypto Recommendations to the UK Government, Charles Hoskinson Warns About the Rise in AI-generated Frauds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-jpmorgan-partners-with-6-indian-banks-on-blockchain-based-interbank-transactions-appg-makes-53-crypto-recommendations-to-the-uk-government-charles-hoskinson-warns-about-the-rise-in-ai-generated-frauds.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-jpmorgan-partners-with-6-indian-banks-on-blockchain-based-interbank-transactions-appg-makes-53-crypto-recommendations-to-the-uk-government-charles-hoskinson-warns-about-the-rise-in-ai-generated-frauds.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: JPMorgan Partners with 6 Indian Banks on Blockchain-Based Interbank Transactions, APPG Makes 53 Crypto Recommendations to the UK Government, Charles Hoskinson Warns About the Rise in AI-generated Frauds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>India</category><category>Banking</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Regulation</category><category>UK</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Security</category><category>Fraud</category><category>AI</category><category>Charles Hoskinson</category><category>Legal</category><category>Tornado Cash</category><category>Three Arrows Capital</category><category>Genesis</category><category>Investment</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Mining</category><category>Marathon</category><category>USA</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-jpmorgan-partners-with-6-indian-banks-on-blockchain-based-interbank-transactions-appg-makes-53-crypto-recommendations-to-the-uk-government-charles-hoskinson-warns-about-the-rise-in-ai-generated-frauds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115902/311454/adobestock-monticellllo-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="197143"/></item><item><title>Award-Winning Recycle-to-Earn (R2E) Project Ecoterra’s Presale Raise Surges to Nearly $5 Million - Is This The Ultimate Green Utility Crypto?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/award-winning-recycle-earn-r2e-project-ecoterras-presale-raise-surges-to-nearly-5m-is-this-the-ultimate-green-utility-crypto.htm</link><description>Saturday, 3rd June - One of 2023’s most exciting green crypto projects just hit a huge milestone in its fundraising efforts.  &lt;br /&gt;
Revolutionary web3 Recycle-to-Earn (R2E) platform ecoterra’s presale of its native $ECOTERRA crypto token just hit the $4,775,000 million mark, meaning the presale has entered its eighth stage, with the price of $ECOTERRA rising to $0.00925.  &lt;br /&gt;
And investors have no time to lose to get involved if they want to get in early. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/award-winning-recycle-earn-r2e-project-ecoterras-presale-raise-surges-to-nearly-5m-is-this-the-ultimate-green-utility-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Award-Winning Recycle-to-Earn (R2E) Project Ecoterra’s Presale Raise Surges to Nearly $5 Million - Is This The Ultimate Green Utility Crypto?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/award-winning-recycle-earn-r2e-project-ecoterras-presale-raise-surges-to-nearly-5m-is-this-the-ultimate-green-utility-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115943/311494/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="335017"/></item></channel></rss>
