<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:58:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey Calls Out Tim Cook: Why Doesn&#8217;t Apple Pay Support Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-calls-out-tim-cook-why-doesnt-apple-pay-support-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 23:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257401</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/jackdorsey_cnbc.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/jackdorsey_cnbc.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin-based social app Damus has been banned from Apple’s app store – and Jack Dorsey is not pleased.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Block CEO Jack Dorsey is putting Apple CEO Tim Cook on blast for seemingly not supporting Bitcoin payments, per the app store’s policies.</p>
<p>His comments follow Apple’s recent confirmation that it would be pulling the Bitcoin-based social app, Damus, from its marketplace.</p>
<h2>Apple’s Crackdown On Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Damus is a decentralized social media app for interacting with Nostr – a Bitcoin-based protocol for exchanging information and messages in a censorship-resistant manner.</p>
<p>The app includes a tipping feature called “zaps” which let users tip one another in Bitcoin over the lightning network. The value exchange is totally peer-to-peer, and Damus takes no cut from such transactions.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the feature <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-backed-damus-faces-explusion-from-apples-app-store-over-bitcoin-tipping-feature/" data-wpel-link="internal">ran afoul</a> of Apple’s terms of service two weeks ago. The company said that it could allow for optional tips and donations, but not for payments that were required in exchange for digital content. “They must use in-app purchase in accordance with guideline 3.1.1,” said the company.</p>
<p>Damus refused to remove this functionality from its app, and tried to explain that zaps did not “unlock” any digital content for users. However, it <a href="https://twitter.com/damusapp/status/1673326463297392640" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">received</a> the same message from Apple again on Monday, and accepted that its removal from the app store was imminent.</p>
<p>“Their suggested fix is to use apple pay,” tweeted Damus on Tuesday. “Sure, I&#8217;ll use apple pay when it supports censorship-resistant, peer-to-peer payments to anyone in the world. Maybe start with peer-to-peer first?”</p>
<h2>Jack Dorsey Responds</h2>
<p>Jack Dorsey was quick to defend Damus on Monday upon hearing the news. “Tips aren’t unlocking content,” he <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1673364469068578822" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>, rehashing the company’s own arguments.</p>
<p>He followed up on Tuesday by calling out Apple’s CEO specifically:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Why doesn’t Apple Pay support bitcoin <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@tim_cook</a>? <a href="https://t.co/2TfqzgXUP1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/2TfqzgXUP1</a></p>
<p>&mdash; jack (@jack) <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1673634767403712514?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“Removed from the App Store for enabling tipping to everyone in the world without the need for a bank, payment card, or government permission,” he added.</p>
<p>Dorsey has previously praised Nostr for being one of two “truly censorship resistant technologies at scale” – alongside Bitcoin itself. While still the CEO of Twitter, Dorsey helped enable a tipping feature on the platform that incorporated Bitcoin lightning tips similar to those used by Nostr.</p>
<p>Tim Cook hasn’t shown interest in putting Bitcoin on Apple’s balance sheet but has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/apple-ceo-tim-cook-confirms-owning-bitcoin-or-ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> that he personally owns some coins.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-calls-out-tim-cook-why-doesnt-apple-pay-support-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Jack Dorsey Calls Out Tim Cook: Why Doesn&#8217;t Apple Pay Support Bitcoin?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Has 70% Odds Of Winning SEC Lawsuit: Bloomberg Analyst</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-has-70-odds-of-winning-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257388</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/grayscale_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/grayscale_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Grayscale’s oral arguments and BlackRock’s ETF filing create a strong likelihood that a Bitcoin spot ETF is approved this year, analysts claim.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The company behind the world’s largest Bitcoin fund has a 70% chance of overcoming the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a major crypto industry lawsuit, according to Bloomberg Intelligence Senior Legal Analyst Elliot Z. Stein.</p>
<p>Given the circumstances, the firm’s analysts assign a 50% likelihood to a Bitcoin spot ETF being approved in the United States this year.</p>
<h2>Grayscale, BlackRock, and the SEC</h2>
<p>According to Stein, the optimistic outlook for Grayscale’s lawsuit may actually serve to benefit BlackRock – which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for a spot ETF product last week – rather than Grayscale’s own filing.</p>
<p>“The SEC and Chair Gary Gensler may be bracing for a loss and looking to preemptively soften it or make it meaningless by approving spot Bitcoin ETF application before or around the same time as a court decision,” <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1673685658538323968" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wrote</a> the analyst in a Tuesday note.</p>
<p>Grayscale’s lawsuit <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-rejects-grayscale-spot-bitcoin-etf-sparking-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> the SEC of violating the Administrative Procedure Act and Securities Exchange Act by arbitrarily denying its Bitcoin spot ETF application last year, despite choosing to approve many similar futures ETF products.</p>
<p>The SEC has rejected every spot ETF application to date, citing failures from their prospective issuers to provide sufficient protections and oversight against market manipulation.</p>
<p>During the first round of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judges-scrutinize-sec-during-oral-arguments-in-grayscale-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">oral arguments</a> in March, all three judges overseeing the case expressed skepticism of the SEC’s case, stating that the agency “has not offered any explanation that the petitioners are wrong.” For Stein, this skepticism boosted Grayscale’s odds of victory from 40% to 70%.</p>
<h2>BlackRock’s Approval Odds</h2>
<p>Bitcoin rallied above $31,000 this week on optimism that a Bitcoin spot ETF could be approved after BlackRock’s filing. Prior submissions from the $10 trillion asset manager have a historical <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" data-wpel-link="internal">approval rate</a> of 575:1.</p>
<p>The SEC even <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/27/the-first-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-is-hitting-the-market-as-crypto-gains-new-momentum.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">approved</a> a leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF last week. Bloomberg’s ETF analyst James Seyffart interpreted this as a sign that the SEC’s attitude toward Bitcoin products could be “lightening up,” per a <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1672275688458539009" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> on Friday.</p>
<p>That said, there’s one aspect of BlackRock’s ETF filing that Seyffart thinks could undermine its application: its partnership with Coinbase for custody – an exchange that the SEC just filed a major lawsuit against.</p>
<p>“You have to take that as a risk,” he said during an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ILy-74GVxV8&amp;ab_channel=UnchainedPodcast" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> on the Unchained podcast on Friday. “We don’t think the odds of this thing getting approved are like 70% like we think the Grayscale lawsuit. The odds are still stacked against BlackRock.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-has-70-odds-of-winning-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-analyst/" rel="nofollow">Grayscale Has 70% Odds Of Winning SEC Lawsuit: Bloomberg Analyst</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swiss National Bank Will Do a Test Run of CBDCs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-national-bank-will-do-a-test-run-of-cbdcs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Switzerland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257316</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Switzerland.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Switzerland.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Swiss CBDC will be sold on the SIX platform and counted as a test run for a possible wider release.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the Point Zero Forum banking conference held in Zurich yesterday, the upcoming launch of a Swiss CHF-based CBDC was announced by Thomas Jordan, the chairman of the Swiss Nation Bank (SNB).</p>
<p>Although no exact date has been put forth by the bank, the chairman of the SNB announced that the CBDC would be released sooner rather than later. This seems in line with earlier <a href="https://www.bis.org/about/bisih/topics/cbdc/tourbillon.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statements</a> from the BIS – who often work closely with the SNB – who planned to have a working prototype ready by mid-2023 as part of Switzerland’s research into cryptocurrencies, codenamed Project Tourbillon.</p>
<h2>Launching On SIX</h2>
<p>According to Jordan, the CBDC will be available – for a limited time only – on SIX Digital Exchange. SIX Digital Exchange is a subsidiary of the SIX Group, which also controls the official stock exchange of Switzerland and the 3<sup>rd</sup> largest stock exchange in Europe.</p>
<p>Although the institution he represents will view the endeavor as a simple test run to ascertain whether a larger scale approach to eCHF is warranted or not, the chairman of the SNB has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/snb-launch-digital-currency-pilot-chairman-2023-06-26/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">confirmed</a> that the CBDC will be “real money”, backed by his institution.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This is not just an experiment, it will be real money equivalent to bank reserves and the objective is to test real transactions with market participants. We do not exclude that we will never introduce retail [CBDCs] but nevertheless we are a little bit prudent at the moment.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Cash Will Remain A Fixture</h2>
<p>At a separate panel held at the same conference, Andrea Maechler – the governor of the SNB – clarified that even if CBDCs are introduced at a larger scale within Switzerland, cash will not be going anywhere.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;[Cash] is the one way that retail households can hold central bank money. That feature needs to be maintained irrespective of the technology&#8221;.</p></blockquote>
<p>The introduction of a CBDC – even if only as a test run – is indicative of the constant research performed by Swiss authorities on the subject, considering their prior outright <a href="https://www.handelszeitung.ch/unternehmen/nationalbank-blockchain-ist-ungeeignet-fur-digitales-zentralbankengeld-342522" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">refusal</a> to consider blockchain-based reserves.</p>
<p>Known worldwide as a banking sector leader, Switzerland has always ensured that its citizens have easy and equitable access to a share of the country’s vast resources and reserves.</p>
<p>Although Switzerland has always been open to exploring new technical solutions – regarding financial products or otherwise – the financial stability of its citizens has remained a steadfast priority of the small yet powerful nation nestled within the Alps.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-national-bank-will-do-a-test-run-of-cbdcs/" rel="nofollow">Swiss National Bank Will Do a Test Run of CBDCs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Pays Close Attention to Hong Kong&#8217;s Crypto Policies, CEO Allaire Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circle-pays-close-attention-to-hong-kongs-crypto-policies-ceo-allaire-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257266</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Jeremy_Allaire.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Jeremy_Allaire.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to Circle's CEO, Asia is a huge area of focus.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jeremy Allaire &#8211; co-founder and CEO of the stablecoin-issuer Circle &#8211; said his company has been closely observing the regulatory developments in Hong Kong. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of the former British colony have recently allowed investors to trade cryptocurrency under a new regime as they carry &#8220;fundamental value.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Asia is a &#8216;Huge Area of Focus&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-firm-circle-eyeing-hong-kong-policies-with-asia-in-focus-1.1938301" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Bloomberg, Allaire noted Hong Kong&#8217;s efforts to establish itself as a &#8220;very significant center for digital markets and for stablecoins.&#8221; As such, Circle is paying &#8220;very close attention to that,&#8221; he added.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The executive sees Asia as an important region for the industry. Recall that Circle </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-and-paxos-secure-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> regulatory approval from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) in November last year. The license enabled the firm to offer digital payment token products and conduct cross-border and local transactions in the city-state.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ruling body of Hong Kong has shown a pro-crypto stance lately, introducing a regulatory framework for the sector at the beginning of the month. According to the new rules, digital asset providers can offer services to retail clients, assuming disclaimers of the possible investment risks are in place.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some suggested that Hong Kong&#8217;s positive approach could signal that China might start warming up to the industry. The government of the world&#8217;s most populated country </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/trading-and-mining-crackdown-in-china-escalates-bitcoin-plunges-3k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">banned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> all crypto-related activities on its territory in 2021.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Moreover, the subsidiaries of some of the largest Chinese banking institutions, including the Bank of Communications, the Bank of China, and Shanghai Pudong Development Bank, have supposedly </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/leading-chinese-banks-support-hong-kong-based-crypto-firms-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">supported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> crypto companies based in Hong Kong.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;What&#8217;s happening in Hong Kong may be a proxy for ultimately how do these markets grow in Greater China,&#8221; Allaire concluded.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_173640" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-173640" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-173640" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" alt="Jeremy Allaire" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-173640" class="wp-caption-text">Jeremy Allaire, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hong Kong Said &#8216;Yes&#8217; to Crypto ETFs</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides implementing cryptocurrency rules, Hong Kong </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/hsbc-hong-kong-lets-clients-trade-btc-and-eth-etfs-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">recently jumped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on the cryptocurrency ETF bandwagon. Earlier this week, Hong Kong and Shanghai Banking Corporation (HSBC) – the largest domestic bank &#8211; enabled clients to buy and sell Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The approved products include CSOP Bitcoin Futures ETF, CSOP Ethereum Futures, and Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, the bank launched an educational program called the Virtual Asset Investor Education Centre, whose goal is to tutor investors for the risks they might encounter when joining the ecosystem.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-pays-close-attention-to-hong-kongs-crypto-policies-ceo-allaire-says/" rel="nofollow">Circle Pays Close Attention to Hong Kong&#8217;s Crypto Policies, CEO Allaire Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Reason Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Surged Over 100% in 7 Days</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-reason-bitcoin-cash-bch-surged-over-100-in-7-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257357</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/bitcoin_cash-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/bitcoin_cash-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash is seriously outperforming the rest of the crypto market. Where’s the hype coming from?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) – the most popular hardfork of Bitcoin (BTC)&#8217;s blockchain – is up over 117% this week, outperforming Bitcoin’s still sizable 15% rise. As of this writing, its the only coin to see anything close to 2X gains within that time frame.</p>
<p>What’s attracting traders and investors to the large-blocker network? Let’s dive in.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash’s EDX Listing</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Cash’s seismic gains began on June 21, precisely when the Wall Street-backed crypto exchange EDX Markets (EDXM) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-backed-cryptocurrency-exchange-edx-goes-live/" data-wpel-link="internal">went live</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/citadel-charles-schwab-fidelity-launched-crypto-exchange-edx-markets/" data-wpel-link="internal">Announced</a> in September 2022, the exchange – backed by Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, and Charles Schwab – promised: “a platform that can meet the needs of both retail traders and institutional investors with high compliance and security standards.”</p>
<p>Upon launch, the high-profile exchange kept its listing count to a conservative four digital assets. One of them, however, was BCH – which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-explodes-100-weekly-as-btc-looks-for-direction-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">rose</a> to $231 on Tuesday, from just $111 on June 21.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257361" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257361" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257361 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-1024x564.png" alt="" width="1024" height="564" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-1024x564.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-300x165.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-768x423.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-1536x846.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20-50x28.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCHUSD_2023-06-27_10-46-20.png 1574w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257361" class="wp-caption-text">BCH / USD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>According to crypto market intelligence platform Santiment, BCH was the biggest beneficiary of the EDXM listing compared to the platform’s other coins, including BTC, Ether (ETH), and Litecoin (LTC). “Notably, $BCH has seen a 3-year high in social discussion rates, &amp; volume has easily eclipsed 2023 highs,” the company <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1672443431602491392" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweeted</a> on Friday.</p>
<p>Data from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/currencies/BCH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Coinglass</a> shows that liquidations for trades involving the coin have also moonshot this week and have mostly impacted short traders, indicating that something of a short squeeze is underway.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Cash’s Regulatory Status</h2>
<p>Bitcoin Cash’s approval by an exchange backed by Wall Street incumbents may be viewed as tacit approval of the coin’s safe regulatory status compared to other altcoins.</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued crypto exchange giants Binance and Coinbase earlier this month for listing many alleged “securities” including large caps coins like Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC).</p>
<p>The four coins listed have already been granted regulatory safeguards in certain segments of the global crypto market. Canada, for example, <a href="https://help.newton.co/hc/en-us/articles/4413904757651" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">imposes</a> a net buy limit on exchange users of $30,000 per year for most cryptocurrencies, but excludes BTC, ETH, LTC, and BCH from that rule.</p>
<p>SEC Chair Gary Gensler has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-reasserts-every-crypto-is-a-security-aside-from-bitcoin-lawyers-disagree/" data-wpel-link="internal">explained</a> that he considers Bitcoin a unique commodity because of its “unique history and creation story.” Bitcoin Cash, however, is a mere fork of Bitcoin’s blockchain code, sharing Bitcoin’s history in terms of how it is issued.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-reason-bitcoin-cash-bch-surged-over-100-in-7-days/" rel="nofollow">The Reason Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Surged Over 100% in 7 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fireblocks Expands Support for Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud Platform, Alibaba Cloud</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fireblocks-expands-support-for-amazon-web-services-google-cloud-platform-alibaba-cloud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257224</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Fireblocks.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Fireblocks.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The new additions are expected to allow banks to configure the Fireblocks platform to their existing IT infrastructure and security policies.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto infrastructure giant Fireblocks has announced that it has started offering support for cloud service providers Amazon Web Services (AWS), Google Cloud Platform (GCP), Alibaba Cloud, Thales, and Securosus by expanding its MPC-CMP wallet and key management technology.</p>
<p>The latest move is expected to help banks and financial institutions to leverage Fireblocks&#8217; security and technology stack to seamlessly bring their digital asset initiatives into production while meeting their risk, compliance, and regulatory requirements.</p>
<h2>Roping in Prominent Financial Institutions</h2>
<p>Since its inception in 2019, Fireblocks has roped some of the most prominent banks and financial institutions in the world into the digital asset space. This includes &#8211; BNY Mellon, BNP Paribas, ANZ Bank, NAB, ABN AMRO, BTG Pactual, Tel Aviv Stock Exchange, and SIX Digital Exchange, according to the official<a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/fireblocks-expands-support-for-banking--financial-institutions-with-new-hsm-public--private-cloud-capabilities-301863908.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> press release</a>.</p>
<p>Building new digital asset custody, trading, clearing, and settlement services, and tokenization of financial products such as tokenized fiat, central bank digital currencies (CBDC), carbon credits, etc, are some of the use cases that these financial institutions have leveraged Fireblocks for.</p>
<p>Orly Grinfeld, EVP, Head of Clearing at Tel Aviv Stock Exchange, said that the platform managed to take its digital treasury bond initiative &#8211; Project Eden &#8211; from ideation to go live in just five months due to the collaboration with Fireblocks.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Their world-class security operations and modular infrastructure allowed us to deploy wallets to our primary dealers, which included international banks like Goldman Sachs, Deutsche Bank, and JP Morgan. Not only were we able to ensure that the entire workflow operations were secure, but that all the vendors were streamlined and deployed in order to bring Eden live quickly.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Fireblocks&#8217; Journey So Far</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/talking-fireblocks-massive-growth-and-crypto-biggest-challenges-ceo-michael-shaulov-exclusive-interview/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">conversation</a> with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Fireblocks Co-Founder and CEO Michael Shaulov had said that he didn’t anticipate the company to grow so quickly and described the journey as &#8220;very unexpected and occasionally even unplanned.&#8221;</p>
<p>Last January, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fireblocks-valued-at-8-billion-following-a-550-million-fundraiser/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">raised</a> $550 million at a whopping valuation of $8 billion. Its clients include Silicon Valley-based online trading firm Robinhood as well as fintech company Revolut.</p>
<p>Earlier this year, Fireblocks also laid off around 30 employees, accounting for 5% of the team for the first time as digital assets plummeted in value and several prominent companies slid into bankruptcy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fireblocks-expands-support-for-amazon-web-services-google-cloud-platform-alibaba-cloud/" rel="nofollow">Fireblocks Expands Support for Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud Platform, Alibaba Cloud</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Forta and QuickNode Partner to Better Monitor and Protect All Assets in Web3</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/forta-and-quicknode-partner-to-better-monitor-and-protect-all-assets-in-web3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257342</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/10_1687790106cFpRO8ACWj.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/10_1687790106cFpRO8ACWj.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; North Miami Beach, United States, June 27th, 2023] Developers now have safe and seamless access to Forta scan nodes via QuickNode’s high-performance infrastructure. Forta Network, a leading provider in machine learning-powered threat detection, has entered into a new partnership with QuickNode, the leading end-to-end development platform for web3 innovation. This partnership will [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; North Miami Beach, United States, June 27th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><strong>Developers now have safe and seamless access to Forta scan nodes via QuickNode’s high-performance infrastructure.</strong></p>
<p>Forta Network, a leading provider in machine learning-powered threat detection, has entered into a new partnership with <a href="https://www.quicknode.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">QuickNode</a>, the leading end-to-end development platform for web3 innovation. This partnership will allow developers to easily and securely access Forta scan nodes via QuickNode’s best-in-class blockchain infrastructure.</p>
<p>QuickNode is the leading web3 blockchain development platform, offering powerful tools to simplify and expedite dApp development, saving countless hours for Web3 engineers. Utilizing QuickNode to run Forta nodes ensures the accuracy, reliability, and data consistency that top-tier web3 and global companies like Chainalysis, Nansen, Magic Eden, Twitter, and Adobe require to delight their users.</p>
<p>Together, QuickNode and Forta are committed to protecting Web3 users and supporting the developers that are building solutions to make blockchain safer for everyone. Thanks to this new partnership, Forta scan node runners have access to 22+ chains and advanced developer tooling on QuickNode’s Build Plan.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Reliable data providers are a critical component of the Forta Network. This collaboration with QuickNode provides the Forta scan node community with important optionality and furthers our mission to create a decentralized and sustainable detection network for Web3.” – Andy Beal, Ecosystem Lead at the Forta Foundation.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://docs.forta.network/en/latest/quicknode-partnership/?_gl=1*1qzpsv7*_ga*Njk5NzAyODIxLjE2ODc3ODcwNDU.*_ga_3ERDDVRGQQ*MTY4Nzg2OTU2My40LjAuMTY4Nzg2OTU2My4wLjAuMA.." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Forta&#8217;s new docs page</a> provides a step-by-step guide on setting up your scan node with QuickNode.</p>
<p><strong>Features included in QuickNode’s Build Plan:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>20 Million API Credits per month</li>
<li>100 Requests/sec</li>
<li>10 Endpoints</li>
<li>Multiple Regions</li>
<li>24hrs Support response time</li>
<li>Support for 21+ chains</li>
<li>Archive data</li>
<li>Trace &amp; Debug</li>
<li>QuickAlerts</li>
<li>Graph API</li>
<li>NFT Fetch API</li>
<li>Token API</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>About QuickNode</strong></p>
<p>Since its founding in 2017, QuickNode has emerged as the top choice for businesses and innovators requiring best-in-class blockchain development tools for speed, reliability, and security. QuickNode handles over eight billion blockchain requests daily and offers a 2.5X faster response time than competitors across 22+ chains and 35+ networks. With a user-friendly interface and a robust multi-chain developer tool suite, QuickNode has become the preferred choice for leading Web3 businesses and global brands.</p>
<p>To learn more about Forta and QuickNode, please visit the following links:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Forta:</strong> <a href="https://forta.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://forta.network/</a></li>
<li><strong>QuickNode:</strong> <a href="https://quicknode.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://quicknode.com/</a></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/forta-and-quicknode-partner-to-better-monitor-and-protect-all-assets-in-web3/" rel="nofollow">Forta and QuickNode Partner to Better Monitor and Protect All Assets in Web3</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>As Shiba Inu Price Flatlines, Wall Street Memes Presale Raises $11 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/as-shiba-inu-price-flatlines-wall-street-memes-presale-raises-11-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257332</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shiba_wsm_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shiba_wsm_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu ($SHIB) price has dropped 9% from Thursday’s high, with the token trading around the $0.00000765 level. $SHIB’s sharp drop has led to questions about the token’s future – with many wondering whether its price potential is dead in the water. In other news, the Wall Street Memes ($WSM) presale has now raked [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Shiba Inu ($SHIB) price has dropped 9% from Thursday’s high, with the token trading around the $0.00000765 level.</p>
<p>$SHIB’s sharp drop has led to questions about the token’s future – with many wondering whether its price potential is dead in the water.</p>
<p>In other news, the Wall Street Memes ($WSM) presale has now raked in an incredible $11 million, reflecting investors’ appetite for community-backed meme coins.</p>
<h2>A Week of Volatility Prompts Caution from $SHIB Holders</h2>
<p>It’s been a whirlwind week for Shiba Inu holders, given the coin’s extreme level of volatility.</p>
<p>Price soared early last week, breezing through the 20-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) on the daily price chart and hitting a high of $0.00000846.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, $SHIB could not breach the 50-day EMA – and immediately rejected the indicator, prompting a sharp drop in value.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257334" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-19.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="269" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-19.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-19-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-19-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Price is now stuck between the 20-day and 50-day EMAs, with no clear directional bias presenting itself.</p>
<p>The price stagnation over the past three days has led to a sense of unease among the investor base, given Shiba Inu’s history of capitulation.</p>
<p>Market sentiment has turned cautious, with $SHIB holders hoping for a catalyst to swing the token&#8217;s price in either direction.</p>
<h2>Shibarium Development Provides Beacon of Hope for Shiba Inu</h2>
<p>Amid this uncertainty, many meme coin enthusiasts are deliberating whether the ongoing volatility is the &#8220;new normal&#8221; for Shiba Inu.</p>
<p>However, crypto influencer Myles G, who has an audience of nearly 150,000 on YouTube, released a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8XAObebIrNs&amp;ab_channel=MylesGInvestments" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> detailing his short-term optimism – referencing the recent development updates for Shibarium.</p>
<p>Shibarium is an upcoming layer-2 network for the Shiba Inu ecosystem that will be built on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-26.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257335" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-26.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="335" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-26.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-26-300x167.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-26-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This layer-2 network is expected to go live later this year and aims to expand the Shiba Inu ecosystem to include decentralized finance (DeFi) apps, metaverse worlds, and blockchain-based games.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu’s developers are simultaneously working on a service called “Shibacals” that will be used to link real-world assets (like artwork) to NFTs – thereby helping prove ownership.</p>
<p>This ambitious development strategy has stirred excitement among $SHIB holders – many of whom are hopeful that these upgrades can add significant value to the token.</p>
<p>As such, although the $SHIB price has been rocky of late, the ongoing ecosystem developments suggest that there could be a bright future ahead for this popular meme coin.</p>
<h2>Which Meme Coins Could Outpace Shiba Inu?</h2>
<p>While the $SHIB price remains turbulent, a new entrant in the meme coin arena has attracted attention – Wall Street Memes.</p>
<p>This fresh-off-the-block coin has garnered massive interest from the trading community and raised a remarkable $11 million through its presale phase.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Poised to Disrupt Meme Coin Space After Raising $11m</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a>, the self-proclaimed champion of the &#8220;little guy,&#8221; is a meme coin currently shaking up the status quo in the crypto market.</p>
<p>With the viral power of crypto-based memes, Wall Street Memes aims to &#8220;tokenize&#8221; a community of over 1.1 million people by launching the $WSM token.</p>
<p>Importantly, Wall Street Memes’ team has already demonstrated their ability to generate demand for a viral digital asset, with their <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls NFT collection</a> selling out in just over half an hour in 2021.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257336" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-24.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="297" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-24.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-24-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-24-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This netted the creators a cool $2.5 million – solidifying the Wall Street Memes brand in the crypto-sphere.</p>
<p>Now that the Wall Street Memes team is gearing up to launch $WSM on Tier-1 crypto exchanges, many early investors speculate that the token could be primed for an exponential price increase.</p>
<p>Over 9,000 people have already opted to join the project’s <a href="https://t.me/wallst_memes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>, which has seen massive growth due to the presale&#8217;s early success.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Memes presale is currently in Stage 19 out of 30, meaning that eager investors have snapped up nearly two-thirds of the token allocation.</p>
<p>With $WSM available for just $0.0304, some believe this could be a golden opportunity to get in at the ground floor of a potential crypto revolution.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-shiba-inu-price-flatlines-wall-street-memes-presale-raises-11-million/" rel="nofollow">As Shiba Inu Price Flatlines, Wall Street Memes Presale Raises $11 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Skyrockets 15% Weekly but Bearish Signs Start Flashing: is a Correction Coming? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-skyrockets-15-weekly-but-bearish-signs-start-flashing-is-a-correction-coming-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257290</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is facing challenges in surpassing the significant resistance at $30K, which has been holding the price for a prolonged period. If successful, this breakthrough would result in a bullish bias for the cryptocurrency in the medium term. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Bitcoin recently found support at both the static support level [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is facing challenges in surpassing the significant resistance at $30K, which has been holding the price for a prolonged period. If successful, this breakthrough would result in a bullish bias for the cryptocurrency in the medium term.</p>
<h1>Technical Analysis</h1>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h1>The Daily Chart</h1>
<p>Bitcoin recently found support at both the static support level of $25K and the lower trendline of the channel. Consequently, the substantial buying pressure in this support region led to a significant surge, with the aim of breaking through the $30K resistance.</p>
<p>However, upon reaching the $30K level, Bitcoin entered a consolidation phase, accompanied by weakened bullish momentum.</p>
<p>It is important to note that the price has formed a double-top &#8211; a well-known bearish reversal pattern, at this level, thereby increasing the likelihood of a short-term reversal. Furthermore, the RSI indicator currently indicates an overbought condition in the market, acting as a catalyst for the potential reversal scenario.</p>
<p>In the event that the price faces rejection within this crucial price range, the first target for Bitcoin would be the 100-day moving average of $27,900.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257294" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257294" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257294 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2706231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257294" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h1>The 4-Hour Chart</h1>
<p>Switching to the 4-hour chart, Bitcoin developed a series of higher highs and higher lows during the recent bullish phase, indicating a healthy and robust upward rally. However, upon encountering the $30K resistance, the rally stopped, and the price entered a consolidation phase without providing any clear indication of its next move.</p>
<p>Most recently, the price slightly surpassed the previous major high at $31K, creating a new high. Nonetheless, since the cryptocurrency hasn&#8217;t continued its upward movement beyond the $31K mark, this cannot be considered a new significant high.</p>
<p>Ultimately, if Bitcoin breaks above the $30K region and consolidates at higher levels, it will likely trigger a solid bullish rally. Conversely, if selling pressure dominates the market and leads to a decline, the following targets for Bitcoin would be the 100-day moving average at $29K and the static support level of $25K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257293" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257293" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257293 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2706232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257293" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h1>On-chain Analysis</h1>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Funding Rates</strong></p>
<p>There is no denying how much Bitcoin&#8217;s price action is influenced by the futures market, especially during the recent cycle. Therefore, analyzing its sentiment could provide some useful insight into how the price is likely to act in the short term.</p>
<p>This chart represents the Bitcoin funding rates metric, indicating whether the long traders or the short sellers dominate at any given time.</p>
<p>It is evident that following the recent surge in price, the funding rates have been demonstrating positive values constantly, pointing to the fact that the futures market is partly responsible for the recent rally and that the derivatives traders are bullish on BTC.</p>
<p>Yet, positive funding rates also increase the probability of a long liquidation cascade happening, which could reverse the current trend in a matter of days. As a result, investors should be wary of a growing chance of a rapid decline in the coming weeks, especially if the funding rates experience more growth.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257292" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257292" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257292 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_funding_rates_2706231" width="2560" height="1613" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-1536x968.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jun-27-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257292" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-skyrockets-15-weekly-but-bearish-signs-start-flashing-is-a-correction-coming-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Skyrockets 15% Weekly but Bearish Signs Start Flashing: is a Correction Coming? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple v. SEC Case Update: The Latest Developments as of June 27th</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-case-update-the-latest-developments-as-of-june-27th/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257300</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/secvripple_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/secvripple_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are this month's developments regarding the case between Ripple and the US SEC. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The case between Ripple and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission rages on.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-the-ripple-v-sec-lawsuit-could-affect-the-entire-crypto-industry-a-lawyers-take/" data-wpel-link="internal">explored</a> how the lawsuit could affect the entire crypto industry, talking to legal experts with interesting commentary on the matter.</p>
<p>With that said, let&#8217;s have a look at some of the most recent developments as of today &#8211; June 27th, 2023.</p>
<ul>
<li>The most recent development came yesterday when the lawyer representing thousands of XRP holders &#8211; John E. Deaton &#8211; <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1673348550334324736" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that he got an email that initially worried him.</li>
<li>However, it turned out that there was just one lawyer who withdrew from the case. Deaton, as well as Marc Fagel &#8211; a former SEC litigator &#8211; both confirmed that this is a non-event.</li>
<li>Speaking of Fagel, a couple of weeks back, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-settlement-former-sec-director-doubts-it-says-ruling-might-come-in-days/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that a ruling might be coming in days.</li>
<li>Perhaps the most important development this month came on or about June 13th when the SEC, under a court request, finally unsealed the documents pertaining to William Hinman&#8217;s speech.</li>
<li>You can find more about it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-and-the-hinman-speech-what-happened-behind-the-scenes/" data-wpel-link="internal">here</a>.</li>
<li>Commenting on the matter was Stuart Alderoty, the Chief Legal Officer at Ripple, who said:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>Seeing the depth to which the SEC has essentially weaponized the lack of regulatory clarity through enforcement actions since this speech was given &#8211; it&#8217;s no surprise that we can call bluff on their claims to &#8220;just come in and register&#8221;  as nothing but in bad faith.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-case-update-the-latest-developments-as-of-june-27th/" rel="nofollow">Ripple v. SEC Case Update: The Latest Developments as of June 27th</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
