<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>XBTC Coin is Up 30,000% Today But Crypto Experts are Saying This Lesser-Known Project is the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xbtc-coin-is-up-30000-today-but-crypto-experts-are-saying-this-lesser-known-project-is-the-next-crypto-to-explode.htm</link><description>In the latest jaw-dropping DEX skyrocket, Bitcoin spin-off token XBTC has exploded up +30,000%, but is all as it seems as experts warn it could be a scam. &lt;br /&gt;
The alluring pump comes on the tail-end of a wider interest in Bitcoin DEX tokens in recent weeks, which saw rival projects such as BITCOIN2 post equally impressive moon-shots....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xbtc-coin-is-up-30000-today-but-crypto-experts-are-saying-this-lesser-known-project-is-the-next-crypto-to-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: XBTC Coin is Up 30,000% Today But Crypto Experts are Saying This Lesser-Known Project is the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xbtc-coin-is-up-30000-today-but-crypto-experts-are-saying-this-lesser-known-project-is-the-next-crypto-to-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121947/322844/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="776866"/></item><item><title>Federal Reserve Establishes Program to Monitor Crypto Activities in US Banks</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/federal-reserve-establishes-program-monitor-crypto-activities-us-banks.htm</link><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve has introduced a new set of guidelines aimed at closely monitoring banks' involvement with cryptocurrencies.  &lt;br /&gt;
This program, termed the "novel activities supervision program," was unveiled on Tuesday, clarifying the central bank's strategy for supervising banks' interactions with digital assets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/federal-reserve-establishes-program-monitor-crypto-activities-us-banks.htm"&gt;Read More: Federal Reserve Establishes Program to Monitor Crypto Activities in US Banks&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/federal-reserve-establishes-program-monitor-crypto-activities-us-banks.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121946/322836/federal-reserve-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="227645"/></item><item><title>Here's How PayPal Plans to Monetize Its New PYUSD Stablecoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/heres-how-paypal-plans-monetize-its-new-pyusd-stablecoin.htm</link><description>Payments giant PayPal plans to generate revenue from its upcoming stablecoin in a number of ways, including its use in payment transactions. &lt;br /&gt;
The PYUSD stablecoin would also bring the company revenue in the form of interest income from assets backing it, Jose Fernandez da Ponte, senior vice president of PayPal’s blockchain, crypto, and digital currencies, said in a recent interview with Bloomberg. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/heres-how-paypal-plans-monetize-its-new-pyusd-stablecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Here's How PayPal Plans to Monetize Its New PYUSD Stablecoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>PYUSD</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/heres-how-paypal-plans-monetize-its-new-pyusd-stablecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121949/322834/paypal-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="102119"/></item><item><title>Pepe Coin Price Prediction as PEPE Surges Up 15% and Becomes Best Performing Meme Coin in the Market – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-surges-up-15-becomes-best-performing-meme-coin-market-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The Pepe Coin price has surged to $0.00000124 in the past 24 hours, with its 15% rise in the past 24 hours making it the best-performing meme token in the market right now. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite this gain, PEPE remains down by 1.5% in the last 7 days and by 15% in the last 30, with the altcoin also having declined by 71% since hitting an all-time high of $0.00000431 in early May....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-surges-up-15-becomes-best-performing-meme-coin-market-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin Price Prediction as PEPE Surges Up 15% and Becomes Best Performing Meme Coin in the Market – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-surges-up-15-becomes-best-performing-meme-coin-market-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121938/322833/pepe-coin-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1053458"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Gains Traction Amid Key Macro Influences and ETF Approval Hopes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-gains-traction-amid-key-macro-influences-etf-approval-hopes.htm</link><description>On Wednesday, Bitcoin (BTC/USD) is witnessing a notable surge, registering a 1.60% increase and trading at a promising $29,700.  &lt;br /&gt;
This uptrend appears to be bolstered by key macroeconomic influences, most notably the looming CPI report and the forthcoming Federal Reserve interest rate decision.  &lt;br /&gt;
Furthermore, the financial landscape is rife with optimism as hopes for a Bitcoin ETF approval intensify, fueling the cryptocurrency's price rally....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-gains-traction-amid-key-macro-influences-etf-approval-hopes.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Gains Traction Amid Key Macro Influences and ETF Approval Hopes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-gains-traction-amid-key-macro-influences-etf-approval-hopes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121931/322799/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1508435"/></item><item><title>Most Russians Wary of Digital Ruble, Survey Finds – Blow for Moscow’s CBDC?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/most-russians-wary-of-digital-ruble-survey-finds-blow-for-moscows-cbdc.htm</link><description>Most Russian citizens say they distrust or have no interest in using the digital ruble, Russia’s CBDC, a survey has found. &lt;br /&gt;
The survey was carried out by the media outlet and information service provider BankInform, which asked its subscribers to give their thoughts on the CBDC. &lt;br /&gt;
The coin is currently being piloted in “real-world” scenarios with what the Central Bank has labeled a “select group of consumers.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/most-russians-wary-of-digital-ruble-survey-finds-blow-for-moscows-cbdc.htm"&gt;Read More: Most Russians Wary of Digital Ruble, Survey Finds – Blow for Moscow’s CBDC?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/most-russians-wary-of-digital-ruble-survey-finds-blow-for-moscows-cbdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121901/322748/kremlin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="571830"/></item><item><title>SEC-Ripple Ruling a ‘Silver Lining’ for South Korean Prosecutors in Do Kwon Case</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-ruling-a-silver-lining-for-south-korean-prosecutors-in-do-kwon-case.htm</link><description>The XRP trial ruling may reportedly negatively impact South Korean prosecutors’ bid to convict Do Kwon and Terraform Labs of fraud and securities violations, but officials claim otherwise. &lt;br /&gt;
The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has expressed its “disappointment” at a court ruling last month that declared that Ripple’s XRP token was “not in and of itself” a security. &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC has since claimed that Terraform’s coin LUNC (formerly LUNA) is indeed a security....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-ruling-a-silver-lining-for-south-korean-prosecutors-in-do-kwon-case.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC-Ripple Ruling a ‘Silver Lining’ for South Korean Prosecutors in Do Kwon Case&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-ruling-a-silver-lining-for-south-korean-prosecutors-in-do-kwon-case.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121796/322493/skorea-0708.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="577054"/></item><item><title>Former FTX Co-CEO Ryan Salame Considering Guilty Plea Talks – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-co-ceo-ryan-salame-considering-guilty-plea-talks-heres-the-latest-1.htm</link><description>Ryan Salame, the former co-CEO of FTX Digital Markets, is reportedly discussing a potential guilty plea with U.S. authorities....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-co-ceo-ryan-salame-considering-guilty-plea-talks-heres-the-latest-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Former FTX Co-CEO Ryan Salame Considering Guilty Plea Talks – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Fraud</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-co-ceo-ryan-salame-considering-guilty-plea-talks-heres-the-latest-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121920/322772/b8402f706581cf173c4f428ea.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="106093"/></item><item><title>Pepe Coin Price Jumps 9%, But BTC20 Launch Expected to Be Much More Explosive – 24-Hour Countdown Begins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-jumps-9-but-btc20-launch-expected-to-be-much-more-explosive-24-hour-countdown-begins.htm</link><description>The price of Pepe Coin (PEPE) has leaped around 9% in tandem with a broader cryptocurrency market rally on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s third-largest meme coin by market capitalization, which burst onto the scene back in May, was last trading around $0.0000012, now up more than 12% from the multi-month lows it hit on Monday around $0.00000107....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-jumps-9-but-btc20-launch-expected-to-be-much-more-explosive-24-hour-countdown-begins.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin Price Jumps 9%, But BTC20 Launch Expected to Be Much More Explosive – 24-Hour Countdown Begins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Pepe</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>ERC-20</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-jumps-9-but-btc20-launch-expected-to-be-much-more-explosive-24-hour-countdown-begins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121910/322765/btc20.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1418219"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 8 August – Hedera, MultiversX, Algorand</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-8-august-hedera-multiversx-algorand.htm</link><description>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is anticipated to give the green light to spot Bitcoin ETF applications from financial giants BlackRock and Invesco. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Mike Novogratz, CEO of Galaxy Digital, the approval could occur within a four to six-month window. &lt;br /&gt;
Considering this evolving macroeconomic circumstance, what are the best cryptocurrencies to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-8-august-hedera-multiversx-algorand.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 8 August – Hedera, MultiversX, Algorand&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Hedera</category><category>Xrp20</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>Algorand</category><category>HBAR</category><category>HBAR price</category><category>MultiversX</category><category>EGLD</category><category>EGLD price</category><category>ALGO</category><category>ALGO PRICE</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Cryptos</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptos</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Altcoin</category><category>Crypto Projects</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Crypto Presales</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-8-august-hedera-multiversx-algorand.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121908/322759/bctbt-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="275411"/></item><item><title>Green Crypto Chimpzee Helps to Fight Climate Change using Blockchain Technology – Next Big Thing?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-chimpzee-helps-fight-climate-change-using-blockchain-technology-next-big-thing.htm</link><description>In a time when climate change threatens ecosystems around the globe, the collective effort to protect our planet has become a focal point for many. From reforestation projects to the conservation of endangered species, a multitude of initiatives are sprouting up to safeguard the environment....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-chimpzee-helps-fight-climate-change-using-blockchain-technology-next-big-thing.htm"&gt;Read More: Green Crypto Chimpzee Helps to Fight Climate Change using Blockchain Technology – Next Big Thing?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Chimpzee Presale</category><category>Eco Friendly Crypto</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Best Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-chimpzee-helps-fight-climate-change-using-blockchain-technology-next-big-thing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121904/322757/chimp-1822540-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="274913"/></item><item><title>Is Bitrock Price Going To Zero? Down 80%, New ERC-20 Token Launches This Week</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/is-bitrock-price-going-to-zero-down-80-new-erc-20-token-launches-this-week.htm</link><description>After a stratospheric run-in mid-July that saw the Bitrock (BITROCK) nearly 8000x from its decentralized exchange (DEX) launch price of $0.000037 to reach highs of around $0.30 per token, the token has come under massive sell pressure. &lt;br /&gt;
BITROCK was last trading slightly below $0.06, more than 80% down from its recent highs and with its market cap having shrunk to around $6 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/is-bitrock-price-going-to-zero-down-80-new-erc-20-token-launches-this-week.htm"&gt;Read More: Is Bitrock Price Going To Zero? Down 80%, New ERC-20 Token Launches This Week&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Bitrock</category><category>Ethereum layer-2</category><category>ERC-20 token</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/is-bitrock-price-going-to-zero-down-80-new-erc-20-token-launches-this-week.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121906/322758/btc20.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1418219"/></item><item><title>Cathie Wood Expects SEC to Approve Multiple Spot Crypto ETFs Simultaneously – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-wood-expects-sec-approve-multiple-spot-crypto-etfs-simultaneously-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>In an interview on August 7, Cathie Wood, the CEO of ARK Investment Management, stated that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) might approve multiple spot-Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) simultaneously.  &lt;br /&gt;
This marks a change from her belief that her firm would be the first to receive approval for the much-awaited product....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-wood-expects-sec-approve-multiple-spot-crypto-etfs-simultaneously-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Cathie Wood Expects SEC to Approve Multiple Spot Crypto ETFs Simultaneously – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Etf Bitcoin</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>Cathie Wood</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bitcoin ETF</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-wood-expects-sec-approve-multiple-spot-crypto-etfs-simultaneously-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121905/322755/getpaidstock-com-64d29859.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="216511"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as $29,000 Level Holds Stable – Here are Key Levels to Watch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-29000-level-holds-stable-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin maintains its position around the $29,000 threshold, several market dynamics emerge, offering potential trajectories for the world's leading cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
The sentiment surrounding BTC witnessed a positive shift post the encouraging remarks by renowned investor Cathie Wood.  &lt;br /&gt;
Moreover, a recent report by CoinShares highlights an evolving landscape among institutional investors, with a noticeable decrease in the shorting of Bitcoin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-29000-level-holds-stable-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as $29,000 Level Holds Stable – Here are Key Levels to Watch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-29000-level-holds-stable-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121886/322724/8-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="488060"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Rallies Towards $30,000 Amid Rising Spot ETF Application Approval and PayPal Stablecoin Optimism</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-rallies-towards-30000-amid-rising-spot-etf-application-approval-paypal-stablecoin-optimism.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) is approaching a retest of the psychologically important $30,000 amid a fresh wave of optimism about the likelihood of near-term spot bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) application approvals, as well as optimism about crypto’s broader adoption. &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s first and largest digital asset by market capitalization was last up around 2.5% and on course for its best one-day performance since mid-July....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-rallies-towards-30000-amid-rising-spot-etf-application-approval-paypal-stablecoin-optimism.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin (BTC) Price Rallies Towards $30,000 Amid Rising Spot ETF Application Approval and PayPal Stablecoin Optimism&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>PYUSD</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>spot bitcoin ETF</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-rallies-towards-30000-amid-rising-spot-etf-application-approval-paypal-stablecoin-optimism.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121902/322751/btc-14.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="106946"/></item><item><title>Ex-FTX US Head of Partnerships, Sina Nader, Takes on Role as Head of Strategy at Mysten Labs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-ftx-us-head-of-partnerships-sina-nader-takes-on-role-as-head-of-strategy-at-mysten-labs.htm</link><description>Sina Nader, the former head of partnerships at FTX US, has joined Mysten Labs as its new head of strategy.  &lt;br /&gt;
Nader will report directly to Evan Cheng, the CEO and co-founder of the Palo Alto-based Web3 startup, according to a Monday report from Bloomberg.  &lt;br /&gt;
Cheng, along with other former employees of Meta Platforms (formerly known as Facebook), created Mysten Labs with the vision of making the decentralized web safer and more accessible. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-ftx-us-head-of-partnerships-sina-nader-takes-on-role-as-head-of-strategy-at-mysten-labs.htm"&gt;Read More: Ex-FTX US Head of Partnerships, Sina Nader, Takes on Role as Head of Strategy at Mysten Labs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>FTX US</category><category>Sina Nader</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-ftx-us-head-of-partnerships-sina-nader-takes-on-role-as-head-of-strategy-at-mysten-labs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121896/322732/getpaidstock-com-64c99d70.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="171399"/></item><item><title>Identity Verification in Crypto: Addressing the Clash Between Blockchain Anonymity and KYC Compliance</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/identity-verification-crypto-addressing-clash-between-blockchain-anonymity-kyc-compliance.htm</link><description>Financial privacy and anonymity online have been among the key principles of blockchains since Satoshi Nakamoto first unveiled the Bitcoin white paper, but recent actions from regulators have put this principle under pressure. &lt;br /&gt;
To better understand regulatory actions, listening to what regulators are actually saying can be useful....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/identity-verification-crypto-addressing-clash-between-blockchain-anonymity-kyc-compliance.htm"&gt;Read More: Identity Verification in Crypto: Addressing the Clash Between Blockchain Anonymity and KYC Compliance&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>KYC</category><category>Privacy</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/identity-verification-crypto-addressing-clash-between-blockchain-anonymity-kyc-compliance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121894/322730/anonymous.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="970521"/></item><item><title>Crypto-Focused Public Companies Outdo Q2 Profit Projections, Boosted by Cryptocurrency Price Surge</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-focused-public-companies-outdo-q2-profit-projections-boosted-by-cryptocurrency-price-surge.htm</link><description>Major crypto companies reported strong earnings last quarter as swelling crypto asset prices drove up profits across the industry. &lt;br /&gt;
Last week, institutional Bitcoin (BTC) giant MicroStrategy reported a return to profit in Q2, with $120.4 million in revenue. The company also stacked an additional 12,800 BTC over the quarter at an average price of $28,233 per coin, bringing its total holdings to 152,800 BTC ($4.5 billion)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-focused-public-companies-outdo-q2-profit-projections-boosted-by-cryptocurrency-price-surge.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto-Focused Public Companies Outdo Q2 Profit Projections, Boosted by Cryptocurrency Price Surge&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-focused-public-companies-outdo-q2-profit-projections-boosted-by-cryptocurrency-price-surge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121899/322737/adobestock-602816766.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="64870"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – TOSHI, BULLET, XBTC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-clown-unibase-fuku-biao.htm</link><description>Blue chip crypto markets are on the front foot on Tuesday, with Bitcoin (BTC) at its highest level in nearly a week above $29,500 and up close to 3% in the last 24 hours, and Ether (ETH) approaching a retest of $1,850 and up around 2% in the last 24 hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-clown-unibase-fuku-biao.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – TOSHI, BULLET, XBTC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ether</category><category>btc</category><category>ETH</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Xrp20</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-clown-unibase-fuku-biao.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121898/322736/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Binance Becomes First Fully Licensed Exchange in El Salvador, Coinbase Offers to Buy Back Up to $150 Million of Its $1 Billion Bonds, Bitstamp in Talks to Raise Fresh Funding, Brazilian CBDC Gets Its Official Name and Logo</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-exchange-in-el-salvador-coinbase-offers-to-buy-back-up-to-150-million-of-its-1-billion-bonds-bitstamp-in-talks-to-raise-fresh-funding-brazilian-cbdc-gets-its-official-name-and-logo.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-exchange-in-el-salvador-coinbase-offers-to-buy-back-up-to-150-million-of-its-1-billion-bonds-bitstamp-in-talks-to-raise-fresh-funding-brazilian-cbdc-gets-its-official-name-and-logo.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Binance Becomes First Fully Licensed Exchange in El Salvador, Coinbase Offers to Buy Back Up to $150 Million of Its $1 Billion Bonds, Bitstamp in Talks to Raise Fresh Funding, Brazilian CBDC Gets Its Official Name and Logo&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Investment</category><category>Bitstamp</category><category>Europe</category><category>UK</category><category>Asia</category><category>Brazil</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Bank of England</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>FCA</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Blockchain.com</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Mining</category><category>Jihan Wu</category><category>Career</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-becomes-first-fully-licensed-exchange-in-el-salvador-coinbase-offers-to-buy-back-up-to-150-million-of-its-1-billion-bonds-bitstamp-in-talks-to-raise-fresh-funding-brazilian-cbdc-gets-its-official-name-and-logo.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121863/322688/adobestock-rafael-henrique-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="216003"/></item></channel></rss>
