<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>If You Are Looking For the Next Decentraland Then RobotEra Could be Your 25x Opportunity</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/if-you-are-looking-for-next-decentraland-then-robotera-could-25x-opportunity.htm</link><description>RobotEra is an upcoming metaverse cryptocurrency project that is building an interactive world for users to build with no code, play, and enjoy entertainment experiences. It will also allow players to buy and work on virtual property and characters in the form of NFTs (non-fungible tokens). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/if-you-are-looking-for-next-decentraland-then-robotera-could-25x-opportunity.htm"&gt;Read More: If You Are Looking For the Next Decentraland Then RobotEra Could be Your 25x Opportunity&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Metaverse Cryptocurrency</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Taro</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Web3 Game</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/if-you-are-looking-for-next-decentraland-then-robotera-could-25x-opportunity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100641/248836/robotera-land.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="367990"/></item><item><title>Buying an EV? This Crypto Project Rewards You With Carbon Credits For Charging and Makes Payments Easy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/buying-an-ev-crypto-project-rewards-you-with-carbon-credits-for-charging-makes-payments-easy.htm</link><description>C+Charge is a peer-to-peer payment platform and EV charging app that aims to increase electric vehicle adoption buy expanding access to EV charging networks. The platform allows users to easily and cheaply pay for their charging sessions and earn carbon credits in the process....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/buying-an-ev-crypto-project-rewards-you-with-carbon-credits-for-charging-makes-payments-easy.htm"&gt;Read More: Buying an EV? This Crypto Project Rewards You With Carbon Credits For Charging and Makes Payments Easy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Sustainable Cryptocurrency</category><category>Sustainable Crypto</category><category>C+Charge</category><category>C-Charge</category><category>CCHG</category><category>Ev Charging App</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/buying-an-ev-crypto-project-rewards-you-with-carbon-credits-for-charging-makes-payments-easy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100640/248826/c-charge-nft.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="303643"/></item><item><title>Crypto Listing and Delisting Announcements: Week 2</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-listing-and-delisting-announcements-week-2.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
BitfinexListings: Flare (FLR) &lt;br /&gt;
BitForexListings: Bonk (BONK)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-listing-and-delisting-announcements-week-2.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Listing and Delisting Announcements: Week 2&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Trading</category><category>Exchange</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-listing-and-delisting-announcements-week-2.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100541/248813/a16faad5d1-media-library-original-900-600-media-library-original-900-600-media-library-original-900-600-media-library-original-900-600-media-library-original-900-600-media-library-original-900-600-media-library-original-900-600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="71066"/></item><item><title>This is Why Crypto Prices Are Exploding Higher Today? 6 Altcoins to Buy - January 9th</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/this-is-why-crypto-prices-are-exploding-higher-today-6-altcoins-to-buy-january-9th.htm</link><description>The crypto market beams with hope for recovery as this week's trading leaves the station. Selected altcoins like Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), Cosmos (ATOM) and ApeCoin (APE) spiked significantly in double-digits, yet Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) remain relatively unchanged. The total market capitalization jumped slightly to $852 billion after dropping to $798 billion on January 4....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/this-is-why-crypto-prices-are-exploding-higher-today-6-altcoins-to-buy-january-9th.htm"&gt;Read More: This is Why Crypto Prices Are Exploding Higher Today? 6 Altcoins to Buy - January 9th&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/this-is-why-crypto-prices-are-exploding-higher-today-6-altcoins-to-buy-january-9th.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100629/248787/chart-5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="141236"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Traders at an Institutional Crypto Firm Targeted by Hackers Since July 2022, Huobi Korea to Reportedly Cut Ties with Huobi Global</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-traders-at-an-institutional-crypto-firm-targeted-by-hackers-since-july-2022-huobi-korea-to-reportedly-cut-ties-with-huobi-global.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-traders-at-an-institutional-crypto-firm-targeted-by-hackers-since-july-2022-huobi-korea-to-reportedly-cut-ties-with-huobi-global.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Traders at an Institutional Crypto Firm Targeted by Hackers Since July 2022, Huobi Korea to Reportedly Cut Ties with Huobi Global&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Microsoft</category><category>Hack</category><category>Security</category><category>Huobi</category><category>Binance</category><category>Australia</category><category>South Korea</category><category>USA</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Legal</category><category>SEC</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>Genesis</category><category>Mexico</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Payments</category><category>TON</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-traders-at-an-institutional-crypto-firm-targeted-by-hackers-since-july-2022-huobi-korea-to-reportedly-cut-ties-with-huobi-global.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100563/248659/adobestock-vegefox-com-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103532"/></item><item><title>This Move-to-Earn Project Takes Fitness and Gyms Into the Metaverse And CME May Be Taking Notice</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/this-move-earn-project-takes-fitness-and-gyms-into-the-metaverse-and-cme-may-be-taking-notice.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
The New Web 3.0 health and wellness platform Fight Out is set to revolutionize the fitness space with a new move-to-earn (M2E) model that incentivizes and rewards users for being proactive. The project is in its first presale stage and has raised over $2.79 million in its presale in a matter of weeks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/this-move-earn-project-takes-fitness-and-gyms-into-the-metaverse-and-cme-may-be-taking-notice.htm"&gt;Read More: This Move-to-Earn Project Takes Fitness and Gyms Into the Metaverse And CME May Be Taking Notice&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/this-move-earn-project-takes-fitness-and-gyms-into-the-metaverse-and-cme-may-be-taking-notice.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100606/248752/buy-fightout.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="529095"/></item><item><title>The DOJ Seizes $500M of Robinhood Shares Tied to Bankman-Fried</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/the-doj-seizes-500m-of-robinhood-shares-tied-to-bankman-fried.htm</link><description>The US Department of Justice has retained control of the contested 56 million shares of Robinhood, a popular financial trading app, worth approximately $500 million.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a January 6 court filing, the DOJ notified the court handling the bankruptcy of BlockFi that it has seized 55,273,469 shares of Robinhood, worth more than $450 million at the time of publication. The shares had been held at an account at brokerage firm ED&amp;F Man....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/the-doj-seizes-500m-of-robinhood-shares-tied-to-bankman-fried.htm"&gt;Read More: The DOJ Seizes $500M of Robinhood Shares Tied to Bankman-Fried&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>Robinhood</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/the-doj-seizes-500m-of-robinhood-shares-tied-to-bankman-fried.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100612/248750/emysjg4jhforxdumonbnptdcra-media-library-original-1200-692.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="151662"/></item><item><title>North Korean Crypto Hacks to ‘Surge’ This Year, Say Experts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-crypto-hacks-surge-say-experts.htm</link><description>A “surge” in North Korean crypto hacks is on its way in 2023, a security provider has claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
The South Korean media outlet Money S reported that Panda Security, a Spanish cybersecurity software firm, predicted a “surge in fraudulent activities” and attempts to “steal virtual assets” in the year ahead. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm stated that hackers from North Korea would look to “exploit the renewed public interest in cryptocurrency” as markets recover from crypto winter....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-crypto-hacks-surge-say-experts.htm"&gt;Read More: North Korean Crypto Hacks to ‘Surge’ This Year, Say Experts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hack</category><category>Security</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-crypto-hacks-surge-say-experts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100520/248590/adobestock-151848557.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="7301729"/></item><item><title>Wyre Limits Client Withdrawals to 90% so it Can ‘Navigate the Current Environment’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wyre-limits-client-withdrawals-90-so-it-can-navigate-current-environment.htm</link><description>The crypto-focused payments provider Wyre has limited withdrawals for its clients to 90% of funds held in the account, citing a need to “navigate the current market environment.” &lt;br /&gt;
"We are modifying our withdrawal policy. While customers will continue to be able to withdraw their funds, at this time, we are limiting withdrawals to no more than 90% of the funds currently in each customer account, subject to current daily limits," Wyre said in a statement posted on Twitter this weekend....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wyre-limits-client-withdrawals-90-so-it-can-navigate-current-environment.htm"&gt;Read More: Wyre Limits Client Withdrawals to 90% so it Can ‘Navigate the Current Environment’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Wyre</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wyre-limits-client-withdrawals-90-so-it-can-navigate-current-environment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100567/248681/path.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="939163"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 9th January – FGHT, GALA, D2T, SOL, CCHG, ZIL, RIA, ADA</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-9th-january-fght-gala-d2t-sol-cchg-zil-ria-ada.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has risen by 3.5% in the past 24 hours, leaving behind a disappointing start to the year as it reaches a total cap of $887 billion. This figure represents a 6% rise in a week, although the market's value is much the same as it was a week ago, undermining any claim that today's jump means it has turned a corner....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-9th-january-fght-gala-d2t-sol-cchg-zil-ria-ada.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 9th January – FGHT, GALA, D2T, SOL, CCHG, ZIL, RIA, ADA&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-9th-january-fght-gala-d2t-sol-cchg-zil-ria-ada.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100512/248663/best-crypto-to-buy-today-9th-january.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="322136"/></item><item><title>Gala Price Prediction – What’s Behind the Pump as Metaverse Games Coin Rockets 65%?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-price-prediction-whats-behind-pump-as-metaverse-games-coin-rockets-65.htm</link><description>Gala price rises to the helm of crypto recovery with a 56% move to $0.03759. The metaverse token has shocked market participants with its trading volume jumping by 495% to $992 million in 24 hours. Intriguingly, the optimistic outlook for GALA seems intact and might even carry on as the day’s trading progresses....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-price-prediction-whats-behind-pump-as-metaverse-games-coin-rockets-65.htm"&gt;Read More: Gala Price Prediction – What’s Behind the Pump as Metaverse Games Coin Rockets 65%?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/gala-price-prediction-whats-behind-pump-as-metaverse-games-coin-rockets-65.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100551/248636/galausd-2023-01-09-13-36-14.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="379898"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Shanghai Testnet May Launch As Early as February to Enable Validator Staking Withdrawal</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-shanghai-testnet-may-launch-as-early-as-february-enable-validator-staking-withdrawal.htm</link><description>Ethereum developers plan to release a public test network for the Shanghai upgrade, which will include code allowing withdrawals of ether staked in the Beacon Chain since December 2020, by the end of February. &lt;br /&gt;
In a call on January 5, Ethereum developers chose March 2023 as the tentative target for the Shanghai hard fork. And in a bid to make sure they meet this date, developers plan to release a public test network for the Shanghai upgrade by the end of February....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-shanghai-testnet-may-launch-as-early-as-february-enable-validator-staking-withdrawal.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Shanghai Testnet May Launch As Early as February to Enable Validator Staking Withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Ethereum 2.0</category><category>Shanghai</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-shanghai-testnet-may-launch-as-early-as-february-enable-validator-staking-withdrawal.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100543/248623/ethereum-media-library-original-900-600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="130457"/></item><item><title>Dash 2 Trade Hits $14.65m, Only $700k Left to Raise – 2 Days Until Exchange Listings on 11th January</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dash-2-trade-hits-1465m-only-700k-left-raise-2-days-until-exchange-listings-11th-january.htm</link><description>Dash 2 Trade, the highly anticipated trading analytics and signals platform, has raised $14.65 million with just 2 days to go before its exchange listings on 11th January. &lt;br /&gt;
The D2T token begins trading on four exchanges at 10am UTC on Wednesday: Gate.io, LBank, BitMart and decentralized exchange Uniswap.  &lt;br /&gt;
Dash 2 Trade has also signed a deal to list its token on Changelly Pro at a later date. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dash-2-trade-hits-1465m-only-700k-left-raise-2-days-until-exchange-listings-11th-january.htm"&gt;Read More: Dash 2 Trade Hits $14.65m, Only $700k Left to Raise – 2 Days Until Exchange Listings on 11th January&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dash-2-trade-hits-1465m-only-700k-left-raise-2-days-until-exchange-listings-11th-january.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100534/248619/2-days-left-to-buy-cheap.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="262679"/></item><item><title>Hong Kong’s Financial Secretary Doubles Down on Crypto Hub Positioning Despite Crypto Winter</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kongs-financial-secretary-doubles-down-crypto-hub-positioning-despite-crypto-winter.htm</link><description>Paul Chan, Hong Kong's Financial Secretary, said that, despite the ongoing market downturn, the city would continue to work toward becoming a major crypto hub, attracting businesses from across the world. &lt;br /&gt;
Chan, the Financial Secretary since 2017,  was speaking at a Web3 forum, Bloomberg reported, when he said that Hong Kong would become the place for startups of all kinds – including crypto and fintech – to set up shop in 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kongs-financial-secretary-doubles-down-crypto-hub-positioning-despite-crypto-winter.htm"&gt;Read More: Hong Kong’s Financial Secretary Doubles Down on Crypto Hub Positioning Despite Crypto Winter&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Regulation</category><category>CBDC</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kongs-financial-secretary-doubles-down-crypto-hub-positioning-despite-crypto-winter.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100506/248582/adobestock-f11photo-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="227420"/></item><item><title>Russians Set to ‘Turn to Crypto En Masse’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russians-set-turn-crypto-en-masse.htm</link><description>A Russian professor has claimed that “mass” crypto adoption is on its way in the country – with interest in digital versions of the Chinese yuan and the ruble also spiking. &lt;br /&gt;
Per V1, the crypto forecast was delivered by Igor Belskikh, a Doctor of Economics, and Professor at the Department of Economics and Finance at the Plekhanov Russian University of Economics....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russians-set-turn-crypto-en-masse.htm"&gt;Read More: Russians Set to ‘Turn to Crypto En Masse’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russians-set-turn-crypto-en-masse.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100505/248567/adobestock-513733058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4456541"/></item><item><title>Play-to-Earn Gaming is Crypto's Killer App – Calvaria Shows the Way Ahead for Fantasy Game Cards</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/play-earn-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app-calvaria-shows-the-way-ahead-for-fantasy-game-cards.htm</link><description>One of the main trends over the course of the 2021 bull market was the meteoric rise in play to earn gaming projects such as Axie Infinity and the Sandbox, which experienced parabolic rises and were some of the best performing assets throughout the entire cycle.  &lt;br /&gt;
Amongst venture capitalists, there are a range of different approaches to the cryptocurrency market, with some of the largest trends including blockchain infrastructure, layer ones, and play to earn gaming. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/play-earn-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app-calvaria-shows-the-way-ahead-for-fantasy-game-cards.htm"&gt;Read More: Play-to-Earn Gaming is Crypto's Killer App – Calvaria Shows the Way Ahead for Fantasy Game Cards&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/play-earn-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app-calvaria-shows-the-way-ahead-for-fantasy-game-cards.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100504/248566/snimok-ekrana-2022-10-10-014141-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="809183"/></item></channel></rss>
