<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:28:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BinaryX and AiGC Labs Developing First AI-Powered Virtual Reality Game on the Metaverse]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binaryx-and-aigc-labs-developing-first-ai-powered-virtual-reality-game-on-the-metaverse</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1_5_1686046860BJao6VqY5T.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1_5_1686046860BJao6VqY5T.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1_5_1686046860BJao6VqY5T.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:05:33 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binaryx-and-aigc-labs-developing-first-ai-powered-virtual-reality-game-on-the-metaverse</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 7th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>BinaryX today announced their plans to expand into Virtual Reality (VR) and Artificial Intelligence Game Content (AIGC). Building upon their GameFi expertise, BinaryX has reportedly entered into agreements with their VR and AIGC partners, AiGC Labs, to develop a groundbreaking new GameFi genre of AI-based VR games.</p><p>First AI-Powered Virtual Reality Game on the Metaverse</p><p>According to the team, BinaryX is preparing for the launch of the first-ever VR game which heavily features both VR and AIGC in collaboration with AiGC Labs. The team has not released the full details of the game yet, but has hinted that the game will be set in a character-rich universe, inspired by heroes and characters from East Asian folklore.&nbsp;</p><p>This comes just after Apple&rsquo;s official reveal of their VR headset, Apple Vision Pro, during the Worldwide Developers Conference event on June 5.&nbsp;</p><p>Using ChatGPT and GameGPT for Game Design</p><p>The team revealed that they have been experimenting with ChatGPT and GameGPT to generate engaging gameplay, characters and build compelling narratives for their games. The AI models helped the team to explore and refine ideas for world-building as well, including ideas for environmental layout, challenges, and level design. Besides the AI-powered VR game in collaboration with AiGC Labs, BinaryX has also been working on a separate AI-powered game that will be released sometime this year.&nbsp;</p>"We are incredibly excited to unveil our latest venture into VR and AIGC technologies," said Rudy, Head of Growth at BinaryX. "This is a significant milestone for our companies as we continue to push the boundaries of innovation in the Web3 gaming industry. Together with our partners, our team has poured talent and dedication into creating a game that will redefine the gaming experience and captivate players like never before. We&rsquo;re excited to reveal the game to our players soon."<p>The game is currently still under development and more details about the official release will be shared on their social media.&nbsp;</p>About BinaryX<p>BinaryX is a GameFi and IGO platform, and the force behind popular blockchain games such as CyberChess, CyberDragon, and CyberLand. These games run on the BNB Chain.</p><p>Aside from developing games, BinaryX has now evolved into a full-fledged GameFi platform by offering Initial Game Offering (IGO) services, giving game developers the opportunity to launch their GameFi projects on their platform, and for users to get early access to innovative new games.</p><p>As one of the top 10 projects on the BNB Chain, BinaryX has a vast community of more than 100k coin holders and 30K monthly active wallets. It is also one of the top few metaverse projects by trading volume on the BNB chain, with more than 200 million in market cap. BinaryX also has a token, $BNX, that has consistently demonstrated strong performance despite the bear market.</p><p>For more details and information about BinaryX, please visit</p><p>Official website | Medium | Discord | Telegram | Twitter</p><p>Check out BinaryX's games on their website and on YouTube</p>ContactCommunicationsKoraBinaryXmarketing@binaryx.pro]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 7th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>BinaryX today announced their plans to expand into Virtual Reality (VR) and Artificial Intelligence Game Content (AIGC). Building upon their GameFi expertise, BinaryX has reportedly entered into agreements with their VR and AIGC partners, AiGC Labs, to develop a groundbreaking new GameFi genre of AI-based VR games.</p><p>First AI-Powered Virtual Reality Game on the Metaverse</p><p>According to the team, BinaryX is preparing for the launch of the first-ever VR game which heavily features both VR and AIGC in collaboration with AiGC Labs. The team has not released the full details of the game yet, but has hinted that the game will be set in a character-rich universe, inspired by heroes and characters from East Asian folklore.&nbsp;</p><p>This comes just after Apple&rsquo;s official reveal of their VR headset, Apple Vision Pro, during the Worldwide Developers Conference event on June 5.&nbsp;</p><p>Using ChatGPT and GameGPT for Game Design</p><p>The team revealed that they have been experimenting with ChatGPT and GameGPT to generate engaging gameplay, characters and build compelling narratives for their games. The AI models helped the team to explore and refine ideas for world-building as well, including ideas for environmental layout, challenges, and level design. Besides the AI-powered VR game in collaboration with AiGC Labs, BinaryX has also been working on a separate AI-powered game that will be released sometime this year.&nbsp;</p>"We are incredibly excited to unveil our latest venture into VR and AIGC technologies," said Rudy, Head of Growth at BinaryX. "This is a significant milestone for our companies as we continue to push the boundaries of innovation in the Web3 gaming industry. Together with our partners, our team has poured talent and dedication into creating a game that will redefine the gaming experience and captivate players like never before. We&rsquo;re excited to reveal the game to our players soon."<p>The game is currently still under development and more details about the official release will be shared on their social media.&nbsp;</p>About BinaryX<p>BinaryX is a GameFi and IGO platform, and the force behind popular blockchain games such as CyberChess, CyberDragon, and CyberLand. These games run on the BNB Chain.</p><p>Aside from developing games, BinaryX has now evolved into a full-fledged GameFi platform by offering Initial Game Offering (IGO) services, giving game developers the opportunity to launch their GameFi projects on their platform, and for users to get early access to innovative new games.</p><p>As one of the top 10 projects on the BNB Chain, BinaryX has a vast community of more than 100k coin holders and 30K monthly active wallets. It is also one of the top few metaverse projects by trading volume on the BNB chain, with more than 200 million in market cap. BinaryX also has a token, $BNX, that has consistently demonstrated strong performance despite the bear market.</p><p>For more details and information about BinaryX, please visit</p><p>Official website | Medium | Discord | Telegram | Twitter</p><p>Check out BinaryX's games on their website and on YouTube</p>ContactCommunicationsKoraBinaryXmarketing@binaryx.pro]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The Rise of Meme Tokens and How They're Driving Exchanges to Embrace Unconventional Trends ]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/the-rise-of-meme-tokens-and-how-theyre-driving-exchanges-to-embrace-unconventional-trends</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-631.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-631.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-631.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/the-rise-of-meme-tokens-and-how-theyre-driving-exchanges-to-embrace-unconventional-trends</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins have experienced an unprecedented rise in interest and value. With exuberant community support, meme coins are largely associated with meme images, cartoon characters, and animals. Dogecoin, SHIBA INU, and the recent Pepecoin ($PEPE) are a few of the top-selling meme coins in the crypto space. These coins have gained thousands in price surges in the shortest period. Offering investors ample opportunities to make significant profits based on a small investment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The trending meme coin, $PEPE, barely a month after its release, reached a whopping $1.5 billion in market cap. And a Spot Trading volume exceeding $2.7 billion. This value, according to various reports, rivaled Bitcoin&rsquo;s Spot Trading on the top crypto exchanges within the same timeframe. A testament to these coins&rsquo; ability to generate gargantuan returns for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>$PEPE&rsquo;s initial price at the time of launch was a mere $0.000000001 and with a total token supply of over 420 trillion. Since listing on top exchanges, the meme coin experienced a price surge of over 3000%. While it has suffered countless sell-offs from early investors looking to make huge profits, Pepecoin is still ranked as one of the top 100 coins (number 78) based on market cap, per CoinMarketCap. Again, substantial proof of its unprompted leap in price in the shortest time possible.&nbsp;</p>
The Role of Exchanges and How Early Listing Impact Investors&rsquo; Returns&nbsp;
<p>Crypto exchanges enable the seamless purchase of Bitcoin, altcoins, and meme coins alike. They are committed to providing customers with the hottest coins on the market, allowing them to become early investors. Now, why crypto exchanges are core components of the industry, obviously, their effect on the market continues to grow daily, partly a work of meme coins. How?&nbsp;</p>
<p>These crypto exchanges understand the influence meme coins have on the market and investors. Hence why they are constantly on the lookout for the next hot project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To better understand the impact of early listing and how these exchanges actively influence investors&rsquo; returns, we&rsquo;ll use $PEPE and LBank, and other exchanges as examples.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Via LBank&rsquo;s Articles Section, the global crypto exchange announced its decision to list the newly launched meme coin, $PEPE on its platform. Per the source above, the listing was scheduled for April 18, 2023, at 8 AM (UTC). LBank claimed the meme coin was a feasible, high-quality coin for its users. 12 days later, OKX Exchange announced its decision to list $PEPE. The result? An 850% surge in price. LBank users enjoyed a whopping 850% increase in their investment. Bitget Exchange also listed $PEPE the same day as LBank and since then (until the time of writing) has raked in returns exceeding a 5346% increase in price for investors. Substantial proof of early listing&rsquo;s impact on investments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Besides $PEPE, the listing of emerging meme coins like $PSYOP, $GEN, $SPONGE, $AIDOGE, $BEN, and $RFD further shows the role exchanges play in price surges. According to available market data, LBank, MEXC, and HUOBI are at the forefront of early token listings. For the previously mentioned emerging meme coins, LBank was the first to list 5 out of the 6 tokens&mdash;$BEN, $PSYOP, $RFD, $GEN, and $SPONGE. With MEXC Exchange listing $AIDOGE first and HUOBI following behind. In line with this data, LBank also recorded the highest gains for these meme coins, except for $AIDOGE and $BEN where MEXC recorded the highest gains.&nbsp;</p>
LBank Exchange:&nbsp;
<ul>
<li>$PEPE; 6387%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$AIDOGE; 19364%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$BEN; 313%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$PSYOP; 433%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$RFD; 216%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$SPONGE; 296%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$GEN; 716%&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
MEXC Exchange&nbsp;
<ul>
<li>$PEPE; 2259%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$AIDOGE; 70429%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$BEN; 353%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$PSYOP; 0%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$RFD; 138%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$SPONGE; 0%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$GEN; None&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>HUOBI and Gate.io recorded impressive gains&mdash;2710% and 2324%, respectively&mdash;for $PEPE. However, listing a day after LBank and Bitget cost their users over 2300% value increases on their investments.</p>
How Meme Coins are Driving Unconventional Innovation&nbsp;&nbsp;
<p>As these crypto exchanges compete against themselves by constantly searching for potentially hot coins, one thing stands out&mdash;their willingness to openly embrace unconventional projects. By actively seeking out new projects to list, crypto exchanges show their commitment to supporting peculiar projects. Although meme coins are loosely based on famous memes, animals, or characters, they have become an avenue for experimentation in the web3 space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meme coins are continually pushing the boundaries of conventional investments and attracting a diverse audience. Comprising a community of exuberant individuals committed to contributing to the growth of a project. By fervently seeking the next big meme coin, exchanges are encouraging developers to keep experimenting and launching unique projects. Additionally, the rise of these meme coins is proof of the impact of the internet and meme culture.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Memes have become a huge part of the internet and social media experience. And by listing meme-based coins, exchanges are tapping into a potentially replete environment with millions of global supporters waiting to be onboarded. Speaking about these meme coins and how they're opening doors for mass adoption, Johnasson Chen, co-founder of LBank reiterates that the pursuit of meme coins contributes to the resilience and diversity of the emerging web3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Staying on top of the market for memes is crucial to delivering top-notch investments to our users as early as possible. The pursuit of meme coins also contributes to the overall diversity and resilience of the Web3 ecosystem. The inclusion of such coins alongside more established cryptocurrencies fosters a healthy balance between established projects and innovative newcomers, allowing for a continuous cycle of disruption and growth,&rdquo; the co-founder said.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins have experienced an unprecedented rise in interest and value. With exuberant community support, meme coins are largely associated with meme images, cartoon characters, and animals. Dogecoin, SHIBA INU, and the recent Pepecoin ($PEPE) are a few of the top-selling meme coins in the crypto space. These coins have gained thousands in price surges in the shortest period. Offering investors ample opportunities to make significant profits based on a small investment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The trending meme coin, $PEPE, barely a month after its release, reached a whopping $1.5 billion in market cap. And a Spot Trading volume exceeding $2.7 billion. This value, according to various reports, rivaled Bitcoin&rsquo;s Spot Trading on the top crypto exchanges within the same timeframe. A testament to these coins&rsquo; ability to generate gargantuan returns for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>$PEPE&rsquo;s initial price at the time of launch was a mere $0.000000001 and with a total token supply of over 420 trillion. Since listing on top exchanges, the meme coin experienced a price surge of over 3000%. While it has suffered countless sell-offs from early investors looking to make huge profits, Pepecoin is still ranked as one of the top 100 coins (number 78) based on market cap, per CoinMarketCap. Again, substantial proof of its unprompted leap in price in the shortest time possible.&nbsp;</p>
The Role of Exchanges and How Early Listing Impact Investors&rsquo; Returns&nbsp;
<p>Crypto exchanges enable the seamless purchase of Bitcoin, altcoins, and meme coins alike. They are committed to providing customers with the hottest coins on the market, allowing them to become early investors. Now, why crypto exchanges are core components of the industry, obviously, their effect on the market continues to grow daily, partly a work of meme coins. How?&nbsp;</p>
<p>These crypto exchanges understand the influence meme coins have on the market and investors. Hence why they are constantly on the lookout for the next hot project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To better understand the impact of early listing and how these exchanges actively influence investors&rsquo; returns, we&rsquo;ll use $PEPE and LBank, and other exchanges as examples.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Via LBank&rsquo;s Articles Section, the global crypto exchange announced its decision to list the newly launched meme coin, $PEPE on its platform. Per the source above, the listing was scheduled for April 18, 2023, at 8 AM (UTC). LBank claimed the meme coin was a feasible, high-quality coin for its users. 12 days later, OKX Exchange announced its decision to list $PEPE. The result? An 850% surge in price. LBank users enjoyed a whopping 850% increase in their investment. Bitget Exchange also listed $PEPE the same day as LBank and since then (until the time of writing) has raked in returns exceeding a 5346% increase in price for investors. Substantial proof of early listing&rsquo;s impact on investments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Besides $PEPE, the listing of emerging meme coins like $PSYOP, $GEN, $SPONGE, $AIDOGE, $BEN, and $RFD further shows the role exchanges play in price surges. According to available market data, LBank, MEXC, and HUOBI are at the forefront of early token listings. For the previously mentioned emerging meme coins, LBank was the first to list 5 out of the 6 tokens&mdash;$BEN, $PSYOP, $RFD, $GEN, and $SPONGE. With MEXC Exchange listing $AIDOGE first and HUOBI following behind. In line with this data, LBank also recorded the highest gains for these meme coins, except for $AIDOGE and $BEN where MEXC recorded the highest gains.&nbsp;</p>
LBank Exchange:&nbsp;
<ul>
<li>$PEPE; 6387%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$AIDOGE; 19364%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$BEN; 313%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$PSYOP; 433%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$RFD; 216%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$SPONGE; 296%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$GEN; 716%&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
MEXC Exchange&nbsp;
<ul>
<li>$PEPE; 2259%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$AIDOGE; 70429%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$BEN; 353%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$PSYOP; 0%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$RFD; 138%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$SPONGE; 0%&nbsp;</li>
<li>$GEN; None&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>HUOBI and Gate.io recorded impressive gains&mdash;2710% and 2324%, respectively&mdash;for $PEPE. However, listing a day after LBank and Bitget cost their users over 2300% value increases on their investments.</p>
How Meme Coins are Driving Unconventional Innovation&nbsp;&nbsp;
<p>As these crypto exchanges compete against themselves by constantly searching for potentially hot coins, one thing stands out&mdash;their willingness to openly embrace unconventional projects. By actively seeking out new projects to list, crypto exchanges show their commitment to supporting peculiar projects. Although meme coins are loosely based on famous memes, animals, or characters, they have become an avenue for experimentation in the web3 space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meme coins are continually pushing the boundaries of conventional investments and attracting a diverse audience. Comprising a community of exuberant individuals committed to contributing to the growth of a project. By fervently seeking the next big meme coin, exchanges are encouraging developers to keep experimenting and launching unique projects. Additionally, the rise of these meme coins is proof of the impact of the internet and meme culture.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Memes have become a huge part of the internet and social media experience. And by listing meme-based coins, exchanges are tapping into a potentially replete environment with millions of global supporters waiting to be onboarded. Speaking about these meme coins and how they're opening doors for mass adoption, Johnasson Chen, co-founder of LBank reiterates that the pursuit of meme coins contributes to the resilience and diversity of the emerging web3 ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Staying on top of the market for memes is crucial to delivering top-notch investments to our users as early as possible. The pursuit of meme coins also contributes to the overall diversity and resilience of the Web3 ecosystem. The inclusion of such coins alongside more established cryptocurrencies fosters a healthy balance between established projects and innovative newcomers, allowing for a continuous cycle of disruption and growth,&rdquo; the co-founder said.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Do Kwon Released on Bail After Request Approved]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/do-kwon-released-on-bail-after-request-approved</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kwon-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kwon-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/kwon-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:05:24 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/do-kwon-released-on-bail-after-request-approved</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Terra founder Do Kwon has been released on bail after a Montenegrin court handling his passport forgery case accepted his 400,000-euro request. </p>
<p>According to an announcement, a Montenegro High Court granted Do Kwon bail after accepting his 400,000-euro request. The decision comes after a previous approval was overturned on May 25. &nbsp;</p>
<p>An official release from the Basic Court in Podgorica stated that an appeal against an earlier bail agreement by the State Prosecutor&rsquo;s Office was set aside. The decision means that Kwon and his fellow accused, Han Chang-Joon, can await further legal proceedings under house arrest in Montenegro.</p>
<p>The value of their property has complicated the decisions regarding the defendant&rsquo;s bail request. During the initial bail hearing on May 11, Kwon and Chang-Joon told the court that they had &ldquo;property worth millions.&rdquo; A High Court, however, disputed the value, and their bail was revoked. The High Court argued that the lower court could not accept the property&rsquo;s value &ldquo;based on their statements, but only concrete evidence.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The value of the property has been verified after evaluation using a sales contract, bank account statements, and invoices.</p>
<p>The Court said:</p>

<p>The court appreciated the fact that they are persons who are not Montenegrin citizens, which is why it accepted their statements about the value of the property they own, which were supported by concrete evidence.</p>

<p>It concluded by saying:</p>

<p>The possibility of losing the security deposit in the amount of EUR 400,000.00 each had a sufficiently discouraging effect on the defendants to dissuade them from any desire to escape.</p>

Kwon and Chang-Joon Arrested in Montenegro
<p>The pair were arrested at an airport in the capital of Podgorica on March 23 as they tried to board a flight to Dubai using falsified travel documents. Kwon and Chang-Joon were charged with forging official documents.</p>
<p>Shortly after their arrest, the United States and South Korean authorities announced that they were seeking the extradition of Kwon. US federal prosecutors indicted Kwon with two counts each of securities fraud, wire fraud, commodities fraud, and conspiracy.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terra founder Do Kwon has been released on bail after a Montenegrin court handling his passport forgery case accepted his 400,000-euro request. </p>
<p>According to an announcement, a Montenegro High Court granted Do Kwon bail after accepting his 400,000-euro request. The decision comes after a previous approval was overturned on May 25. &nbsp;</p>
<p>An official release from the Basic Court in Podgorica stated that an appeal against an earlier bail agreement by the State Prosecutor&rsquo;s Office was set aside. The decision means that Kwon and his fellow accused, Han Chang-Joon, can await further legal proceedings under house arrest in Montenegro.</p>
<p>The value of their property has complicated the decisions regarding the defendant&rsquo;s bail request. During the initial bail hearing on May 11, Kwon and Chang-Joon told the court that they had &ldquo;property worth millions.&rdquo; A High Court, however, disputed the value, and their bail was revoked. The High Court argued that the lower court could not accept the property&rsquo;s value &ldquo;based on their statements, but only concrete evidence.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The value of the property has been verified after evaluation using a sales contract, bank account statements, and invoices.</p>
<p>The Court said:</p>

<p>The court appreciated the fact that they are persons who are not Montenegrin citizens, which is why it accepted their statements about the value of the property they own, which were supported by concrete evidence.</p>

<p>It concluded by saying:</p>

<p>The possibility of losing the security deposit in the amount of EUR 400,000.00 each had a sufficiently discouraging effect on the defendants to dissuade them from any desire to escape.</p>

Kwon and Chang-Joon Arrested in Montenegro
<p>The pair were arrested at an airport in the capital of Podgorica on March 23 as they tried to board a flight to Dubai using falsified travel documents. Kwon and Chang-Joon were charged with forging official documents.</p>
<p>Shortly after their arrest, the United States and South Korean authorities announced that they were seeking the extradition of Kwon. US federal prosecutors indicted Kwon with two counts each of securities fraud, wire fraud, commodities fraud, and conspiracy.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin and crypto rebound after SEC attacks Binance and Coinbase]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-and-crypto-rebound-after-sec-attacks-binance-and-coinbase</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitup-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitup-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitup-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:56:45 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-and-crypto-rebound-after-sec-attacks-binance-and-coinbase</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Fresh on the heels of the latest SEC enforcement actions on Binance and Coinbase the crypto market is seeing a healthy bounce.</p>
The grand plan
<p>This must have been thought out a while ago. First sue Binance, and before the dust even settles, sue Coinbase. It hasn&rsquo;t happened yet, but it really wouldn&rsquo;t be a surprise if the SEC served Tether with a Wells Notice in the near future.</p>
<p>All planned to sow fear and distrust among retail investors and scare them out of the crypto market. Of course, cutting off the banks that do business with crypto, getting the main market makers to back off from the sector, and embroiling the big exchanges in expensive litigation are also part of the Operation Choke Point plan.</p>
Crypto market rebounds
<p>With all of this as a backdrop, the crypto market has the audacity to start rebounding after yesterday&rsquo;s Binance news and today&rsquo;s similar news for Coinbase.</p>
<p>Of course, when the Binance news dropped yesterday it came out of the blue and the crypto market did take a hammering. Bitcoin fell fairly precipitously 6.4% on the day, going as low as just under $25,400, from $27,100 at the previous day&rsquo;s close.</p>
<p>However, even amid today&rsquo;s fresh news of the SEC going after Coinbase, bitcoin has staged a recovery and is up 3.6% so far at time of going to press. Part of the reason for this is that technically, the charts were pointing to a new upsurge for Bitcoin, and the bad news has just caused a blip.</p>
<p>All the short term time frame Stochastic RSIs have reset at the bottom, and even the daily and the weekly RSIs are on their way down as well. When these all cross up from the bottom the momentum is going to be difficult to stop.</p>
Strong fundamental cryptos are surging
<p>The same story is also being played out for many of the more fundamentally sound crypto projects. Ethereum has rebounded 4.4% since yesterday&rsquo;s low point, making back two thirds of the losses so far.</p>
<p>Hot crypto projects such as decentralised exchange Injective Protocol ($INJ), and decentralised GPU-based rendering solution Render ($RNDR) are both coming back fast, making 4.8% and 5.7% respectively so far today.</p>
Joke coin has its day
<p>Even meme coin Pepe ($PEPE) has made a move like Lazarus from the dead, increasing 26% from yesterday&rsquo;s low.</p>
Let battle commence
<p>The crypto market is rebounding because it was in the charts. Be that as it may, stand by for more anti-crypto action from the US government and its financial enforcement agencies. The war has only just begun.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fresh on the heels of the latest SEC enforcement actions on Binance and Coinbase the crypto market is seeing a healthy bounce.</p>
The grand plan
<p>This must have been thought out a while ago. First sue Binance, and before the dust even settles, sue Coinbase. It hasn&rsquo;t happened yet, but it really wouldn&rsquo;t be a surprise if the SEC served Tether with a Wells Notice in the near future.</p>
<p>All planned to sow fear and distrust among retail investors and scare them out of the crypto market. Of course, cutting off the banks that do business with crypto, getting the main market makers to back off from the sector, and embroiling the big exchanges in expensive litigation are also part of the Operation Choke Point plan.</p>
Crypto market rebounds
<p>With all of this as a backdrop, the crypto market has the audacity to start rebounding after yesterday&rsquo;s Binance news and today&rsquo;s similar news for Coinbase.</p>
<p>Of course, when the Binance news dropped yesterday it came out of the blue and the crypto market did take a hammering. Bitcoin fell fairly precipitously 6.4% on the day, going as low as just under $25,400, from $27,100 at the previous day&rsquo;s close.</p>
<p>However, even amid today&rsquo;s fresh news of the SEC going after Coinbase, bitcoin has staged a recovery and is up 3.6% so far at time of going to press. Part of the reason for this is that technically, the charts were pointing to a new upsurge for Bitcoin, and the bad news has just caused a blip.</p>
<p>All the short term time frame Stochastic RSIs have reset at the bottom, and even the daily and the weekly RSIs are on their way down as well. When these all cross up from the bottom the momentum is going to be difficult to stop.</p>
Strong fundamental cryptos are surging
<p>The same story is also being played out for many of the more fundamentally sound crypto projects. Ethereum has rebounded 4.4% since yesterday&rsquo;s low point, making back two thirds of the losses so far.</p>
<p>Hot crypto projects such as decentralised exchange Injective Protocol ($INJ), and decentralised GPU-based rendering solution Render ($RNDR) are both coming back fast, making 4.8% and 5.7% respectively so far today.</p>
Joke coin has its day
<p>Even meme coin Pepe ($PEPE) has made a move like Lazarus from the dead, increasing 26% from yesterday&rsquo;s low.</p>
Let battle commence
<p>The crypto market is rebounding because it was in the charts. Be that as it may, stand by for more anti-crypto action from the US government and its financial enforcement agencies. The war has only just begun.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[CoinMarketCap Web3 Conference "Catalyst" Early-Bird Registration Now Open]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/coinmarketcap-web3-conference-catalyst-early-bird-registration-now-open</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Catalyst_16860692657iuGIbVuck.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Catalyst_16860692657iuGIbVuck.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Catalyst_16860692657iuGIbVuck.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:47:33 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/coinmarketcap-web3-conference-catalyst-early-bird-registration-now-open</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>CoinMarketCap&rsquo;s flagship Web3 conference "Catalyst" has opened early-bird registration. The conference will take place at the (Lisbon Congress Centre, Portugal), on February 21st ~ 22nd, 2024. Catalyst will bring together the world's brightest minds in technology, art, philosophy, and finance to reimagine the future of Web3.</p><p>The Conference, originally scheduled for October 2023, has been changed to February 2024. This decision was made following careful consideration by the event organizers. With an already congested European conference calendar in Q4 2023, CoinMarketCap&rsquo;s Catalyst conference will provide more value to attendees, speakers and the industry at large with its new date.</p><p>Tickets are limited for this exclusive gathering and will be available on a first-come, first-served basis through the Catalyst website. Payment for the tickets can be made with fiat.</p><p>With the European crypto scene thriving, Lisbon serves as the perfect backdrop for this groundbreaking event. The Catalyst conference will provide a platform for innovative discussions and collaborations that will shape the industry's future. This is the ideal opportunity for professionals and enthusiasts to come together, exchange ideas, and drive the next big breakthrough in the crypto world.</p><p>Rush Luton, CEO of CoinMarketCap, said that Catalyst would bring together experts &ldquo;to collaborate and learn about upcoming trends, challenges, and opportunities.&rdquo; In alignment with the conference&rsquo;s title, Luton stated that &ldquo;Catalyst is designed to spark new ideas and initiatives.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p><p>Conference attendees can expect a high-caliber event featuring some of the most prominent figures in the crypto and blockchain space. Tickets are available on the official Catalyst website. Attendees can follow upcoming announcements on CoinMarketCap&rsquo;s newsletter and social channels.</p><p>Conference Website:</p><p>https://coinmarketcap.com/events/catalyst2024</p><p>About CoinMarketCap: CoinMarketCap is the world's most-referenced price-tracking website for crypto assets in the rapidly growing cryptocurrency space. Its mission is to make crypto discoverable and efficient globally by empowering retail users with unbiased, high quality and accurate information for drawing their own informed conclusions.</p>ContactEvents Teamevents@coinmarketcap.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>CoinMarketCap&rsquo;s flagship Web3 conference "Catalyst" has opened early-bird registration. The conference will take place at the (Lisbon Congress Centre, Portugal), on February 21st ~ 22nd, 2024. Catalyst will bring together the world's brightest minds in technology, art, philosophy, and finance to reimagine the future of Web3.</p><p>The Conference, originally scheduled for October 2023, has been changed to February 2024. This decision was made following careful consideration by the event organizers. With an already congested European conference calendar in Q4 2023, CoinMarketCap&rsquo;s Catalyst conference will provide more value to attendees, speakers and the industry at large with its new date.</p><p>Tickets are limited for this exclusive gathering and will be available on a first-come, first-served basis through the Catalyst website. Payment for the tickets can be made with fiat.</p><p>With the European crypto scene thriving, Lisbon serves as the perfect backdrop for this groundbreaking event. The Catalyst conference will provide a platform for innovative discussions and collaborations that will shape the industry's future. This is the ideal opportunity for professionals and enthusiasts to come together, exchange ideas, and drive the next big breakthrough in the crypto world.</p><p>Rush Luton, CEO of CoinMarketCap, said that Catalyst would bring together experts &ldquo;to collaborate and learn about upcoming trends, challenges, and opportunities.&rdquo; In alignment with the conference&rsquo;s title, Luton stated that &ldquo;Catalyst is designed to spark new ideas and initiatives.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p><p>Conference attendees can expect a high-caliber event featuring some of the most prominent figures in the crypto and blockchain space. Tickets are available on the official Catalyst website. Attendees can follow upcoming announcements on CoinMarketCap&rsquo;s newsletter and social channels.</p><p>Conference Website:</p><p>https://coinmarketcap.com/events/catalyst2024</p><p>About CoinMarketCap: CoinMarketCap is the world's most-referenced price-tracking website for crypto assets in the rapidly growing cryptocurrency space. Its mission is to make crypto discoverable and efficient globally by empowering retail users with unbiased, high quality and accurate information for drawing their own informed conclusions.</p>ContactEvents Teamevents@coinmarketcap.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Atomic Hack Funds Sent to Crypto Mixer Used by Lazarus Group]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/atomic-hack-funds-sent-to-crypto-mixer-used-by-lazarus-group</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/atomic-wallet.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/atomic-wallet.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/atomic-wallet.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/atomic-hack-funds-sent-to-crypto-mixer-used-by-lazarus-group</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>According to reports from Elliptic, funds drained from the Atomic Wallet hack have been sent to Sinbad, a crypto mixer used by the Lazarus Group. </p>
<p>According to reports by crypto tracing firm Elliptic Enterprises, the funds drained from the hack on the Atomic Wallet on June 3 have been sent to a crypto mixer used by the Lazarus Group, a notorious North Korean hacking operation.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The $35 million stolen from @AtomicWallet users is being laundered through Sinbad - the mixer fka(?) Blender and used heavily by NK's Lazarus Grouphttps://t.co/UHCwfZiw8e</p>
&mdash; Elliptic Investigations (@Elliptic_Inv) June 5, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Elliptic reported that its Investigation Team traced funds from the $35 million hack to Sinbad.io, a cryptocurrency mixer used by the hacking group.</p>

<p>Elliptic&rsquo;s Investigations Team is also following the transaction trail, and has determined that the stolen funds are being swapped for bitcoin, before being laundered through Sinbad.io - a mixer. Previous Elliptic&nbsp;research&nbsp;revealed that Sinbad has been used intensively to launder over $100 million in proceeds of hacks perpetrated by North Korea&rsquo;s Lazarus Group.</p>
<p>This includes assets from the $540 million Axie Infinity hack and $100 million Horizon Bridge attack.</p>

Atomic Wallet Users Drained of Over $35 Million
<p>On June 3, the self-custodial, decentralised Atomic Wallet received reports that several wallets had been drained of their funds. The project confirmed the compromise on June 4 and said it would investigate the matter. &nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We have received reports of wallets being compromised. We are doing all we can to investigate and analyse the situation. As we have more information, we will share it accordingly.For any questions and concerns, contact support@atomicwallet.io</p>
&mdash; Atomic - Crypto Wallet (@AtomicWallet) June 3, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Atomic said on June 5 that less than 1% of its monthly active users were compromised in the attack, adding that it continues to investigate.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">At the moment less than 1% of our monthly active users have been affected/reported. Last drained transaction was confirmed over 40h ago.Security investigation is ongoing. We report victim addresses to major exchanges &amp; blockchain analytics to trace and block the stolen funds.</p>
&mdash; Atomic - Crypto Wallet (@AtomicWallet) June 5, 2023
<p>

</p>
Blender.io Relaunches As Sinbad.io
<p>Earlier reports indicated North Korean hackers had been using a new mixing service to launder stolen cryptocurrencies. Elliptic found that the crypto mixing service used by the Lazarus Group, Blender, is likely to have been re-launched as Sinbad.</p>
<p>Following a series of high-profile hacks, the United States Treasury&rsquo;s Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) imposed sanctions against Blender and Tornado Cash for helping Lazarus launder close to $500 million in illicitly obtained cryptocurrencies. After the US imposed sanctions against the mixing services, Tornado Cash continued to operate while Blender ceased its operations and disappeared after reportedly taking $22 million in Bitcoin from the mixer.</p>
<p>According to Elliptic, Blender likely started operating the new service called Sinbad, which Lazarus used to launder illicit funds in October 2022.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to reports from Elliptic, funds drained from the Atomic Wallet hack have been sent to Sinbad, a crypto mixer used by the Lazarus Group. </p>
<p>According to reports by crypto tracing firm Elliptic Enterprises, the funds drained from the hack on the Atomic Wallet on June 3 have been sent to a crypto mixer used by the Lazarus Group, a notorious North Korean hacking operation.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The $35 million stolen from @AtomicWallet users is being laundered through Sinbad - the mixer fka(?) Blender and used heavily by NK's Lazarus Grouphttps://t.co/UHCwfZiw8e</p>
&mdash; Elliptic Investigations (@Elliptic_Inv) June 5, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Elliptic reported that its Investigation Team traced funds from the $35 million hack to Sinbad.io, a cryptocurrency mixer used by the hacking group.</p>

<p>Elliptic&rsquo;s Investigations Team is also following the transaction trail, and has determined that the stolen funds are being swapped for bitcoin, before being laundered through Sinbad.io - a mixer. Previous Elliptic&nbsp;research&nbsp;revealed that Sinbad has been used intensively to launder over $100 million in proceeds of hacks perpetrated by North Korea&rsquo;s Lazarus Group.</p>
<p>This includes assets from the $540 million Axie Infinity hack and $100 million Horizon Bridge attack.</p>

Atomic Wallet Users Drained of Over $35 Million
<p>On June 3, the self-custodial, decentralised Atomic Wallet received reports that several wallets had been drained of their funds. The project confirmed the compromise on June 4 and said it would investigate the matter. &nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We have received reports of wallets being compromised. We are doing all we can to investigate and analyse the situation. As we have more information, we will share it accordingly.For any questions and concerns, contact support@atomicwallet.io</p>
&mdash; Atomic - Crypto Wallet (@AtomicWallet) June 3, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Atomic said on June 5 that less than 1% of its monthly active users were compromised in the attack, adding that it continues to investigate.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">At the moment less than 1% of our monthly active users have been affected/reported. Last drained transaction was confirmed over 40h ago.Security investigation is ongoing. We report victim addresses to major exchanges &amp; blockchain analytics to trace and block the stolen funds.</p>
&mdash; Atomic - Crypto Wallet (@AtomicWallet) June 5, 2023
<p>

</p>
Blender.io Relaunches As Sinbad.io
<p>Earlier reports indicated North Korean hackers had been using a new mixing service to launder stolen cryptocurrencies. Elliptic found that the crypto mixing service used by the Lazarus Group, Blender, is likely to have been re-launched as Sinbad.</p>
<p>Following a series of high-profile hacks, the United States Treasury&rsquo;s Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) imposed sanctions against Blender and Tornado Cash for helping Lazarus launder close to $500 million in illicitly obtained cryptocurrencies. After the US imposed sanctions against the mixing services, Tornado Cash continued to operate while Blender ceased its operations and disappeared after reportedly taking $22 million in Bitcoin from the mixer.</p>
<p>According to Elliptic, Blender likely started operating the new service called Sinbad, which Lazarus used to launder illicit funds in October 2022.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Absorb 25474 Target - 7 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-absorb-25474-target-7-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-absorb-25474-target-7-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Absorb 25474 Target:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 7 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent pullback early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 25474.18 level, a downside price objective associated with selling pressure that strengthened around the 28334.75 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 25474.18 area by bears as BTC/USD was pushed lower to the 25351.92 area, its weakest print since mid-March.&nbsp; This move lower also represents a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 26088, 26544, 29813, 26696, 26912, 27281, 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26904.71 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26409.93.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Absorb 25474 Target:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 7 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent pullback early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 25474.18 level, a downside price objective associated with selling pressure that strengthened around the 28334.75 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 25474.18 area by bears as BTC/USD was pushed lower to the 25351.92 area, its weakest print since mid-March.&nbsp; This move lower also represents a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 26088, 26544, 29813, 26696, 26912, 27281, 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26904.71 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26409.93.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Optimism Gears Up For Bedrock Mainnet Update]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/optimism-gears-up-for-bedrock-mainnet-update</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/optimism-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/optimism-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/optimism-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/optimism-gears-up-for-bedrock-mainnet-update</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Optimism, the Ethereum Layer 2 scaling solution, is preparing to roll out its "Bedrock" upgrade today, June 6th.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The step is considered to be a significant leap towards becoming a utility-oriented "Superchain" featuring reduced gas fees and significantly faster transaction finality and block rendering. The Ethereum-based protocol's vision of its technological progress towards becoming a Superchain, which is to say an interconnected network of interoperable and highly composable blockchains, is getting nearer through these planned enhancements.</p>
Optimism Bedrock Update
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Bedrock update is expected to go live by 16:00 UTC today via Optimism's mainnet.&ldquo;Bedrock was named Bedrock for a reason. It is the foundation for the Superchain," shares Karl Floersch.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Floersch currently serves as CEO and and is co-founder at OP Labs, the development organization behind Optimism and its suite of blockchain products.The move is considered an instrumental point towards the transformation of Optimism.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the upgrade, all associated and integrated chains either constructed within or designed in alignment with the OP tech stack (developer tooling, APIs, and SDKs) will be linked over, enabling smooth communication over a unified ecosystem. Floersche emphasizes further that the "Superchain" status isn't a mere moniker, it is, in essence, a long-term vision towards producing an industry standard with the OP Stack as a baseline. Among the key features outlined in anticipation of the upgrade is a 40% reduction in gas fees through an optimized data compression strategy. This means that Bedrock is set to introduce internal mechanisms that will curtail the reliance towards block reorganization, which costs a significant amount of resources on the side of a Layer 2 chain such as Optimism. Block-based reorganizations (reorgs) are instances in which a blockchain simultaneously produces two blocks, hence generating a duplicate blockchain. The code changes set out in Bedrock will effectively cut down confirmation intervals for deposits to approximately 60 seconds, down from the average interval of 600 seconds for the same typical transaction.</p>
Key Enhancements To Expect On Optimism Bedrock Update
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Another well-intentioned upgrade that comes with the Bedrock update is slew of enhancements to proof of modularity in the OP Stack. This open-source toolkit provides developers with functionalities for providing customizable environments on the Optimism blockchain, opening constructs and experiences for users who wish to leverage validity proofs and fault proofs within the OP Stack. Alongside the transaction upgrades, this feature set wil provide a performance boost for node-related functions across the Optimism ecosystem. Another significant advancement Bedrock brings to the table is facilitating Optimism's transition to a multi-client ecosystem. Floersch claims that Optimism will be the first layer 2 protocol to boast multiple clients, thereby enhancing system resilience by eliminating potential single points of failure. Client software is utilized to operate the blockchain, with layer 1 blockchains like Ethereum relying on several clients to ensure network security.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The upgrade process is expected to last between two to four hours. During this period, deposits and withdrawals will be temporarily suspended, and the chain will be momentarily paused.</p>
What is Optimism?
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Optimism functions as a scaling solution for Ethereum, allowing users to carry out transactions on the blockchain at a lower cost while retaining the underlying security of Ethereum. It utilizes a technology called an &ldquo;optimistic rollup,&rdquo; which consolidates multiple transactions into a single transaction, consequently accelerating transaction speed and reducing gas fees.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The layer 2 landscape atop Ethereum has witnessed stiff competition in recent months. L2Beat statistics indicate that Optimism's closest rival, Arbitrum, leads the pack with a total value locked (TVL) of $5.69 billion, with Optimism trailing with a TVL of $1.68 billion. The Bedrock upgrade, however, is expected to boost Optimism's competitiveness.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Alternative solutions to optimistic rollups, like ZK Rollups, have also been gaining traction. Polygon and Matter Labs recently introduced their zkEVMs, a type of ZK Rollup compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine, providing users with more choices for faster, cheaper transactions on Ethereum.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Optimism, the Ethereum Layer 2 scaling solution, is preparing to roll out its "Bedrock" upgrade today, June 6th.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The step is considered to be a significant leap towards becoming a utility-oriented "Superchain" featuring reduced gas fees and significantly faster transaction finality and block rendering. The Ethereum-based protocol's vision of its technological progress towards becoming a Superchain, which is to say an interconnected network of interoperable and highly composable blockchains, is getting nearer through these planned enhancements.</p>
Optimism Bedrock Update
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Bedrock update is expected to go live by 16:00 UTC today via Optimism's mainnet.&ldquo;Bedrock was named Bedrock for a reason. It is the foundation for the Superchain," shares Karl Floersch.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Floersch currently serves as CEO and and is co-founder at OP Labs, the development organization behind Optimism and its suite of blockchain products.The move is considered an instrumental point towards the transformation of Optimism.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the upgrade, all associated and integrated chains either constructed within or designed in alignment with the OP tech stack (developer tooling, APIs, and SDKs) will be linked over, enabling smooth communication over a unified ecosystem. Floersche emphasizes further that the "Superchain" status isn't a mere moniker, it is, in essence, a long-term vision towards producing an industry standard with the OP Stack as a baseline. Among the key features outlined in anticipation of the upgrade is a 40% reduction in gas fees through an optimized data compression strategy. This means that Bedrock is set to introduce internal mechanisms that will curtail the reliance towards block reorganization, which costs a significant amount of resources on the side of a Layer 2 chain such as Optimism. Block-based reorganizations (reorgs) are instances in which a blockchain simultaneously produces two blocks, hence generating a duplicate blockchain. The code changes set out in Bedrock will effectively cut down confirmation intervals for deposits to approximately 60 seconds, down from the average interval of 600 seconds for the same typical transaction.</p>
Key Enhancements To Expect On Optimism Bedrock Update
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Another well-intentioned upgrade that comes with the Bedrock update is slew of enhancements to proof of modularity in the OP Stack. This open-source toolkit provides developers with functionalities for providing customizable environments on the Optimism blockchain, opening constructs and experiences for users who wish to leverage validity proofs and fault proofs within the OP Stack. Alongside the transaction upgrades, this feature set wil provide a performance boost for node-related functions across the Optimism ecosystem. Another significant advancement Bedrock brings to the table is facilitating Optimism's transition to a multi-client ecosystem. Floersch claims that Optimism will be the first layer 2 protocol to boast multiple clients, thereby enhancing system resilience by eliminating potential single points of failure. Client software is utilized to operate the blockchain, with layer 1 blockchains like Ethereum relying on several clients to ensure network security.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The upgrade process is expected to last between two to four hours. During this period, deposits and withdrawals will be temporarily suspended, and the chain will be momentarily paused.</p>
What is Optimism?
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Optimism functions as a scaling solution for Ethereum, allowing users to carry out transactions on the blockchain at a lower cost while retaining the underlying security of Ethereum. It utilizes a technology called an &ldquo;optimistic rollup,&rdquo; which consolidates multiple transactions into a single transaction, consequently accelerating transaction speed and reducing gas fees.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The layer 2 landscape atop Ethereum has witnessed stiff competition in recent months. L2Beat statistics indicate that Optimism's closest rival, Arbitrum, leads the pack with a total value locked (TVL) of $5.69 billion, with Optimism trailing with a TVL of $1.68 billion. The Bedrock upgrade, however, is expected to boost Optimism's competitiveness.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Alternative solutions to optimistic rollups, like ZK Rollups, have also been gaining traction. Polygon and Matter Labs recently introduced their zkEVMs, a type of ZK Rollup compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine, providing users with more choices for faster, cheaper transactions on Ethereum.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Sues Coinbase, Alleging It Acted as an Unregistered Broker]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sec-sues-coinbase-alleging-it-acted-as-an-unregistered-broker</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:32:49 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sec-sues-coinbase-alleging-it-acted-as-an-unregistered-broker</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In a shocking development, the SEC filed suit against crypto exchange Coinbase on Tuesday, alleging it acted as an unregistered broker and exchange. </p>
<p>On Tuesday, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), in its relentless pursuit of the crypto industry, sued crypto exchange Coinbase in a New York federal court. The agency alleges the exchange acted as an unregistered broker and exchange and is demanding that the firm be &ldquo;permanently restrained and enjoined&rdquo; from further doing so.</p>
<p>The complaint comes less than a day after the agency sued Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao.</p>
SEC: Coinbase Is an Unregistered Exchange, Broker, and Clearing Agency
<p>In a press release, the securities regulator said Coinbase acted as an unregistered securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency and charged it for &ldquo;the unregistered offer and sale of securities in connection with its staking-as-a-service program.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The SEC details:</p>

<p>Since 2019, Coinbase has been engaging in an unregistered securities offering through its staking-as-a-service program, which allows customers to earn profits from the &ldquo;proof of stake&rdquo; mechanisms of certain blockchains and Coinbase&rsquo;s efforts.</p>

<p>Through its unregistered services, the agency said Coinbase allegedly:</p>

<p>Provides a marketplace and brings together the orders for securities of multiple buyers and sellers using established, non-discretionary methods under which such orders interact.</p>

<p>Further, it states that Coinbase:</p>

<p>Engages in the business of effecting securities transactions for the accounts of Coinbase customers.</p>

<p>Finally, the SEC alleges that Coinbase:</p>

<p>Provides facilities for comparison of data respecting the terms of settlement of crypto asset securities transactions, serves as an intermediary in settling transactions in crypto asset securities by Coinbase customers, and acts as a securities depository.</p>

<p>The regulator further deems at least 13 crypto assets available to Coinbase users as &ldquo;crypto asset securities&rdquo;.</p>
Gensler and Grewal Comment
<p>Chairman of the SEC, Gary Gensler, took to Twitter to share the news.</p>
<p>Gensler commented:</p>

<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s alleged failures deprive investors of critical protections, including rulebooks that prevent fraud and manipulation, proper disclosure, safeguards against conflicts of interest, and routine inspection by the SEC.</p>

<p>Director of the SEC&rsquo;s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, had this to say:</p>

<p>You simply can&rsquo;t ignore the rules because you don&rsquo;t like them or because you&rsquo;d prefer different ones: the consequences for the investing public are far too great.</p>
<p>As alleged in our complaint, Coinbase was fully aware of the applicability of the federal securities laws to its business activities, but deliberately refused to follow them. While Coinbase&rsquo;s calculated decisions may have allowed it to earn billions, it&rsquo;s done so at the expense of investors by depriving them of the protections to which they are entitled.&nbsp;Today&rsquo;s action seeks to hold Coinbase accountable for its choices.</p>

The SEC Appears to be Out for Blood
<p>The crypto market has been in free fall since news broke that the agency filed suit against crypto exchange Binance and its founder and CEO, Changpeng Zhao. The agency accused Binance of mishandling funds and lying to investors and regulators about its operations.</p>
<p>Binance responded by denying the claims.</p>
<p>Coinbase has been under the radar amid the SEC&rsquo;s broader crackdown on unregistered securities.</p>
<p>After the SEC and crypto exchange Kraken reached a settlement earlier in the year where the company agreed to shutter its staking program, Coinbase said they would defend the agency&rsquo;s classification of staking as a security. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase executives claim that staking cannot be classified as a security under the US Securities Act or the Howey Test.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a shocking development, the SEC filed suit against crypto exchange Coinbase on Tuesday, alleging it acted as an unregistered broker and exchange. </p>
<p>On Tuesday, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), in its relentless pursuit of the crypto industry, sued crypto exchange Coinbase in a New York federal court. The agency alleges the exchange acted as an unregistered broker and exchange and is demanding that the firm be &ldquo;permanently restrained and enjoined&rdquo; from further doing so.</p>
<p>The complaint comes less than a day after the agency sued Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao.</p>
SEC: Coinbase Is an Unregistered Exchange, Broker, and Clearing Agency
<p>In a press release, the securities regulator said Coinbase acted as an unregistered securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency and charged it for &ldquo;the unregistered offer and sale of securities in connection with its staking-as-a-service program.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The SEC details:</p>

<p>Since 2019, Coinbase has been engaging in an unregistered securities offering through its staking-as-a-service program, which allows customers to earn profits from the &ldquo;proof of stake&rdquo; mechanisms of certain blockchains and Coinbase&rsquo;s efforts.</p>

<p>Through its unregistered services, the agency said Coinbase allegedly:</p>

<p>Provides a marketplace and brings together the orders for securities of multiple buyers and sellers using established, non-discretionary methods under which such orders interact.</p>

<p>Further, it states that Coinbase:</p>

<p>Engages in the business of effecting securities transactions for the accounts of Coinbase customers.</p>

<p>Finally, the SEC alleges that Coinbase:</p>

<p>Provides facilities for comparison of data respecting the terms of settlement of crypto asset securities transactions, serves as an intermediary in settling transactions in crypto asset securities by Coinbase customers, and acts as a securities depository.</p>

<p>The regulator further deems at least 13 crypto assets available to Coinbase users as &ldquo;crypto asset securities&rdquo;.</p>
Gensler and Grewal Comment
<p>Chairman of the SEC, Gary Gensler, took to Twitter to share the news.</p>
<p>Gensler commented:</p>

<p>Coinbase&rsquo;s alleged failures deprive investors of critical protections, including rulebooks that prevent fraud and manipulation, proper disclosure, safeguards against conflicts of interest, and routine inspection by the SEC.</p>

<p>Director of the SEC&rsquo;s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, had this to say:</p>

<p>You simply can&rsquo;t ignore the rules because you don&rsquo;t like them or because you&rsquo;d prefer different ones: the consequences for the investing public are far too great.</p>
<p>As alleged in our complaint, Coinbase was fully aware of the applicability of the federal securities laws to its business activities, but deliberately refused to follow them. While Coinbase&rsquo;s calculated decisions may have allowed it to earn billions, it&rsquo;s done so at the expense of investors by depriving them of the protections to which they are entitled.&nbsp;Today&rsquo;s action seeks to hold Coinbase accountable for its choices.</p>

The SEC Appears to be Out for Blood
<p>The crypto market has been in free fall since news broke that the agency filed suit against crypto exchange Binance and its founder and CEO, Changpeng Zhao. The agency accused Binance of mishandling funds and lying to investors and regulators about its operations.</p>
<p>Binance responded by denying the claims.</p>
<p>Coinbase has been under the radar amid the SEC&rsquo;s broader crackdown on unregistered securities.</p>
<p>After the SEC and crypto exchange Kraken reached a settlement earlier in the year where the company agreed to shutter its staking program, Coinbase said they would defend the agency&rsquo;s classification of staking as a security. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase executives claim that staking cannot be classified as a security under the US Securities Act or the Howey Test.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Unigrid Secures $25M Investment Commitment from GEM Digital, Partners WeSendit, Targets Cloud Giants]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/unigrid-secures-25m-investment-commitment-from-gem-digital-partners-wesendit-targets-cloud-giants</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ugd-pr.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ugd-pr.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ugd-pr.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/unigrid-secures-25m-investment-commitment-from-gem-digital-partners-wesendit-targets-cloud-giants</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Unigrid, a pioneering force in the development of a decentralized and anonymous Internet, is excited to announce a significant milestone, a new strategic partnership, and an ambitious market positioning. Unigrid has recently secured a $25 million investment commitment from GEM Digital Limited. Additionally, Unigrid has partnered with WeSendit, the world's first file transfer service specializing in anonymous data transfer and decentralized storage solutions.</p>
<p>Unigrid is poised to become a formidable European alternative to dominant providers such as Amazon AWS and Google Cloud. Unigrid's CTO, Adam Waldenberg, emphasizes the transformative power of blockchain technology in guaranteeing the permanence of information, thereby fundamentally reshaping the cloud industry. Businesses will be able to leverage Unigrid to deliver and store data at significantly lower costs compared to traditional cloud providers like Amazon AWS, resulting in substantial savings.</p>
<p>Unigrid's innovation stems from the underutilized storage capacities found in numerous European data centers. By harnessing their blockchain node technology, Unigrid taps into this vast reservoir, which was previously seen as almost inexhaustible. Their intelligent blockchain application ensures secure data encryption and organization. Unigrid's groundbreaking "plug-and-switch" approach allows businesses to effortlessly monetize their available storage capacity, particularly during non-peak hours. This approach not only optimizes the use of idle server capacity but also provides an additional revenue stream for businesses. Customers benefit from cost-effective cloud services, and Unigrid envisions significant growth opportunities ahead. Even with a modest 0.1% market share in the global cloud business, CEO Evan Green envisions a turnover potential in the hundreds of millions.</p>
<p>The substantial commitment from GEM Digital Limited is a testament to Unigrid's potential and the unwavering dedication of its team. It also signifies a strong vote of confidence from a group with a profound understanding of the digital asset space and a global reach.</p>
<p>Unigrid's partnership with WeSendit marks a significant stride in its mission to revolutionize the Internet. WeSendit has been offering its file transfer service since 2014 and has since convinced more than 3 million customers, including global brands such as Nike, Facebook, Dreamworks, and Red Bull. The new platform WeSendit 3.0 and its central component, the $WSI token, mark the company&rsquo;s transition from Web2 to Web3. WeSendit&rsquo;s interdisciplinary team is developing a new generation of decentralized data processing tools that will encourage users to explore the benefits of the decentralized Internet. WeSendit's decision to leverage Unigrid's decentralized storage offering for its Web3 storage solution underscores the transformative power of Unigrid's technology.</p>
<p>This commitment ensures a broad market launch for Unigrid this year, propelling its growth and market development. Unigrid remains open to additional seed commitments and private sales, with strategic guidance and expertise provided by Valuex AG, renowned specialists in strategy and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Unigrid is at the forefront of the next Internet revolution, providing a truly decentralized global network that is free from geographical limitations and centralized control. Unigrid's innovative solution is a game-changer in the cloud infrastructure landscape, offering a network that is completely anonymous and resistant to attacks.</p>
<p>For more information about Unigrid, please visit https://www.unigrid.org/. For more information about GEM Digital Limited, please visit https://www.gemny.com/. For more information about WeSendit, please visit https://linktr.ee/wesendit.</p>
<p>About Unigrid</p>
<p>Unigrid is creating a decentralized and anonymous cloud service, free from centralized control and resistant to attacks. Unigrid is committed to delivering a network that changes everything, forever. For more information, visit https://www.unigrid.org/.</p>
<p>About GEM Digital Limited</p>
<p>GEM Digital Limited is a digital asset investment firm. Based in The Bahamas, the firm actively sources, structures, and invests in utility tokens listed on over 30 CEXs and DEXs globally. Global Emerging Markets (&ldquo;GEM&rdquo;) is a $3.4 billion alternative investment group with offices in Paris, New York, and the Bahamas. GEM manages a diverse set of investment vehicles focused on emerging markets and has completed over 530 transactions in seventy-two countries. https://www.gemny.com/.</p>
<p>About WeSendit</p>
<p>WeSendit is a Swiss file transfer service specializing in anonymous data transfer and decentralized storage solutions. The company has been a successful Web2 file transfer provider for almost 10 years and has now entered the Web3 era. Powered by the $WSI token, the new platform WeSendit 3.0 will help the world transition to the decentralized Internet of the future. For more information, visit https://linktr.ee/wesendit.</p>
<p>Press Contact</p>
<p>info@unigrid.org</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p></p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unigrid, a pioneering force in the development of a decentralized and anonymous Internet, is excited to announce a significant milestone, a new strategic partnership, and an ambitious market positioning. Unigrid has recently secured a $25 million investment commitment from GEM Digital Limited. Additionally, Unigrid has partnered with WeSendit, the world's first file transfer service specializing in anonymous data transfer and decentralized storage solutions.</p>
<p>Unigrid is poised to become a formidable European alternative to dominant providers such as Amazon AWS and Google Cloud. Unigrid's CTO, Adam Waldenberg, emphasizes the transformative power of blockchain technology in guaranteeing the permanence of information, thereby fundamentally reshaping the cloud industry. Businesses will be able to leverage Unigrid to deliver and store data at significantly lower costs compared to traditional cloud providers like Amazon AWS, resulting in substantial savings.</p>
<p>Unigrid's innovation stems from the underutilized storage capacities found in numerous European data centers. By harnessing their blockchain node technology, Unigrid taps into this vast reservoir, which was previously seen as almost inexhaustible. Their intelligent blockchain application ensures secure data encryption and organization. Unigrid's groundbreaking "plug-and-switch" approach allows businesses to effortlessly monetize their available storage capacity, particularly during non-peak hours. This approach not only optimizes the use of idle server capacity but also provides an additional revenue stream for businesses. Customers benefit from cost-effective cloud services, and Unigrid envisions significant growth opportunities ahead. Even with a modest 0.1% market share in the global cloud business, CEO Evan Green envisions a turnover potential in the hundreds of millions.</p>
<p>The substantial commitment from GEM Digital Limited is a testament to Unigrid's potential and the unwavering dedication of its team. It also signifies a strong vote of confidence from a group with a profound understanding of the digital asset space and a global reach.</p>
<p>Unigrid's partnership with WeSendit marks a significant stride in its mission to revolutionize the Internet. WeSendit has been offering its file transfer service since 2014 and has since convinced more than 3 million customers, including global brands such as Nike, Facebook, Dreamworks, and Red Bull. The new platform WeSendit 3.0 and its central component, the $WSI token, mark the company&rsquo;s transition from Web2 to Web3. WeSendit&rsquo;s interdisciplinary team is developing a new generation of decentralized data processing tools that will encourage users to explore the benefits of the decentralized Internet. WeSendit's decision to leverage Unigrid's decentralized storage offering for its Web3 storage solution underscores the transformative power of Unigrid's technology.</p>
<p>This commitment ensures a broad market launch for Unigrid this year, propelling its growth and market development. Unigrid remains open to additional seed commitments and private sales, with strategic guidance and expertise provided by Valuex AG, renowned specialists in strategy and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Unigrid is at the forefront of the next Internet revolution, providing a truly decentralized global network that is free from geographical limitations and centralized control. Unigrid's innovative solution is a game-changer in the cloud infrastructure landscape, offering a network that is completely anonymous and resistant to attacks.</p>
<p>For more information about Unigrid, please visit https://www.unigrid.org/. For more information about GEM Digital Limited, please visit https://www.gemny.com/. For more information about WeSendit, please visit https://linktr.ee/wesendit.</p>
<p>About Unigrid</p>
<p>Unigrid is creating a decentralized and anonymous cloud service, free from centralized control and resistant to attacks. Unigrid is committed to delivering a network that changes everything, forever. For more information, visit https://www.unigrid.org/.</p>
<p>About GEM Digital Limited</p>
<p>GEM Digital Limited is a digital asset investment firm. Based in The Bahamas, the firm actively sources, structures, and invests in utility tokens listed on over 30 CEXs and DEXs globally. Global Emerging Markets (&ldquo;GEM&rdquo;) is a $3.4 billion alternative investment group with offices in Paris, New York, and the Bahamas. GEM manages a diverse set of investment vehicles focused on emerging markets and has completed over 530 transactions in seventy-two countries. https://www.gemny.com/.</p>
<p>About WeSendit</p>
<p>WeSendit is a Swiss file transfer service specializing in anonymous data transfer and decentralized storage solutions. The company has been a successful Web2 file transfer provider for almost 10 years and has now entered the Web3 era. Powered by the $WSI token, the new platform WeSendit 3.0 will help the world transition to the decentralized Internet of the future. For more information, visit https://linktr.ee/wesendit.</p>
<p>Press Contact</p>
<p>info@unigrid.org</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Circle to launch USDC Stablecoin on Arbitrum, Tradecurve exchange to implement AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/circle-to-launch-usdc-stablecoin-on-arbitrum-tradecurve-exchange-to-implement-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-630.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-630.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-630.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/circle-to-launch-usdc-stablecoin-on-arbitrum-tradecurve-exchange-to-implement-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Prominent stablecoin issuer Circle announced that they would launch USDC natively on top of Arbitrum starting on June 8, 2023, and they will be replacing the abridged version of the stablecoin. A competing project, Tradecurve, will allow users the ability to create AI-powered trading bots with the ability to optimize the performance of their portfolios, leading to better efficiency.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Circle to launch USDC Stablecoin on top of Arbitrum</p>
<p>"USDC issued by Circle will be native to Arbitrum and will be considered the official version of USDC for the Arbitrum ecosystem. Over time, native USDC liquidity will grow and replace the currently circulating 'bridged USDC' liquidity that comes from Ethereum." announced Circle in their statement.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrum will be renaming the Ethereum-bridged version of USDC on block explorers, and it will now be known as USDC.e. The firm also announced that there would be an outreach to ecosystem applications that will make the same change within their in-application user interfaces and other documentation.</p>
<p>Moreover, Circle noted numerous benefits of the native USDC launch on Arbitrum, such as the upcoming support by the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP), which will eliminate bridge withdrawal delays. There will be an upgradable smart contract for any future improvements by the company and the possibility for institutional on and off-ramps, with other perks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Anyone Can Access AI Trading Bots to Optimize Their Portfolio with Tradecurve</p>
<p>Circle isn't the only firm that is innovating with the launch of USDC on top of Arbitrum, and competing projects like Tradecurve are also implementing new ideas and innovations that can change DeFi for traders and investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Tradecurve ecosystem is powered by the TCRV utility token and offers users access to features like automated trading and artificial intelligence. Users can access hundreds of algorithmic and AI trading systems through which they can enhance and optimize the performance of their portfolio.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Alongside that, traders are able to build their own communities, and members can automatically copy their trades through a subscription model. Tradecurve's team will implement Proof of Reserves (PoR) to bolster transparency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There's also high leverage starting at 500:1, a VIP account service, a dedicated Trading Academy, and negative balance protection. Users are not required to complete KYC, making it a truly borderless platform accessible from anywhere.</p>
<p>TCRV is now at Stage 3 of its presale, where one token is worth $0.015. A total of 23,637,981 TCRV tokens have already been sold, and its next price increase will be by 20% at $0.018 at Stage 4. Analysts predict that the price of TCRV can climb by 100x at launch, especially as it will get listed on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap&rsquo;s DEX.</p>
<p>Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV token below:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent stablecoin issuer Circle announced that they would launch USDC natively on top of Arbitrum starting on June 8, 2023, and they will be replacing the abridged version of the stablecoin. A competing project, Tradecurve, will allow users the ability to create AI-powered trading bots with the ability to optimize the performance of their portfolios, leading to better efficiency.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Circle to launch USDC Stablecoin on top of Arbitrum</p>
<p>"USDC issued by Circle will be native to Arbitrum and will be considered the official version of USDC for the Arbitrum ecosystem. Over time, native USDC liquidity will grow and replace the currently circulating 'bridged USDC' liquidity that comes from Ethereum." announced Circle in their statement.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrum will be renaming the Ethereum-bridged version of USDC on block explorers, and it will now be known as USDC.e. The firm also announced that there would be an outreach to ecosystem applications that will make the same change within their in-application user interfaces and other documentation.</p>
<p>Moreover, Circle noted numerous benefits of the native USDC launch on Arbitrum, such as the upcoming support by the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP), which will eliminate bridge withdrawal delays. There will be an upgradable smart contract for any future improvements by the company and the possibility for institutional on and off-ramps, with other perks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Anyone Can Access AI Trading Bots to Optimize Their Portfolio with Tradecurve</p>
<p>Circle isn't the only firm that is innovating with the launch of USDC on top of Arbitrum, and competing projects like Tradecurve are also implementing new ideas and innovations that can change DeFi for traders and investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Tradecurve ecosystem is powered by the TCRV utility token and offers users access to features like automated trading and artificial intelligence. Users can access hundreds of algorithmic and AI trading systems through which they can enhance and optimize the performance of their portfolio.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Alongside that, traders are able to build their own communities, and members can automatically copy their trades through a subscription model. Tradecurve's team will implement Proof of Reserves (PoR) to bolster transparency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There's also high leverage starting at 500:1, a VIP account service, a dedicated Trading Academy, and negative balance protection. Users are not required to complete KYC, making it a truly borderless platform accessible from anywhere.</p>
<p>TCRV is now at Stage 3 of its presale, where one token is worth $0.015. A total of 23,637,981 TCRV tokens have already been sold, and its next price increase will be by 20% at $0.018 at Stage 4. Analysts predict that the price of TCRV can climb by 100x at launch, especially as it will get listed on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap&rsquo;s DEX.</p>
<p>Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV token below:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Rosbank Launches Crypto Solution For Cross-Border Settlements]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/rosbank-launches-crypto-payment-solution-for-cross-border-settlements</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/russia-crypto-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/russia-crypto-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/russia-crypto-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/rosbank-launches-crypto-payment-solution-for-cross-border-settlements</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Russia&rsquo;s Rosbank, one of the most important banks in the country, has announced the launch of a crypto payments solution to facilitate cross-border settlements.</p>
<p>Rosbank has been conducting a pilot for transactions using cryptocurrencies despite being sanctioned by the United States Treasury Department.</p>
Rosbank Makes Its Foray Into Crypto
<p>According to a representative from Rosbank, the financial institution is now conducting pilot transactions with private and corporate clients. According to Rosbank, the service is the first of its kind in the sector and is compliant with all Russian legislation and the requirements of the Central Bank of Russia (CBR). While the Central Bank of Russia has steadfastly opposed the free circulation of cryptocurrencies within the country, it is far more welcoming to allowing their use in cross-border transactions. However, the central bank has stated that they must be carried out outside of the Russian financial infrastructure.</p>
<p>The move comes after Rosbank&rsquo;s owner, Vladimir Olegovich Potanin, stated that tokenized assets and a central bank digital currency (CBDC) could play a critical role in driving the country&rsquo;s digital economy.</p>
Russia&rsquo;s Stance On Crypto
<p>Russia&rsquo;s law on digital financial assets prohibits residents in Russia from accepting digital currencies as payments for goods and services. However, lawmakers in the State Duma are weighing their options and considering specific amendments. These amendments would allow the expansion of the legal framework and include cryptocurrencies, legalizing crypto transactions under an &ldquo;experimental legal regime.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, with Russia under severe pressure thanks to unprecedented Western sanctions following the invasion of Ukraine, the government and businesses in the country have been looking at ways to circumvent the sanctions. One of the options includes increasing the use of cryptocurrencies and national currencies. Officials in Moscow have admitted to several companies using crypto to complete cross-border payments despite a lack of regulation. President Vladimir Putin has also suggested that Russia could become a Bitcoin mining hub. The Russian government also curtailed plans to create a state-run cryptocurrency exchange, opting instead for the regulation of private operators.</p>
Partnership With B-Crypto
<p>Rosbank has entered into a partnership with B-crypto to support the new service. B-crypto specializes in processing cross-border transactions and settlements using digital currencies. Whenever a company initiates a cross-border transaction using cryptocurrency, the payment made in crypto to the foreign counterpart must be reflected in the contract. Furthermore, the invoice issued by the supplier must also indicate a wallet address and the amount of crypto that has been sent. Under the partnership, Rosbank will accept fiat deposits, while B-crypto will be responsible for processing the payment and crypto conversion.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Russia&rsquo;s Rosbank, one of the most important banks in the country, has announced the launch of a crypto payments solution to facilitate cross-border settlements.</p>
<p>Rosbank has been conducting a pilot for transactions using cryptocurrencies despite being sanctioned by the United States Treasury Department.</p>
Rosbank Makes Its Foray Into Crypto
<p>According to a representative from Rosbank, the financial institution is now conducting pilot transactions with private and corporate clients. According to Rosbank, the service is the first of its kind in the sector and is compliant with all Russian legislation and the requirements of the Central Bank of Russia (CBR). While the Central Bank of Russia has steadfastly opposed the free circulation of cryptocurrencies within the country, it is far more welcoming to allowing their use in cross-border transactions. However, the central bank has stated that they must be carried out outside of the Russian financial infrastructure.</p>
<p>The move comes after Rosbank&rsquo;s owner, Vladimir Olegovich Potanin, stated that tokenized assets and a central bank digital currency (CBDC) could play a critical role in driving the country&rsquo;s digital economy.</p>
Russia&rsquo;s Stance On Crypto
<p>Russia&rsquo;s law on digital financial assets prohibits residents in Russia from accepting digital currencies as payments for goods and services. However, lawmakers in the State Duma are weighing their options and considering specific amendments. These amendments would allow the expansion of the legal framework and include cryptocurrencies, legalizing crypto transactions under an &ldquo;experimental legal regime.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, with Russia under severe pressure thanks to unprecedented Western sanctions following the invasion of Ukraine, the government and businesses in the country have been looking at ways to circumvent the sanctions. One of the options includes increasing the use of cryptocurrencies and national currencies. Officials in Moscow have admitted to several companies using crypto to complete cross-border payments despite a lack of regulation. President Vladimir Putin has also suggested that Russia could become a Bitcoin mining hub. The Russian government also curtailed plans to create a state-run cryptocurrency exchange, opting instead for the regulation of private operators.</p>
Partnership With B-Crypto
<p>Rosbank has entered into a partnership with B-crypto to support the new service. B-crypto specializes in processing cross-border transactions and settlements using digital currencies. Whenever a company initiates a cross-border transaction using cryptocurrency, the payment made in crypto to the foreign counterpart must be reflected in the contract. Furthermore, the invoice issued by the supplier must also indicate a wallet address and the amount of crypto that has been sent. Under the partnership, Rosbank will accept fiat deposits, while B-crypto will be responsible for processing the payment and crypto conversion.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bybit Boosts Middle East Presence With UAE Blockchain Scholarship]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bybit-boosts-middle-east-presence-with-uae-blockchain-scholarship</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-250.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-250.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-250.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bybit-boosts-middle-east-presence-with-uae-blockchain-scholarship</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto spot and derivatives exchange Bybit has reinforced its Middle Eastern credentials by inking a memorandum of understanding with the American University of Sharjah (AUS). The agreement with the United Arab Emirates seat of learning will support a scholarship in which Bybit is to contribute AED 1 million (US$272,000).</p>
<p>The AUS collaboration with Bybit is the first of its kind and a further demonstration to the world that the United Arab Emirates is open for crypto business. The scholarship fund provided by Bybit will support the education of 20 students at the university as they carve out careers in fintech and blockchain.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bybit Digs Deep to Further Crypto Education</p>
<p>The agreement enacted between Bybit and the AUS will enable blockchain students to rapidly get up and running; there are plans for the first scholarship grants to be disbursed this fall when the academic year starts. Computer science and computer engineering students who apply and are deemed eligible will have their tuition fees paid by the Bybit Scholarship.</p>
<p>In addition to the AED 1 million scholarship fund, Bybit has pledged an additional AED 100,000 to sponsor a hackathon at the American University of Sharjah. This will be open to the local blockchain community, providing a testbed for innovative ideas to flourish and giving developers a chance to demonstrate not only their coding skills, but all their out-the-box thinking.</p>
<p>Hackathons have proven a successful means of incubating crypto startups and giving developers a leg up on their blockchain journey. Over the years, numerous successful DeFi projects have been spun out of hackathons, where the best ideas can sometimes receive additional funding to turn a proof of concept into a working prototype. The maiden AUS-Bybit Inter-College Hackathon will take place at the AUS College of Engineering during the 2023-2024 academic year.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Younger generations hold the key in driving the blockchain revolution forward,&rdquo; said Bybit CEO Ben Zhou. &ldquo;We are pleased to create the Bybit Scholarship at AUS to help their talented students future-proof their knowledge and skills. We thank AUS for the opportunities to raise crypto awareness and share first-hand knowledge of the industry with students from one of the most prestigious universities in the region. I look forward to being inspired by the future engineers, blockchain scientists, and Web3 startup founders.&rdquo;</p>

<p></p>
<p>Crypto&rsquo;s Big Hitters Eye the Middle East&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bybit&rsquo;s decision to support the initiative in the UAE arrives at a time when investment is pouring into the Middle East from a number of crypto exchanges intent on establishing a regional presence. While some have been attracted by the massive demand for digital assets across the region, others have been swayed by the hostile regulatory landscape elsewhere, particularly in the US.</p>
<p>In April, Bybit opened its new headquarters in Dubai, the Middle Eastern stronghold for an increasing number of crypto companies. The city&rsquo;s business-friendly credentials, world-class amenities, and excellent travel links have made it a favorite with crypto firms seeking a stable base of operations. The new Bybit HQ occupies an entire floor of One Central in the prestigious Dubai World Trade Center.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto spot and derivatives exchange Bybit has reinforced its Middle Eastern credentials by inking a memorandum of understanding with the American University of Sharjah (AUS). The agreement with the United Arab Emirates seat of learning will support a scholarship in which Bybit is to contribute AED 1 million (US$272,000).</p>
<p>The AUS collaboration with Bybit is the first of its kind and a further demonstration to the world that the United Arab Emirates is open for crypto business. The scholarship fund provided by Bybit will support the education of 20 students at the university as they carve out careers in fintech and blockchain.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bybit Digs Deep to Further Crypto Education</p>
<p>The agreement enacted between Bybit and the AUS will enable blockchain students to rapidly get up and running; there are plans for the first scholarship grants to be disbursed this fall when the academic year starts. Computer science and computer engineering students who apply and are deemed eligible will have their tuition fees paid by the Bybit Scholarship.</p>
<p>In addition to the AED 1 million scholarship fund, Bybit has pledged an additional AED 100,000 to sponsor a hackathon at the American University of Sharjah. This will be open to the local blockchain community, providing a testbed for innovative ideas to flourish and giving developers a chance to demonstrate not only their coding skills, but all their out-the-box thinking.</p>
<p>Hackathons have proven a successful means of incubating crypto startups and giving developers a leg up on their blockchain journey. Over the years, numerous successful DeFi projects have been spun out of hackathons, where the best ideas can sometimes receive additional funding to turn a proof of concept into a working prototype. The maiden AUS-Bybit Inter-College Hackathon will take place at the AUS College of Engineering during the 2023-2024 academic year.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Younger generations hold the key in driving the blockchain revolution forward,&rdquo; said Bybit CEO Ben Zhou. &ldquo;We are pleased to create the Bybit Scholarship at AUS to help their talented students future-proof their knowledge and skills. We thank AUS for the opportunities to raise crypto awareness and share first-hand knowledge of the industry with students from one of the most prestigious universities in the region. I look forward to being inspired by the future engineers, blockchain scientists, and Web3 startup founders.&rdquo;</p>

<p></p>
<p>Crypto&rsquo;s Big Hitters Eye the Middle East&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bybit&rsquo;s decision to support the initiative in the UAE arrives at a time when investment is pouring into the Middle East from a number of crypto exchanges intent on establishing a regional presence. While some have been attracted by the massive demand for digital assets across the region, others have been swayed by the hostile regulatory landscape elsewhere, particularly in the US.</p>
<p>In April, Bybit opened its new headquarters in Dubai, the Middle Eastern stronghold for an increasing number of crypto companies. The city&rsquo;s business-friendly credentials, world-class amenities, and excellent travel links have made it a favorite with crypto firms seeking a stable base of operations. The new Bybit HQ occupies an entire floor of One Central in the prestigious Dubai World Trade Center.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC Crashes Below $26000, Crypto Daily TV 6/6/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/btc-crashes-below-26000-crypto-daily-tv-6-6-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-700-btc-below-26.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-700-btc-below-26.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-700-btc-below-26.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/btc-crashes-below-26000-crypto-daily-tv-6-6-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Ethereum reserves at multi-year lows</p>
<p>Ethereum token reserves on exchange wallets have declined to their lowest level since 2018. As of June 5, ETH reserves sit at 17.2 million Ether, a multi-year low.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Atomic Wallet users hacked for $35M</p>
<p>The crypto industry&rsquo;s latest causality occurred over the weekend as nearly $35 million worth of various tokens were stolen from Atomic Wallet, a centralized storage and wallet service. These tokens included bitcoin, ether, tether, dogecoin, litecoin, bnb coin and polygon.</p>
<p>Bitcoin dropped below $26,000 </p>
<p>Cryptocurrency prices dropped after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charged Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world, with violating securities laws. Bitcoin fell more than 6% to its lowest level since March.</p>
BTC/USD dove 5.5% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 5.5% in the last session. The RSI's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 26695.3333 and Resistance is at 27661.3333.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD plummeted 4.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 4.4% in the last session. According to the Stochastic-RSI, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 1866.6167 and Resistance is at 1925.8567.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 6.1% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dropped 6.1% in the last session after rising as much as 1.3% during the session. The MACD is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.5017 and Resistance is at 0.5629.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD plummeted 7.1% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dove 7.1% in the last session. The Williams indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 92.571 and Resistance is at 97.311.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US API Weekly Crude Oil Stock</p>
<p>The API&rsquo;s Weekly Statistical Bulletin reports overall U.S. and regional data relating to refinery operations and the production of the four major petroleum products. The US API Weekly Crude Oil Stock will be released at 20:30 GMT, the UK's 30-y Bond Auction at 09:30 GMT, Australia's RBA Interest Rate Decision at 04:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK 30-y Bond Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bonds auctioned off. Yields are set by bond market investors, and therefore they can be used to estimate investors' outlook on future interest rates.</p>
<p>AU RBA Interest Rate Decision</p>
<p>The RBA Interest Rate Decision is announced by the Reserve Bank of Australia. The interest rates are a key mechanism through which the central bank influences inflation.</p>
<p>AU RBA Rate Statement</p>
<p>Decisions regarding the interest rates are made by the Reserve Bank Board and are explained in a media release that announces the decision after each meeting. Australia's RBA Rate Statement will be released at 04:30 GMT, Japan's JP Foreign Reserves at 23:50 GMT, the US Redbook Index at 12:55 GMT.</p>
<p>JP JP Foreign Reserves</p>
<p>The Foreign Reserves are the total of a country's gold holdings and convertible foreign currencies held by its central bank. </p>
<p>US Redbook Index</p>
<p>The Johnson Redbook Index measures the year-over-year same-store sales growth from a sample of large general merchandise retailers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Ethereum reserves at multi-year lows</p>
<p>Ethereum token reserves on exchange wallets have declined to their lowest level since 2018. As of June 5, ETH reserves sit at 17.2 million Ether, a multi-year low.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Atomic Wallet users hacked for $35M</p>
<p>The crypto industry&rsquo;s latest causality occurred over the weekend as nearly $35 million worth of various tokens were stolen from Atomic Wallet, a centralized storage and wallet service. These tokens included bitcoin, ether, tether, dogecoin, litecoin, bnb coin and polygon.</p>
<p>Bitcoin dropped below $26,000 </p>
<p>Cryptocurrency prices dropped after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission charged Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world, with violating securities laws. Bitcoin fell more than 6% to its lowest level since March.</p>
BTC/USD dove 5.5% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 5.5% in the last session. The RSI's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 26695.3333 and Resistance is at 27661.3333.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD plummeted 4.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 4.4% in the last session. According to the Stochastic-RSI, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 1866.6167 and Resistance is at 1925.8567.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 6.1% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dropped 6.1% in the last session after rising as much as 1.3% during the session. The MACD is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.5017 and Resistance is at 0.5629.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD plummeted 7.1% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dove 7.1% in the last session. The Williams indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 92.571 and Resistance is at 97.311.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US API Weekly Crude Oil Stock</p>
<p>The API&rsquo;s Weekly Statistical Bulletin reports overall U.S. and regional data relating to refinery operations and the production of the four major petroleum products. The US API Weekly Crude Oil Stock will be released at 20:30 GMT, the UK's 30-y Bond Auction at 09:30 GMT, Australia's RBA Interest Rate Decision at 04:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK 30-y Bond Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bonds auctioned off. Yields are set by bond market investors, and therefore they can be used to estimate investors' outlook on future interest rates.</p>
<p>AU RBA Interest Rate Decision</p>
<p>The RBA Interest Rate Decision is announced by the Reserve Bank of Australia. The interest rates are a key mechanism through which the central bank influences inflation.</p>
<p>AU RBA Rate Statement</p>
<p>Decisions regarding the interest rates are made by the Reserve Bank Board and are explained in a media release that announces the decision after each meeting. Australia's RBA Rate Statement will be released at 04:30 GMT, Japan's JP Foreign Reserves at 23:50 GMT, the US Redbook Index at 12:55 GMT.</p>
<p>JP JP Foreign Reserves</p>
<p>The Foreign Reserves are the total of a country's gold holdings and convertible foreign currencies held by its central bank. </p>
<p>US Redbook Index</p>
<p>The Johnson Redbook Index measures the year-over-year same-store sales growth from a sample of large general merchandise retailers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Gensler is dedicated to bringing crypto down]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sec-gensler-is-dedicated-to-bringing-crypto-down</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gens-6.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gens-6.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gens-6.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:15:12 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sec-gensler-is-dedicated-to-bringing-crypto-down</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With no thought for the industry or for retail investors Gary Gensler has bombed the crypto market with the suing of Binance.</p>
Gensler&rsquo;s plan
<p>If there was ever the slightest doubt over SEC Chairman Gensler&rsquo;s strategy towards the cryptocurrency sector, there can now be none. The SEC, with its main mandate to protect retail investors, has dropped another bomb on crypto and sent the market into a tailspin.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s be clear, if Binance has done anything that warrants sanctions and penalties, then there would be a due process for the SEC to make its case. However, it appears that the SEC is tarring the entire crypto industry with the same brush and would bring it to its knees in order to apply the letter of the securities law, or at least the securities law as Gensler sees it.</p>
<p>It would appear that Gensler&rsquo;s ultimate goal is to force all retail investors out of crypto and back to the embrace of the banking system. He would do this by choking off all on/off ramps to the exchanges, and by entangling all the exchanges in costly litigation.</p>
<p>The SEC has gone for the jugular by choosing to first attack some of the exchanges working towards full compliance in Coinbase, Kraken, Paxos, and now Binance. Is it the fault of any crypto project that they cannot approach the SEC in order to register, given that even SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce says that this process is almost impossible?</p>
Why the SEC is attacking crypto
<p>It needs to be absolutely clear that what is happening today with the US government, and its enforcement agencies, is that they are systematically attempting to put the entire crypto industry out of business.</p>
<p>Why would this be the case?</p>
<p>An industry that is for the people, in that it wants to provide innovation and wealth-making means that will enable everyone to be able to be their own bank and make financial decisions that are outside of the system, is seen as a threat to the system itself.</p>
<p>Banks have become monstrous entities that seem to have more power than governments now. They have become obsolete and no longer serve the people. Governments are printing more and more fiat currency which is borne by the people in the form of inflation, and reduced purchasing power.</p>
<p></p>
<p>A system such as this can do without a competitor right now. Banks are failing and the Federal Reserve just backs them with currency printed out of thin air. Interest rates are high, unemployment is rising, and prices are going through the roof.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and various strands of the cryptocurrency sector are building another system that each individual can be part of. When the monetary system as we know it comes tumbling down, things are going to be bad beyond imagining. However, with Bitcoin and crypto a new and fairer world can exist.&nbsp;</p>
An all-important stand
<p>It is up to the few to make a stand and resist the likes of Gensler. He talks of everything being a security and has stated that he would like to see a middle man between every crypto project and their customers. He has even resorted to applying enforcement actions against developers of DeFi projects because he can&rsquo;t get at the project itself.</p>
<p>The fight today between the government, the banks, global financial agencies, and the enforcement agencies on the one side, and the crypto industry on the other, will deeply affect the lives of our children tomorrow. Let us hope that the few will prevail for the benefit of the many.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With no thought for the industry or for retail investors Gary Gensler has bombed the crypto market with the suing of Binance.</p>
Gensler&rsquo;s plan
<p>If there was ever the slightest doubt over SEC Chairman Gensler&rsquo;s strategy towards the cryptocurrency sector, there can now be none. The SEC, with its main mandate to protect retail investors, has dropped another bomb on crypto and sent the market into a tailspin.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s be clear, if Binance has done anything that warrants sanctions and penalties, then there would be a due process for the SEC to make its case. However, it appears that the SEC is tarring the entire crypto industry with the same brush and would bring it to its knees in order to apply the letter of the securities law, or at least the securities law as Gensler sees it.</p>
<p>It would appear that Gensler&rsquo;s ultimate goal is to force all retail investors out of crypto and back to the embrace of the banking system. He would do this by choking off all on/off ramps to the exchanges, and by entangling all the exchanges in costly litigation.</p>
<p>The SEC has gone for the jugular by choosing to first attack some of the exchanges working towards full compliance in Coinbase, Kraken, Paxos, and now Binance. Is it the fault of any crypto project that they cannot approach the SEC in order to register, given that even SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce says that this process is almost impossible?</p>
Why the SEC is attacking crypto
<p>It needs to be absolutely clear that what is happening today with the US government, and its enforcement agencies, is that they are systematically attempting to put the entire crypto industry out of business.</p>
<p>Why would this be the case?</p>
<p>An industry that is for the people, in that it wants to provide innovation and wealth-making means that will enable everyone to be able to be their own bank and make financial decisions that are outside of the system, is seen as a threat to the system itself.</p>
<p>Banks have become monstrous entities that seem to have more power than governments now. They have become obsolete and no longer serve the people. Governments are printing more and more fiat currency which is borne by the people in the form of inflation, and reduced purchasing power.</p>
<p></p>
<p>A system such as this can do without a competitor right now. Banks are failing and the Federal Reserve just backs them with currency printed out of thin air. Interest rates are high, unemployment is rising, and prices are going through the roof.</p>
<p>Bitcoin and various strands of the cryptocurrency sector are building another system that each individual can be part of. When the monetary system as we know it comes tumbling down, things are going to be bad beyond imagining. However, with Bitcoin and crypto a new and fairer world can exist.&nbsp;</p>
An all-important stand
<p>It is up to the few to make a stand and resist the likes of Gensler. He talks of everything being a security and has stated that he would like to see a middle man between every crypto project and their customers. He has even resorted to applying enforcement actions against developers of DeFi projects because he can&rsquo;t get at the project itself.</p>
<p>The fight today between the government, the banks, global financial agencies, and the enforcement agencies on the one side, and the crypto industry on the other, will deeply affect the lives of our children tomorrow. Let us hope that the few will prevail for the benefit of the many.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ThunderCore and SushiSwap joined forces for a sustainable DeFi ecosystem]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/thundercore-and-sushiswap-joined-forces-for-a-sustainable-defi-ecosystem</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-05-155156.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-05-155156.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-05-155156.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/thundercore-and-sushiswap-joined-forces-for-a-sustainable-defi-ecosystem</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">ThunderCore, the leading layer-1 blockchain, and SushiSwap, a pioneer in multi-chain decentralized finance, are excited to announce their partnership aimed at establishing an innovative and sustainable DeFi ecosystem. The collaboration between these two industry leaders brings together ThunderCore's rapid growth and expertise in web3 games and SushiSwap's entrepreneurial spirit, this collaboration creates a powerful synergy to drive the future of decentralized finance.</p>
<p class="s6">With a shared vision and aligned goals, SushiSwap and ThunderCore are poised to revolutionize the DeFi landscape. Together, they have developed a cutting-edge fee-boosting model that enhances Annual Percentage Rates (APRs), allowing liquidity providers (LPs) to maximize their earnings within the ThunderCore ecosystem. This breakthrough mechanism ensures a sustainable circulation of liquidity, benefitting both ThunderCore and SushiSwap ecosystems.</p>
<p class="s6">Meanwhile, ThunderCore is proud to pioneer the launch of V3 farming in SushiSwap, cementing its position as one of the first chains to implement this groundbreaking feature. Leveraging ThunderCore's low gas fees, the platform is set to attract a diverse range of users eager to participate in liquidity provision. This strategic collaboration between ThunderCore and SushiSwap signifies a paradigm shift in the DeFi landscape, ushering in a new era of collaboration, scalability, and user-centric approaches.</p>
<p class="s6">This partnership will bring a suite of innovative Sushi products to ThunderCore, including:</p>
● Sushi v3 AMM: Sushi&rsquo;s framework for spinning up and interacting with pools of different types with varying fee tiers as well.
&nbsp;
● SushiXSwap: Sushi's cross-chain swap tool for quick, trustless swaps between supported chains.
&nbsp;
● Onsen: Onsen farms are Sushi&rsquo;s &ldquo;double reward&rdquo; farms that are for either new projects seeking liquidity or for established projects that Sushi is working with closely; these pools payout in two assets instead of one.
&nbsp;
● Furo: Sushi&rsquo;s token-streaming platform built upon BentoBox, which allows for token streaming of any compatible asset to any wallet over any timeframe, along with options to create token vestings and cliffs as well.
&nbsp;
<p class="s11">The Partnership aims to a sustainable DeFi ecosystem</p>
<p>ThunderCore and SushiSwap share the belief that a novel business model is essential for promoting sustainable growth and driving ongoing innovation in the blockchain and DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>Consequently, alongside the deployment of the aforementioned products, it can be predicted that both ThunderCore and SushiSwap are actively working on the development of an innovative revenue-sharing mechanism that aims to disrupt the DeFi space.</p>
<p>Here's a breakdown of how our forthcoming revenue-sharing mechanism will operate:</p>
● ThunderCore and Sushi will use a percentage of fees generated by activity conducted on ThunderCore via SushiSwap.
&nbsp;
● Both parties will allocate and distribute these $TT and $SUSHI as rewards to LPs, thereby boosting APRs for everyone.
&nbsp;
● ThunderCore will also buy back $TT and incentivize the community for a sustainable ecosystem.
<p>Roger Hsu, CEO of ThunderCore, acknowledges the stifling deadlock in the DeFi market and expresses the intention to create inspiration and break free from this state. The partnership with SushiSwap plays a vital role in achieving this goal, as they work towards establishing a sustainable DeFi ecosystem with improved reward mechanics.</p>

<p class="s6">&ldquo;We are excited to launch on the ThunderCore chain and join the ThunderCore ecosystem to help ThunderCore further cement its ranking as a top 5 blockchain in terms of DAUs.&rdquo; said Head Chef Jared Grey.</p>

<p class="s14">About ThunderCore</p>
<p>ThunderCore is a fast and secure EVM-Compatible layer-1 blockchain founded in Silicon Valley in 2017 to provide a robust infrastructure for DApps and the broader DeFi ecosystem. Its high-performance blockchain offers a breakthrough consensus protocol PaLa, 4,000+ TPS, sub-second confirmation times, and low gas fees.</p>
<p>With over 8 million addresses, 680 million transactions, and 133 million block height on its network, ThunderCore is dedicated to bringing blockchain technology to broad adoption.</p>
<p class="s14">About SushiSwap</p>
<p>SushiSwap is a leading decentralized exchange, offering a wide range of DeFi products and services. We&rsquo;re committed to driving innovation and supporting a diverse ecosystem of blockchain projects. Our community-driven organization aims to solve liquidity issues for the DeFi space, by leveraging network effects and connecting many decentralized markets and instruments.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">ThunderCore, the leading layer-1 blockchain, and SushiSwap, a pioneer in multi-chain decentralized finance, are excited to announce their partnership aimed at establishing an innovative and sustainable DeFi ecosystem. The collaboration between these two industry leaders brings together ThunderCore's rapid growth and expertise in web3 games and SushiSwap's entrepreneurial spirit, this collaboration creates a powerful synergy to drive the future of decentralized finance.</p>
<p class="s6">With a shared vision and aligned goals, SushiSwap and ThunderCore are poised to revolutionize the DeFi landscape. Together, they have developed a cutting-edge fee-boosting model that enhances Annual Percentage Rates (APRs), allowing liquidity providers (LPs) to maximize their earnings within the ThunderCore ecosystem. This breakthrough mechanism ensures a sustainable circulation of liquidity, benefitting both ThunderCore and SushiSwap ecosystems.</p>
<p class="s6">Meanwhile, ThunderCore is proud to pioneer the launch of V3 farming in SushiSwap, cementing its position as one of the first chains to implement this groundbreaking feature. Leveraging ThunderCore's low gas fees, the platform is set to attract a diverse range of users eager to participate in liquidity provision. This strategic collaboration between ThunderCore and SushiSwap signifies a paradigm shift in the DeFi landscape, ushering in a new era of collaboration, scalability, and user-centric approaches.</p>
<p class="s6">This partnership will bring a suite of innovative Sushi products to ThunderCore, including:</p>
● Sushi v3 AMM: Sushi&rsquo;s framework for spinning up and interacting with pools of different types with varying fee tiers as well.
&nbsp;
● SushiXSwap: Sushi's cross-chain swap tool for quick, trustless swaps between supported chains.
&nbsp;
● Onsen: Onsen farms are Sushi&rsquo;s &ldquo;double reward&rdquo; farms that are for either new projects seeking liquidity or for established projects that Sushi is working with closely; these pools payout in two assets instead of one.
&nbsp;
● Furo: Sushi&rsquo;s token-streaming platform built upon BentoBox, which allows for token streaming of any compatible asset to any wallet over any timeframe, along with options to create token vestings and cliffs as well.
&nbsp;
<p class="s11">The Partnership aims to a sustainable DeFi ecosystem</p>
<p>ThunderCore and SushiSwap share the belief that a novel business model is essential for promoting sustainable growth and driving ongoing innovation in the blockchain and DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p>Consequently, alongside the deployment of the aforementioned products, it can be predicted that both ThunderCore and SushiSwap are actively working on the development of an innovative revenue-sharing mechanism that aims to disrupt the DeFi space.</p>
<p>Here's a breakdown of how our forthcoming revenue-sharing mechanism will operate:</p>
● ThunderCore and Sushi will use a percentage of fees generated by activity conducted on ThunderCore via SushiSwap.
&nbsp;
● Both parties will allocate and distribute these $TT and $SUSHI as rewards to LPs, thereby boosting APRs for everyone.
&nbsp;
● ThunderCore will also buy back $TT and incentivize the community for a sustainable ecosystem.
<p>Roger Hsu, CEO of ThunderCore, acknowledges the stifling deadlock in the DeFi market and expresses the intention to create inspiration and break free from this state. The partnership with SushiSwap plays a vital role in achieving this goal, as they work towards establishing a sustainable DeFi ecosystem with improved reward mechanics.</p>

<p class="s6">&ldquo;We are excited to launch on the ThunderCore chain and join the ThunderCore ecosystem to help ThunderCore further cement its ranking as a top 5 blockchain in terms of DAUs.&rdquo; said Head Chef Jared Grey.</p>

<p class="s14">About ThunderCore</p>
<p>ThunderCore is a fast and secure EVM-Compatible layer-1 blockchain founded in Silicon Valley in 2017 to provide a robust infrastructure for DApps and the broader DeFi ecosystem. Its high-performance blockchain offers a breakthrough consensus protocol PaLa, 4,000+ TPS, sub-second confirmation times, and low gas fees.</p>
<p>With over 8 million addresses, 680 million transactions, and 133 million block height on its network, ThunderCore is dedicated to bringing blockchain technology to broad adoption.</p>
<p class="s14">About SushiSwap</p>
<p>SushiSwap is a leading decentralized exchange, offering a wide range of DeFi products and services. We&rsquo;re committed to driving innovation and supporting a diverse ecosystem of blockchain projects. Our community-driven organization aims to solve liquidity issues for the DeFi space, by leveraging network effects and connecting many decentralized markets and instruments.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Exchange Will List Switch (SWITCH) on June 8, 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-exchange-will-list-switch-switch-on-june-8-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600x900-en_1686047139q07H9uNnbt.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600x900-en_1686047139q07H9uNnbt.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600x900-en_1686047139q07H9uNnbt.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:34:09 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-exchange-will-list-switch-switch-on-june-8-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Switch (SWITCH) on Jun 8, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SWITCH/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 4:00 UTC on Jun 8, 2023.&nbsp;This is the first Centralized Exchange listing for the SWITCH Token.</p><p>About The Switch Token</p><p>The Switch Token was launched on the decentralized exchange Uniswap on February 23, 2023.&nbsp;Since its launch it has been listed on CoinGecko, CoinMarketCap and has had an average trading volume over $100,000 on the decentralized exchange.</p><p>The community surrounding the Switch Blockchain continues to grow in numbers on platforms such as Twitter, Discord and Reddit. At time of this writing the SWITCH ERC-20 token was held in over 1800 individual wallets, which can be verified by the Etherscan block explorer.</p><p>Whereas some tokens are created from ICOs, or Initial Coin Offerings, the SWITCH Token is minted on and by the Switch Blockchain as a digital reward for node owners who own and host node licenses that power the blockchain. The SWITCH Token is an ERC-20 Token that has been bridged over to the Ethereum Network from the Native Switch Blockchain. SWITCH will have a Max Supply of 50 Billion Tokens.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>The Switch Blockchain is managed by the community of node owners and driven by a Distributed Governance Framework (DGF) Charter that was voted in and approved by node owners.</p><p>About Switch Reward Card</p><p>Switch Reward Card is a blockchain-based financial services company delivering products for its users. Switch Reward Card offers debit payment solutions for both traditional and cryptocurrencies around the world.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>Switch is a unique payment ecosystem composed of the Switch App, the Switch Card, and the Switch Network.&nbsp;Each component plays a vital role in fostering a more secure, predictable, and reliable payment environment that organically incentivizes strong user advocacy.</p><p>The Switch App is a convenient and easy-to-use payment service and digital asset trading platform. This software application enables users to send and receive blockchain-based payments that are secure, irreversible, and near-instant. It is the glue that ties the ecosystem together and allows Switch members to enjoy benefits that are not possible on legacy payment platforms.&nbsp;The Switch Trading Platform offers users both a custodial and a self-custody wallet giving users more control over their assets.</p><p>Learn More about Switch Reward Card and the Switch Blockchain Community:</p><p>Official Website | Twitter | Facebook | Instagram | LinkedIn | Telegram | Contract</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram l&nbsp;Twitter l&nbsp;Facebook l&nbsp;LinkedIn l&nbsp;Instagram l&nbsp;YouTube</p><p>Contact Details:</p><p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p><p>LBank Exchange</p><p>business@lbank.info</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list Switch (SWITCH) on Jun 8, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the SWITCH/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 4:00 UTC on Jun 8, 2023.&nbsp;This is the first Centralized Exchange listing for the SWITCH Token.</p><p>About The Switch Token</p><p>The Switch Token was launched on the decentralized exchange Uniswap on February 23, 2023.&nbsp;Since its launch it has been listed on CoinGecko, CoinMarketCap and has had an average trading volume over $100,000 on the decentralized exchange.</p><p>The community surrounding the Switch Blockchain continues to grow in numbers on platforms such as Twitter, Discord and Reddit. At time of this writing the SWITCH ERC-20 token was held in over 1800 individual wallets, which can be verified by the Etherscan block explorer.</p><p>Whereas some tokens are created from ICOs, or Initial Coin Offerings, the SWITCH Token is minted on and by the Switch Blockchain as a digital reward for node owners who own and host node licenses that power the blockchain. The SWITCH Token is an ERC-20 Token that has been bridged over to the Ethereum Network from the Native Switch Blockchain. SWITCH will have a Max Supply of 50 Billion Tokens.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>The Switch Blockchain is managed by the community of node owners and driven by a Distributed Governance Framework (DGF) Charter that was voted in and approved by node owners.</p><p>About Switch Reward Card</p><p>Switch Reward Card is a blockchain-based financial services company delivering products for its users. Switch Reward Card offers debit payment solutions for both traditional and cryptocurrencies around the world.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>Switch is a unique payment ecosystem composed of the Switch App, the Switch Card, and the Switch Network.&nbsp;Each component plays a vital role in fostering a more secure, predictable, and reliable payment environment that organically incentivizes strong user advocacy.</p><p>The Switch App is a convenient and easy-to-use payment service and digital asset trading platform. This software application enables users to send and receive blockchain-based payments that are secure, irreversible, and near-instant. It is the glue that ties the ecosystem together and allows Switch members to enjoy benefits that are not possible on legacy payment platforms.&nbsp;The Switch Trading Platform offers users both a custodial and a self-custody wallet giving users more control over their assets.</p><p>Learn More about Switch Reward Card and the Switch Blockchain Community:</p><p>Official Website | Twitter | Facebook | Instagram | LinkedIn | Telegram | Contract</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram l&nbsp;Twitter l&nbsp;Facebook l&nbsp;LinkedIn l&nbsp;Instagram l&nbsp;YouTube</p><p>Contact Details:</p><p>LBK Blockchain Co. Limited</p><p>LBank Exchange</p><p>business@lbank.info</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cboe Gets Approval For Margin Trades On Crypto Futures Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cboe-gets-approval-for-margin-trades-on-crypto-futures-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cftc-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cftc-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cftc-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cboe-gets-approval-for-margin-trades-on-crypto-futures-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission has approved an amended order of registration, allowing Cboe Clear Digital to clear additional products as a derivatives clearing organization.&nbsp;</p>
Green Signal For Cboe&nbsp;
<p>The announcement means that traders on Cboe Global Markets&rsquo; digital-asset exchange would be able to enter into margined Ether and Bitcoin contracts. The amended order will allow Cboe Clear Digital to offer clearing services for digital asset futures on a margined basis for futures commission merchants.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Commodity Futures Trading Commission today approved an amended order of registration for Cboe Clear Digital, LLC (Cboe Clear) to clear additional products, subject to the terms and conditions specified in the order, as a derivatives clearing organization (DCO) under the Commodity Exchange Act.&rdquo;</p>

<p>This will be in addition to the fully collateralized futures and fully collateralized swaps that were previously approved.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The amended order permits Cboe Clear to provide clearing services for digital asset futures on a margined basis for futures commission merchants, in addition to the fully collateralized futures and fully collateralized swaps previously authorized.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Previously, Cboe only offered fully collateralized trading of cryptocurrency futures, which required clients to furnish the entire amount of a particular contract before trading. With margined trading, traders can put up less capital when opening a position. Furthermore, the physical settlement of digital assets will enable traditional financial firms to access Bitcoin and Ether futures without handing over custody to intermediaries. Cboe Digital president John Palmer added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;That&rsquo;s where the concept of us also having a spot market has advantages. We didn&rsquo;t want to have to force participants to custody or touch the physical asset.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Prudent Risk-Mitigation Measures&nbsp;
<p>Cboe Clear&rsquo;s parent company, Cboe Digital Exchange, is registered with the Commodities Futures Trading Commission as a designated contract market. This gives Cboe the authority to expand its clearing of futures contracts for crypto assets while ensuring that it does so within the traditional US futures intermediated market structure. Christy Goldsmith Romero, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission president, in a separate statement, added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Order is accompanied by prudent risk-mitigation measures implemented by Cboe. I have been vocal about the benefits of bringing appropriate crypto activities into the regulated space in order to protect customers, but in a way that supports oversight, accountability, transparency, and risk management.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Romero added that Cboe&rsquo;s application was in stark contrast with another from the now-collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX for a &ldquo;bespoke disintermediated direct-to-customer market structure.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Too often in recent years, crypto firms have sought to take a business model or market structure that exists in an unregulated environment and port it over to the regulated environment. &ldquo;Cboe has not done that, instead operating within the parameters of the traditional futures market structure and regulatory framework. It has constructively engaged with the staff and my office to address concerns related to risk and implement risk-mitigating measures.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission has approved an amended order of registration, allowing Cboe Clear Digital to clear additional products as a derivatives clearing organization.&nbsp;</p>
Green Signal For Cboe&nbsp;
<p>The announcement means that traders on Cboe Global Markets&rsquo; digital-asset exchange would be able to enter into margined Ether and Bitcoin contracts. The amended order will allow Cboe Clear Digital to offer clearing services for digital asset futures on a margined basis for futures commission merchants.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Commodity Futures Trading Commission today approved an amended order of registration for Cboe Clear Digital, LLC (Cboe Clear) to clear additional products, subject to the terms and conditions specified in the order, as a derivatives clearing organization (DCO) under the Commodity Exchange Act.&rdquo;</p>

<p>This will be in addition to the fully collateralized futures and fully collateralized swaps that were previously approved.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The amended order permits Cboe Clear to provide clearing services for digital asset futures on a margined basis for futures commission merchants, in addition to the fully collateralized futures and fully collateralized swaps previously authorized.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Previously, Cboe only offered fully collateralized trading of cryptocurrency futures, which required clients to furnish the entire amount of a particular contract before trading. With margined trading, traders can put up less capital when opening a position. Furthermore, the physical settlement of digital assets will enable traditional financial firms to access Bitcoin and Ether futures without handing over custody to intermediaries. Cboe Digital president John Palmer added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;That&rsquo;s where the concept of us also having a spot market has advantages. We didn&rsquo;t want to have to force participants to custody or touch the physical asset.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Prudent Risk-Mitigation Measures&nbsp;
<p>Cboe Clear&rsquo;s parent company, Cboe Digital Exchange, is registered with the Commodities Futures Trading Commission as a designated contract market. This gives Cboe the authority to expand its clearing of futures contracts for crypto assets while ensuring that it does so within the traditional US futures intermediated market structure. Christy Goldsmith Romero, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission president, in a separate statement, added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Order is accompanied by prudent risk-mitigation measures implemented by Cboe. I have been vocal about the benefits of bringing appropriate crypto activities into the regulated space in order to protect customers, but in a way that supports oversight, accountability, transparency, and risk management.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Romero added that Cboe&rsquo;s application was in stark contrast with another from the now-collapsed cryptocurrency exchange FTX for a &ldquo;bespoke disintermediated direct-to-customer market structure.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Too often in recent years, crypto firms have sought to take a business model or market structure that exists in an unregulated environment and port it over to the regulated environment. &ldquo;Cboe has not done that, instead operating within the parameters of the traditional futures market structure and regulatory framework. It has constructively engaged with the staff and my office to address concerns related to risk and implement risk-mitigating measures.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Walbi AI-Powered Platform to Launch MVP, Enhance Decision-Making for Crypto Traders]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/walbi-ai-powered-platform-to-launch-mvp-enhance-decision-making-for-crypto-traders</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/walbi.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/walbi.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/walbi.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:00:36 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/walbi-ai-powered-platform-to-launch-mvp-enhance-decision-making-for-crypto-traders</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Whether it's crypto, stocks, or forex, the cold hard truth is that most traders lose.</p>
<p>An analysis of eToro trades revealed that nearly 80% of the platform's active users were unprofitable over the course of a year, with a 36.3% median loss. Another study found that 97% of futures traders in Brazil lost money over 300 days. Only 5% of Taiwanese day traders were profitable between 1992 and 2006.</p>
<p>When the stakes are high, human error becomes costly. This is the case with trading, where trader decisions are often tainted with split-second decisions, panic-based actions, and a sunk cost fallacy mentality. This is likely why the stock market is increasingly run by machines and algorithms.</p>
<p>Artificial intelligence has proved capable of tackling this challenge, and one company called Walbi has already designed an AI solution to assist crypto traders.</p>
Tapping Into the Power of AI
<p>Recent breakthroughs in generative AI have created tremendous hype around artificial intelligence tools.</p>
<p>The technology has proven effective in tasks thought to be impossible for an algorithm, like content creation and art generation. Now, AI technology is increasingly prolific in the financial industry. While robo-advisor AUM is expected to reach $2.02 trillion by 2027, startups are leveraging AI to enhance crypto trader performance.</p>
<p>AI offers the advantage of processing data much faster than a human. Where a human has to spend hours or days understanding trends and making decisions based on them, an AI can recognize patterns in seconds and offer advice to the trader. It can analyze the market in real-time and catch sudden shifts, fraud, and malicious activity, and even make low-level trading decisions. This allows traders with AI assistance to make quick and confident trading decisions, which in the trading world is incredibly important.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Walbi is currently building a crypto trading platform that offers all these benefits, and the project is expected to achieve a significant milestone with the launch of its minimum viable product (MVP) in June 2023.</p>
Walbi's AI-Driven Crypto Trading Solution
<p>Walbi is a next-gen hybrid decentralized finance (DeFi) platform consisting of a crypto exchange, non-custodial Web3 wallet, and AI tool suite to supercharge trader decision-making. The project has multiple flagship solutions that aim to fulfill Walbi&rsquo;s mission to make the blockchain industry simpler and more intuitive for everyone.</p>
<p>The first one is the Walbi Exchange, a crypto exchange offering up to 500 times more leverage for futures traders without a mandatory KYC. Besides managing liquidity, Walbi's AI tools optimize the order book by predicting demand for digital assets and automatically detecting wash trading, spoofing, and other malicious activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Besides Walbi Exchange, the project will offer:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Lighthouse: An AI-based trading assistant that does research on behalf of traders and assists them with real-time financial data analysis and personalized trading advice. Lighthouse helps traders make more confident and well-informed decisions while minimizing the risks of human error</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Earn: Allows users to stake their crypto assets on Walbi to earn interest without any locking periods and with weekly payouts</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Cloud Miner: A cloud mining solution enabling users to mine BTC without purchasing or operating expensive equipment</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Wallet: A decentralized, non-custodial Web3 wallet offering users full control over their funds</li>
</ul>
Walbi's Upcoming MVP Launch
<p>Walbi is currently in closed alpha but will soon launch its MVP. This release will expand the project's ecosystem with several features and functions, including:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">WalletConnect integration</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">digital asset deposits and withdrawals</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">margin trading</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">AI-driven trading insights via Walbi Lighthouse</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">the Walbi Waves invite system</li>
</ul>
<p>Besides the features listed above, Walbi's roadmap includes numerous future feature releases. During Q3-Q4 2023, the platform plans to launch WalletConnect integration and margin trading, NFTs, Walbi Lighthouse, and token swaps. Walbi Waves and Cloud Mining, Walbi Exchange, Walbi Earn and portfolio tools, and Walbi Wallet will become accessible to platform users throughout 2024.</p>

Crypto Trading, Supercharged
<p>Artificial intelligence models are poised to be an unprecedented improvement to trader performance which has long struggled with unprofitable strategies and approaches.</p>
<p>Walbi is arriving soon and will be one of the first to leverage the power of AI to make trading faster, easier, and safer. With the assistance of AI tools, the project enables crypto traders to make data-driven decisions, potentially increasing their long-term profitability.</p>
<p>Want to learn more about Walbi? Check out the project's blog and subscribe to its Telegram and Twitter channels.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether it's crypto, stocks, or forex, the cold hard truth is that most traders lose.</p>
<p>An analysis of eToro trades revealed that nearly 80% of the platform's active users were unprofitable over the course of a year, with a 36.3% median loss. Another study found that 97% of futures traders in Brazil lost money over 300 days. Only 5% of Taiwanese day traders were profitable between 1992 and 2006.</p>
<p>When the stakes are high, human error becomes costly. This is the case with trading, where trader decisions are often tainted with split-second decisions, panic-based actions, and a sunk cost fallacy mentality. This is likely why the stock market is increasingly run by machines and algorithms.</p>
<p>Artificial intelligence has proved capable of tackling this challenge, and one company called Walbi has already designed an AI solution to assist crypto traders.</p>
Tapping Into the Power of AI
<p>Recent breakthroughs in generative AI have created tremendous hype around artificial intelligence tools.</p>
<p>The technology has proven effective in tasks thought to be impossible for an algorithm, like content creation and art generation. Now, AI technology is increasingly prolific in the financial industry. While robo-advisor AUM is expected to reach $2.02 trillion by 2027, startups are leveraging AI to enhance crypto trader performance.</p>
<p>AI offers the advantage of processing data much faster than a human. Where a human has to spend hours or days understanding trends and making decisions based on them, an AI can recognize patterns in seconds and offer advice to the trader. It can analyze the market in real-time and catch sudden shifts, fraud, and malicious activity, and even make low-level trading decisions. This allows traders with AI assistance to make quick and confident trading decisions, which in the trading world is incredibly important.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Walbi is currently building a crypto trading platform that offers all these benefits, and the project is expected to achieve a significant milestone with the launch of its minimum viable product (MVP) in June 2023.</p>
Walbi's AI-Driven Crypto Trading Solution
<p>Walbi is a next-gen hybrid decentralized finance (DeFi) platform consisting of a crypto exchange, non-custodial Web3 wallet, and AI tool suite to supercharge trader decision-making. The project has multiple flagship solutions that aim to fulfill Walbi&rsquo;s mission to make the blockchain industry simpler and more intuitive for everyone.</p>
<p>The first one is the Walbi Exchange, a crypto exchange offering up to 500 times more leverage for futures traders without a mandatory KYC. Besides managing liquidity, Walbi's AI tools optimize the order book by predicting demand for digital assets and automatically detecting wash trading, spoofing, and other malicious activity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Besides Walbi Exchange, the project will offer:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Lighthouse: An AI-based trading assistant that does research on behalf of traders and assists them with real-time financial data analysis and personalized trading advice. Lighthouse helps traders make more confident and well-informed decisions while minimizing the risks of human error</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Earn: Allows users to stake their crypto assets on Walbi to earn interest without any locking periods and with weekly payouts</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Cloud Miner: A cloud mining solution enabling users to mine BTC without purchasing or operating expensive equipment</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Walbi Wallet: A decentralized, non-custodial Web3 wallet offering users full control over their funds</li>
</ul>
Walbi's Upcoming MVP Launch
<p>Walbi is currently in closed alpha but will soon launch its MVP. This release will expand the project's ecosystem with several features and functions, including:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">WalletConnect integration</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">digital asset deposits and withdrawals</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">margin trading</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">AI-driven trading insights via Walbi Lighthouse</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">the Walbi Waves invite system</li>
</ul>
<p>Besides the features listed above, Walbi's roadmap includes numerous future feature releases. During Q3-Q4 2023, the platform plans to launch WalletConnect integration and margin trading, NFTs, Walbi Lighthouse, and token swaps. Walbi Waves and Cloud Mining, Walbi Exchange, Walbi Earn and portfolio tools, and Walbi Wallet will become accessible to platform users throughout 2024.</p>

Crypto Trading, Supercharged
<p>Artificial intelligence models are poised to be an unprecedented improvement to trader performance which has long struggled with unprofitable strategies and approaches.</p>
<p>Walbi is arriving soon and will be one of the first to leverage the power of AI to make trading faster, easier, and safer. With the assistance of AI tools, the project enables crypto traders to make data-driven decisions, potentially increasing their long-term profitability.</p>
<p>Want to learn more about Walbi? Check out the project's blog and subscribe to its Telegram and Twitter channels.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKX Partners with Komainu, Enabling 24/7 Secure Trading of Segregated Assets Under Custody for Institutions]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-247-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Blog_1600x844_1_1686038713oAjQKCfO0K.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Blog_1600x844_1_1686038713oAjQKCfO0K.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Blog_1600x844_1_1686038713oAjQKCfO0K.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 09:33:41 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-partners-with-komainu-enabling-247-secure-trading-of-segregated-assets-under-custody-for-institutions</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>ST HELLIER, Jersey, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>OKX, the world&rsquo;s second-largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, and regulated digital asset custody service provider Komainu, today announced that OKX has joined collateral management platform Komainu Connect, enabling institutional customers to conduct secure 24/7 trading of segregated assets under custody through the OKX platform.</p><p>Launched in April of 2023, Komainu Connect reduces client counterparty risk by removing the need to store collateral with trading counterparties, and offering the ability to keep assets in safe custody instead.&nbsp;</p>Nicolas Bertrand, CEO at Komainu, said: &ldquo;This strategic partnership marks a milestone in our mission to provide secure and compliant digital asset custody solutions. OKX's reputation as a leading cryptocurrency exchange, combined with our expertise in institutional-grade custody services is paving the way for a new era of trust and innovation in the industry.&rdquo;Sebastian Widmann, Head of Strategy at Komainu, said: &ldquo;Komainu Connect is rapidly emerging as the leading collateral management solution. Partnering with one of the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchanges is a testament to the infrastructure and expertise committed to this service and our focus remains on seamless execution for all parties.&rdquo;Lennix Lai, Global Chief Commercial Officer at OKX, said: &ldquo;Institutions need the peace of mind that comes with knowing their assets are being kept safe with a leading custodian, while retaining their ability to capitalize when investment opportunities arise. That is why we are delighted to partner with Komainu to allow investors a way to keep their assets secure while not compromising on returns.&rdquo;<p>The off-exchange settlement and tripartite mirroring solution is a significant step forward for large-scale institutional crypto traders requiring immediate access to OKX's market-leading portfolio margin account mode and liquid markets.</p><p>Komainu was established in 2018 to provide institutions with a secure and compliant custody service for investment in digital assets. Launched in June 2020, Komainu currently custodies assets for exchanges, financial institutions, asset managers, corporations, and government agencies.</p><p>Find out more about why institutions choose OKX here.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as the most reliable crypto trading platform for traders, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume.</p><p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download OKX's app or visit: okx.com</p><p>About Komainu</p><p>Komainu is a regulated digital asset custodian built by institutions for institutions and created as a joint venture between Nomura, digital asset manager CoinShares, and digital asset security company Ledger. Offering multi-asset support with regulatory compliance, Komainu is merging traditional financial services with leading security standards for the next generation of institutional custody. Headquartered in Jersey and with offices in London, Dublin, Dubai, and Singapore, Komainu is regulated by the Jersey Financial Services Commission (JFSC) and Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA). For more information, visit https://www.komainu.com</p><p>Media Contact: Armel Leslie, Peaks Strategies, +1 (914) 320-7620, aleslie@peaksstrategies.com&nbsp;</p><p>DISCLAIMER</p><p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p><p></p>ContactMediaOKXmedia@okx.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ST HELLIER, Jersey, June 6th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>OKX, the world&rsquo;s second-largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, and regulated digital asset custody service provider Komainu, today announced that OKX has joined collateral management platform Komainu Connect, enabling institutional customers to conduct secure 24/7 trading of segregated assets under custody through the OKX platform.</p><p>Launched in April of 2023, Komainu Connect reduces client counterparty risk by removing the need to store collateral with trading counterparties, and offering the ability to keep assets in safe custody instead.&nbsp;</p>Nicolas Bertrand, CEO at Komainu, said: &ldquo;This strategic partnership marks a milestone in our mission to provide secure and compliant digital asset custody solutions. OKX's reputation as a leading cryptocurrency exchange, combined with our expertise in institutional-grade custody services is paving the way for a new era of trust and innovation in the industry.&rdquo;Sebastian Widmann, Head of Strategy at Komainu, said: &ldquo;Komainu Connect is rapidly emerging as the leading collateral management solution. Partnering with one of the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchanges is a testament to the infrastructure and expertise committed to this service and our focus remains on seamless execution for all parties.&rdquo;Lennix Lai, Global Chief Commercial Officer at OKX, said: &ldquo;Institutions need the peace of mind that comes with knowing their assets are being kept safe with a leading custodian, while retaining their ability to capitalize when investment opportunities arise. That is why we are delighted to partner with Komainu to allow investors a way to keep their assets secure while not compromising on returns.&rdquo;<p>The off-exchange settlement and tripartite mirroring solution is a significant step forward for large-scale institutional crypto traders requiring immediate access to OKX's market-leading portfolio margin account mode and liquid markets.</p><p>Komainu was established in 2018 to provide institutions with a secure and compliant custody service for investment in digital assets. Launched in June 2020, Komainu currently custodies assets for exchanges, financial institutions, asset managers, corporations, and government agencies.</p><p>Find out more about why institutions choose OKX here.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as the most reliable crypto trading platform for traders, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume.</p><p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download OKX's app or visit: okx.com</p><p>About Komainu</p><p>Komainu is a regulated digital asset custodian built by institutions for institutions and created as a joint venture between Nomura, digital asset manager CoinShares, and digital asset security company Ledger. Offering multi-asset support with regulatory compliance, Komainu is merging traditional financial services with leading security standards for the next generation of institutional custody. Headquartered in Jersey and with offices in London, Dublin, Dubai, and Singapore, Komainu is regulated by the Jersey Financial Services Commission (JFSC) and Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA). For more information, visit https://www.komainu.com</p><p>Media Contact: Armel Leslie, Peaks Strategies, +1 (914) 320-7620, aleslie@peaksstrategies.com&nbsp;</p><p>DISCLAIMER</p><p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p><p></p>ContactMediaOKXmedia@okx.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
