<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 03:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[New project pairs NFTs with real diamonds]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/new-project-pairs-nfts-with-real-diamonds</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dd-8.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dd-8.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dd-8.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 21:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/new-project-pairs-nfts-with-real-diamonds</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>333 limited edition art NFTs, each paired with a high quality, GIA-certified Cape diamond, will go on private sale January 11, followed by a public sale on January 18.</p>
<p>A first of its kind, Diamond Dawn is an NFT project created by Mike Moldawsky, with the collaboration of Moldawsky Diamonds, renowned artist David Ariew, and Tony Herrera, an experienced entrepreneur and innovator in the web 3.0 space.</p>
<p>The project uses blockchain and NFT technology to promote the transparent and ethical sourcing of diamonds.</p>
<p>It is the brain-child of entrepreneur Mike Moldawsky, of the well-known Moldawsky family, steeped in the history of the diamond industry.</p>
<p>David Ariew is one of the most prominent NFT artists in the world, recently selling an NFT artwork at Sotheby's for $224,000. He designed 2 of the 3 Beeple X Madonna NFTs, and has collaborated with top artists who include Katy Perry, Zedd, and Deadmau5.</p>
<p>Tony Herrera is a visionary with a long track record of building and innovating in the fields of cryptocurrency, blockchain, and NFTs. He is a founding member of Galaxis, and of several DAOs dedicated to the metaverse, including MeebitsDAO, NeonDAO, and ReadyPlayerDAO.</p>
The Diamond Dawn NFT project
<p>Diamond Dawn is a project that matures over a 6-month period. The four phases of the project are similar to those of the natural diamond processing that takes place in the real world.</p>
<p>All of these steps are performed through an interactive interface designed by Asaf Snir, an expert with 15 years in website design specialising in unique visual experiences and parallax technologies.</p>
<p>In the first phase, the collector will mine a digital Rough Stone in Diamond Dawn&rsquo;s virtual mine. There then follow two further phases where the collector evolves their diamond until it reaches the perfection of the digital diamond designed by David Ariew.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Box opening - a luxury design by Moldawsky that weighs 8kg and measures 25*25*25 cm</p>
<p>The fourth and final phase is when the collector has to make the choice of whether to keep the virtual digital diamond, or whether to have it transformed into its physical diamond form.</p>
<p>If they choose the physical diamond, they will receive a limited-edition art piece in the form of a GIA-certified diamond created by Moldawsky. The physical diamond will have exactly the same attributes of colour, shape, and carat weight of the NFT diamond.</p>
<p>One very important aspect of the project is that the NFT that backs the physical diamond is then destroyed by being burned. This will then give greater scarcity value to the remaining NFTs, potentially having the effect that they become more valuable than the physical diamonds themselves.</p>
<p>The diamonds are stored at the Moldawsky Diamonds vault, inside of the Israel Diamond Exchange, which is the largest diamond exchange in the world.</p>
Aims of the project
<p>Primarily, the Diamond Dawn project looks to demonstrate the power and ability of decentralised NFT technology to solve the very real problem of certification fraud and manipulation in the $100 billion diamond industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Also, the fact that blockchain and NFT technology is able to certify and verify a diamond&rsquo;s provenance, will enable the tracking of diamonds mined in conflict areas, known as blood diamonds. This in turn should lead to the transparency and ethical sourcing of diamonds that the industry sorely needs.</p>
<p>Secondly, the project seeks to find the value balance between the physical real-world asset, and the virtual-world twin in the form of its paired NFT.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The market, in the form of the Diamond Dawn collectors, will decide whether to own the physical diamond, or its digital representation. How many of the 333 NFTs will need to be burned before the value of the NFT becomes akin to that of the physical diamond? Which one will end up being worth more?</p>
Further information
<p>The Diamond Dawn project is only available through a submission process on the official website. If accepted as a collector, an individual is then given two invitations which they can share with other potential collectors. This keeps the process fair, and allows the public to form the&nbsp; collector community rather than the project team itself. There is a limit of two NFTs per collector.</p>
<p>Those wishing to find out more about Diamond Dawn can also watch a short introductory video of the project on the Diamond Dawn Twitter account.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>333 limited edition art NFTs, each paired with a high quality, GIA-certified Cape diamond, will go on private sale January 11, followed by a public sale on January 18.</p>
<p>A first of its kind, Diamond Dawn is an NFT project created by Mike Moldawsky, with the collaboration of Moldawsky Diamonds, renowned artist David Ariew, and Tony Herrera, an experienced entrepreneur and innovator in the web 3.0 space.</p>
<p>The project uses blockchain and NFT technology to promote the transparent and ethical sourcing of diamonds.</p>
<p>It is the brain-child of entrepreneur Mike Moldawsky, of the well-known Moldawsky family, steeped in the history of the diamond industry.</p>
<p>David Ariew is one of the most prominent NFT artists in the world, recently selling an NFT artwork at Sotheby's for $224,000. He designed 2 of the 3 Beeple X Madonna NFTs, and has collaborated with top artists who include Katy Perry, Zedd, and Deadmau5.</p>
<p>Tony Herrera is a visionary with a long track record of building and innovating in the fields of cryptocurrency, blockchain, and NFTs. He is a founding member of Galaxis, and of several DAOs dedicated to the metaverse, including MeebitsDAO, NeonDAO, and ReadyPlayerDAO.</p>
The Diamond Dawn NFT project
<p>Diamond Dawn is a project that matures over a 6-month period. The four phases of the project are similar to those of the natural diamond processing that takes place in the real world.</p>
<p>All of these steps are performed through an interactive interface designed by Asaf Snir, an expert with 15 years in website design specialising in unique visual experiences and parallax technologies.</p>
<p>In the first phase, the collector will mine a digital Rough Stone in Diamond Dawn&rsquo;s virtual mine. There then follow two further phases where the collector evolves their diamond until it reaches the perfection of the digital diamond designed by David Ariew.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Box opening - a luxury design by Moldawsky that weighs 8kg and measures 25*25*25 cm</p>
<p>The fourth and final phase is when the collector has to make the choice of whether to keep the virtual digital diamond, or whether to have it transformed into its physical diamond form.</p>
<p>If they choose the physical diamond, they will receive a limited-edition art piece in the form of a GIA-certified diamond created by Moldawsky. The physical diamond will have exactly the same attributes of colour, shape, and carat weight of the NFT diamond.</p>
<p>One very important aspect of the project is that the NFT that backs the physical diamond is then destroyed by being burned. This will then give greater scarcity value to the remaining NFTs, potentially having the effect that they become more valuable than the physical diamonds themselves.</p>
<p>The diamonds are stored at the Moldawsky Diamonds vault, inside of the Israel Diamond Exchange, which is the largest diamond exchange in the world.</p>
Aims of the project
<p>Primarily, the Diamond Dawn project looks to demonstrate the power and ability of decentralised NFT technology to solve the very real problem of certification fraud and manipulation in the $100 billion diamond industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Also, the fact that blockchain and NFT technology is able to certify and verify a diamond&rsquo;s provenance, will enable the tracking of diamonds mined in conflict areas, known as blood diamonds. This in turn should lead to the transparency and ethical sourcing of diamonds that the industry sorely needs.</p>
<p>Secondly, the project seeks to find the value balance between the physical real-world asset, and the virtual-world twin in the form of its paired NFT.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The market, in the form of the Diamond Dawn collectors, will decide whether to own the physical diamond, or its digital representation. How many of the 333 NFTs will need to be burned before the value of the NFT becomes akin to that of the physical diamond? Which one will end up being worth more?</p>
Further information
<p>The Diamond Dawn project is only available through a submission process on the official website. If accepted as a collector, an individual is then given two invitations which they can share with other potential collectors. This keeps the process fair, and allows the public to form the&nbsp; collector community rather than the project team itself. There is a limit of two NFTs per collector.</p>
<p>Those wishing to find out more about Diamond Dawn can also watch a short introductory video of the project on the Diamond Dawn Twitter account.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Russian Federation Presents Bill on Digital Ruble to State Duma]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/russian-federation-presents-bill-on-digital-ruble-to-state-duma</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/russia-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/russia-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/russia-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/russian-federation-presents-bill-on-digital-ruble-to-state-duma</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Federation has submitted a draft bill regarding the digital ruble to the State Duma, the lower house of the Russian parliament. </p>
<p>&nbsp;Russian lawmakers, led by the Chairman of the Financial Market Committee Anatoly Aksakov, have presented draft legislation on the central bank digital currency (CBDC) minted by Russia&rsquo;s monetary authority &ndash; the digital ruble. The main purpose of the bill is to develop a necessary payment infrastructure for the CBDC and will allow Russian citizens, businesses, and the state access to fast, convenient, and low-cost money transfers according to reports.</p>
<p>Under the proposal, the Bank of Russia will be the sole entity responsible for managing the CBDC system and it will also lay out the steps necessary to create a digital ruble wallet and gain access to the network. The document submitted to Parliament codifies the digital ruble as the official currency of the Russian Federation and deems CBDCs issued by the central banks of foreign countries as non-domestic.</p>
<p>The digital ruble will be introduced as a third legal tender option for payments and purchases in Russia, along with traditional cash and other forms of money. Deputy Minister of Finance, Alexei Moiseev, said that the digital currency will be ready to implement in April 2023. The CBDC will enable the nation to increase the government&rsquo;s control over the targeted expenditure of money from its budget, make targeted payments and optimize the process of recovering monies not spent. Reports also indicate that blockchain technology is being used to build the digital ruble which will make it possible to identify certain types of money and track their movements according to distinct digital codes, which are analogous to serial numbers that are also found on paper money.</p>
Bank of Russia Testing Crypto for International Payments
<p>The Bank of Russia is reportedly planning to test the use of crypto for international payments within the regulatory framework. The Deputy Chairperson of the Central Bank said:</p>

<p>We currently plan to test using cryptocurrency for international payments, meaning for international economic activities, within the framework of the regulatory sandbox.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Federation has submitted a draft bill regarding the digital ruble to the State Duma, the lower house of the Russian parliament. </p>
<p>&nbsp;Russian lawmakers, led by the Chairman of the Financial Market Committee Anatoly Aksakov, have presented draft legislation on the central bank digital currency (CBDC) minted by Russia&rsquo;s monetary authority &ndash; the digital ruble. The main purpose of the bill is to develop a necessary payment infrastructure for the CBDC and will allow Russian citizens, businesses, and the state access to fast, convenient, and low-cost money transfers according to reports.</p>
<p>Under the proposal, the Bank of Russia will be the sole entity responsible for managing the CBDC system and it will also lay out the steps necessary to create a digital ruble wallet and gain access to the network. The document submitted to Parliament codifies the digital ruble as the official currency of the Russian Federation and deems CBDCs issued by the central banks of foreign countries as non-domestic.</p>
<p>The digital ruble will be introduced as a third legal tender option for payments and purchases in Russia, along with traditional cash and other forms of money. Deputy Minister of Finance, Alexei Moiseev, said that the digital currency will be ready to implement in April 2023. The CBDC will enable the nation to increase the government&rsquo;s control over the targeted expenditure of money from its budget, make targeted payments and optimize the process of recovering monies not spent. Reports also indicate that blockchain technology is being used to build the digital ruble which will make it possible to identify certain types of money and track their movements according to distinct digital codes, which are analogous to serial numbers that are also found on paper money.</p>
Bank of Russia Testing Crypto for International Payments
<p>The Bank of Russia is reportedly planning to test the use of crypto for international payments within the regulatory framework. The Deputy Chairperson of the Central Bank said:</p>

<p>We currently plan to test using cryptocurrency for international payments, meaning for international economic activities, within the framework of the regulatory sandbox.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The Finest Cryptocurrency Mining Software, Brought to You by Miner US Limited]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/the-finest-cryptocurrency-mining-software-brought-to-you-by-miner-us-limited</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-03-at-194247.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-03-at-194247.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-03-at-194247.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/the-finest-cryptocurrency-mining-software-brought-to-you-by-miner-us-limited</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>If you are interested to know more about Miner US Limited you can check out the : Miner US Limited Introduction Video</p>
<p>Introducing Miner US Limited </p>
<p>Graves David Gavin, the man behind the cryptocurrency investment firm Miner US Limited, spent four years studying the market before launching the company in New York in April 2019. Our parent company, Miner US Limited, put on a great party for us to celebrate the launch. Miner US plans to provide an alternative to the usual risks and limitations associated with investing in cryptocurrencies, decentralized finance projects, crypto securities, and blockchain technology. Ethical cryptocurrency and blockchain investment is a top priority for this team of analysts, engineers, data scientists, operators, and risk managers. Managing resources wisely is a top priority for the organization.</p>
<p>Models for Cloud Mining</p>
<p>The responses to the question "How does cloud mining work?" highlight cloud crypto mining models. Cloud-based cryptocurrency miners can choose between two distinct models. Two models of cloud-based crypto mining are described here.</p>
<p>HashPowerLeasing</p>
<p>In this model, cloud miners lease a portion of a mining farm's hashing power. To participate in the mining farm's profits, miners must subscribe to a cloud mining company plan. Miners leasing hash power from the farm pay neither setup nor maintenance fees. The mining rewards of each miner are also determined by the hashing power of each miner.</p>
<p>Cloud mining benefits</p>
<p>Cloud mining's benefits must also be mentioned. Cloud-based cryptocurrency mining is efficient and maintenance-free. Cloud mining Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies offers numerous benefits.</p>
<p>Cost-effectiveness</p>
<p>Mining in the cloud is cost-effective because miners do not require equipment. Also, miners are not required to upgrade or maintain equipment. Miners need not be concerned with electricity costs, heat and noise from mining equipment.</p>
<p>Trouble-free</p>
<p>The biggest benefit of cloud mining is that it is maintenance-free. Mining service companies maintain miners' equipment. Typically, mining service providers avoid maintenance problems by situating mining farms in cooler climates and utilizing chilling towers.</p>
<p>Support</p>
<p>Consider the technological support provided by the mining service provider. Cloud-based cryptocurrency mining requires no cryptocurrency, mining hardware, or protocol expertise. Create an account with a mining service provider and pay the hashing power fees. All account rewards can be viewed on a tablet or smartphone.</p>
<p>Miner US Launch and Services</p>
<p>Miner US offers lifetime cloud mining for cryptocurrencies based on USDT. They provide multi-algorithm, multi-coin cloud mining by utilizing cutting-edge technology. Since its inception, the company's open hash power market has been a tremendous success. Mobile apps enable users to access our services from any location.</p>
<p>Upon enrollment, new users earn 10 USDT in hashing power. As indicated in the table below, Miner US provides 150 days and exclusive lifetime mining power plans with a wide range of hash rate power.</p>
<p>VIP 1 Hashrates(GH/s) (0.00~999.99USDT) Daily earning (2.50%)</p>
<p>VIP 2 Hashrates(GH/s) (1000.00~9999.99USDT) Daily earning (3.00%)</p>
<p>VIP 3 Hashrates(GH/s) (10000.00~29999.99USDT) Daily earning (4.00%)</p>
<p>VIP 4 Hashrates(GH/s) (30000.00~99999.99USDT) Daily earning (5.00%)</p>
<p>VIP 5 Hashrates(GH/s) (100000.00~499999.99USDT) Daily earning (6.00%)</p>
<p>SVIP Hashrates(GH/s) (500000.00~599999.99USDT) Daily earning (10.00%)</p>
<p>After the completion of the contract duration, the remaining balance can be fully withdrawn along with the principal amount.</p>
<p>Miner US Referral Programs</p>
<p>A user can invite a friend to join by giving them a unique code or a link to the sign-up page. After signing up, your friend's profile will appear in the "My Team" area. Commission income is not eligible for dividends until offline computer power is purchased, and then only at a ratio based on the number of users. Only when offline processing power is purchased can commission income be distributed as dividends.</p>
<p>Referral Purchase Rebates </p>
<p>VIP 1 </p>
<p>Level 1 : 3.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 2 </p>
<p>Level 1 : 4.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 3</p>
<p>Level 1 : 5.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 4</p>
<p>Level 1 : 7.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 5</p>
<p>Level 1 : 9.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 2.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>SVIP </p>
<p>Level 1 : 12.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 2.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 1.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Final Thought</p>
<p>Now that we've gotten that out of the way, we can get to the meat of this post: Miner US will always be the greatest option for making a profit without investing in expensive equipment and paying a monthly fee to keep it online and running. In addition to the financial rewards that can be gained, mining in the United States also provides an opportunity to provide excellent service to mining sector clients. In this article, we've covered what cloud mining is and why you should choose Miner US as your service provider.</p>
<p class="s11">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Registration Link | Official Website | Telegram | Facebook | Twitter | Youtube | Telegram Support</p>
<p class="s11">WhatsApp Support | LINE Support | Live Customer Support | Terms &amp; Conditions | Certificate</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you are interested to know more about Miner US Limited you can check out the : Miner US Limited Introduction Video</p>
<p>Introducing Miner US Limited </p>
<p>Graves David Gavin, the man behind the cryptocurrency investment firm Miner US Limited, spent four years studying the market before launching the company in New York in April 2019. Our parent company, Miner US Limited, put on a great party for us to celebrate the launch. Miner US plans to provide an alternative to the usual risks and limitations associated with investing in cryptocurrencies, decentralized finance projects, crypto securities, and blockchain technology. Ethical cryptocurrency and blockchain investment is a top priority for this team of analysts, engineers, data scientists, operators, and risk managers. Managing resources wisely is a top priority for the organization.</p>
<p>Models for Cloud Mining</p>
<p>The responses to the question "How does cloud mining work?" highlight cloud crypto mining models. Cloud-based cryptocurrency miners can choose between two distinct models. Two models of cloud-based crypto mining are described here.</p>
<p>HashPowerLeasing</p>
<p>In this model, cloud miners lease a portion of a mining farm's hashing power. To participate in the mining farm's profits, miners must subscribe to a cloud mining company plan. Miners leasing hash power from the farm pay neither setup nor maintenance fees. The mining rewards of each miner are also determined by the hashing power of each miner.</p>
<p>Cloud mining benefits</p>
<p>Cloud mining's benefits must also be mentioned. Cloud-based cryptocurrency mining is efficient and maintenance-free. Cloud mining Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies offers numerous benefits.</p>
<p>Cost-effectiveness</p>
<p>Mining in the cloud is cost-effective because miners do not require equipment. Also, miners are not required to upgrade or maintain equipment. Miners need not be concerned with electricity costs, heat and noise from mining equipment.</p>
<p>Trouble-free</p>
<p>The biggest benefit of cloud mining is that it is maintenance-free. Mining service companies maintain miners' equipment. Typically, mining service providers avoid maintenance problems by situating mining farms in cooler climates and utilizing chilling towers.</p>
<p>Support</p>
<p>Consider the technological support provided by the mining service provider. Cloud-based cryptocurrency mining requires no cryptocurrency, mining hardware, or protocol expertise. Create an account with a mining service provider and pay the hashing power fees. All account rewards can be viewed on a tablet or smartphone.</p>
<p>Miner US Launch and Services</p>
<p>Miner US offers lifetime cloud mining for cryptocurrencies based on USDT. They provide multi-algorithm, multi-coin cloud mining by utilizing cutting-edge technology. Since its inception, the company's open hash power market has been a tremendous success. Mobile apps enable users to access our services from any location.</p>
<p>Upon enrollment, new users earn 10 USDT in hashing power. As indicated in the table below, Miner US provides 150 days and exclusive lifetime mining power plans with a wide range of hash rate power.</p>
<p>VIP 1 Hashrates(GH/s) (0.00~999.99USDT) Daily earning (2.50%)</p>
<p>VIP 2 Hashrates(GH/s) (1000.00~9999.99USDT) Daily earning (3.00%)</p>
<p>VIP 3 Hashrates(GH/s) (10000.00~29999.99USDT) Daily earning (4.00%)</p>
<p>VIP 4 Hashrates(GH/s) (30000.00~99999.99USDT) Daily earning (5.00%)</p>
<p>VIP 5 Hashrates(GH/s) (100000.00~499999.99USDT) Daily earning (6.00%)</p>
<p>SVIP Hashrates(GH/s) (500000.00~599999.99USDT) Daily earning (10.00%)</p>
<p>After the completion of the contract duration, the remaining balance can be fully withdrawn along with the principal amount.</p>
<p>Miner US Referral Programs</p>
<p>A user can invite a friend to join by giving them a unique code or a link to the sign-up page. After signing up, your friend's profile will appear in the "My Team" area. Commission income is not eligible for dividends until offline computer power is purchased, and then only at a ratio based on the number of users. Only when offline processing power is purchased can commission income be distributed as dividends.</p>
<p>Referral Purchase Rebates </p>
<p>VIP 1 </p>
<p>Level 1 : 3.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 2 </p>
<p>Level 1 : 4.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 3</p>
<p>Level 1 : 5.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 4</p>
<p>Level 1 : 7.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 0.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VIP 5</p>
<p>Level 1 : 9.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 2.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 0.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>SVIP </p>
<p>Level 1 : 12.00%</p>
<p>Level 2 : 2.00%</p>
<p>Level 3 : 1.00%</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Final Thought</p>
<p>Now that we've gotten that out of the way, we can get to the meat of this post: Miner US will always be the greatest option for making a profit without investing in expensive equipment and paying a monthly fee to keep it online and running. In addition to the financial rewards that can be gained, mining in the United States also provides an opportunity to provide excellent service to mining sector clients. In this article, we've covered what cloud mining is and why you should choose Miner US as your service provider.</p>
<p class="s11">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Registration Link | Official Website | Telegram | Facebook | Twitter | Youtube | Telegram Support</p>
<p class="s11">WhatsApp Support | LINE Support | Live Customer Support | Terms &amp; Conditions | Certificate</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance (BNB) Faces Security Questions Over FTX Fiasco While Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Marches To 6000% Growth]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/binance-bnb-faces-security-questions-over-ftx-fiasco-while-orbeon-protocol-orbn-marches-to-6000-growth</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-504.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-504.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-504.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/binance-bnb-faces-security-questions-over-ftx-fiasco-while-orbeon-protocol-orbn-marches-to-6000-growth</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>This year has been extremely unpredictable for crypto enthusiasts. While the overall crypto market crashed in the first half of 2022, the second half witnessed a mix of both positive and negative events. On one hand, the long-standing crypto project, FTX, became bankrupt, making tens of thousands of investors lose millions. While on the other hand, a new entrant, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), has registered historical growth during its presale round, which is in its third phase. Due to its market viability and unique business roadmap, the value of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has recorded a growth of 805% in the first two phases of its presale.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Binance (BNB) Takes A Dip Amid Security Questions</p>
<p>After the US Securities and Exchange Commission labeled FTT, the token of the FTX exchange, as a security in a recent filing in a New York court, several concerns have emerged about Binance&rsquo;s BNB. In its filing, the SEC noted that FTT has a buy-and-burn program similar to a stock buyback, and they both result in increasing the asset&rsquo;s value. Interestingly, Binance also has a similar program called BNB Burn, and investors wonder what will happen to their investments if the SEC initiates legal actions against Binance (BNB) as well.</p>
<p>Although Binance CEO, Changpeng Zhao, has asserted that BNB is more than just a security, he has not been able to convince investors who are considering leaving the project. Consequently, Binance (BNB) has witnessed a sharp decline of 17% in its value in the last few weeks. Currently, Binance (BNB) is being traded at $244.79, which is 65% below its all-time high of $690.93. However, Binance (BNB) continues to assure its users that the platform is healthy.</p>
<p>Binance (BNB), the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the world, is used for trading and paying fees on the Binance exchange. Binance (BNB), launched in 2017, can also be exchanged or traded for other cryptocurrencies, like Ethereum, Bitcoin, and more.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Raises Millions In Just A Few Weeks</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is the leading blockchain-based investment platform that mints equity-backed fractional NFTs to help startups raise capital quickly and cheaply. The platform also helps retail investors make investments in high-potential start-ups. With the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), people can invest in promising start-ups for as low as $1.</p>
<p>Usually, if companies fail to raise the minimum required capital after starting the investment process, investors lose their money. But Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has introduced a tool to tackle these issues. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has a &ldquo;Fill or Kill&rdquo; mechanism ensuring that all users get their money back if the investment process fails. Besides, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) promises to list only real-world growing companies on the platform to help investors choose profitable investment options.</p>
<p>The value of ORBN, the project&rsquo;s native token, has increased by more than 805% in the first three phases. ORBN tokens were launched at a price of $0.004, which now has reached $0.0362. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is projected to post a growth rate of 6000% during the presale round. According to market analysts, the price of ORBN tokens will reach $0.24 before the presale ends.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol &nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year has been extremely unpredictable for crypto enthusiasts. While the overall crypto market crashed in the first half of 2022, the second half witnessed a mix of both positive and negative events. On one hand, the long-standing crypto project, FTX, became bankrupt, making tens of thousands of investors lose millions. While on the other hand, a new entrant, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), has registered historical growth during its presale round, which is in its third phase. Due to its market viability and unique business roadmap, the value of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has recorded a growth of 805% in the first two phases of its presale.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Binance (BNB) Takes A Dip Amid Security Questions</p>
<p>After the US Securities and Exchange Commission labeled FTT, the token of the FTX exchange, as a security in a recent filing in a New York court, several concerns have emerged about Binance&rsquo;s BNB. In its filing, the SEC noted that FTT has a buy-and-burn program similar to a stock buyback, and they both result in increasing the asset&rsquo;s value. Interestingly, Binance also has a similar program called BNB Burn, and investors wonder what will happen to their investments if the SEC initiates legal actions against Binance (BNB) as well.</p>
<p>Although Binance CEO, Changpeng Zhao, has asserted that BNB is more than just a security, he has not been able to convince investors who are considering leaving the project. Consequently, Binance (BNB) has witnessed a sharp decline of 17% in its value in the last few weeks. Currently, Binance (BNB) is being traded at $244.79, which is 65% below its all-time high of $690.93. However, Binance (BNB) continues to assure its users that the platform is healthy.</p>
<p>Binance (BNB), the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the world, is used for trading and paying fees on the Binance exchange. Binance (BNB), launched in 2017, can also be exchanged or traded for other cryptocurrencies, like Ethereum, Bitcoin, and more.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Raises Millions In Just A Few Weeks</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is the leading blockchain-based investment platform that mints equity-backed fractional NFTs to help startups raise capital quickly and cheaply. The platform also helps retail investors make investments in high-potential start-ups. With the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), people can invest in promising start-ups for as low as $1.</p>
<p>Usually, if companies fail to raise the minimum required capital after starting the investment process, investors lose their money. But Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has introduced a tool to tackle these issues. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) has a &ldquo;Fill or Kill&rdquo; mechanism ensuring that all users get their money back if the investment process fails. Besides, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) promises to list only real-world growing companies on the platform to help investors choose profitable investment options.</p>
<p>The value of ORBN, the project&rsquo;s native token, has increased by more than 805% in the first three phases. ORBN tokens were launched at a price of $0.004, which now has reached $0.0362. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is projected to post a growth rate of 6000% during the presale round. According to market analysts, the price of ORBN tokens will reach $0.24 before the presale ends.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol &nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Former chairman of S Korean crypto exchange Bithumb not guilty]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/former-chairman-of-s-korean-crypto-exchange-bithumb-not-guilty</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bithumb.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bithumb.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bithumb.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/former-chairman-of-s-korean-crypto-exchange-bithumb-not-guilty</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Lee Jung-Hoon, the former chairman of South Korea's Bithumb exchange, was declared not guilty of fraud over the failed acquisition of the exchange according to a report by the Korea Economic Daily.&nbsp;</p>
Accusation
<p>In October 2018, Lee was accused of violating the Act on the Aggravated Punishment of Specific Economic Crimes while negotiating with the founder of the cosmetic surgery company BK Group, Kim Byung-gun, for the acquisition of Bithumb.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lee accepted a $70 million "contract fee" on the condition that Bithumb would list the Bithumb Coin (BXA) and use the token sale to pay for the acquisition. However, the BXA token was never listed and the acquisition fell through.&nbsp;</p>
Acquisition failure not due to investors
<p>South Korean investigators determined that the failure of the acquisition was not due to Kim or other investors, but rather due to fraudulent activity.</p>
<p>Bithumb stated that the company is run under a "professional management system," and that Lee Jung-Hoon "has no involvement in Bithumb's management." The news of Lee's acquittal follows the suicide of Park Mo, the Vice President of Vidente, who is Bithumb's largest shareholder.</p>
No show in Terra investigation
<p>In October of last year, Lee Jung-Hoon failed to appear as a witness at a hearing of the Korean National Assembly's Political Affairs Committee after being summoned. He was one of six witnesses called to testify in the ongoing investigation into the collapse of Terra, which had a $40 billion valuation. Lee cited panic disorder and claimed he was no longer involved in the management of Bithumb as a reason for not appearing.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lee Jung-Hoon, the former chairman of South Korea's Bithumb exchange, was declared not guilty of fraud over the failed acquisition of the exchange according to a report by the Korea Economic Daily.&nbsp;</p>
Accusation
<p>In October 2018, Lee was accused of violating the Act on the Aggravated Punishment of Specific Economic Crimes while negotiating with the founder of the cosmetic surgery company BK Group, Kim Byung-gun, for the acquisition of Bithumb.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lee accepted a $70 million "contract fee" on the condition that Bithumb would list the Bithumb Coin (BXA) and use the token sale to pay for the acquisition. However, the BXA token was never listed and the acquisition fell through.&nbsp;</p>
Acquisition failure not due to investors
<p>South Korean investigators determined that the failure of the acquisition was not due to Kim or other investors, but rather due to fraudulent activity.</p>
<p>Bithumb stated that the company is run under a "professional management system," and that Lee Jung-Hoon "has no involvement in Bithumb's management." The news of Lee's acquittal follows the suicide of Park Mo, the Vice President of Vidente, who is Bithumb's largest shareholder.</p>
No show in Terra investigation
<p>In October of last year, Lee Jung-Hoon failed to appear as a witness at a hearing of the Korean National Assembly's Political Affairs Committee after being summoned. He was one of six witnesses called to testify in the ongoing investigation into the collapse of Terra, which had a $40 billion valuation. Lee cited panic disorder and claimed he was no longer involved in the management of Bithumb as a reason for not appearing.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  16789 Paid - 4 January 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-16789-paid-4-january-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-3-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-3-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-3-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-16789-paid-4-january-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Seeking More Upside:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 4 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent upside progress early in the Asian session as the pair traded above the 16700 area after trading as high as the 16789.99 area, a level that represents the 61.8% retracement of the depreciating range from 17070.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; Additional retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 16887.47 and 16903.63 areas.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 16693.51 area during the recent move higher, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the same depreciating range.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and it was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16738.04 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16664.93.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Seeking More Upside:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 4 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent upside progress early in the Asian session as the pair traded above the 16700 area after trading as high as the 16789.99 area, a level that represents the 61.8% retracement of the depreciating range from 17070.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; Additional retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 16887.47 and 16903.63 areas.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 16693.51 area during the recent move higher, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the same depreciating range.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and it was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16738.04 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16664.93.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Big Short investor expects Fed stimulus in 2023 - Bitcoin anyone?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/big-short-investor-expects-fed-stimulus-in-2023-bitcoin-anyone</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/burr-3.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/burr-3.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/burr-3.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/big-short-investor-expects-fed-stimulus-in-2023-bitcoin-anyone</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Burry, an investor who was featured in the book and movie "The Big Short," has said that the US will have a recession and more inflation in 2023. He thinks that inflation is currently very high, but it will not remain so.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Inflation peaked. But it is not the last peak of this cycle. We are likely to see CPI lower, possibly negative in 2H 2023, and the US in recession by any definition. Fed will cut and government will stimulate. And we will have another inflation spike. It's not hard.</p>
&mdash; Cassandra B.C. (@michaeljburry) January 2, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>He believes that the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which measures how much prices have gone up, could be expected to go down a lot in the new year and might even go negative in the second half of 2023, causing a recession.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In June, inflation in the US was 9.1%, which is the highest it has been in 40 years. In November, it was still above 7%. These numbers are much higher than the 2% goal set by the Federal Reserve. Because of this, the Federal Reserve increased the base interest rate, which is the rate at which banks can borrow money, from almost 0% to over 4%, with a plan to make it go even higher in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Higher interest rates can help lower inflation by decreasing how much people buy, invest, and work, but they can also make it harder for businesses to make money and slow down the economy, which can lead to a recession and make investment prices go down.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Burry says that in 2023, inflation will go down and the economy will get weaker. He then expects the Federal Reserve to lower interest rates and the government to spend more money to try to make the economy grow, causing inflation to spike yet again.</p>
Opinion
<p>This seesaw process has always happened since central banks were given control over monetary policy. As the Federal Reserve continues to ramp up interest rates it would appear that it is doing so blindly, given that the increases will take many months before they are properly felt in the market.</p>
<p>The problem will be that once inflation starts coming down significantly, it is likely that the economy will already be in a serious recession, and then the Fed will have to start trying to tip the scales in the other direction by unleashing yet another round of quantitative easing.</p>
<p>The up and down seesaw in the economy is worsening as debt increases and fiat purchasing power decreases. This is why Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies were born. Over a long period Bitcoin might just become that inflation hedge, and out of the crypto sector might arrive a decentralised way of transacting that saves us all from the hell of central banks and their fiat currencies.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Burry, an investor who was featured in the book and movie "The Big Short," has said that the US will have a recession and more inflation in 2023. He thinks that inflation is currently very high, but it will not remain so.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Inflation peaked. But it is not the last peak of this cycle. We are likely to see CPI lower, possibly negative in 2H 2023, and the US in recession by any definition. Fed will cut and government will stimulate. And we will have another inflation spike. It's not hard.</p>
&mdash; Cassandra B.C. (@michaeljburry) January 2, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>He believes that the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which measures how much prices have gone up, could be expected to go down a lot in the new year and might even go negative in the second half of 2023, causing a recession.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In June, inflation in the US was 9.1%, which is the highest it has been in 40 years. In November, it was still above 7%. These numbers are much higher than the 2% goal set by the Federal Reserve. Because of this, the Federal Reserve increased the base interest rate, which is the rate at which banks can borrow money, from almost 0% to over 4%, with a plan to make it go even higher in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Higher interest rates can help lower inflation by decreasing how much people buy, invest, and work, but they can also make it harder for businesses to make money and slow down the economy, which can lead to a recession and make investment prices go down.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Burry says that in 2023, inflation will go down and the economy will get weaker. He then expects the Federal Reserve to lower interest rates and the government to spend more money to try to make the economy grow, causing inflation to spike yet again.</p>
Opinion
<p>This seesaw process has always happened since central banks were given control over monetary policy. As the Federal Reserve continues to ramp up interest rates it would appear that it is doing so blindly, given that the increases will take many months before they are properly felt in the market.</p>
<p>The problem will be that once inflation starts coming down significantly, it is likely that the economy will already be in a serious recession, and then the Fed will have to start trying to tip the scales in the other direction by unleashing yet another round of quantitative easing.</p>
<p>The up and down seesaw in the economy is worsening as debt increases and fiat purchasing power decreases. This is why Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies were born. Over a long period Bitcoin might just become that inflation hedge, and out of the crypto sector might arrive a decentralised way of transacting that saves us all from the hell of central banks and their fiat currencies.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto And Blockchain Future Holds Promise: WEF]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-and-blockchain-future-holds-promise-wef</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wef-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wef-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wef-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-and-blockchain-future-holds-promise-wef</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The World Economic Forum (WEF) has said that crypto and blockchain technology will continue to be an integral component of the modern economy.&nbsp;</p>
WEF Talks Crypto &lsquo;Ice Age&rsquo;
<p>On Monday, the WEF published a blog detailing what the future holds for the crypto industry. The blog covered points about how the industry has already established itself as a key player in the financial sector and summed up how the industry will be moving forward in light of the catastrophic events of 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The blog detailed how 2022 turned out to be way worse than a mere &ldquo;crypto winter&rdquo; for most investors, as not one but three major catastrophic crashes wiped out nearly $2 trillion worth of assets from the speculative market. The international organization acknowledged that the year had proven right most policymakers, who had repeatedly issued warnings about the high-risk nature of the industry. WEF opined that the end of 2022 probably marked the end of crypto speculation due to the multiple hits the industry took this year.</p>
<p>An excerpt from the blog reads,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;To the diehard crypto utopians (and some crypto-anarchists), 2022 was not just another &ldquo;crypto winter,&rdquo; but more of an ice age. Along with a broad loss of confidence, economic value and a market littered with the tombstones of failed firms and projects, perhaps the era of crypto speculation will remain frozen in ice.&rdquo;</p>

Web2 vs. Web3
<p>The WEF also talked about the future of crypto while comparing it with the internet and the dot-com bubble burst of the early 2000s. That incident famously wiped out more speculative companies and pushed a more stable and durable version of the internet to the forefront. Similarly, the organization believes that the struggles of 2022 could open gates for &ldquo;responsible, always-on internet finance,&rdquo; claiming that countries that enforce responsible regulation of the sector will emerge as future leaders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>WEF wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Just as it took the dot-com bubble bursting in the early 2000s to hand over the future of the internet to more durable companies, business models, and use cases, perhaps 2022 marks a handover of crypto technology and blockchain infrastructure to steadier hands.&rdquo;</p>

Staying Power Of Blockchain
<p>The blog also pointed out the positives of the large-scale institutional adoption of crypto and blockchain technology that happened in 2022. It mentioned, by name, JPMorgan and the aggressively pro-crypto business strategy the financial giant adopted this year. According to the organization, crypto technology will become an inevitable part of innovation and business models, similar to cybersecurity and digital transformation mandates for major companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>WEF wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Indeed, as a test of the staying power of digital assets and blockchains at the core of financial services (and other areas of the global economy), watch what the big banks and mature financial services firms do, not what they say.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The World Economic Forum (WEF) has said that crypto and blockchain technology will continue to be an integral component of the modern economy.&nbsp;</p>
WEF Talks Crypto &lsquo;Ice Age&rsquo;
<p>On Monday, the WEF published a blog detailing what the future holds for the crypto industry. The blog covered points about how the industry has already established itself as a key player in the financial sector and summed up how the industry will be moving forward in light of the catastrophic events of 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The blog detailed how 2022 turned out to be way worse than a mere &ldquo;crypto winter&rdquo; for most investors, as not one but three major catastrophic crashes wiped out nearly $2 trillion worth of assets from the speculative market. The international organization acknowledged that the year had proven right most policymakers, who had repeatedly issued warnings about the high-risk nature of the industry. WEF opined that the end of 2022 probably marked the end of crypto speculation due to the multiple hits the industry took this year.</p>
<p>An excerpt from the blog reads,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;To the diehard crypto utopians (and some crypto-anarchists), 2022 was not just another &ldquo;crypto winter,&rdquo; but more of an ice age. Along with a broad loss of confidence, economic value and a market littered with the tombstones of failed firms and projects, perhaps the era of crypto speculation will remain frozen in ice.&rdquo;</p>

Web2 vs. Web3
<p>The WEF also talked about the future of crypto while comparing it with the internet and the dot-com bubble burst of the early 2000s. That incident famously wiped out more speculative companies and pushed a more stable and durable version of the internet to the forefront. Similarly, the organization believes that the struggles of 2022 could open gates for &ldquo;responsible, always-on internet finance,&rdquo; claiming that countries that enforce responsible regulation of the sector will emerge as future leaders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>WEF wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Just as it took the dot-com bubble bursting in the early 2000s to hand over the future of the internet to more durable companies, business models, and use cases, perhaps 2022 marks a handover of crypto technology and blockchain infrastructure to steadier hands.&rdquo;</p>

Staying Power Of Blockchain
<p>The blog also pointed out the positives of the large-scale institutional adoption of crypto and blockchain technology that happened in 2022. It mentioned, by name, JPMorgan and the aggressively pro-crypto business strategy the financial giant adopted this year. According to the organization, crypto technology will become an inevitable part of innovation and business models, similar to cybersecurity and digital transformation mandates for major companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>WEF wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Indeed, as a test of the staying power of digital assets and blockchains at the core of financial services (and other areas of the global economy), watch what the big banks and mature financial services firms do, not what they say.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Tax Break For Foreigners In UK, Crypto Daily TV 3/1/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-tax-break-for-foreigners-in-uk-crypto-daily-tv-3-1-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-uk.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-uk.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-uk.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-tax-break-for-foreigners-in-uk-crypto-daily-tv-3-1-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>UK enforces crypto tax break for foreigners</p>
<p>The U.K. is enforcing a tax exemption for foreign investors purchasing crypto through local investment managers or brokers. The tax break, announced in December, is a part of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak&rsquo;s plans to turn the U.K. into a crypto hub.</p>
<p>Bitcoin assists in Musk's wealth plunge.</p>
<p>Elon Musk's wealth plunged to $137 billion due to the performance of Tesla shares, which saw another 11% drop last week before 2022 ended. Aside from the plummeting Tesla shares, the electric vehicle maker also lost a significant amount due to its Bitcoin holding, around $180 million.</p>
<p>FTX Japan to allow customers to withdraw funds.</p>
<p>FTX Japan customers will be able to withdraw their funds as of mid-February, the subsidiary of FTX Trading said in a blog post, making them some of the first customers of the collapsed crypto exchange to get their money back.</p>
BTC/USD gained 0.7% in the last session.
<p>Bitcoin gained 0.7% against the Dollar in the last session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 16474.3333 and resistance at 16728.3333.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD skyrocketed 1.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 1.4% in the last session. According to the Stochastic-RSI, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 1186.291 and resistance at 1211.211.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 3.7% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 3.7% in the last session. According to the CCI, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 0.3338 and resistance at 0.3423.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded 6.0% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair skyrocketed 6.0% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal. Support is at 68.0833 and resistance at 72.8433.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity. The US 3-Month Bill Auction will be released at 16:30 GMT, the US 6-Month Bill Auction at 16:30 GMT, and Germany's Unemployment Change at 08:55 GMT.</p>
<p>US 6-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bills auctioned by US Department of Treasury. Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive.</p>
<p>DE Unemployment Change</p>
<p>The Unemployment Change is a measure of the absolute change in the number of unemployed people using seasonally adjusted data. A rise in this indicator has negative implications for consumer spending.</p>
<p>DE Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market. Germany's Unemployment Rate will be released at 08:55 GMT, Japan's Foreign Bond Investment at 23:50 GMT, Japan's Foreign Investment in Japan Stocks at 23:50 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Foreign Bond Investment</p>
<p>The Foreign Bond Investment refers to bonds issued in a domestic market by a foreign entity in the domestic market&rsquo;s currency.</p>
<p>JP Foreign Investment in Japanese Stocks</p>
<p>Securities investment referrers to bonds issued in a domestic market by a foreign entity in the domestic market&rsquo;s currency.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>UK enforces crypto tax break for foreigners</p>
<p>The U.K. is enforcing a tax exemption for foreign investors purchasing crypto through local investment managers or brokers. The tax break, announced in December, is a part of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak&rsquo;s plans to turn the U.K. into a crypto hub.</p>
<p>Bitcoin assists in Musk's wealth plunge.</p>
<p>Elon Musk's wealth plunged to $137 billion due to the performance of Tesla shares, which saw another 11% drop last week before 2022 ended. Aside from the plummeting Tesla shares, the electric vehicle maker also lost a significant amount due to its Bitcoin holding, around $180 million.</p>
<p>FTX Japan to allow customers to withdraw funds.</p>
<p>FTX Japan customers will be able to withdraw their funds as of mid-February, the subsidiary of FTX Trading said in a blog post, making them some of the first customers of the collapsed crypto exchange to get their money back.</p>
BTC/USD gained 0.7% in the last session.
<p>Bitcoin gained 0.7% against the Dollar in the last session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 16474.3333 and resistance at 16728.3333.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD skyrocketed 1.4% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 1.4% in the last session. According to the Stochastic-RSI, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 1186.291 and resistance at 1211.211.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 3.7% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 3.7% in the last session. According to the CCI, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 0.3338 and resistance at 0.3423.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded 6.0% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair skyrocketed 6.0% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal. Support is at 68.0833 and resistance at 72.8433.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity. The US 3-Month Bill Auction will be released at 16:30 GMT, the US 6-Month Bill Auction at 16:30 GMT, and Germany's Unemployment Change at 08:55 GMT.</p>
<p>US 6-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bills auctioned by US Department of Treasury. Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive.</p>
<p>DE Unemployment Change</p>
<p>The Unemployment Change is a measure of the absolute change in the number of unemployed people using seasonally adjusted data. A rise in this indicator has negative implications for consumer spending.</p>
<p>DE Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market. Germany's Unemployment Rate will be released at 08:55 GMT, Japan's Foreign Bond Investment at 23:50 GMT, Japan's Foreign Investment in Japan Stocks at 23:50 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Foreign Bond Investment</p>
<p>The Foreign Bond Investment refers to bonds issued in a domestic market by a foreign entity in the domestic market&rsquo;s currency.</p>
<p>JP Foreign Investment in Japanese Stocks</p>
<p>Securities investment referrers to bonds issued in a domestic market by a foreign entity in the domestic market&rsquo;s currency.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cameron Winklevoss Accuses Genesis Of Negotiating In Bad Faith]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/cameron-winklevoss-accuses-genesis-ceo-of-negotiating-in-bad-faith</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/cameron-winklevoss-accuses-genesis-ceo-of-negotiating-in-bad-faith</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Co-founder of crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co, Cameron Winklevoss, has accused the CEO of Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert, of negotiating in bad faith.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The comments were made in an open letter over funds to the tune of $900 million owed to Gemini as part of the Gemini Earn Program.&nbsp;</p>
Winklevoss Calls Out Silbert&nbsp;
<p>Crypto broker Genesis has been put in a spot of bother since the collapse of FTX. The company&rsquo;s lending arm had to halt customer withdrawals and owes members of Gemini Earn around $900 million. Now, Cameron Winklevoss, co-founder of Gemini, has accused Genesis and the Digital Currency Group of bad faith and stall tactics, asking him to resolve the $900 million worth of disputed assets by the 8th of January, 2023. Winklevoss wrote the letter after claiming to have been trying to reach a consensus with Silbert for weeks.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Every time we ask you for tangible engagement, you hide behind lawyers, investment bankers, and process.&rdquo;</p>

The Open Letter&nbsp;
<p>Seemingly tired of getting nowhere, co-founder of Gemini, Cameron Winklevoss, penned an open letter to the Digital Currency Group founder and CEO, accusing DCG and Silbert of evasive tactics and failing to attempt to resolve the ongoing situation with the funds. Winklevoss stated in the letter that Gemini, on its part, has tried to reach a &ldquo;consensual resolution&rdquo; to the dispute with DCG and Genesis over the funds and their return. However, he alleged that Silbert and his companies have been stalling the entire process.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We appreciate that there are startup costs to any restructuring, and at times things don&rsquo;t go as fast as we would all like. However, it is now becoming clear that you have been engaging in bad faith stall tactics.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also accused Silbert of refusing to &ldquo;get into a room&rdquo; with Gemini management, ironing things out, and refusing to agree to any timeline with the company after weeks of trying.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;After six weeks, your behavior is not only completely unacceptable; it is unconscionable. The idea in your head that you can quietly hide in your ivory tower and that this will all just magically go away, or that this is someone else&rsquo;s problem, is pure fantasy.&rdquo;</p>

Silbert Fires Back&nbsp;
<p>According to the Winklevoss Twins, DCG owes Genesis around $1.67 billion, citing figures shared by Silvert with investors back in November. This figure also included a $575 million loan which was due in May, and a further $1.1 billion promissory note, tied to the collapse of Three Arrows Capital (3AC). Silbert responded to Winklevoss, refuting the framing around the money owed to Genesis by DCG. He further claimed that DCG had sent a recent proposal to both Genesis and Gemini. Silbert Stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;DCG did not borrow $1.675 billion from Genesis. DCG has never missed an interest payment to Genesis and is current on all loans outstanding; next loan maturity is May 2023. DCG delivered a proposal to Genesis and your advisors on the 29th of December and has not received any response.&rdquo;</p>

<p>On his part, Winklevoss asked Silbert to publicly commit to resolving the ongoing deadlock by the 8th of January, 2023. However, he did not elaborate on any potential consequences or future action should Silbert not comply.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;There you go again. Stop trying to pretend that you and DCG are innocent bystanders and had nothing to do with creating this mess. It&rsquo;s completely disingenuous. Will you, or will you not, commit to solving this by the 8th of January in a manner that treats the $1.1 billion promissory note as $1.1 billion?&rdquo;</p>

The Gemini Earn Program&nbsp;
<p>The Gemini Earn Program is a high-yield savings product, offering users an annual return of up to 8% on their crypto deposits, depending on where the assets in question are held. Genesis was Gemini&rsquo;s primary lending partner, and when Genesis suspended loan withdrawals, it led to Gemini halting withdrawals for its Earn program as well. Winklevoss has pegged the amount owed to Gemini Earn Customers at $900 million. Back in November, Silbert tried to reassure investors that DCG did not face any immediate risk following FTX&rsquo;s collapse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Co-founder of crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co, Cameron Winklevoss, has accused the CEO of Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert, of negotiating in bad faith.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The comments were made in an open letter over funds to the tune of $900 million owed to Gemini as part of the Gemini Earn Program.&nbsp;</p>
Winklevoss Calls Out Silbert&nbsp;
<p>Crypto broker Genesis has been put in a spot of bother since the collapse of FTX. The company&rsquo;s lending arm had to halt customer withdrawals and owes members of Gemini Earn around $900 million. Now, Cameron Winklevoss, co-founder of Gemini, has accused Genesis and the Digital Currency Group of bad faith and stall tactics, asking him to resolve the $900 million worth of disputed assets by the 8th of January, 2023. Winklevoss wrote the letter after claiming to have been trying to reach a consensus with Silbert for weeks.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Every time we ask you for tangible engagement, you hide behind lawyers, investment bankers, and process.&rdquo;</p>

The Open Letter&nbsp;
<p>Seemingly tired of getting nowhere, co-founder of Gemini, Cameron Winklevoss, penned an open letter to the Digital Currency Group founder and CEO, accusing DCG and Silbert of evasive tactics and failing to attempt to resolve the ongoing situation with the funds. Winklevoss stated in the letter that Gemini, on its part, has tried to reach a &ldquo;consensual resolution&rdquo; to the dispute with DCG and Genesis over the funds and their return. However, he alleged that Silbert and his companies have been stalling the entire process.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We appreciate that there are startup costs to any restructuring, and at times things don&rsquo;t go as fast as we would all like. However, it is now becoming clear that you have been engaging in bad faith stall tactics.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also accused Silbert of refusing to &ldquo;get into a room&rdquo; with Gemini management, ironing things out, and refusing to agree to any timeline with the company after weeks of trying.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;After six weeks, your behavior is not only completely unacceptable; it is unconscionable. The idea in your head that you can quietly hide in your ivory tower and that this will all just magically go away, or that this is someone else&rsquo;s problem, is pure fantasy.&rdquo;</p>

Silbert Fires Back&nbsp;
<p>According to the Winklevoss Twins, DCG owes Genesis around $1.67 billion, citing figures shared by Silvert with investors back in November. This figure also included a $575 million loan which was due in May, and a further $1.1 billion promissory note, tied to the collapse of Three Arrows Capital (3AC). Silbert responded to Winklevoss, refuting the framing around the money owed to Genesis by DCG. He further claimed that DCG had sent a recent proposal to both Genesis and Gemini. Silbert Stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;DCG did not borrow $1.675 billion from Genesis. DCG has never missed an interest payment to Genesis and is current on all loans outstanding; next loan maturity is May 2023. DCG delivered a proposal to Genesis and your advisors on the 29th of December and has not received any response.&rdquo;</p>

<p>On his part, Winklevoss asked Silbert to publicly commit to resolving the ongoing deadlock by the 8th of January, 2023. However, he did not elaborate on any potential consequences or future action should Silbert not comply.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;There you go again. Stop trying to pretend that you and DCG are innocent bystanders and had nothing to do with creating this mess. It&rsquo;s completely disingenuous. Will you, or will you not, commit to solving this by the 8th of January in a manner that treats the $1.1 billion promissory note as $1.1 billion?&rdquo;</p>

The Gemini Earn Program&nbsp;
<p>The Gemini Earn Program is a high-yield savings product, offering users an annual return of up to 8% on their crypto deposits, depending on where the assets in question are held. Genesis was Gemini&rsquo;s primary lending partner, and when Genesis suspended loan withdrawals, it led to Gemini halting withdrawals for its Earn program as well. Winklevoss has pegged the amount owed to Gemini Earn Customers at $900 million. Back in November, Silbert tried to reassure investors that DCG did not face any immediate risk following FTX&rsquo;s collapse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto CEO Voorhees says we are in a financial revolution]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-ceo-voorhees-says-we-are-in-a-financial-revolution</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voor-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voor-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voor-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-ceo-voorhees-says-we-are-in-a-financial-revolution</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Voorhees, founder and CEO of crypto exchange Shapeshifter, says he cannot call the next bull market with any exactitude, but that it would come in the next 6 months to 3 years.</p>
$40,000 by the Summer?
<p>Erik Voorhees, the CEO and founder of ShapeShift, expressed optimism about the potential recovery of Bitcoin's price during an interview with Bankless on January 2nd. He stated that he "wouldn't be surprised" if Bitcoin reaches "around $40,000" by the summer.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This would be a "great return," Voorhees said, as it would be 2.5 times the current price of $16,666. While he could not pinpoint the exact timing of the next bull run, he estimated it would occur within the next six months to three years. He dismissed the idea that it could take as long as 10 years, stating that if that were the case, it would mean the whole "thing... probably failed."&nbsp;</p>
Crypto reputation
<p>Voorhees noted that the macro environment, interest rates, and monetary conditions will greatly impact the crypto market this year. He also acknowledged that the reputation of crypto among non-industry individuals is "just trash," but added that these same individuals will be "blindsided" when the next rally occurs. Voorhees concluded by stating that, regardless of whether we are in a bull or bear market, we are "in the middle of a revolution right now."</p>
Money needs to be decentralised
<p>The Shapeshift founder has always made it known that he is in the cryptocurrency space to help build and promote freedom from the monopoly that the State has over money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To this end, in the Bankless interview he stated:</p>
<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m here to separate money and State, and every technology, every blockchain, every app, that helps further that, is something that I&rsquo;m going to be supporting.&rdquo;</p>
<p>He added:</p>
<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m here for the principle of decentralising money away from the State.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eric Voorhees, founder and CEO of crypto exchange Shapeshifter, says he cannot call the next bull market with any exactitude, but that it would come in the next 6 months to 3 years.</p>
$40,000 by the Summer?
<p>Erik Voorhees, the CEO and founder of ShapeShift, expressed optimism about the potential recovery of Bitcoin's price during an interview with Bankless on January 2nd. He stated that he "wouldn't be surprised" if Bitcoin reaches "around $40,000" by the summer.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This would be a "great return," Voorhees said, as it would be 2.5 times the current price of $16,666. While he could not pinpoint the exact timing of the next bull run, he estimated it would occur within the next six months to three years. He dismissed the idea that it could take as long as 10 years, stating that if that were the case, it would mean the whole "thing... probably failed."&nbsp;</p>
Crypto reputation
<p>Voorhees noted that the macro environment, interest rates, and monetary conditions will greatly impact the crypto market this year. He also acknowledged that the reputation of crypto among non-industry individuals is "just trash," but added that these same individuals will be "blindsided" when the next rally occurs. Voorhees concluded by stating that, regardless of whether we are in a bull or bear market, we are "in the middle of a revolution right now."</p>
Money needs to be decentralised
<p>The Shapeshift founder has always made it known that he is in the cryptocurrency space to help build and promote freedom from the monopoly that the State has over money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To this end, in the Bankless interview he stated:</p>
<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m here to separate money and State, and every technology, every blockchain, every app, that helps further that, is something that I&rsquo;m going to be supporting.&rdquo;</p>
<p>He added:</p>
<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m here for the principle of decentralising money away from the State.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SushiSwap to Shut Lending Protocol Kashi And Token Launchpad Miso]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/sushiswap-to-shut-lending-protocol-kashi-and-token-launchpad-miso</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sushi-1450-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sushi-1450-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sushi-1450-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/sushiswap-to-shut-lending-protocol-kashi-and-token-launchpad-miso</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>DeFi protocol SushiSwap has announced it would be shutting down its lending protocol, Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The company stated that it had come to its decision due to a number of reasons, including poor execution, poor design choices, and a lack of resources.&nbsp;</p>
A Slew Of Changes&nbsp;
<p>The latest move by SushiSwap comes after the protocol&rsquo;s CEO had proposed new tokenomics for increased liquidity and better decentralization. The new tokenomics model would see the introduction of time-lock tiers for emission-based rewards. It would also introduce a token-burning mechanism and liquidity lock for price support. CEO Jared Grey hopes the new tokenomics will boost liquidity and decentralization on the platform, help strengthen treasury reserves and ensure the continual operation and development of the protocol.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Grey took to Twitter, asking the community for questions and feedback.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am excited to share the vision for @SushiSwap&rsquo;s new token model. I&rsquo;ve posted a brief tl;dr write-up on the Sushi forum &amp; linked the entire proposal. We look forward to your questions &amp; feedback.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Kashi And Miso Shut Down&nbsp;
<p>Now the DeFi protocol has announced that it is shutting down its lending protocol Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso. Elaborating on the rationale behind the move, Matthew Lilley, SushiSwap CTO, stated that Kashi had several issues, including several design flaws, a lack of resources, and considerable losses. However, in the larger picture, the team had to prioritize and improve their most prominent offering, the SushiSwap DEX.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We made the decision to deprecate Kashi (Sushi Lending) and Miso (Sushi Launch Pad). 1. Kashi, for a number of reasons, had a number of design flaws, ran at a loss, and had a lack of resources to dedicate to it. 2. MISO had a lack of resources.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Lilley assured the community that they do plan on launching new staking and launchpad products in the near future to replace the soon-to-be-defunct services as soon as additional liquidity becomes available. However, for now, the team&rsquo;s focus would be on the DEX, which he described as the &ldquo;breadwinner&rdquo; of the company.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have the plan to launch successors of these products in the future once we have the resources to dedicate product teams towards them, but believe that requires focusing entirely on the breadwinner at the time being, which is inarguably the DEX.&rdquo;</p>

An Expected Move&nbsp;
<p>The move to shutter the two platforms did not surprise many, with developers having already announced in mid-December that the Kashi 1.0 interface would no longer support deposits or borrowing. According to the announcement, the original UI would remain online, but the markets would not be updated. It also stated that MISO UI would be accessible indefinitely, but no further support or development would be provided.</p>
SushiSwap&rsquo;s Recent Financial Woes&nbsp;
<p>SushiSwap has made the decision to shutter specific offerings against the backdrop of significant financial stress over the past few months. In an update shared in December, the firm revealed it had only 1.5 years of operating costs in hand, and the situation required immediate attention and action to ensure that the firm had sufficient resources to ensure seamless operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CEO Grey had stated that the company was pursuing a strategy that would see it renegotiate infrastructure contracts and cut back on underperforming and superfluous dependencies. It would also enforce a budget freeze on non-critical personnel and infrastructure as it looks to cut back on expenses. Gray also revealed the company had made a loss of $30 million over the past 12 months.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;In the past 12 months, Sushi has experienced a 30M USD loss in its emissions-based reward strategy to bootstrap liquidity &amp; incentivize LPing; Sushi spends more on emissions than swap volume generated.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi protocol SushiSwap has announced it would be shutting down its lending protocol, Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The company stated that it had come to its decision due to a number of reasons, including poor execution, poor design choices, and a lack of resources.&nbsp;</p>
A Slew Of Changes&nbsp;
<p>The latest move by SushiSwap comes after the protocol&rsquo;s CEO had proposed new tokenomics for increased liquidity and better decentralization. The new tokenomics model would see the introduction of time-lock tiers for emission-based rewards. It would also introduce a token-burning mechanism and liquidity lock for price support. CEO Jared Grey hopes the new tokenomics will boost liquidity and decentralization on the platform, help strengthen treasury reserves and ensure the continual operation and development of the protocol.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Grey took to Twitter, asking the community for questions and feedback.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am excited to share the vision for @SushiSwap&rsquo;s new token model. I&rsquo;ve posted a brief tl;dr write-up on the Sushi forum &amp; linked the entire proposal. We look forward to your questions &amp; feedback.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Kashi And Miso Shut Down&nbsp;
<p>Now the DeFi protocol has announced that it is shutting down its lending protocol Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso. Elaborating on the rationale behind the move, Matthew Lilley, SushiSwap CTO, stated that Kashi had several issues, including several design flaws, a lack of resources, and considerable losses. However, in the larger picture, the team had to prioritize and improve their most prominent offering, the SushiSwap DEX.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We made the decision to deprecate Kashi (Sushi Lending) and Miso (Sushi Launch Pad). 1. Kashi, for a number of reasons, had a number of design flaws, ran at a loss, and had a lack of resources to dedicate to it. 2. MISO had a lack of resources.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Lilley assured the community that they do plan on launching new staking and launchpad products in the near future to replace the soon-to-be-defunct services as soon as additional liquidity becomes available. However, for now, the team&rsquo;s focus would be on the DEX, which he described as the &ldquo;breadwinner&rdquo; of the company.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have the plan to launch successors of these products in the future once we have the resources to dedicate product teams towards them, but believe that requires focusing entirely on the breadwinner at the time being, which is inarguably the DEX.&rdquo;</p>

An Expected Move&nbsp;
<p>The move to shutter the two platforms did not surprise many, with developers having already announced in mid-December that the Kashi 1.0 interface would no longer support deposits or borrowing. According to the announcement, the original UI would remain online, but the markets would not be updated. It also stated that MISO UI would be accessible indefinitely, but no further support or development would be provided.</p>
SushiSwap&rsquo;s Recent Financial Woes&nbsp;
<p>SushiSwap has made the decision to shutter specific offerings against the backdrop of significant financial stress over the past few months. In an update shared in December, the firm revealed it had only 1.5 years of operating costs in hand, and the situation required immediate attention and action to ensure that the firm had sufficient resources to ensure seamless operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CEO Grey had stated that the company was pursuing a strategy that would see it renegotiate infrastructure contracts and cut back on underperforming and superfluous dependencies. It would also enforce a budget freeze on non-critical personnel and infrastructure as it looks to cut back on expenses. Gray also revealed the company had made a loss of $30 million over the past 12 months.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;In the past 12 months, Sushi has experienced a 30M USD loss in its emissions-based reward strategy to bootstrap liquidity &amp; incentivize LPing; Sushi spends more on emissions than swap volume generated.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[UK Enforces Crypto Tax Exemption for Foreign Investors]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/uk-enforces-crypto-tax-exemption-for-foreign-investors</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uk-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uk-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uk-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/uk-enforces-crypto-tax-exemption-for-foreign-investors</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In its latest effort to become a global cryptocurrency hub, the United Kingdom has introduced a tax exemption for non-residents and foreign investors. The exemption applies when users purchase digital assets through local investment managers or brokers. </p>
<p>As part of newly elected Prime Minister, Rishi Sunak&rsquo;s, efforts to make the U.K. a global cryptocurrency hub, a new crypto tax break for non-residents and foreign investors came into effect on January 1, 2023. The news was first reported by CoinDesk, which said that the U.K. government&rsquo;s tax arm, the HM Revenue, and Customs, said in an email:</p>

<p>This exemption is an important factor in attracting global investors, meaning foreign investors won&rsquo;t be brought into U.K. tax simply by appointing U.K.-based investment managers.</p>

<p>It continued to say:</p>

<p>To build upon the U.K.&rsquo;s position as an investment management hub, this exemption has been extended to include crypto assets, so that funds which include them aren&rsquo;t put off from appointing U.K. managers.</p>

<p>The United Kingdom already has a tax guide in place for resident cryptocurrency traders and in July, the HM Revenue and Customs issued a consultation to obtain the views of investors and professionals on how the country should go about taxing decentralized finance.</p>
Bank of England Says Crypto is Too Dangerous Not to Regulate
<p>The Bank of England recently made statements regarding the danger of cryptocurrencies and the absolute need to regulate the industry. The deputy governor of the BoE warned that crypto trading is simply &ldquo;too dangerous&rdquo; to remain unregulated and added that it could pose &ldquo;a systemic problem&rdquo; should action not be taken. The deputy governor added that the BoE might soon regulate the industry in an attempt to protect investors against the danger of crypto trading, as well as the wider financial system against the fallout associated with crypto. The BoE&rsquo;s stance is that retail investors should be able to safely speculate on crypto, as they do in traditional markets.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In its latest effort to become a global cryptocurrency hub, the United Kingdom has introduced a tax exemption for non-residents and foreign investors. The exemption applies when users purchase digital assets through local investment managers or brokers. </p>
<p>As part of newly elected Prime Minister, Rishi Sunak&rsquo;s, efforts to make the U.K. a global cryptocurrency hub, a new crypto tax break for non-residents and foreign investors came into effect on January 1, 2023. The news was first reported by CoinDesk, which said that the U.K. government&rsquo;s tax arm, the HM Revenue, and Customs, said in an email:</p>

<p>This exemption is an important factor in attracting global investors, meaning foreign investors won&rsquo;t be brought into U.K. tax simply by appointing U.K.-based investment managers.</p>

<p>It continued to say:</p>

<p>To build upon the U.K.&rsquo;s position as an investment management hub, this exemption has been extended to include crypto assets, so that funds which include them aren&rsquo;t put off from appointing U.K. managers.</p>

<p>The United Kingdom already has a tax guide in place for resident cryptocurrency traders and in July, the HM Revenue and Customs issued a consultation to obtain the views of investors and professionals on how the country should go about taxing decentralized finance.</p>
Bank of England Says Crypto is Too Dangerous Not to Regulate
<p>The Bank of England recently made statements regarding the danger of cryptocurrencies and the absolute need to regulate the industry. The deputy governor of the BoE warned that crypto trading is simply &ldquo;too dangerous&rdquo; to remain unregulated and added that it could pose &ldquo;a systemic problem&rdquo; should action not be taken. The deputy governor added that the BoE might soon regulate the industry in an attempt to protect investors against the danger of crypto trading, as well as the wider financial system against the fallout associated with crypto. The BoE&rsquo;s stance is that retail investors should be able to safely speculate on crypto, as they do in traditional markets.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance enters S Korean market - acquires major crypto exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/binance-enters-s-korean-market-acquires-major-crypto-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gop.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gop.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gop.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 18:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/binance-enters-s-korean-market-acquires-major-crypto-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Binance is said to be wrapping up the acquisition of Gopax, one of the top five South Korean cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
Final discussions underway
<p>Binance has reportedly completed due diligence for the acquisition of Gopax and is in the process of finalising the deal. According to the South Korean crypto news platform Decenter, the announcement of the acquisition was originally planned for around Christmas of last year, but final discussions on the value of the stake are still underway.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is known that Binance will be purchasing a 41.2% stake in Gopax from CEO Lee Jun-haeng, the largest shareholder, but will maintain the current management structure for the continuance of stable operations.</p>
<p>Gopax is one of the five biggest exchanges in South Korea, and with Binance behind it, it could challenge the dominance of the number one exchange Upbit.&nbsp;</p>
Upbit faces new stiff competition
<p>Up till now, Binance has not been able to enter the Korean market directly due to the regulatory barriers in place. The acquisition of Gopax, which has Won-denominated settlement, would make things a lot easier for Binance.</p>
<p>Upbit&rsquo;s 80% share of the South Korean crypto market has been pretty much unrivalled up to this point, but with Binance entering the space things would likely be shaken up quite a bit.</p>
<p>Binance lists 350 cryptocurrencies, and should most of these be added to Gopax then it would double the offering that Upbit is currently providing.</p>
<p>According to the Decenter article, another huge plus for Binance would be the entry, not only into the South Korean market, but also into the entire East Asian market.</p>
All still up in the air
<p>However, all this is just conjecture at the moment, given that Binance and Gopax have still not signed the deal. Also, another potential issue could be the South Korean regulatory authority&rsquo;s seal on the deal.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance has gone through some tough times recently after its auditing company Mazars distanced itself from the Binance proof-of-reserves audit, and a huge amount of FUD was experienced from those in and outside of the cryptocurrency sector who believe that Binance still has some way to go in order to display the necessary transparence and trust needed by such a huge player in the space.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance is said to be wrapping up the acquisition of Gopax, one of the top five South Korean cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
Final discussions underway
<p>Binance has reportedly completed due diligence for the acquisition of Gopax and is in the process of finalising the deal. According to the South Korean crypto news platform Decenter, the announcement of the acquisition was originally planned for around Christmas of last year, but final discussions on the value of the stake are still underway.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is known that Binance will be purchasing a 41.2% stake in Gopax from CEO Lee Jun-haeng, the largest shareholder, but will maintain the current management structure for the continuance of stable operations.</p>
<p>Gopax is one of the five biggest exchanges in South Korea, and with Binance behind it, it could challenge the dominance of the number one exchange Upbit.&nbsp;</p>
Upbit faces new stiff competition
<p>Up till now, Binance has not been able to enter the Korean market directly due to the regulatory barriers in place. The acquisition of Gopax, which has Won-denominated settlement, would make things a lot easier for Binance.</p>
<p>Upbit&rsquo;s 80% share of the South Korean crypto market has been pretty much unrivalled up to this point, but with Binance entering the space things would likely be shaken up quite a bit.</p>
<p>Binance lists 350 cryptocurrencies, and should most of these be added to Gopax then it would double the offering that Upbit is currently providing.</p>
<p>According to the Decenter article, another huge plus for Binance would be the entry, not only into the South Korean market, but also into the entire East Asian market.</p>
All still up in the air
<p>However, all this is just conjecture at the moment, given that Binance and Gopax have still not signed the deal. Also, another potential issue could be the South Korean regulatory authority&rsquo;s seal on the deal.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance has gone through some tough times recently after its auditing company Mazars distanced itself from the Binance proof-of-reserves audit, and a huge amount of FUD was experienced from those in and outside of the cryptocurrency sector who believe that Binance still has some way to go in order to display the necessary transparence and trust needed by such a huge player in the space.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  16780 Resistance Tested - 3 January 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-16780-resistance-tested-3-january-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-2-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-2-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-2-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-16780-resistance-tested-3-january-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Tests 16780 Resistance:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 3 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) worked to extend recent upside progress early in the Asian session as the pair climbed as high as the 16761.92 level, representing a test of the 61.8% retracement of the depreciating range from 17060.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 16693.51 area during the move higher, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and it was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16672.81 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16672.54.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Tests 16780 Resistance:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 3 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) worked to extend recent upside progress early in the Asian session as the pair climbed as high as the 16761.92 level, representing a test of the 61.8% retracement of the depreciating range from 17060.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 16693.51 area during the move higher, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and it was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16672.81 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16672.54.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Australia Becomes Crypto ATM Hub, Overtakes El Salvador]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/australia-becomes-crypto-atm-hub-overtakes-el-salvador</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/atm-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/atm-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/atm-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/australia-becomes-crypto-atm-hub-overtakes-el-salvador</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Australia has overtaken El Salvador to become the fourth-largest ATM hub. Australia recorded a total of 216 crypto ATM installations going into 2023. </p>
<p>El Salvador, the first country in the world to adopt Bitcoin as a legal tender, had dropped from its position as the fourth-largest crypto ATM hub after Australia stepped up its installation game. As part of El Salvador&rsquo;s campaign to make Bitcoin legal tender, the country&rsquo;s president decided to install over 200 crypto ATMs across the country. At the time of this move, El Salvador became the third-largest ATM hub, after the United States and Canada, put was soon overtaken by Spain and Australia in 2022. In October 2022, Spain was reported as being the third-largest crypto ATM hub after it installed 215 ATMs.</p>
<p>Australia however deployed 99 crypto ATMs in the last three months of 2022, according to data by Coin ATM Radar &ndash; an internet analytics company that keeps track of the total number of cryptocurrency ATMs all over the world. While the United States continues to lead the charge when it comes to ATMs, Poland has also taken over El Salvador in terms of the number of crypto ATMs, having 222 of their own according to reports by Cryptopolitan. Canada and Spain remain in second and third place respectively.</p>
Australia Keeps Up with Installations Despite Stricter Incoming Regulations
<p>The country has taken an active effort to improve its regulation of crypto services with Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese confirming this. The government down under is also set to publish a consultation paper in early 2023 to determine which digital assets will be subject to legal regulation. This proposed regulation will involve a range of activities, from the registration and licensing of crypto service providers to the implementation of AML and counter-terrorism financing measures.</p>
<p>As part of its focus on cryptocurrencies, the Australian Federal Police recently established a new crypto unit to focus on monitoring cryptocurrency-related transactions and has been set up with the goal of targeting money laundering as more criminals seek to bypass the financial system.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Australia has overtaken El Salvador to become the fourth-largest ATM hub. Australia recorded a total of 216 crypto ATM installations going into 2023. </p>
<p>El Salvador, the first country in the world to adopt Bitcoin as a legal tender, had dropped from its position as the fourth-largest crypto ATM hub after Australia stepped up its installation game. As part of El Salvador&rsquo;s campaign to make Bitcoin legal tender, the country&rsquo;s president decided to install over 200 crypto ATMs across the country. At the time of this move, El Salvador became the third-largest ATM hub, after the United States and Canada, put was soon overtaken by Spain and Australia in 2022. In October 2022, Spain was reported as being the third-largest crypto ATM hub after it installed 215 ATMs.</p>
<p>Australia however deployed 99 crypto ATMs in the last three months of 2022, according to data by Coin ATM Radar &ndash; an internet analytics company that keeps track of the total number of cryptocurrency ATMs all over the world. While the United States continues to lead the charge when it comes to ATMs, Poland has also taken over El Salvador in terms of the number of crypto ATMs, having 222 of their own according to reports by Cryptopolitan. Canada and Spain remain in second and third place respectively.</p>
Australia Keeps Up with Installations Despite Stricter Incoming Regulations
<p>The country has taken an active effort to improve its regulation of crypto services with Australian Prime Minister Anthony Albanese confirming this. The government down under is also set to publish a consultation paper in early 2023 to determine which digital assets will be subject to legal regulation. This proposed regulation will involve a range of activities, from the registration and licensing of crypto service providers to the implementation of AML and counter-terrorism financing measures.</p>
<p>As part of its focus on cryptocurrencies, the Australian Federal Police recently established a new crypto unit to focus on monitoring cryptocurrency-related transactions and has been set up with the goal of targeting money laundering as more criminals seek to bypass the financial system.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC Developer Loses 200 BTCs In Hack]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/btc-developer-loses-200-btcs-in-hack</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lost-bitcoin-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lost-bitcoin-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lost-bitcoin-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/btc-developer-loses-200-btcs-in-hack</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>One of the core developers of Bitcoin, Luke Dashjr, has claimed that he lost almost his entire Bitcoin holding on December 31.</p>
PGP Keys Compromised
<p>Bitcoin core developer Luke Dashjr revealed that he lost over 200 BTCs when his wallet was compromised just before the new year. Dashjr addressed the community via a Twitter post, stating that a PGP key compromise resulted in the loss of his funds. He stated that the alleged hackers had somehow gained control of his Pretty Good Privacy (PGP) key and accessed his wallet. The PGP key system is a common security method with encrypted information hidden behind two private keys.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Dashjr tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;PSA: My server was accessed this morning by an unknown person. Full analysis in progress, but take extra care that you PGP-verified any downloads.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Dashjr also tweeted a wallet address to which some of the stolen Bitcoin had been sent. Even though he did not disclose the total amount stolen, the wallet address he reported has received four transactions between the hours of 2:08 and 2:16 pm UTC on Dec. 31. These transaction amounts totaled 216.93 BTC, which is worth $3.6 million at current prices.</p>
Twitter And Reddit Sleuths At Work
<p>When a Twitter user asked what the connection with PGP was, Dashjr responded,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;That's how you might verify that your Bitcoin Knots or Core download isn't infested with malware. So to be clear: DO NOT DOWNLOAD BITCOIN KNOTS AND TRUST IT UNTIL THIS IS RESOLVED. If you already did in the last few months, consider shutting that system down for now.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He addressed another user on Twitter and revealed that he had only noticed the hack after getting emails from Coinbase and Kraken about login attempts. Even though Dashjr claimed that he did not know how the hackers gained access to his key, some Twitter users have pointed out a potential connection with a previous Twitter post from him. On November 17, Dashjr tweeted about his server being undermined by &ldquo;new malware/indirect accesses on the framework.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
CZ Expresses Condolences
<p>A Reddit user has suggested that Dashjr did not take the November 17 security breach seriously enough and failed to take measures to separate his different activities. According to this user, Dashjr kept his hot wallet on the same computer that he used for all his other activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The event has come to the attention of Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, who tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Sorry to see you lose so much. Informed our security team to monitor. If it comes our way, we will freeze it. If there is anything else we can help with, please let us know. We deal with these often, and have Law Enforcement (LE) relationships worldwide.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the core developers of Bitcoin, Luke Dashjr, has claimed that he lost almost his entire Bitcoin holding on December 31.</p>
PGP Keys Compromised
<p>Bitcoin core developer Luke Dashjr revealed that he lost over 200 BTCs when his wallet was compromised just before the new year. Dashjr addressed the community via a Twitter post, stating that a PGP key compromise resulted in the loss of his funds. He stated that the alleged hackers had somehow gained control of his Pretty Good Privacy (PGP) key and accessed his wallet. The PGP key system is a common security method with encrypted information hidden behind two private keys.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Dashjr tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;PSA: My server was accessed this morning by an unknown person. Full analysis in progress, but take extra care that you PGP-verified any downloads.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Dashjr also tweeted a wallet address to which some of the stolen Bitcoin had been sent. Even though he did not disclose the total amount stolen, the wallet address he reported has received four transactions between the hours of 2:08 and 2:16 pm UTC on Dec. 31. These transaction amounts totaled 216.93 BTC, which is worth $3.6 million at current prices.</p>
Twitter And Reddit Sleuths At Work
<p>When a Twitter user asked what the connection with PGP was, Dashjr responded,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;That's how you might verify that your Bitcoin Knots or Core download isn't infested with malware. So to be clear: DO NOT DOWNLOAD BITCOIN KNOTS AND TRUST IT UNTIL THIS IS RESOLVED. If you already did in the last few months, consider shutting that system down for now.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He addressed another user on Twitter and revealed that he had only noticed the hack after getting emails from Coinbase and Kraken about login attempts. Even though Dashjr claimed that he did not know how the hackers gained access to his key, some Twitter users have pointed out a potential connection with a previous Twitter post from him. On November 17, Dashjr tweeted about his server being undermined by &ldquo;new malware/indirect accesses on the framework.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
CZ Expresses Condolences
<p>A Reddit user has suggested that Dashjr did not take the November 17 security breach seriously enough and failed to take measures to separate his different activities. According to this user, Dashjr kept his hot wallet on the same computer that he used for all his other activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The event has come to the attention of Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, who tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Sorry to see you lose so much. Informed our security team to monitor. If it comes our way, we will freeze it. If there is anything else we can help with, please let us know. We deal with these often, and have Law Enforcement (LE) relationships worldwide.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Buys More Bitcoin  Warns Against the SEC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/robert-kiyosaki-buys-more-bitcoin-warns-against-the-sec</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/kiyosaki-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/kiyosaki-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/kiyosaki-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/robert-kiyosaki-buys-more-bitcoin-warns-against-the-sec</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Renowned author Robert Kiyosaki has revealed he had bought more Bitcoin and why he chose to do this arguing that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regulations will &ldquo;crush&rdquo; most other currencies. </p>
<p>Author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, has said that the main reason for his investment in Bitcoin stems from a belief that the SEC will &ldquo;crush&rdquo; most other tokens with its regulations. In a Tweet on December 30, Kiyosaki revealed that he is investing in Bitcoin and explained he is &ldquo;very excited&rdquo; about the currency &ldquo;is classified as a commodity much like gold, silver, and oil.&rdquo; Kiyosaki said he is buying more Bitcoin, and the SEC classified bitcoin as a commodity while most other cryptocurrencies have been deemed to be securities. Kiyosaki has also cautioned that &ldquo;SEC regulations will crush most of them.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Q: Are you investing in Bitcoin?A: Yes I am. I am very excited about Bitcoin. Why? Because Bitcoin is classified as a commodity much like gold, silver, and oil. Most crypto tokens are classifed as a security and SEC regulations will crush most of them. I am buying more BC</p>
&mdash; therealkiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) December 31, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p>The Rich Dad Poor Dad author has for a long time advised investors to buy gold, silver, and Bitcoin and previously stated that he is now a Bitcoin investor rather than a trader according to a blog post by Binance. Earlier in December, Kiyosaki made the bold claim that when the Federal Reserve pivots and creates trillions of &ldquo;false&rdquo; dollars, this token investor will benefit. After the fall of the now-bankrupt crypto exchange FTX, Kiyosaki stated that he is still bullish on Bitcoin and underscored that investors need to remember that cryptocurrencies as such cannot be claimed for the crash of FTX. Kiyosaki also in September urged investors to invest in crypto now, before the next market crash.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Renowned author Robert Kiyosaki has revealed he had bought more Bitcoin and why he chose to do this arguing that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regulations will &ldquo;crush&rdquo; most other currencies. </p>
<p>Author of Rich Dad Poor Dad, Robert Kiyosaki, has said that the main reason for his investment in Bitcoin stems from a belief that the SEC will &ldquo;crush&rdquo; most other tokens with its regulations. In a Tweet on December 30, Kiyosaki revealed that he is investing in Bitcoin and explained he is &ldquo;very excited&rdquo; about the currency &ldquo;is classified as a commodity much like gold, silver, and oil.&rdquo; Kiyosaki said he is buying more Bitcoin, and the SEC classified bitcoin as a commodity while most other cryptocurrencies have been deemed to be securities. Kiyosaki has also cautioned that &ldquo;SEC regulations will crush most of them.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Q: Are you investing in Bitcoin?A: Yes I am. I am very excited about Bitcoin. Why? Because Bitcoin is classified as a commodity much like gold, silver, and oil. Most crypto tokens are classifed as a security and SEC regulations will crush most of them. I am buying more BC</p>
&mdash; therealkiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) December 31, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p>The Rich Dad Poor Dad author has for a long time advised investors to buy gold, silver, and Bitcoin and previously stated that he is now a Bitcoin investor rather than a trader according to a blog post by Binance. Earlier in December, Kiyosaki made the bold claim that when the Federal Reserve pivots and creates trillions of &ldquo;false&rdquo; dollars, this token investor will benefit. After the fall of the now-bankrupt crypto exchange FTX, Kiyosaki stated that he is still bullish on Bitcoin and underscored that investors need to remember that cryptocurrencies as such cannot be claimed for the crash of FTX. Kiyosaki also in September urged investors to invest in crypto now, before the next market crash.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Orbiting 16504 - 2 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-16504-2-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-16504-2-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 16504 Technicals:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 2 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to orbit the 16504 area early in the Asian session as the pair was drawn to the level that represents the 78.6% retracement of the appreciating range from 15992.64 to 18385.36.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16691.47 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16543.73.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 16504 Technicals:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 2 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to orbit the 16504 area early in the Asian session as the pair was drawn to the level that represents the 78.6% retracement of the appreciating range from 15992.64 to 18385.36.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, and was off more than 3% in December.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16691.47 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16543.73.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Blockchain & Internet Of Things Are A Perfect Match]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/blockchain-and-internet-of-things-are-a-perfect-match</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockchain-2.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockchain-2.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockchain-2.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/blockchain-and-internet-of-things-are-a-perfect-match</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Internet of Things technology has given rise to concepts such as smart factories, cities and vehicles and next-generation agri-tech, among many other use cases. Almost every industry is looking to take advantage of IoT and the world is well set for that to happen. These days, almost everyone owns a smartphone or tablet device, and a great many machines are equipped with Wi-Fi enabled sensors that can send data to a centralized server. Things like factory machines, traffic lights, airplanes - you name it, they all have the ability to talk to one another thanks to IoT.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the rise of IoT may present some problems. With so many devices in the world all collecting, sending, receiving and processing data, existing networks will soon become clogged, resulting in very high costs for compute and storage power.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is why blockchain is often touted as an ideal platform for IoT devices. With blockchain, data is stored on a distributed, decentralized ledger that&rsquo;s hosted on multiple nodes. Its immutable nature means that the data stored within it cannot be corrupted.&nbsp; The merger of blockchain and IoT results in a reliable and secure method of storing that&rsquo;s generated and processed by intelligent devices. Moreover, because it&rsquo;s decentralized, there&rsquo;s no need for centralized control, management and maintenance, and no expensive costs associated with it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
How Blockchain Benefits IoT
<p>Given the advantages, it&rsquo;s no surprise that blockchain and IoT have already made considerable progress. In 2019, almost 20% of all IoT deployments were powered by blockchain solutions, according to data from International Data Corp. There&rsquo;s lots of room for potential growth in this area too, with Statista estimating the total installed base of IoT devices to exceed 75 billion by the end of 2025.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The growth of IoT will result in enormous volumes of data being generated, and dealing with all of that information is likely going to be a daunting challenge if we continue to rely on conventional cloud-based networks. For one thing there&rsquo;s the enormous costs to consider. Today&rsquo;s cloud networks can be extremely costly in terms of storage and processing power.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The issue is that existing IoT ecosystems are powered by a highly centralized, brokered communication model based on a client/server architecture. Within this infrastructure, each device is identified, connected and authenticated by cloud servers that use massive amounts of storage and processing power at extremely high costs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another issue with cloud networks is the risk of outages, which can cause data to become inaccessible and sometimes even lost forever.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Proponents of blockchain for IoT say decentralized networks will make it simpler to track billions of devices, enabling distributed processing and coordination at much lower costs. By adopting a standardized, peer-to-peer communication model to process large volumes of transactions between connected devices, companies will no longer need to rely on cloud servers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, blockchain will eliminate single points of failure, which is a big problem with today&rsquo;s centralized cloud networks. Blockchain is incredibly secure too, thanks to its use of cryptography to secure the data it collects.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Problems To Overcome
<p>It won&rsquo;t all be plain sailing if we&rsquo;re to migrate IoT workloads to a blockchain-based infrastructure. There are some key issues that need to be overcome, but luckily a number of interesting solutions are already being built.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One of the main challenges with blockchain is that it&rsquo;s not a low-latency protocol. As such, most blockchains process a very low number of transactions per second, and that presents issues for large-scale IoT device networks, as these require extremely rapid rates of data transfer to keep up. Ethereum, the world&rsquo;s most popular smart contract blockchain, is only capable of processing around seven transactions per second, for example. Moreover, the Ethereum network is often congested, leading to high transaction costs. In its natural state, it&rsquo;s not a realistic platform for large-scale IoT deployments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The answer to this problem may lie in scaling solutions like Boba Network, which is a Layer-2 network and hybrid compute platform that powers lightning fast transactions with much lower costs than traditional Layer-1 networks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Boba Network relies on a technology called optimistic rollups, which enable multiple transactions to be bundled into one and processed simultaneously. In this way, transactions are not only performed more quickly, but are more cost-effective too, as the gas fees for each bundle are split between them. What&rsquo;s more, Boba Network&rsquo;s hybrid compute technology makes it a perfect fit for IoT data, as it enables Ethereum smart contracts to talk to any external Web2 API or sensor to collect and process real-world information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A second problem that needs to be solved is blockchain&rsquo;s compatibility issues. SQL datasets have emerged as the standard for IoT networks, but blockchain is not well suited for use as a traditional database as it stores data differently, in blocks, as opposed to rows and columns. Its distributed nature is also not compatible with SQL-type databases. Still, there are some promising projects working to fix these compatibility issues. IOTA, for instance, has developed an IoT compatible blockchain that relies on a Directed Acyclic Graph-based tangle structure, as opposed to standard blocks. This makes it more suited for storing the kind of chronologically-ordered data created by IoT devices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
IoT Blockchain Applications At Work
<p>The combination of blockchain and IoT is an extremely powerful one for many specific application use cases. One of the best examples is in logistics, which is the backbone of most global industries, ensuring that raw materials and finished products are always in stock, and get where they need to go.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The logistics and supply chain industries face numerous challenges, including too much paperwork, lack of control over shipping, issues around traceability, transportation difficulties and more.&nbsp;</p>
<p>IoT and blockchain together can fix many of these issues. For instance, they can combine to collect and store data on things such as locations, times of departure and arrival, the temperature of goods in transit, the status of containers being shipped and so on. Because blockchain is decentralized and immutable, anyone can access this data at any time and be sure that it hasn&rsquo;t been corrupted.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One company doing this is Ambrosus, the creator of a blockchain-powered IoT network for the pharmaceutical and food logistics industries. It relies on a network of blockchain-connected sensors to provide full visibility into goods throughout the supply chain, leading to faster and more efficient movement of these goods.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Connected cars are another obvious example of how blockchain and IoT can be utilized together. Car manufacturers are increasingly turning to IoT enabled sensors to develop automated vehicles, and the addition of blockchain creates many new possibilities for the industry around smart parking, automated traffic control and more. Take NetObjex, which has created a smart parking solution that&rsquo;s powered by IoT and blockchain. Through its collaboration with PNI, which designs smart parking sensors, it has created a platform for autonomous vehicles to quickly find an available parking spot with integrated payments using cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Last but not least is the energy sector, which has already enjoyed the benefits of IoT enabled sensors that led to the creation of so-called smart meters. When IoT is merged with blockchain, smart meters can upload data in real-time and enable better distribution of energy across the grid. A home equipped with solar panels for instance can provide surplus power back to the grid, reducing energy wastage. An example of how this works can be found in Brooklyn, New York. There, solar powered homes are connected through so-called &ldquo;microgrids&rdquo; that enable smart meters to talk to one another across a distributed network. Through this network, these homes now have a way to buy and sell electricity from one another, with the blockchain facilitating transactions and ensuring everyone can save money on their energy bills.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Internet of Things technology has given rise to concepts such as smart factories, cities and vehicles and next-generation agri-tech, among many other use cases. Almost every industry is looking to take advantage of IoT and the world is well set for that to happen. These days, almost everyone owns a smartphone or tablet device, and a great many machines are equipped with Wi-Fi enabled sensors that can send data to a centralized server. Things like factory machines, traffic lights, airplanes - you name it, they all have the ability to talk to one another thanks to IoT.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the rise of IoT may present some problems. With so many devices in the world all collecting, sending, receiving and processing data, existing networks will soon become clogged, resulting in very high costs for compute and storage power.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is why blockchain is often touted as an ideal platform for IoT devices. With blockchain, data is stored on a distributed, decentralized ledger that&rsquo;s hosted on multiple nodes. Its immutable nature means that the data stored within it cannot be corrupted.&nbsp; The merger of blockchain and IoT results in a reliable and secure method of storing that&rsquo;s generated and processed by intelligent devices. Moreover, because it&rsquo;s decentralized, there&rsquo;s no need for centralized control, management and maintenance, and no expensive costs associated with it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
How Blockchain Benefits IoT
<p>Given the advantages, it&rsquo;s no surprise that blockchain and IoT have already made considerable progress. In 2019, almost 20% of all IoT deployments were powered by blockchain solutions, according to data from International Data Corp. There&rsquo;s lots of room for potential growth in this area too, with Statista estimating the total installed base of IoT devices to exceed 75 billion by the end of 2025.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The growth of IoT will result in enormous volumes of data being generated, and dealing with all of that information is likely going to be a daunting challenge if we continue to rely on conventional cloud-based networks. For one thing there&rsquo;s the enormous costs to consider. Today&rsquo;s cloud networks can be extremely costly in terms of storage and processing power.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The issue is that existing IoT ecosystems are powered by a highly centralized, brokered communication model based on a client/server architecture. Within this infrastructure, each device is identified, connected and authenticated by cloud servers that use massive amounts of storage and processing power at extremely high costs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another issue with cloud networks is the risk of outages, which can cause data to become inaccessible and sometimes even lost forever.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Proponents of blockchain for IoT say decentralized networks will make it simpler to track billions of devices, enabling distributed processing and coordination at much lower costs. By adopting a standardized, peer-to-peer communication model to process large volumes of transactions between connected devices, companies will no longer need to rely on cloud servers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, blockchain will eliminate single points of failure, which is a big problem with today&rsquo;s centralized cloud networks. Blockchain is incredibly secure too, thanks to its use of cryptography to secure the data it collects.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Problems To Overcome
<p>It won&rsquo;t all be plain sailing if we&rsquo;re to migrate IoT workloads to a blockchain-based infrastructure. There are some key issues that need to be overcome, but luckily a number of interesting solutions are already being built.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One of the main challenges with blockchain is that it&rsquo;s not a low-latency protocol. As such, most blockchains process a very low number of transactions per second, and that presents issues for large-scale IoT device networks, as these require extremely rapid rates of data transfer to keep up. Ethereum, the world&rsquo;s most popular smart contract blockchain, is only capable of processing around seven transactions per second, for example. Moreover, the Ethereum network is often congested, leading to high transaction costs. In its natural state, it&rsquo;s not a realistic platform for large-scale IoT deployments.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The answer to this problem may lie in scaling solutions like Boba Network, which is a Layer-2 network and hybrid compute platform that powers lightning fast transactions with much lower costs than traditional Layer-1 networks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Boba Network relies on a technology called optimistic rollups, which enable multiple transactions to be bundled into one and processed simultaneously. In this way, transactions are not only performed more quickly, but are more cost-effective too, as the gas fees for each bundle are split between them. What&rsquo;s more, Boba Network&rsquo;s hybrid compute technology makes it a perfect fit for IoT data, as it enables Ethereum smart contracts to talk to any external Web2 API or sensor to collect and process real-world information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A second problem that needs to be solved is blockchain&rsquo;s compatibility issues. SQL datasets have emerged as the standard for IoT networks, but blockchain is not well suited for use as a traditional database as it stores data differently, in blocks, as opposed to rows and columns. Its distributed nature is also not compatible with SQL-type databases. Still, there are some promising projects working to fix these compatibility issues. IOTA, for instance, has developed an IoT compatible blockchain that relies on a Directed Acyclic Graph-based tangle structure, as opposed to standard blocks. This makes it more suited for storing the kind of chronologically-ordered data created by IoT devices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
IoT Blockchain Applications At Work
<p>The combination of blockchain and IoT is an extremely powerful one for many specific application use cases. One of the best examples is in logistics, which is the backbone of most global industries, ensuring that raw materials and finished products are always in stock, and get where they need to go.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The logistics and supply chain industries face numerous challenges, including too much paperwork, lack of control over shipping, issues around traceability, transportation difficulties and more.&nbsp;</p>
<p>IoT and blockchain together can fix many of these issues. For instance, they can combine to collect and store data on things such as locations, times of departure and arrival, the temperature of goods in transit, the status of containers being shipped and so on. Because blockchain is decentralized and immutable, anyone can access this data at any time and be sure that it hasn&rsquo;t been corrupted.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One company doing this is Ambrosus, the creator of a blockchain-powered IoT network for the pharmaceutical and food logistics industries. It relies on a network of blockchain-connected sensors to provide full visibility into goods throughout the supply chain, leading to faster and more efficient movement of these goods.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Connected cars are another obvious example of how blockchain and IoT can be utilized together. Car manufacturers are increasingly turning to IoT enabled sensors to develop automated vehicles, and the addition of blockchain creates many new possibilities for the industry around smart parking, automated traffic control and more. Take NetObjex, which has created a smart parking solution that&rsquo;s powered by IoT and blockchain. Through its collaboration with PNI, which designs smart parking sensors, it has created a platform for autonomous vehicles to quickly find an available parking spot with integrated payments using cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Last but not least is the energy sector, which has already enjoyed the benefits of IoT enabled sensors that led to the creation of so-called smart meters. When IoT is merged with blockchain, smart meters can upload data in real-time and enable better distribution of energy across the grid. A home equipped with solar panels for instance can provide surplus power back to the grid, reducing energy wastage. An example of how this works can be found in Brooklyn, New York. There, solar powered homes are connected through so-called &ldquo;microgrids&rdquo; that enable smart meters to talk to one another across a distributed network. Through this network, these homes now have a way to buy and sell electricity from one another, with the blockchain facilitating transactions and ensuring everyone can save money on their energy bills.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
