<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:31:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Singapore Red Cross Enables Crypto Donations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/singapore-red-cross-enables-crypto-donations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 22:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265718</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The initially supported digital assets by Singapore Red Cross include BTC, ETH, USDT, and USDC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Singapore Red Cross &#8211; a humanitarian aid and community services charity in the Asian city-state &#8211; allowed people to contribute to its cause via donations in digital currencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The option became possible after a partnership between the organization and the crypto payment gateway Triple-A.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Coin a new Way to Give Today&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The charity entity </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://redcross.sg/news-stories/stories/1292-coin-a-new-way-to-give.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that individuals willing to make such donations can set an amount in fiat, and the system will automatically convert the sum into crypto. Singapore Red Cross is currently able to receive some of the largest digital assets by market capitalization, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), USDT, and USDC.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We do not have any preferred cryptocurrency, and we accept any of the cryptocurrencies stated above,&#8221; it clarified.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization explained that this type of contribution is not tax-deductible at the moment. People who want to obtain such deductions should donate via credit card.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Singapore Red Cross said that each crypto handout will support its humanitarian efforts focused on improving the welfare of children, isolated seniors, persons with disabilities, and families from disadvantaged backgrounds.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Coin a new way to give today, your support will go a long way,&#8221; the entity emphasized.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other Charity Organizations Accepting Crypto Donations</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nicklaus Children’s Hospital Foundation &#8211; a non-profit charity based in Florida that aims to provide better healthcare for children &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/from-fashion-to-charity-bitcoin-adoption-blossoms/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">allowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> people to send contributions in crypto in October 2021. People could make donations using a variety of assets, such as BTC, ETH, BCH, LTC, DOGE, and more.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American breast cancer organization – Susan G. Komen (better known as Komen) &#8211; and the National Children’s Advocacy Center are two more examples. The former </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/susan-g-komen-organization-now-accepts-btc-eth-shib-and-other-cryptocurrencies-for-donations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">collaborated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with The Giving Rock at the end of 2021 to enable donations in over 50 cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latter made a similar move in November 2022, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.nationalcac.org/crypto-give/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">becoming</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the first non-profit in Huntsville, Alabama, to accept such handouts. The supported coins are over 90, as those who prefer to contribute with crypto are subjects of tax benefits. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“For us, it equates to a cash donation which turns into therapy hours for children, parenting classes, medical examines. It turns into hope and healing and justice for kids who have been hurt by the people who were supposed to be taking care of them,” Crypto-project Coordinator – Hannah Alderson – said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapore-red-cross-enables-crypto-donations/" rel="nofollow">Singapore Red Cross Enables Crypto Donations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>4 People Charged for Allgedly Defrauding Investors in Crypto and Precious Metal Scam</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/4-people-charged-for-allgedly-defrauding-investors-in-crypto-and-precious-metal-scam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266089</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The four people, alongside their unincorporated entity, promised investors extremely high returns. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission said earlier this week that it had filed a complaint against four individuals and their unincorporated entity for operating a fraudulent project involving precious metals and digital assets.</p>
<p>The alleged scam had over 14,000 customers at one point.</p>
<ul>
<li>The complaint was <a href="https://www.cftc.gov/PressRoom/PressReleases/8766-23" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed</a> in the US District Court for the Middle District of Florida against Rene Larralde, Brian Early, Alisha Ann Kingrey, and Juan Pablo Valcarce.</li>
<li>The group of four, alongside their unincorporated entity called Fundsz, were charged with &#8220;fraudulent solicitation from clients to purportedly trade in cryptocurrencies and precious metals.&#8221;</li>
<li>The press release informed that the project ran from October 2020 until now and promised investors over 3% returns per week using a &#8220;proprietary algorithm&#8221; for trading and something the founders described as &#8220;secret sauce.&#8221;</li>
<li>Speaking of their historical performance, the four charged people claimed they had made &#8220;on-time and accurate payments&#8221; for seven years. Additionally, they said a one-time $2,500 investment in their project can be turned into $1 million within 48 months with no additional contributions.</li>
<li>The founders also said they run a parallel charity organization and use portions of the contributions to Fundsz to support several initiatives, including cleaning oceans and others related to health, education, and humanitarianism.</li>
<li>It seems Fundsz&#8217; tactics had worked as it had amassed over 14,000 customers at its peak. However, the CFTC argued that the charged individuals never actually traded any funds. All clients&#8217; gains are &#8220;illusory,&#8221; as the defendants &#8220;simply make up fictional weekly returns to report to customers.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“The CFTC continues to root out individuals who defraud customers in the cryptocurrency and precious metals markets. Though the products fraudsters purport to trade and their methods of attracting victims &#8211; in this case through social media &#8211; may have changed, the old adage ‘if something sounds too good to be true, it probably is’ remains as valid as ever,” said Director of Enforcement Ian McGinley.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-people-charged-for-allgedly-defrauding-investors-in-crypto-and-precious-metal-scam/" rel="nofollow">4 People Charged for Allgedly Defrauding Investors in Crypto and Precious Metal Scam</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager Reportedly Moved $5.5M of ETH and SHIB to Coinbase Amid Bankruptcy Procedures</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-reportedly-moved-5-5m-of-eth-and-shib-to-coinbase-amid-bankruptcy-procedures/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 17:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266060</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/voyager_defaultnotice_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/voyager_defaultnotice_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Voyager had given a deadline to its users previously to withdraw 36% of their tokens held on the platform.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cryptocurrency company Voyager has reportedly transferred a significant portion of its holdings to Coinbase as part of its bankruptcy proceedings. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The transferred assets include 1,500 $ETH, valued at approximately $2.77 million, and 250 billion $SHIB, worth around $2.7 million, bringing the total to approximately $5.5 million.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overall, $81.63 million worth of cryptocurrency has been </span><a href="https://www.tronweekly.com/bankrupt-crypto-firm-voyager-transfers-millions/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">identified</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in Voyager addresses, according to data from ArkhamIntel. The company is consolidating tokens from various wallet addresses into its main one as </span><a href="https://twitter.com/EmberCN/status/1690166987610345472" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">a strategic move</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the company faces financial turbulence, it aims to optimize its assets, and we may expect more significant transfers in the coming weeks.</span></li>
<li>Previously, Voyager allowed users to claim and withdraw 35.72% of their token holdings between June 20 and July 5. If customers chose not to withdraw during this period, the firm would sell the tokens after 30 days and compensate them in USD.</li>
<li>Now that the cryptocurrency claims period has ended, Voyager will sell the remaining tokens and provide compensation in fiat currency.</li>
<li>Voyager&#8217;s selection of Coinbase as its custodial service provider is a strategic decision. The US exchange is renowned for its stringent security measures and extensive experience in the cryptocurrency space, offering <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-voyager-digital-shrinks-portfolio-by-nearly-40/" data-wpel-link="internal">Voyager stakeholders</a> a sense of assurance and credibility during uncertain times.</li>
<li>Given the volatility of the cryptocurrency market, the movements of Voyager and its assets are closely observed by investors and industry experts.</li>
<li>The results of these transfers and the fate of Voyager&#8217;s substantial<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyagers-creditors-charged-5-2m-by-law-firm-in-latest-bill-adds-up-to-16-5m/" data-wpel-link="internal"> crypto holdings</a> may serve as precedents for other firms facing challenges in this ever-evolving industry.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-reportedly-moved-5-5m-of-eth-and-shib-to-coinbase-amid-bankruptcy-procedures/" rel="nofollow">Voyager Reportedly Moved $5.5M of ETH and SHIB to Coinbase Amid Bankruptcy Procedures</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Bitcoin &#8216;Drivechains&#8217; The Future of Scaling? BitMEX Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/are-bitcoin-drivechains-the-future-of-scaling-bitmex-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitMEX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265494</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Drivechains could unleash major new applications on Bitcoin, but may also include vulnerabilities and added complexity.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the Bitcoin (BTC) network’s programmability and scalability still relatively limited compared to other blockchains, developers continue mulling over ways to push the protocol’s capabilities to its limits.</p>
<p>One hotly debated idea comes from BIP 300 and BIP 301 – aka “Drivechains” – a soft fork proposal to allow Bitcoin to effectively scale through sidechains. In a blog post on Monday, analysts from BitMEX explored the benefits and tradeoffs of the proposal.</p>
<h2>BIP 300: Sidechain Peg-Out</h2>
<p>Proposed by developer Paul Sztorc, Drivechains is an “improved merged mined sidechain mechanism for Bitcoin.” A sidechain is another blockchain that connects itself to Bitcoin’s main network by using the same internal currency, BTC, for transactions and gas payments.</p>
<p>The upgrade’s first component part – BIP 300 – would imbue Bitcoin with the necessary peg-out mechanism for sidechains. This would allow users to “trustlessly” move their BTC between the main blockchain and connected sidechains without requiring centralized support – a glaring issue with sidechains like <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/iovlabs-introduces-a-2-5m-program-to-boost-the-development-of-bitcoins-sidechain-rootstock/" data-wpel-link="internal">Roostock</a> and Liquid today.</p>
<p>However, BitMEX <a href="https://blog.bitmex.com/drivechains/?ref=nobsbitcoin.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">claims</a> the technicals of the peg-out mechanism are “controversial” and contain “many significant weaknesses.”</p>
<p>Specifically, the proposal puts miners in charge of responsibly redeeming users’ peg-outs every three months. This gives miners the power to steal user funds if over 50% of the network’s hash rate conspires to do so, while also being very slow for users.</p>
<blockquote><p>“In a way, Paul’s proposal embraces the reality that under any known peg-out system… Bitcoin miners could either censor data, fake data or cooperate with the administrator and steal the sidechain Bitcoin,” BitMEX wrote.</p></blockquote>
<h2>BIP 301: Blind Merged Mining</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, BIP301 would unlock “blind merged mining” for sidechains. Regular merged mining is when a miner <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mining-2-0-crypto-miners-embrace-artificial-intelligence-ai-as-the-new-frontier/" data-wpel-link="internal">mines</a> for two or more blockchains at the same time, leveraging the same hashing algorithm to score fees on both chains.</p>
<p>While most miners run some form of merged mining today, they must explicitly choose to run the sidechain’s software. Blind merged mining dispenses with this need by letting a third party run the sidechain, receive its fees, and later pass on those funds to miners as BTC transaction fees.</p>
<p>While BitMEX said this proposal may introduce complexity to Bitcoin, the benefits it provides could outweigh that complexity.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Increased usage of sidechains could potentially be positive for Bitcoin’s utility, and blind merged mining may be an improvement over regular merged mining,” analysts wrote.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/are-bitcoin-drivechains-the-future-of-scaling-bitmex-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Are Bitcoin &#8216;Drivechains&#8217; The Future of Scaling? BitMEX Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>eTukTuk is Helping The World Charge Forward into an Electric Future, Learn About The TUK Presale</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/etuktuk-is-helping-the-world-charge-forward-into-an-electric-future-learn-about-the-tuk-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266090</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-16.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-16.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There are all sorts of projects out there in the crypto market, but there’s one notable niche that’s been growing rapidly in the past 12 months. This niche consists of projects that are working on eco-friendly use cases and ecosystems that are making the world a better place. One of the most notable of these [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are all sorts of projects out there in the crypto market, but there’s one notable niche that’s been growing rapidly in the past 12 months. This niche consists of projects that are working on eco-friendly use cases and ecosystems that are making the world a better place.</p>
<p>One of the most notable of these projects is eTukTUk, a transport-focused project that is aiming to eradicate carbon emissions from our planet. We tell you everything you need to know about eTukTuk here, including its excellent and innovative TUK token.</p>
<h2>Why Does eTukTuk Matter?</h2>
<p><a href="http://buy.tuktoken.io" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">eTukTuk (TUK)</a> is a blockchain-based project that is aiming to create an ecosystem that helps deal with carbon emissions. Sustainable transport solutions are its focus, and it wants to lead the charge of electric vehicle transportation in the future. While it is doing this, it also wants to help support drivers and other stakeholders in the ecosystem. As a user, eTukTuk will offer the opportunity to be a part of the solution to tackle carbon emissions, as well as provide rewards.</p>
<p>The project also has the eTukTuk EV, which is a more affordable and reliable alternative to traditional TukTuks. It utilizes charging stations that are efficient.</p>
<p>There’s a lot else going for eTukTuk, but this is best described by the actual milestones it has hit in recent times. The project has been steadily racking up the laurels, and it is well on its way to becoming a global phenomenon.</p>
<h2>eTukTuk is Driving Forward Fast in 2023</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266093" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="468" height="468" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16.jpg 468w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16-300x300.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16-239x239.jpg 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-16-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 468px) 100vw, 468px" /></a></p>
<p>eTukTuk has taken a number of steps that showcase its potential. 2023 has been a wildly progressive year, as proven by multiple developments.</p>
<p>One of the significant developments among them is the company&#8217;s strategic decision to integrate BNB Chain&#8217;s Layer 2 opBNB into its operations. This move is a clear testament to the company&#8217;s dedication to driving innovation and efficiency and providing opportunities for adopters in the dynamic digital landscape.</p>
<p>The decision to switch to BNB Chain was influenced primarily by scalability, as BNB Chain&#8217;s Proof of Staked Authority (PoSA) consensus mechanism demonstrated remarkable growth in 2023.</p>
<p>In addition to this, earlier this year, eTukTuk made another noteworthy announcement, appointing The Capital Maharaja Group as a partner and a 20% equity stakeholder in its Sri Lanka operations. The Capital Maharaja Group, a pioneer in various private sector industries, stands as the leading privately held conglomerate in Sri Lanka, boasting over 44 global partnerships.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Japan&#8217;s Foreign Minister, Yoshimasa Hayashi, highlights Sri Lanka&#8217;s pivotal role in the Tokyo-led Indo-Pacific initiative.</p>
<p>Hayashi emphasised Sri Lanka&#8217;s strategic position in the Indian Ocean for a free and open Indo-Pacific initiative.</p>
<p>Read more: <a href="https://t.co/sN6LtDCPfP" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/sN6LtDCPfP</a></p>
<p>— eTukTuk (@eTukTukio) <a href="https://twitter.com/eTukTukio/status/1685997640121556992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The partnership with the Sri Lankan government is worth talking about further. IT will see over 200 charging station sites installed with the help of the government. One of the benefits claimed is that it will see drivers save up to 400% on operational expenditure compared to a fossil fuel TukTuk.</p>
<h2>The TUK Token Helps Tackle Carbon Emissions</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266092" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-18.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="624" height="312" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-18.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-18-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-18-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>The TUK token has a tagline that states that it wants to “eradicate carbon emissions off the face of our planet for good!”  It’s a lofty goal for sure, but the project is certainly sincere in its effort to help the planet.</p>
<p>The TUK token plays a central part in that process. With it, users can earn rewards as the network of efficient charging expands. The team claims that the resultant impact will not only positively affect the world and the health of people, but also “support communities that are struggling with the cost of living and financial inequality.”</p>
<p>The eTukTuk network’s expansion needs TUK to expand. The ecosystem has drivers pay to recharge their vehicles, which creates network revenue. Meanwhile, territory partners and power stakers earn TUK for each transaction that is processed. When the network in that region is scaled, it facilitates the move away from fossil fuels.  This continues to happen as it expands more globally.</p>
<p>The TUK token is currently being sold for a price of $0.01. It is in its first stage of the presale, with the next stage seeing the price rise to $0.02. There is a $10 million cap, which is no doubt going to be reached very quickly as the hype is already on a roll.</p>
<p>It’s clear that the team has put together a substantial and effective means by which the problem of carbon emissions can be tackled.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>eTukTuk embodies the best aspects of decentralized technology. The project is working on a noble cause and it is sure to benefit all stakeholders involved. As such, it has the potential to become a revolutionary token in the crypto market.</p>
<p><a href="http://buy.tuktoken.io" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Check Out eTukTuk</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/etuktuk-is-helping-the-world-charge-forward-into-an-electric-future-learn-about-the-tuk-presale/" rel="nofollow">eTukTuk is Helping The World Charge Forward into an Electric Future, Learn About The TUK Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Donald Trump Holds Between $250K and $500K Worth of ETH</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-holds-between-250k-and-500k-worth-of-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Donald Trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266062</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/donald_trump_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/donald_trump_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[However, the former US President remains a strong opponent of the crypto industry.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Donald Trump’s latest public financial disclosure shows that he holds between $250,000 and $500,000 worth of Ethereum (ETH).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump’s 2023 OGE financial disclosure </span><a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/23876912-donald-trump-oge-public-financial-disclosure-report-2023-part-1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">documents</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, released recently, featured an item described as a “Cryptocurrency Wallet (Ethereum),” whose value the former President placed between $250,000 and $500,000.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">The </span><a href="https://twitter.com/BotRalgo/status/1690350249100070914?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">content</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of the crypto wallet is likely tied to the sale of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) he </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-announces-personal-nft-collection/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">launched</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in December 2022 after exiting the White House. </span></li>
<li>The limited edition NFT collection <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trumps-nft-collection-sold-out-in-one-day/" data-wpel-link="internal">sold out</a> within a day and comprised 44,000 digital trading cards featuring the former President in different costumes and poses.</li>
<li>According to reports, Trump’s NFT adventure netted upwards of $8.9 million in sales, earning him about $298,000 in licensing fees. The crypto wallet through which the earnings were collected is held under the same Trump entity, CIC Digital, that collected these licensing fees.</li>
<li>Former first lady Melania Trump also briefly dabbled in NFTs, turning several popular images from NASA’s Apollo moon landings into digital pieces that sold for $75 each. However, NASA criticized the venture, stating it violated the space agency’s merchandising regulations.</li>
<li>It is interesting that Trump now holds crypto, considering his past <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-says-crypto-is-a-potential-disaster-waiting-to-happen/" data-wpel-link="internal">skepticism</a>. In 2019, he stated he was “not a fan” of Bitcoin (BTC), which he described as “not money” and whose value he claimed was “based on thin air.”</li>
<li>In 2021, at the height of his re-election campaign, Trump reiterated his stance on crypto, calling the asset class “fake.”</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-holds-between-250k-and-500k-worth-of-eth/" rel="nofollow">Donald Trump Holds Between $250K and $500K Worth of ETH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>THORChain&#8217;s RUNE Explodes 20% in a Day, Bitcoin (BTC) Stalls at $29K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/thorchains-rune-explodes-20-in-a-day-bitcoin-btc-stalls-at-29k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266071</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aside from RUNE, the other top gainer from the larger-cap alts is Toncoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin continues to trade sideways, and the past 24 hours didn&#8217;t bring any deviation from the tight range between $29,000 and $29,500.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also quiet on Sunday, similar to how they performed on Saturday, except for RUNE and TON.</p>
<h2>BTC Boring at $29K</h2>
<p>The past few weeks went in a rather uneventful fashion for the typically more volatile crypto asset. This past Monday saw some movements as BTC dipped below $29,000 to mark a weekly low. However, it went on the offensive almost immediately and had surged past $30,000 by the time Wednesday came.</p>
<p>More volatility was expected on Thursday when the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-unfazed-as-cpi-for-july-increases-by-0-2-mom/" data-wpel-link="internal">US CPI numbers</a> were set to come out. Yet, that wasn&#8217;t the case, and BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-returns-to-29k-after-failing-at-30k-shiba-inu-pumps-16-in-7-days-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">remained</a> at just under $30,000, where it had retraced hours before that.</p>
<p>The following several days were quite stagnant once again. Bitcoin stood still within the same tight range between $29,000 and $29,500. Expectedly, the weekend didn&#8217;t provide anything different, given the typically lower trading volumes.</p>
<p>As such, BTC&#8217;s market cap stands still at around $570 billion, and its dominance over the alts is just shy of 49% on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266072" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266072" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-266072" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="869" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4-1024x485.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4-768x364.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4-1536x727.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-4-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266072" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>RUNE Steals the Show</h2>
<p>Most altcoins have also failed to produce any notable moves in the past 24 hours. ETH, BNB, XRP, DOGE, ADA, TRX, MATIC, and LTC are all slightly in the red.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu, which was among the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-ape-pepe-jump-8-daily-bitcoin-maintains-29k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">top performers</a> on a weekly scale, has finally retraced and is down by 4% overnight. Solana and Polkadot, on the other hand, are with minor gains.</p>
<p>TONCOIN has soared the most from the larger-cap alts. TON is up by 8% and trades at $1.4.</p>
<p>However, THORChain&#8217;s native token &#8211; RUNE &#8211; has stolen the show with a massive 20% surge today. As a result, the asset has jumped above $1.3.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap, though, has remained stuck at around $1.170 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266073" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266073" style="width: 1878px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-266073" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1878" height="841" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3.jpg 1878w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3-1024x459.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3-768x344.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3-1536x688.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-3-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1878px) 100vw, 1878px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266073" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thorchains-rune-explodes-20-in-a-day-bitcoin-btc-stalls-at-29k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">THORChain&#8217;s RUNE Explodes 20% in a Day, Bitcoin (BTC) Stalls at $29K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Third Russian Sees the Digital Ruble as &#8216;Some Kind of Fraud&#8217; (Survey)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/every-third-russian-sees-the-digital-ruble-as-some-kind-of-fraud-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 23:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265649</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Russia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Russia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[One in five survey participants is not interested in Russia’s CBDC at all.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Research conducted by the information service provider Bankinform estimated that many Russians are interested in the news surrounding the potential launch of a digital ruble. However, 32% are not in favor of such a monetary product, viewing it as some sort of scam.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The world&#8217;s largest country by landmass has been among the most active on the CBDC scene. The pilot version, which will include testing with banks, businesses, and consumers, is expected to start in mid-August.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Russians not so Supportive</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The study </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://bankinform.ru/news/129875" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that 13% of the respondents closely monitor the development of the digital ruble and intend to use it once it sees the light of day. Those participants also said they see new opportunities presented by the upcoming CBDC.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Every third questioned person admitted following the news about the new digital form of Russia&#8217;s national currency but has no intention to deal with it. Over 21% are not interested in the topic at all.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The most interesting answer came from 32% of the respondents, who labeled the Russian CBDC as &#8220;some kind of fraud.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">There are different reasons why one might not be in favor of that type of financial product. CBDCs will be issued and controlled by centralized authorities, meaning they could endanger people&#8217;s privacy. According to Bankinform, though, another contributing factor to the distrust in the digital ruble could be the &#8220;ignorance&#8221; and the lack of substantial information on its advancement.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scam or not, many nations (including some leading economies) have already started exploring the product. As </span><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CryptoPotato</span></em><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-global-race-to-cbdcs-130-countries-already-exploring-research/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Japan, Australia, South Korea, the UK, and many others have introduced some programs to test the pros and cons of a central bank digital currency.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Somewhat expectedly (considering the political regime there), China is leading the race. The domestic authorities have introduced multiple initiatives to popularize the digital yuan, such as allowing CBDC settlements during the 2022 Winter Olympic Games held in Beijing.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">How far has Russia Gone?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The country&#8217;s officials seem determined to finalize their CBDC project in the near future. Not long ago, President Vladimir Putin </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/vladimir-putin-approves-russian-cbdc-launches-in-august/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">signed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a law that enables Russia&#8217;s Civil Code to add the digital ruble as a payment method. At the same time, the central bank was allowed to introduce the product to citizens. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We really hope that it will be more convenient and cheaper for both people and businesses, and they will start using it. This is a new opportunity,&#8221; Elvira Nabiullina &#8211; Governor of the bank &#8211; stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Earlier this week, the financial institution </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cbr.ru/press/event/?id=16991" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> plans to start experiments with the CBDC. First Deputy Governor Olga Skorobogatova said the operation will involve 13 banks and a limited circle of their customers. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We plan to introduce the digital ruble into mass circulation based on the results of phased testing and subject to the successful completion of piloting all scenarios for operations with the digital ruble. We expect that starting from 2025, citizens and businesses will be able to actively use the national digital currency, of course, at their own request,&#8221; she added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/every-third-russian-sees-the-digital-ruble-as-some-kind-of-fraud-survey/" rel="nofollow">Every Third Russian Sees the Digital Ruble as &#8216;Some Kind of Fraud&#8217; (Survey)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bakkt Renews Focus on Crypto Custody Solutions as Client Interest Surges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bakkt-renews-focus-on-crypto-custody-solutions-as-client-interest-surges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 20:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bakkt]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265960</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bakkt_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bakkt_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bakkt revealed it signed new custody clients and is engaged in late-stage negotiations with multiple prospects across broad client verticals.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Digital asset platform Bakkt Holdings is refocusing on its cryptocurrency custody solutions due to recent market events and increased client interest.</p>
<p>In a Q2 earnings report, Bakkt <a href="https://s201.q4cdn.com/666322591/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/20230810-2Q23-Bakkt-Earnings-Presentation-vFinal-edit.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">touted</a> its “compliant and trusted” custody platform, citing the current need for multi-custodian access and self-custodial functionality due to clients’ difficulty in storing digital assets safely.</p>
<h2>Bakkt Renews Focus on Crypto Custody</h2>
<p>Bakkt Custody was a core part of the firm’s business before its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bakkt-to-become-public-on-october-18/" data-wpel-link="internal">public listing</a> in October 2021. By May 2020, the company had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bakkt-expands-loyalty-program-increases-insurance-coverage-and-onboards-70-new-clients/" data-wpel-link="internal">expanded</a> its institutional custody solution to serve over 70 clients and struck several partnerships with major financial institutions.</p>
<p>The platform also partnered with insurance broker Marsh to offer customers coverage of more than $500 million in addition to the $125 million already in place at the custody solution.</p>
<p>However, Bakkt shifted its focus to retail payments following several business and management changes after it went public. The company’s renewed push into custody comes months after it acquired crypto brokerage service provider Apex.</p>
<p>The digital asset platform has signed new clients to Bakkt Custody and is engaged in late-stage negotiations with multiple prospects across broad client verticals. Bakkt’s qualified sales opportunities have increased by ten times, and the custody platform generates stable recurring fees.</p>
<p>With time, Bakkt intends to introduce additional features like yield-generating opportunities, including institutional staking. The custody platform would also add new blockchain networks and create a foundation for hot wallets.</p>
<h2>Bakkt Taps Fireblocks</h2>
<p>In line with the renewed focus on custody, Bakkt entered a multi-faceted collaboration with institutional digital asset custody firm Fireblocks. Through the partnership, Bakkt’s clients will maintain control of their private keys with the Fireblocks Off-Exchange solution. On the other hand, Fireblocks Off-Exchange customers will gain access to Bakkt’s Disaster Recovery Services.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We have integrated Fireblocks’ battle-tested custody technology to fortify our custody offerings, leveraging their new-to-market self-hosted keys product that enables us to control and manage all MPC key shares across multiple services in our data centers and cloud. We will continue to work closely with Fireblocks to jointly deliver additional capabilities to the market,” the firm said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, Bakkt <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bakkt-q2-revenue-jumped-by-60-yoy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">generated</a> net revenue of $13.6 million in Q2, indicating a 60% increase year over year, and trimmed its net loss by 13% from the same period last year to $27.6 million.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bakkt-renews-focus-on-crypto-custody-solutions-as-client-interest-surges/" rel="nofollow">Bakkt Renews Focus on Crypto Custody Solutions as Client Interest Surges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can These 10 Bullish Fundamentals for Ethereum Move ETH Prices?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/can-these-10-bullish-fundamentals-for-ethereum-move-eth-prices/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265933</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ethereum_bull_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ethereum_bull_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum prices have been in a languid state of inactivity for five months, trading sideways with volume and volatility diminishing.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>However, fundamentals for the asset and network are as strong as ever.</p>
<p>On Aug. 11, crypto industry and DeFi analyst Miles Deutscher highlighted some of Ethereum’s bullish fundamentals.</p>
<blockquote><p>“It&#8217;s hard not to be ridiculously bullish on Ethereum,” he said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Ethereum Fundamentals Strong</h2>
<p>Firstly, some of the world’s largest companies, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" data-wpel-link="internal">PayPal</a>, have chosen Ethereum to launch their products. Earlier this week, Ethereum advocate Ryan Sean Adams said the network is “becoming the money layer of the internet.”</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-problems-with-sam-altmans-worldcoin-according-to-vitalik/" data-wpel-link="internal">Worldcoin</a> is also using Ethereum and could be a major gas consumer if the digital ID project takes off.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It&#8217;s hard not to be ridiculously bullish on Ethereum.</p>
<p>Here are 9 reasons why.</p>
<p>• The biggest new projects are choosing to launch on ETH (PayPal stable coin, Worldcoin etc.)</p>
<p>• The ETH L2 thesis only continues to gain traction: Base launch, TVL at highs + strongest funding of…</p>
<p>— Miles Deutscher (@milesdeutscher) <a href="https://twitter.com/milesdeutscher/status/1689730899624038400?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The Ethereum layer-2 ecosystem is also growing at an accelerated pace, with networks such as Coinbase’s Base launching on L2. According to <a href="https://l2beat.com/scaling/summary" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">L2beat</a>, total value locked across the ecosystem has surged 150% since the beginning of the year to an all-time high of $10.5 billion.</p>
<p>Additionally, EIP-4844 is on the horizon, which will substantially reduce fees on layer-2 networks.</p>
<p>Ethereum staking continues to grow, with almost 20% of the entire supply, or $42.5 billion worth of ETH, now staked and securing the network.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Ethereum’s total fee revenue is higher than all other protocols combined.</p>
<p>Ethereum issuance remains deflationary, with the total supply declining by around 303,000 ETH since the Merge in September 2022.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Visa, one of the world&#8217;s largest payment processors, continues to use Ethereum for their crypto research.</p>
<p>Yesterday they published a proof of concept that allows users to pay gas fees using credit cards by leveraging Account Abstraction (ERC4337).</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s how it all works <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />: <a href="https://t.co/rYjTlBkdkW" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/rYjTlBkdkW</a></p>
<p>— cygaar (@0xCygaar) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xCygaar/status/1690043602926530561?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Deutscher also pointed out that NFT collections were migrating to Ethereum, citing Degods and y00ts as examples.</p>
<p>Many layer-1 networks are pivoting back towards Ethereum, such as Fantom adding Optimism rollups and Frax launching a layer-2.</p>
<p>Ethereum has also been labeled as a commodity by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission though Congress has yet to officially classify the asset.</p>
<p>Finally, a slew of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-price-unmoved-as-ethereum-futures-etf-race-heats-up/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum-based ETFs</a> have been applied for, so it could be only a matter of time before they get approved.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c8.png" alt="📈" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Ethereum</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a> Realized Cap just reached a 8-month high of $181,571,901,762.15</p>
<p>Previous 8-month high of $181,571,219,723.97 was observed on 11 August 2023</p>
<p>View metric:<a href="https://t.co/JEcbTHEjsD" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/JEcbTHEjsD</a> <a href="https://t.co/KslqrJW7a4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/KslqrJW7a4</a></p>
<p>— glassnode alerts (@glassnodealerts) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1690215339118804992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>ETH Price Outlook</h2>
<p>These ten solid fundamentals should be moving ETH prices, but they’re not at the moment.</p>
<p>ETH is hovering around the $1,850 level, where it has been for the past seven weeks, aside from a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-eth-tops-2000-for-first-time-in-3-months-on-ripple-victory/" data-wpel-link="internal">brief spike</a> in mid-July.</p>
<p>The asset has mirrored Bitcoin, trading in a range-bound channel since the middle of March.</p>
<p>A larger move higher is expected when BTC finally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/when-will-bitcoins-bull-run-start-analyst-chips-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">breaks out</a> of consolidation, and there are several factors that could catalyze this.</p>
<p>There are many reasons to be bullish about Ethereum, and a move higher seems an inevitability sooner or later.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/can-these-10-bullish-fundamentals-for-ethereum-move-eth-prices/" rel="nofollow">Can These 10 Bullish Fundamentals for Ethereum Move ETH Prices?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
