<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Metaverse Coin RobotEra Could be the Next The Sandbox And Deliver 10x Returns to Early Investors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/metaverse-coin-robotera-could-next-sandbox-deliver-10x-returns-early-investors.htm</link><description>The metaverse, described by Wikipedia as "the sum of all virtual spaces", has recently been garnering significant attention as a key component of the future internet. Major technology companies and banks are investing heavily in this space, with some experts forecasting that the metaverse is building towards a value of $13 trillion by 2030....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/metaverse-coin-robotera-could-next-sandbox-deliver-10x-returns-early-investors.htm"&gt;Read More: Metaverse Coin RobotEra Could be the Next The Sandbox And Deliver 10x Returns to Early Investors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Metaverse Building</category><category>Sandbox</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Taro</category><category>Web3 Game</category><category>Web3 Gaming</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/metaverse-coin-robotera-could-next-sandbox-deliver-10x-returns-early-investors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101108/249693/robotia1663740576.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1664129"/></item><item><title>Hong Kong is Setting Up a Shortlist of Tokens Retail Can Trade - Which Coins Will Make the List</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-is-setting-up-a-shortlist-of-tokens-retail-can-trade-which-coins-will-make-the-list.htm</link><description>Hong Kong’s financial regulator is expected to create a dedicated whitelist of tokens that retail users will be allowed to trade. &lt;br /&gt;
The new token whitelist was proposed on Wednesday by Julia Leung, the CEO of Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) during a panel discussion in Hong Kong. Leung did not reveal which specific tokens she had in mind for the proposed whitelist, but she said her agency will now seek public opinion about guardrails for retail crypto trading....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-is-setting-up-a-shortlist-of-tokens-retail-can-trade-which-coins-will-make-the-list.htm"&gt;Read More: Hong Kong is Setting Up a Shortlist of Tokens Retail Can Trade - Which Coins Will Make the List&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-is-setting-up-a-shortlist-of-tokens-retail-can-trade-which-coins-will-make-the-list.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101099/249664/hong-kong.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="104281"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Shows it is back From the Dead - Can the Resurrection Push Coin 2x to $30?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-shows-it-is-back-from-the-dead-can-the-resurrection-push-coin-2x-to-31.htm</link><description>Solana, once touted as the "Ethereum killer," is up 5.84% so far today after a huge rally that has driven the price up 25.67% in the past week. Solana's price is at $16.56, is it climbs the ranks, and it's now up by almost 70% since the end of the 2022 trading year. &lt;br /&gt;
The dramatic upsurge in SOL's value can likely be attributed to two things: strong backing from Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin, and higher participation in the Solana blockchain since the BONK token was released....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-shows-it-is-back-from-the-dead-can-the-resurrection-push-coin-2x-to-31.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Shows it is back From the Dead - Can the Resurrection Push Coin 2x to $30?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Solana Price</category><category>Solana Price Prediction</category><category>SOL price prediction</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>MMEMAG</category><category>Meta Masters Guild</category><category>Fight Out</category><category>FGHT</category><category>Mmag</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-shows-it-is-back-from-the-dead-can-the-resurrection-push-coin-2x-to-31.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101098/249663/sol.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="532578"/></item><item><title>Bankman-Fried Continues to Blame Binance for the Collapse of His Crypto Empire</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankman-fried-continues-to-blame-binance-for-the-collapse-of-his-crypto-empire.htm</link><description>Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried has released an extensive Substack article talking about how his crypto empire collapsed, once again putting the blame on rival crypto exchange Binance. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankman-fried-continues-to-blame-binance-for-the-collapse-of-his-crypto-empire.htm"&gt;Read More: Bankman-Fried Continues to Blame Binance for the Collapse of His Crypto Empire&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankman-fried-continues-to-blame-binance-for-the-collapse-of-his-crypto-empire.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101091/249657/cz-binance-and-sam-ftx-war-of-words-on-the.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1386194"/></item><item><title>Dash 2 Trade Crypto Signs Up 7,000 Beta Users, Subscriptions to Signals and Analytics Dashboard Open in April</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dash-2-trade-crypto-signs-up-7000-beta-users-subscriptions-signals-analytics-dashboard-open-april.htm</link><description>Dash 2 Trade has signed up 7,000 users to the beta of its dashboard product featuring its presale scoring and analytics system. &lt;br /&gt;
The beta release has had no marketing support, making this milestone all the more impressive. &lt;br /&gt;
Community feedback has so far been overwhelmingly positive.  &lt;br /&gt;
Dash 2 Trade’s presale section of its dashboard is the only product of this type available in the crypto analytics space. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dash-2-trade-crypto-signs-up-7000-beta-users-subscriptions-signals-analytics-dashboard-open-april.htm"&gt;Read More: Dash 2 Trade Crypto Signs Up 7,000 Beta Users, Subscriptions to Signals and Analytics Dashboard Open in April&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dash-2-trade-crypto-signs-up-7000-beta-users-subscriptions-signals-analytics-dashboard-open-april.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101089/249656/dash-2-trade-beta-testers-hit-7k.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="884610"/></item><item><title>This Crypto For Traders Will Have Cash Flow From April And Can Easily 20x From Here - Buy D2T Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/this-crypto-for-traders-will-have-cash-flow-from-april-and-can-easily-20x-from-here-buy-d2t-now.htm</link><description>Professional trading intelligence platform Dash 2 Trade, which hosts an array of useful features, including trading signals, social metrics data, on-chain indicators, a presale insights and scoring system, newsfeeds and a strategy back-testing tool, is on course to have cash flow before April....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/this-crypto-for-traders-will-have-cash-flow-from-april-and-can-easily-20x-from-here-buy-d2t-now.htm"&gt;Read More: This Crypto For Traders Will Have Cash Flow From April And Can Easily 20x From Here - Buy D2T Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>20X</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/this-crypto-for-traders-will-have-cash-flow-from-april-and-can-easily-20x-from-here-buy-d2t-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101086/249644/d2t-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="616700"/></item><item><title>Why Crypto Prices Are Breaking to the Upside in a Big Way – Which Coins Should You Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/why-crypto-prices-are-breaking-upside-big-way-which-coins-should-you-buy.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has risen by 4% in the past 24 hours, with prices jumping in response to the publication of positive US inflation figures today. At $920 billion, the market's total cap has increased by 7.5% in the past week, as well as by 3.8% in the last 30 days, buoyed by the arrival of increasingly positive sentiment regarding the direction of the US (and global) economy. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/why-crypto-prices-are-breaking-upside-big-way-which-coins-should-you-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Why Crypto Prices Are Breaking to the Upside in a Big Way – Which Coins Should You Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/why-crypto-prices-are-breaking-upside-big-way-which-coins-should-you-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101066/249637/why-crypto-prices-are-breaking-to-the-upside-in-a-big-way-which-coins-should-you-buy.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="248508"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Nexo's Bulgarian Offices Raided, Samsung to List Bitcoin Futures Active ETF in Hong Kong, Trezor Saw a 300% Spike in Sales</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nexos-bulgarian-offices-raided-samsung-to-list-bitcoin-futures-active-etf-in-hong-kong-trezor-saw-a-300-spike-in-sales.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nexos-bulgarian-offices-raided-samsung-to-list-bitcoin-futures-active-etf-in-hong-kong-trezor-saw-a-300-spike-in-sales.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Nexo's Bulgarian Offices Raided, Samsung to List Bitcoin Futures Active ETF in Hong Kong, Trezor Saw a 300% Spike in Sales&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Nexo</category><category>Europe</category><category>Legal</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Crime</category><category>Samsung</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>Binance</category><category>Sweden</category><category>CME</category><category>Celo</category><category>DEX</category><category>DAO</category><category>Trezor</category><category>Ledger</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Career</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nexos-bulgarian-offices-raided-samsung-to-list-bitcoin-futures-active-etf-in-hong-kong-trezor-saw-a-300-spike-in-sales.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100989/249578/adobestock-zz3701-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="97008"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction - ETH to $2k? Why Upgrades and Staking Will Keep Price on Upward Trajectory</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-eth-to-2k-why-upgrades-and-staking-will-keep-price-on-upward-trajectory.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
Ethereum is currently on an interesting upward trajectory. After reaching the $1,400 mark, the crypto asset is now aiming for the $2,000 milestone. And, with the upcoming Shanghai update, this could be a possibility....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-eth-to-2k-why-upgrades-and-staking-will-keep-price-on-upward-trajectory.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction - ETH to $2k? Why Upgrades and Staking Will Keep Price on Upward Trajectory&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-eth-to-2k-why-upgrades-and-staking-will-keep-price-on-upward-trajectory.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101075/249607/b2b534.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="190123"/></item><item><title>DCG Said to be in Talks with Creditors - Will Gemini Crypto Depositors Get Their Money Back?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-said-to-be-in-talks-with-creditors-will-gemini-crypto-depositors-get-their-money-back.htm</link><description>Barry Silbert’s crypto conglomerate Digital Currency Group (DCG) is “actively engaged” in talks with creditors, according to a little-known crypto exchange....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-said-to-be-in-talks-with-creditors-will-gemini-crypto-depositors-get-their-money-back.htm"&gt;Read More: DCG Said to be in Talks with Creditors - Will Gemini Crypto Depositors Get Their Money Back?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>DCG</category><category>Gemini</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-said-to-be-in-talks-with-creditors-will-gemini-crypto-depositors-get-their-money-back.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101068/249599/barry-silbert.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="79027"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin and Crypto Take Off As US CPI Inflation Cools and Bulls Take Charge</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-crypto-take-off-as-us-inflation-peaks-bulls-charge.htm</link><description>Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have been rapidly gaining traction as the US inflation rate reaches its highest level in decades.  &lt;br /&gt;
The rise of Bitcoin has been credited to the increasing demand from institutional investors, with many believing it to be a better store of value compared to traditional fiat currencies. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-crypto-take-off-as-us-inflation-peaks-bulls-charge.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin and Crypto Take Off As US CPI Inflation Cools and Bulls Take Charge&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-crypto-take-off-as-us-inflation-peaks-bulls-charge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101044/249660/adobestock-488802217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="9327856"/></item><item><title>Avalanche Price Prediction - This is Why AVAX is Pumping 25% and There's Much More to Come</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/avalanche-price-prediction-this-is-why-avax-is-pumping-25-and-theres-much-more-to-come.htm</link><description>Avalanche price breakout over the last 24 hours seems unstoppable, bolstered by a strategic partnership with Amazon Web Service (AWS). The bullish move in AVAX comes amid a market-wide uptick in crypto prices that started last week. Avalanche currently exchanges hands at $15.26, with its weekly cumulative gains increasing to 27.2%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/avalanche-price-prediction-this-is-why-avax-is-pumping-25-and-theres-much-more-to-come.htm"&gt;Read More: Avalanche Price Prediction - This is Why AVAX is Pumping 25% and There's Much More to Come&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/avalanche-price-prediction-this-is-why-avax-is-pumping-25-and-theres-much-more-to-come.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101039/249538/avaxusd-2023-01-12-14-16-21.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="395846"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 12th January – MEMAG, AVAX, FGHT, NEAR, CCHG, FLOW, RIA, AXS, D2T</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-12th-january-memag-avax-fght-near-cchg-flow-ria-axs-d2t.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has risen by a healthy 3% in the past 24 hours, teaching a total cap of $922 billion as investors optimistically await fresh US inflation data. Its current level represents a 7.5% increase in a week and a 3.5% rise in a month, as the 2022 bear market gives way to some New Year bullishness....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-12th-january-memag-avax-fght-near-cchg-flow-ria-axs-d2t.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 12th January – MEMAG, AVAX, FGHT, NEAR, CCHG, FLOW, RIA, AXS, D2T&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-12th-january-memag-avax-fght-near-cchg-flow-ria-axs-d2t.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101025/249543/best-crypto-to-buy-today-12th-january.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="395366"/></item><item><title>Move to Earn Crypto Fight Out Is First to Bring Fitness to the Metaverse - Presale Raises Nearly $3m</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/move-to-earn-crypto-fight-out-is-first-to-bring-fitness-to-the-metaverse-presale-raises-nearly-3m.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
Fight Out is positioning itself to take advantage of all that the move to earn industry has to offer by bringing health and fitness to the metaverse. Its crypto token is one of the hottest on the market right now, with almost $3 million in raised capital. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/move-to-earn-crypto-fight-out-is-first-to-bring-fitness-to-the-metaverse-presale-raises-nearly-3m.htm"&gt;Read More: Move to Earn Crypto Fight Out Is First to Bring Fitness to the Metaverse - Presale Raises Nearly $3m&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/move-to-earn-crypto-fight-out-is-first-to-bring-fitness-to-the-metaverse-presale-raises-nearly-3m.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101021/249500/fight-o.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="16285"/></item><item><title>El Salvador Has Just Approved Law to Allow it to Issue Bitcoin Denominated Bonds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvador-just-approved-law-allow-it-issue-bitcoin-denominated-bonds.htm</link><description>El Salvador’s congress has passed a digital securities law that would allow the nation to issue Bitcoin-backed bonds, also known as Volcano Bonds. &lt;br /&gt;
The Legislative Assembly of El Salvador approved the bill by 62 votes to 16 on January 11. The bill will become law after being ratified by President Bukele....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvador-just-approved-law-allow-it-issue-bitcoin-denominated-bonds.htm"&gt;Read More: El Salvador Has Just Approved Law to Allow it to Issue Bitcoin Denominated Bonds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>El Salvador</category><category>Nayib Bukele</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvador-just-approved-law-allow-it-issue-bitcoin-denominated-bonds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101014/249493/adobestock-mmollaretti-1-1-media-library-original-1200-752.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="109642"/></item><item><title>South Korean Software Giant AhnLab Unveils Crypto Wallet</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-software-giant-ahnlab-unveils-crypto-wallet.htm</link><description>The South Korean software giant AhnLab has released a crypto wallet – becoming the latest in a long line of the country’s IT players to move into the space. &lt;br /&gt;
Per iNews24, AhnLab, the largest computer security company in South Korea and the brainchild of the tech entrepreneur and presidential candidate Ahn Chul-soo, has named the wallet ABC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-software-giant-ahnlab-unveils-crypto-wallet.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Software Giant AhnLab Unveils Crypto Wallet&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Wallet</category><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-software-giant-ahnlab-unveils-crypto-wallet.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/100990/249466/ahnlab-pangyo-building.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="436276"/></item></channel></rss>
