<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 21:46:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Maximum Contol: China Plans to Monitor all Metaverse Users (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/maximum-contol-china-plans-to-monitor-all-metaverse-users-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 23:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267785</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/China.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/China.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The proposed "Digital Identity System" could gather personal information about metaverse users and store it permanently.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The state-owned telecom operator China Mobile has reportedly proposed the creation of a &#8220;Digital Identity System&#8221; to keep track of all local metaverse users. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The idea has been discussed between tech experts and Chinese officials and could set global rules focused on that technology.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Safety Measure or Additional Government Control?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a recent Politico coverage, the proposed &#8220;Digital Identity System&#8221; will require metaverse participants to share personal data points such as occupation and &#8220;identifiable signs.&#8221; The information could be stored permanently and shared with law enforcement agents &#8220;to keep the order and safety of the virtual world.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.politico.eu/article/china-beijing-designing-metaverse-proposal-social-credit-system-un-itu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">seen</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> as a protection measure by the Chinese telecom operator, this idea could violate principles of freedom and privacy. One person who supports that thesis is Chris Kemidas-Courtney &#8211; an executive at Brussels-based think tank Friends of Europe:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;To build a unified digital identity system, to give each human a unique digital ID that includes social characteristics from social media and occupation— that sounds a lot like China&#8217;s social credit system.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">An expert working at the International Telecommunication Union (ITU) also disagreed with China&#8217;s plans to monitor such identities in the metaverse space:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Imagine a metaverse where your identity protocols are set and monitored by Chinese authorities. Every government must ask themselves &#8211; Is that the kind of immersive world we want to live in?&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">China Insists on Centralization</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The government of China (ruled by the Communist party) has made several attempts to eliminate decentralization inside its borders and closely monitors people&#8217;s activities and financial transactions.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As such, it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/trading-and-mining-crackdown-in-china-escalates-bitcoin-plunges-3k/" data-wpel-link="internal">banned</a> all operations involving cryptocurrencies in 2021. The authorities doubled down on their crackdown several months later, warning that taking part in crypto fundraising could lead to hefty penalties and even jail time.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, the Chinese government is in favor of a central bank digital currency (CBDC): a monetary product issued by the People&#8217;s Bank of China whose supply could be adjusted by the financial institution.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The world&#8217;s most populous country is among the most advanced in terms of a CBDC launch and has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/china-distributes-2-3-million-worth-of-digital-yuan-to-shenzhen-citizens-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">introduced</a> multiple initiatives to popularize it among the population in the past few years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous experts, such as Florida&#8217;s Governor <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-cbdc-in-florida-says-governor-ron-desantis/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ron DeSantis</a> and US presidential candidate Robert Kennedy, have labeled that financial product as a tool of surveillance, insisting that it has nothing in common with bitcoin&#8217;s decentralized nature.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/maximum-contol-china-plans-to-monitor-all-metaverse-users-report/" rel="nofollow">Maximum Contol: China Plans to Monitor all Metaverse Users (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Connected Address Sends $1 Million in ETH To Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-connected-address-sends-1-million-in-eth-to-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 21:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267888</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/vitalikbuterin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/vitalikbuterin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Some believe Vitalik may be prepared to sell his ETH, while others believe he’s bridging holdings to Coinbase’s layer 2 blockchain, Base.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An Ethereum address associated with the network’s co-founder, Vitalik Buterin, transferred 600 ETH to crypto reading platform Coinbase, worth roughly $1 million at writing time.</p>
<p>The transfer comes after crypto markets tanked last week, bringing ETH down to $1670 for the first time since June.</p>
<h2>Is Vitalik Selling His ETH?</h2>
<p>According to public blockchain data available on Etherscan, the wallet address behind the <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x6283c4e3a14a45c00a6c1250b521de0d11bea399ddbf6025a34621261ea4a615" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">transfer</a> – Vitalik. eth – now holds a balance of 3,933 ETH, worth $6.58 million right now. It also holds over $500,000 worth of other tokens, including $300,000 worth of DeFi protocol KyberNetowrk (KNC) tokens.</p>
<p>Onchain analysts at PeckShield flagged Vitalik’s transfer on Monday, which first went to a multichain address before being resent to another address that Etherscan marked as belonging to Coinbase. Days earlier, he had sent 0.1 ETH to the same address as a test transfer.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="et" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PeckShieldAlert?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#PeckShieldAlert</a> vitalik.eth has transferred 600 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a> (~$1M) to <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Coinbase?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Coinbase</a> <a href="https://t.co/XVTwLqPENM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/XVTwLqPENM</a></p>
<p>&mdash; PeckShieldAlert (@PeckShieldAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1693541323532620159?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Analysts at <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1693550177863549268" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Lookonchain</a> noted that Vitalik withdrew 1000 ETH ($1.67 million) from MakerProtocol yesterday, after repaying $257,000 in RAI.</p>
<p>Vitalik never clarified what the transfer was about, but inflows to exchanges are generally viewed as a sign that investors intend to sell their coins for fiat or other cryptos. Vitalik has admitted to selling his ETH on multiple occasions, alongside <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-sells-off-dogecoin-clones-shib-akita-and-others-face-massive-dump/" data-wpel-link="internal">random memecoins</a> that he’s received from donors without asking.</p>
<p>Analysts from Nansen told CoinTelegraph that Vitalik’s exchange of choice was out of the ordinary.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Based on the wallet’s history, ETH transfers in the past have typically been to Kraken,” the analysts said. “However, it’s hard to say what’s the purpose of the transfer so we aren’t able to offer much more insight.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Friend.Tech: What’s the Hype?</h2>
<p>Some Twitter users <a href="https://twitter.com/Stefan69998632/status/1693542820856869048" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">suspected</a> that Vitalik might be bridging his holdings to Coinbase’s layer 2 blockchain Base, to use the network’s newly popular social media dapp, Friend.Tech.</p>
<p>The platform lets users sell shares of certain Twitter accounts and social profiles. Over the past 24 hours, its already generated $1.42 million in fees – more than the popular DEX Uniswap.</p>
<p>Some industry members have expressed <a href="https://twitter.com/Legendary_NFT/status/1693199945212555307" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">skepticism</a> of the app, cautioning that it may be a “pump and dump” that dies within weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-connected-address-sends-1-million-in-eth-to-coinbase/" rel="nofollow">Vitalik Connected Address Sends $1 Million in ETH To Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETHWarsaw Returns for its Second Edition Alongside Warsaw Blockchain Week</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethwarsaw-returns-for-its-second-edition-alongside-warsaw-blockchain-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267748</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/AI_BG_photo_1200x720_1692615689YiLkvyELNP.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/AI_BG_photo_1200x720_1692615689YiLkvyELNP.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Warsaw, Poland, August 21st, 2023] ETHWarsaw, a web3 conference and hackathon, organized by a passionate group of local Ethereum enthusiasts, returns for its second edition. The event is set to take place from August 31st to September 3rd, 2023 in Warsaw, Poland, bringing together a global community of builders, founders, and educators [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Warsaw, Poland, August 21st, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.ethwarsaw.dev/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ETHWarsaw</a>, a web3 conference and hackathon, organized by a passionate group of local Ethereum enthusiasts, returns for its second edition. The event is set to take place from August 31st to September 3rd, 2023 in Warsaw, Poland, bringing together a global community of builders, founders, and educators in web3.</p>
<p>Building upon the achievements of its debut, the second edition of ETHWarsaw promises an enhanced experience as it will coincide with the first in the history of <a href="https://warsawblockchainweek.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Warsaw Blockchain Week</a>.</p>
<p>“Despite the backdrop of crypto&#8217;s resurgence after a challenging year, we’re ready to deliver an even more comprehensive experience for the global community traveling across the world to Poland. This year we&#8217;re literally transforming Warsaw, a tech hub teeming with talent, into a hotbed of web3 action,” <strong>said Lukasz Stoczynski, ETHWarsaw’s Co-Founder, Business Development Lead.</strong></p>
<p>This collaborative initiative, set against the charming blend of tradition and modernity that defines Warsaw, promises community-organized side events, including conferences, networking meetups, and parties.</p>
<p>The collective effort is poised to make this year&#8217;s ETHWarsaw, for the second year in a row, the biggest web3 conference in the CEE region and Warsaw Blockchain Week the largest blockchain event ever held in Poland.</p>
<p>ETHWarsaw is structured to cater to both seasoned professionals and curious newcomers including web2 developers and students. The conference spans two dynamic days of talks, panels and fireside chats divided into six key tracks: DeFi, Scalability, Security, Infrastructure, Governance, and Non-Tech.</p>
<p>This year’s speakers include Marius Van Der Wijden, Ethereum Foundation; Akram El Milligy, Ledger; Patrick McCorry, Arbitrum Foundation; Artis from Gitcoin, and Adam Gagol from Aleph Zero.</p>
<p>Similarly to last year, the overnight hackathon will start on Friday evening and it will be a 48 hours marathon of non-stop building. There will be opportunities for teams and individuals to get hands-on, practical experience working with applications and advanced tools with ~$50,000 in value to be won from various competitions.</p>
<p>ETHWarsaw’s reputation as a hub for breakthroughs in the blockchain realm continues to be reinforced by the awe-inspiring success stories of projects born from the event.<strong> Antoni Zolciak, Co-founder of Aleph Zero, Ocean Sponsor of ETHWarsaw, explains:</strong> &#8220;The brilliant team behind our recently launched ecosystem company, AZERO.ID, was formed after they emerged as victorious champions of the ETHWarsaw hackathon. This win led them to secure a grant, develop the platform&#8217;s first version, and successfully close an oversubscribed pre-seed funding round. Their mainnet launch on Aleph Zero is just weeks away, marking an exciting beginning for AZERO.ID. We’re excited for this year&#8217;s hackathon during ETHWarsaw and have no doubt that this year&#8217;s edition will not disappoint.”</p>
<p>Other ETHWarsaw returning sponsors include RedStone Oracles, Arweave, Octant, Scroll, IPOR. In addition, EthWarsaw secured support for the vol2 event from companies like Lukso, zkSync, Request Network, PROPERLY, Beamer Bridge, Mantle &amp; Chronicle.</p>
<p>For more details about the event and to buy tickets for the conference and hackathon, visit: <a href="https://www.ethwarsaw.dev/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://www.ethwarsaw.dev/</a></p>
<p><strong>Stay connected with ETHWarsaw:</strong></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/ETHWarsaw" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">@ETHWarsaw</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/joinethwarsaw" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ETHWarsaw Official</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethwarsaw-returns-for-its-second-edition-alongside-warsaw-blockchain-week/" rel="nofollow">ETHWarsaw Returns for its Second Edition Alongside Warsaw Blockchain Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here is How dYdX Chain Validators and Stakers Will Keep the Ecosystem Unharmed</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-dydx-chain-validators-and-stakers-will-keep-the-ecosystem-unharmed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267826</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/dydx.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/dydx.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Not engaging in MEV activities and the proper storing of signing keys are some of the main obligations.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">dYdX Foundation &#8211; the non-profit organization behind the popular decentralized exchange (DEX) DYDX &#8211; announced some requirements that chain validators and stakers must comply with to ensure maximum user protection.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Good practices are organized into six categories: Maximal Extractable Value (MEV), operations and security, performance, transparency, governance participation, and dYdX ecosystem consideration.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a recent blog post shared by dYdX Foundation, chain validators should not engage in MEV activities or advantage any trading parties over others.</span></span></span></span></span><br />
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We expect that the dYdX community will take steps to disincentivize and punish bad actors who engage in MEV activities. As such, a delegator should consider that they may be impacted if they are delegating to a validator engaging in MEV,&#8221; the team behind the entity <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dydx.foundation/blog/good-practices-for-dydx-chain-validators-and-stakers" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">.</span></span></span></p></blockquote>
</li>
<li>Validators should maintain high uptime, ensure their node is online, and keep mempools across the network more consistent &#8220;to provide a better user experience for traders.&#8221;</li>
<li>Erratic behavior or misleading practices will not be tolerated.</li>
<li>Chain validators should minimize slashing risk by monitoring their nodes&#8217; performance. &#8220;It&#8217;s inadvisable to use &#8220;sentries&#8221; given increased latency, but instead opt for a threshold signer,&#8221; the team added.</li>
<li>Other security practices include properly storing signing keys (they should be backed up in a separate location), implementing a system for alerting critical issues, participating in dYdX chain testnets, and operating nodes via a legal organization.</li>
<li>Validators should also critically analyze governance proposals to be aware if such ideas will benefit the ecosystem. Apart from that, they should stand behind the best interests of the protocol.</li>
<li>Transparency is of critical importance, too. Chain validators and stakers should engage with the dYdX community, providing them with accurate information about current developments.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Validators may choose to be transparent about their operations and provide regular updates to their delegations. This includes publishing information about geographic location, redundancy, physical security, node performance, uptime, and rewards distribution, among other things, and full disclosure of the total number of validators operated and the total stake controlled by them,&#8221; the team concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-dydx-chain-validators-and-stakers-will-keep-the-ecosystem-unharmed/" rel="nofollow">Here is How dYdX Chain Validators and Stakers Will Keep the Ecosystem Unharmed</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Will Go Away If There’s No Privacy: Interview With Anoma and Namada’s Adrian Brink</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-will-go-away-if-theres-no-privacy-interview-with-anoma-and-namadas-adrian-brink/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267794</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto's anonimity has long been touted as one of its cornerstones, but lately, the conversation has been shifting. Will crypto survive without anonimity, though?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To this day, privacy arguably remains the fatal flaw of the most popular blockchain networks.</p>
<p>Both Bitcoin and Ethereum use fully transparent public ledgers to store their transactions. While technically anonymous, careful digging can allow external parties – including governments – to uncover the identity of any number of parties behind an address or set of transactions.</p>
<p>For the more privacy-focused blockchains and protocols, authorities have mostly banned centralized exchanges from listing them or sanctioned them in the West, limiting onramps to crypto privacy-preserving technology. As such, a persistent problem for developers has been striking a balance between privacy tech and realistic adoption.</p>
<p>In conversation with <em>CryptoPotato</em> at EthCC Paris, Adrian Brink – co-founder of Anoma and Namada – explained how he and his team navigate these issues using both the Anoma protocol and Namada blockchain. During the interview, Brink digs into Anoma’s focus on “intent” centric blockchains, Namada’s use of “asset agnostic proof of stake,” and why Layer 2’s are, in fact, <em>not</em> the future of privacy and scaling.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267799" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover.jpg" alt="anoma_adrian_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/anoma_adrian_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Anoma and Namada in Simple Words</h2>
<p><a href="https://namada.net" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Namada</a> is paving the way for a multi-chain privacy feature. In simple terms, it ensures privacy isn&#8217;t tied to a specific asset.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Imagine you have a CryptoPunk that you want to move around. Right now, there&#8217;s no privacy solution for this, but with Namada, it inherits the privacy set from all daily USDT privacy transactions,&#8221; said Brink.</p></blockquote>
<p>He emphasized the fundamental importance of privacy in the crypto space, noting:</p>
<blockquote><p> &#8220;I think privacy is fundamental. If this space isn&#8217;t going to become private, the space goes away.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>At the same time, <a href="https://anoma.net/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Anoma</a> is the first intent-centric (blockchain) architecture, where intents are the most fundamental primitive. Anoma’s intent-centricity provides novel properties for applications, including end-to-end decentralization, information flow control (being able to specify who sees what), decentralized counterparty discovery, and configurable settlement (being able to decide your security domain for settlement.</p>
<p>Less security, higher throughput for things that don&#8217;t need financial level security), configurable ordering, and fully programmable intents.</p>
<h2>Regulatory Compliance: Striking a Balance</h2>
<p>When questioned about compliance with diverse global regulations, Brink reassured that Namada is fully regulatory compliant. He highlighted the flexibility it provides to users in revealing their data, based on their jurisdictional requirements.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Users can decide what kind of information they want to reveal to whom,&#8221; Brink explained.</p></blockquote>
<p>He emphasized that a universal standard for global regulations isn&#8217;t feasible, and the approach <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/zcashs-encrypted-blockchain-satoshis-vision-interview-zooko/" data-wpel-link="internal">adopted by Zcash</a>, from which Namada is an extension, is a testament to the importance of understanding and working with regulators.</p>
<p>Reflecting on his journey since 2016, Brink recalled his entry into the blockchain sphere, emphasizing his belief in a multichain system.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I&#8217;m fundamentally a believer in the multichain. This is like there won&#8217;t be one chain to rule them all,&#8221; he shared.</p></blockquote>
<p>Discussing the industry&#8217;s evolution, Brink noted that during market lows, there&#8217;s a focus on research, while during highs, the spotlight shifts to trends like NFTs.</p>
<h2>ZK Tech: The Next Big Wave?</h2>
<p>Addressing the challenges faced by privacy-oriented protocols, Brink asserted that the industry is still in its infancy when it comes to privacy tech. He believes that it will take another one to two years to see top-notch production quality in privacy solutions.</p>
<p>He encouraged a focus on regulatory education, emphasizing that privacy tech is not against governments but is a fundamental tool for national defense.</p>
<p>As for the future of Anoma and Namada, Brink revealed that Namada&#8217;s mainnet will launch soon, describing it as &#8220;the single best privacy solution in the space at the launch.&#8221;</p>
<p>Highlighting the industry&#8217;s future direction, Brink predicted that everything will become an L1, emphasizing the importance of intents for decentralized systems.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There&#8217;s no way around intents and L1s. This is going to enable user flows that are just not possible right now,&#8221; Brink opined.</p></blockquote>
<p>He ended on the note of ZK tech being the next big wave, with the first consumer applications revolving around censorship-resistant cash.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-will-go-away-if-theres-no-privacy-interview-with-anoma-and-namadas-adrian-brink/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Will Go Away If There’s No Privacy: Interview With Anoma and Namada’s Adrian Brink</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano NFT Floor Price Skyrockets, Exceeding Ethereum: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-nft-floor-price-skyrockets-exceeding-ethereum-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267773</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/nft_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/nft_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cardano has been late to the NFT party but it is slowly emerging as a dominant player. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent years, the non-fungible token (NFT) space has expanded into a billion-dollar industry, with Ethereum traditionally leading the way as the dominant ecosystem. Cardano, on the other hand, faced criticism from numerous quarters, being labeled a &#8220;ghost chain&#8221; due to its absence of a DeFi and NFT economy. However, the NFT landscape is undergoing a shift.</p>
<p>According to the weekly chart shared by Stocktwits NFTs, the Cardano NFT floor price index sits 22% above that of Ethereum.</p>
<ul>
<li>The latest <a href="https://twitter.com/StocktwitsNFTs/status/1693417069167984785" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a> by the platform demonstrated an increasing inclination towards Cardano as a hub for NFTs among market participants.</li>
<li>A major factor that played a crucial role in uplifting the ecosystem is the Vasil upgrade which helped Cardano to <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/crypto-adoption-on-the-rise-reddit-showing-the-way" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">become</a> the third-largest NFT protocol behind Ethereum and Solana last September.</li>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ada-jumps-6-as-cardano-vasil-upgrade-goes-live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Vasil</a> aims to improve block latency speed and efficiency on the blockchain, and its completion pushed the Unique Active Wallets (UAW) on the Cardano blockchain to new heights.</li>
<li>On the other hand, Ethereum&#8217;s dominance in the NFT space dwindled primarily because of its network congestion issues coupled with high gas fees that prompted some users to explore alternative platforms.</li>
<li>While Cardano NFTs floor price may have exceeded Ethereum&#8217;s, the latter still commands position in terms of NFT sales volume over the last 24-hours.</li>
<li>In fact, <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> from CryptoSlam revealed that the latter&#8217;s sales account for a whopping $65 million while that of Cardano&#8217;s stands at $1.47 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-nft-floor-price-skyrockets-exceeding-ethereum-data/" rel="nofollow">Cardano NFT Floor Price Skyrockets, Exceeding Ethereum: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Platform RECUR to Shut Down After Raising $50M Two Years Ago</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nft-platform-recur-to-shut-down-after-raising-50m-two-years-ago/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267772</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Closed.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Closed.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The platform plans to transfer all NFT media and metadata to a decentralized storage protocol to allow users access their NFTs even after the closure. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RECUR, a non-fungible token (NFT) company that raised $50 million in an investment round nearly two years ago, has become the latest victim of the current bear market.</p>
<p>Over the weekend, the NFT platform announced that it plans to gradually shut down its operations starting this month, with a full business closure slated for November.</p>
<h2>RECUR Calls It Quit</h2>
<p>At the time of the announcement, RECUR said it had halted primary and secondary sales on August 18. However, the firm will allow users to transfer their NFTs to external wallets and withdraw all redeemable balances accrued before August 31.</p>
<p>According to the company, RECUR will disable NFT deposits by November 9, 2023. Traders will have until November 16 to withdraw their remaining NFTs and USDC from the platform, and users will be unable to access the website as it is slated to go offline at the withdrawal deadline.</p>
<h2>Users to Still Access Their NFTs</h2>
<p>The firm further noted that all NFT media and attributes would be transferred to the InterPlanetary File System (<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/whats-the-difference-between-btfs-and-ipfs/" data-wpel-link="internal">IPFS</a>), a decentralized storage protocol that ensures data retrieval by November 22, and RECUR will cease to exist.</p>
<p>According to RECUR, the transfer to IPFS is important as it will allow users to access and retrieve their NFTs even after the platform’s closure.</p>
<p>The decision to shut down its operations comes barely two years after RECUR secured $50 million in a Series A funding round from industry investors such as hedge fund mogul <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/changed-mind-steve-cohen-now-a-fan-of-the-crypto-industry-after-previously-doubting-it/" data-wpel-link="internal">Steve Cohen</a>. The fundraiser saw RECUR hit a market valuation of $333 million in September 2021.</p>
<p>After reaching mainstream due to the bull run two years ago, RECUR joined forces with American multinational conglomerate ViacomCBS, now known as Paramount, to offer digital collectibles from mainstream media such as CBS, MTV, Showtime, Paramount Pictures, and Nickelodeon.</p>
<h2>Bear Market Fallout</h2>
<p>However, due to the prolonged bear market, the NFT sector has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bayc-has-tanked-90-as-nft-collection-floor-prices-plummet/" data-wpel-link="internal">underperforming</a>, thus putting a significant hole in RECUR’s pocket, and the company has <a href="https://twitter.com/RecurForever/status/1692633345753002406" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">decided</a> to shut down.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This decision has not been an easy one. However, unforeseen challenges and shifts in the business landscape have made it increasingly difficult for us to continue providing the level of service and dedication that we have always strived to maintain,” the firm said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, RECUR is not the only web3 firm that has decided to wind down operations due to financial struggles. Earlier this month, Nifty’s, a platform dedicated to Web3 creators, announced that it is going out of business due to unfavorable market conditions and financial challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-platform-recur-to-shut-down-after-raising-50m-two-years-ago/" rel="nofollow">NFT Platform RECUR to Shut Down After Raising $50M Two Years Ago</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Ordinals is Far From Dead Despite &#8216;Shift in Winds:&#8217; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-is-far-from-dead-despite-shift-in-winds-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267677</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There are currently over 25.6 million Ordinals inscriptions on the Bitcoin network. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Ordinals stirred up a frenzy in the community soon after its launch in January 2023. More than eight months later, ordinal inscriptions have maintained their prominence in the Bitcoin network&#8217;s activities over the past week.</p>
<p>Despite a sharp drop in sales volume, Bitcoin Ordinals remains very much active.</p>
<h2>Ordinals Account for 85% of Activity on Bitcoin</h2>
<p>Much like NFTs, ordinal inscriptions are digital assets engraved on satoshis, which are the smallest units of Bitcoin. The ability to inscribe on these satoshis became achievable through the Taproot upgrade that was introduced to the Bitcoin network on November 14, 2021.</p>
<p>According to &#8220;Leonidas,&#8221; the developer behind Ordinals, Bitcoin <a href="https://twitter.com/LeonidasNFT/status/1693346274299306133" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">witnessed</a> a total of 530,788 transactions within the last 24 hours. Notably, a significant portion of this activity- specifically, 450,785 transactions &#8211; was intricately tied to Ordinals. This essentially means that Ordinals accounted for 84.9% of the activity on Bitcoin on August 21.</p>
<p>From Q1 to Q2, Bitcoin Ordinals trading volume surged by 2,834%, hitting a staggering $210.7 million. Ordinals peaked around May after the trading volume and sales count neared $452 million and climbed beyond 832k respectively.</p>
<p>However, &#8220;June saw a shift in the winds,&#8221; as observed by the DappRadar <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-sales-volume-plummets-over-97-since-may-peak-dappradar/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> last week with the sales volume plunging by more than 76% to $106 million. Furthermore, the sales count also experienced a sharp decline of 60.3%, plummeting to 330,121, indicating subdued trading enthusiasm.</p>
<p>Despite this, Bitcoin currently boasts more than 25.6 million Ordinals inscriptions, as per <a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> from Dune Analytics, increasing by over 20% in just three weeks.</p>
<p>Besides, Bitcoin Taproot utilization has also been holding strong after hitting an all-time high around February which was largely attributed to the emergence of Ordinals on the network. Fast forward to six months later, Ordinals continued to play a crucial role in the adoption of Taproot, contradicting numbers that suggest waning interest in Bitcoin NFTs.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Every bitcoin maximalist cheered Taproot. </p>
<p>Now that it&#39;s actually used for something, they won&#39;t stop screeching about it! </p>
<p>Stop drinking haterade and just vibe. <a href="https://t.co/k7RVrHDqh6" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/k7RVrHDqh6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Zack Voell (@zackvoell) <a href="https://twitter.com/zackvoell/status/1693351516457861229?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Non-Profit for Bitcoin Developers</h2>
<p>While critics may view Ordinals as exploiting the network, several industry experts have lauded the growth. Ethereum co-founder, Vitalik Buterin recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-lauds-bitcoin-ordinals-believes-brc-20-standard-could-revive-stagnancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">praised</a> the BRC-20 token standard, suggesting that its growing significance signifies a clear departure from what he perceives as &#8220;stagnant&#8221; politics that have been affecting the Bitcoin ecosystem.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Ordinals protocol team <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-team-launches-non-profit-to-support-bitcoin-nft-developers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">introduced</a> a non-profit organization, called ‘Open Ordinals Institute,’ to fund its open-source development. The California-based Open Ordinals Institute is a registered 501(c)(3) public charity that aims to gather donations in Bitcoin to support the protocol’s development by primarily focusing on its core group of developers.</p>
<p>The initiative will also focus on the creation of user-friendly tools to allow users with less technical expertise to easily create Bitcoin Digital Artifacts.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-is-far-from-dead-despite-shift-in-winds-heres-why/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Ordinals is Far From Dead Despite &#8216;Shift in Winds:&#8217; Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Next for SHIB Following 22% Weekly Disaster? 3 Things to Watch This Week (Shiba Inu Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/whats-next-for-shib-following-22-weekly-disaster-3-things-to-watch-this-week-shiba-inu-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267771</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SHIB bounced, but failed to move above the key resistance. Key Support levels: $0.0000080, $0.0000070 Key Resistance levels: $0.0000085, $0.000010  1. Rejection at Key Resistance The price found support at $0.0000080 and tried to move higher but was quickly rejected once reaching the resistance at $0.0000085. Since then, the cryptocurrency fell back on the key [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">SHIB bounced, but failed to move above the key resistance.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.0000080, $0.0000070</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.0000085, $0.000010 </strong></p>
<h2>1. Rejection at Key Resistance</h2>
<p>The price found support at $0.0000080 and tried to move higher but was quickly rejected once reaching the resistance at $0.0000085. Since then, the cryptocurrency fell back on the key support, which is now put under pressure again.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267774" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267774" style="width: 2448px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267774" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40" width="2448" height="1199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40.png 2448w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40-1536x752.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40-2048x1003.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-40-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2448px) 100vw, 2448px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267774" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>2. Sellers Dominate</h2>
<p>In the past nine days, sellers managed to close eight daily candles in red. This shows that bears are dominating the chart right now, but in the past three days, the selling volume has been declining. This could be indicative that SHIB has reached a local bottom.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267777" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267777" style="width: 2447px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267777" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32" width="2447" height="1199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32.png 2447w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32-1536x753.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32-2048x1003.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-30-32-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2447px) 100vw, 2447px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267777" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>3. Bearish Bias Continues</h2>
<p>While the intensity of the selloff has subsided in the past few days, the momentum indicators, such as the daily MACD, still give a bearish signal. The MACD histogram has not yet made a higher low, but this appears likely if sellers start to lose interest. This could be an opportunity for buyers to return.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267778" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267778" style="width: 2447px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267778" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25" width="2447" height="1199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25.png 2447w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25-1536x753.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25-2048x1003.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-21_19-28-25-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2447px) 100vw, 2447px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267778" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for SHIB is bearish.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for SHIB Price</h2>
<p>The support at $0.0000080 must hold if SHIB is to stop this downtrend. If broken, the price can quickly fall to $0.0000070 next. The resistance remains at $0.0000085 and has so far stopped any reversal attempts.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/whats-next-for-shib-following-22-weekly-disaster-3-things-to-watch-this-week-shiba-inu-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">What&#8217;s Next for SHIB Following 22% Weekly Disaster? 3 Things to Watch This Week (Shiba Inu Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price to Pump With SEC ETF Futures Decision Set for October? Plus 2 Other Coins to Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-price-to-pump-with-sec-etf-futures-decision-set-for-october-plus-2-other-coins-to-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267803</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/launchapd_ypred_eth_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/launchapd_ypred_eth_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum’s price has been highly volatile of late, as investors anticipate the SEC’s decision on an $ETH futures ETF, expected by October. While a futures ETF could bring more mainstream adoption, many believe that limitations on direct Ethereum exposure could dampen its impact. Meanwhile, new altcoins like Launchpad XYZ and yPredict have emerged, offering different [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum’s price has been highly volatile of late, as investors anticipate the SEC’s decision on an $ETH futures ETF, expected by October.</p>
<p>While a futures ETF could bring more mainstream adoption, many believe that limitations on direct Ethereum exposure could dampen its impact.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, new altcoins like Launchpad XYZ and yPredict have emerged, offering different value propositions and use cases to Ethereum.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Sinks Below $1,700 As Bear Flag Begins Forming</h2>
<p>It’s been a disastrous week for $ETH holders, with the token’s value sinking over 9% since last Monday.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, $ETH is hovering around the $1,680 level, the same as it was back in mid-June.</p>
<p>Ethereum experienced its worst weekly close since the April crash last week, erasing the gains made in the past two months.</p>
<p>On the 4-hour price chart, the $ETH price appears to be forming a bear flag, which could signal further downside in the near term.</p>
<p>Moreover, the <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index</a> has dropped to just 38, deep into “Fear” territory – indicating that the broader market sentiment is leaning toward caution and pessimism.</p>
<h2>Traders Brace for SEC’s Crucial Ethereum Futures ETF Decision</h2>
<p>In light of the recent price volatility, $ETH investors have shifted their attention to the SEC’s anticipated decision on Ethereum futures exchange-traded funds (ETFs) this October.</p>
<p>At least 12 applications have been submitted for Ethereum futures ETFs, with major players like ProShares, Bitwise, and Valkyrie among the applicants.</p>
<p>A positive response from the SEC could mean a significant increase in institutional investment, given that these investors are often hesitant to invest directly in the spot crypto market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-29.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267806" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-29.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="175" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-29.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-29-300x87.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-29-50x15.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>While spot crypto ETFs have faced roadblocks in the US, the SEC’s approval of several Bitcoin futures funds in 2021 indicates a changing sentiment in the governing body, hinting that there could be a path for an $ETH futures ETF to be launched.</p>
<p>As such, although the recent price dip has made Ethereum holders apprehensive, the SEC’s decision in October could bring significant bullish momentum – meaning investors will be keeping a close eye on regulatory updates in the weeks ahead.</p>
<h2>Which Other Coins May Be Worth Considering?</h2>
<p>While Ethereum is grabbing the headlines, investors are also looking for promising newcomers in the altcoin market.</p>
<p>Two coins that could be worth tracking are Launchpad XYZ and yPredict, both of which are nearing the end of their respective presale phases.</p>
<h2>Launchpad XYZ Presale Sparks Buying Frenzy with Ambitious Web3 Plans</h2>
<p><a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=ethereum-price-to-pump-with-sec-etf-futures-decision-set-for-october-plus-2-other-coins-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ ($LPX)</a> is an emerging Web3-focused platform aiming to streamline access to cryptocurrencies, NFTs, blockchain gaming, and the metaverse.</p>
<p>Its native token, $LPX, has seen steady growth during the ongoing presale phase, which has now raised over $1.3 million as investors begin to take note of the project’s ambitious plans.</p>
<p>During the presale, $LPX tokens are available for $0.0445 before their expected listing on exchanges later this year.</p>
<p>This early buy-in opportunity has generated significant buzz, with <a href="https://t.me/Launchpad_Official_Channel" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ’s Telegram community</a> seeing tremendous growth in recent weeks.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267805" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-21.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="341" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-21-300x170.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-21-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Adding to the buzz is Launchpad XYZ&#8217;s comprehensive suite of features, which include an advanced trading terminal, an AI-powered &#8220;Apollo&#8221; trading assistant, and a Launchpad Quotient ranking system.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://launchpad.xyz/assets/documents/LaunchpadXYZ_Whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ’s whitepaper</a>, $LPX holders can also stake their tokens to benefit from trading fee discounts, NFT allowlist access, and early entry to crypto presales.</p>
<p>Thanks to these features, Launchpad XYZ has positioned itself as an exciting new contender in the crypto space.</p>
<p>As it approaches its first exchange listing, investors will be keenly watching $LPX to see if the token can live up to the overwhelming hype.</p>
<p><a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=ethereum-price-to-pump-with-sec-etf-futures-decision-set-for-october-plus-2-other-coins-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>yPredict Leverages Cutting-Edge AI to Revolutionize Crypto Analytics &amp; SEO with $3.5 Million Raised</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_e65e4a9b.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=ethereum-price-to-pump-with-sec-etf-futures-decision-set-for-october-plus-2-other-coins-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict ($YPRED)</a> is a groundbreaking new platform leveraging AI technology to offer an array of cutting-edge crypto analytics tools.</p>
<p>By using machine learning models trained on colossal datasets, yPredict seeks to provide objective insights like trading signals, automated pattern recognition, and trader sentiment analysis.</p>
<p>Additionally, yPredict’s team recently expanded into SEO solutions with its AI-powered backlink estimator, allowing for more precise keyword ranking strategies.</p>
<p>After a successful preview, this tool is now available for $99 per query – although it can be accessed for free by those who purchased $YPRED through the project&#8217;s presale.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-267804" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-12.jpg" alt="" width="602" height="359" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-12.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-12-300x179.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-12-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>During this presale, 80% of the total $YPRED supply has been made available, with investors able to buy in for $0.10 per token, which is a discount on the planned CEX listing price.</p>
<p>Over $3.5 million has been raised through this presale; however, with it now in Stage 7 out of 8, investors only have a limited window to capitalize on this discounted offer.</p>
<p>Several crypto influencers have also endorsed yPredict, such <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KwoCQl5h4qE&amp;t=459s&amp;pp=ygUPeXByZWRpY3QgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">as YouTuber Michael Wrubel</a>, who has an audience of over 310,000 people.</p>
<p>Overall, yPredict&#8217;s exciting technology and significant community support suggest a promising future for the platform as it seeks to revolutionize the crypto analytics space.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_e65e4a9b.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=ethereum-price-to-pump-with-sec-etf-futures-decision-set-for-october-plus-2-other-coins-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-price-to-pump-with-sec-etf-futures-decision-set-for-october-plus-2-other-coins-to-watch/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Price to Pump With SEC ETF Futures Decision Set for October? Plus 2 Other Coins to Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
