<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:49:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Decentraland shows green on the weekly chart, Tradecurve hits milestone with 13K users]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/decentraland-shows-green-on-the-weekly-chart-tradecurve-hits-milestone-with-13k-users</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-92.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-92.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-92.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/decentraland-shows-green-on-the-weekly-chart-tradecurve-hits-milestone-with-13k-users</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentraland, one of the most well-known virtual worlds, has seen a surge in the value of its native token, MANA. However, it's not the only cryptocurrency to achieve major milestones, as the upcoming Tradecurve exchange has surged in user count and reached a total of 13,000 sign-ups even before launch. We will go over both projects to see why this has been the case.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Decentraland (MANA) Heads Into The Green Zone According to Weekly Chart
<p>Decentraland celebrated Metaverse Pride 23, an event that was held with Polygon Mind. Decentraland also saw numerous developments, where they introduced new profile updates, where users could swap names, modify their bio, add links and other information, and manage their wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As of July 4, 2023, the Decentraland cryptocurrency traded at $0.404545. During the past week, Decentraland saw its high point of value at $0.358488, with its low point at a value of $0.416113. Within the last two weeks, the total price increase of Decentraland was by 20.8%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, within the past seven days, Decentraland climbed by 4%. This indicates that on its weekly chart, Decentraland has maintained its green zone and is heading upward in value.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve Hits 13,000 User Milestone
<p>However, Decentraland was not the only project to reach a significant milestone. Tradecurve is an upcoming hybrid exchange that focuses on privacy and anonymity. In addition, it's not locked to just crypto trading, as anyone can also trade bonds, US and European equity CFDs, ETFs, forex, indices, commodities, and options. As a result, 13,000 people have already signed up for the exchange even before its launch.</p>
TCRV Increased by 80% in Value
<p>During Stage 4 of the presale, TCRV trades at $0.018, indicating that the cryptocurrency has surged in value by 80% since the beginning giving solid ROI for early investors. In addition, it will surge by an additional 40% at Stage 5, meaning that investors who want to make the most significant ROI will want to get into it early.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts are also predicting that based on its feature sets, such as high leverage at 500:1, negative balance protection, and the VIP account system, TCRV can spike in value even further.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Analysts Predict a 100x Jump In value When Tradecurve Launches
<p>Current market experts predict that the growth of the TCRV token will be by 100x, fueled by its future listing on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap, and due to the introduction of Proof of Reserves (PoR) that will bolster transparency in the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, true borderless access appeals to millions of people, and the team estimates that they can onboard 100,000 users at launch. They've already raised $2.8 million out of the estimated $20 million, and the presale has seen significant appeal from investors and whales.&nbsp;</p>
For more information about the Tradecurve presale:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentraland, one of the most well-known virtual worlds, has seen a surge in the value of its native token, MANA. However, it's not the only cryptocurrency to achieve major milestones, as the upcoming Tradecurve exchange has surged in user count and reached a total of 13,000 sign-ups even before launch. We will go over both projects to see why this has been the case.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Decentraland (MANA) Heads Into The Green Zone According to Weekly Chart
<p>Decentraland celebrated Metaverse Pride 23, an event that was held with Polygon Mind. Decentraland also saw numerous developments, where they introduced new profile updates, where users could swap names, modify their bio, add links and other information, and manage their wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As of July 4, 2023, the Decentraland cryptocurrency traded at $0.404545. During the past week, Decentraland saw its high point of value at $0.358488, with its low point at a value of $0.416113. Within the last two weeks, the total price increase of Decentraland was by 20.8%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, within the past seven days, Decentraland climbed by 4%. This indicates that on its weekly chart, Decentraland has maintained its green zone and is heading upward in value.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve Hits 13,000 User Milestone
<p>However, Decentraland was not the only project to reach a significant milestone. Tradecurve is an upcoming hybrid exchange that focuses on privacy and anonymity. In addition, it's not locked to just crypto trading, as anyone can also trade bonds, US and European equity CFDs, ETFs, forex, indices, commodities, and options. As a result, 13,000 people have already signed up for the exchange even before its launch.</p>
TCRV Increased by 80% in Value
<p>During Stage 4 of the presale, TCRV trades at $0.018, indicating that the cryptocurrency has surged in value by 80% since the beginning giving solid ROI for early investors. In addition, it will surge by an additional 40% at Stage 5, meaning that investors who want to make the most significant ROI will want to get into it early.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts are also predicting that based on its feature sets, such as high leverage at 500:1, negative balance protection, and the VIP account system, TCRV can spike in value even further.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Analysts Predict a 100x Jump In value When Tradecurve Launches
<p>Current market experts predict that the growth of the TCRV token will be by 100x, fueled by its future listing on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap, and due to the introduction of Proof of Reserves (PoR) that will bolster transparency in the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, true borderless access appeals to millions of people, and the team estimates that they can onboard 100,000 users at launch. They've already raised $2.8 million out of the estimated $20 million, and the presale has seen significant appeal from investors and whales.&nbsp;</p>
For more information about the Tradecurve presale:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Will Polygon (MATIC) Price Go to Zero as the SEC Begins To Clamp Down on Crypto?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/will-polygon-matic-price-go-to-zero-as-the-sec-begins-to-clamp-down-on-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-09-at-195104.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-09-at-195104.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-09-at-195104.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/will-polygon-matic-price-go-to-zero-as-the-sec-begins-to-clamp-down-on-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Recently, crypto experts and analysts have raised questions on whether Polygon (MATIC) price could plummet to zero amidst the SEC's tightening regulations on the crypto industry. </p>
<p>Amidst the uncertainty, seize the opportunity to participate in Uwerx presale bonuses, offering enticing rewards for early investors. </p>
<p>This article provides a comprehensive overview to help you navigate the evolving crypto community and make informed investment decisions.</p>
Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction
<p>Polygon (MATIC) is a &nbsp;crypto and blockchain platform built on top of the Ethereum (ETH) network. Polygon (MATIC) aims to address the limitations of the Ethereum blockchain by providing faster transaction processing and lower fees. </p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) achieves this through a combination of technologies, including sidechains, plasma chains, and a decentralized network of validators.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) holds a value of $0.6339, boasting a market capitalization of $6B and a 24-hour trading volume of $552M. Market experts project a promising trajectory for Polygon (MATIC), anticipating a rise to $2.05 by the first quarter of 2025.</p>
Disrupting the Industry: Uwerx's (WERX) Low Transaction Fee Sets it Apart from Traditional Platforms.
<p>Uwerx is revolutionizing the freelancer marketplace with its array of innovative features. One notable highlight is its customized matching system, which optimizes connections between freelancers and clients based on their specific requirements, skills, and budget.</p>
<p>Upon its launch on centralized exchanges, Uwerx plans to renounce contracts, cementing its disruptive approach. A significant aspect of this disruption is the platform's transaction fee, set at a mere 1%. This starkly contrasts the excessive charges imposed by traditional platforms like Upwork and Fiverr, making Uwerx a highly appealing choice for freelancers and clients.</p>
<p>Its latest feature&mdash;the Uwerx Vault&mdash;adds another layer of innovation for token holders. Users can earn rewards based on platform variables by staking their WERX tokens in the vault, enhancing their engagement and potential benefits.</p>
<p>Uwerx prioritizes security and reliability, evident in the rigorous audits conducted by reputable firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide users with a sense of confidence and trust in the platform's integrity.</p>
<p>Uwerx's achievements have garnered recognition, leading to its listing on CoinSniper. Moreover, it is set to be listed on Uniswap, a major decentralized exchange, on August 1st. These listings further enhance Uwerx's accessibility, liquidity, and overall standing in the crypto market.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Test Airdrop and Long-Term Stability Measures: Exciting Opportunities and Trust for Token Holders
<p>Uwerx recently launched the initial version of its Alpha platform, providing users with a glimpse into its functionality and user experience. The platform is now preparing to transition from Alpha to the eagerly awaited Beta phase, bringing further improvements and enhanced features for a smoother user journey.</p>
<p>Uwerx has made a comprehensive update available as a PDF document to demonstrate its commitment to transparency and user support. This update covers essential aspects such as sign-up, login, password recovery, freelancer and client roles, job creation, talent discovery, and key pages like activity tracking and the hiring dashboard.</p>
<p>Uwerx's progress in shaping the future of freelancing is undeniable, driven by innovation, lower fees, and user-centric features. The platform highly values user feedback, encouraging individuals to share their insights at feedback@uwerx.network to actively contribute to its evolution.</p>
<p>Exciting times lie ahead as Uwerx prepares for a Test Airdrop scheduled at the end of the presale on July 31st. This presents an excellent opportunity for participants to experience the platform's capabilities personally.</p>
<p>To ensure stability and trust for token holders, Uwerx has implemented a nine-month lock on team tokens and plans to extend the token liquidity lock for 25 years after the presale. These long-term commitments showcase Uwerx's dedication to maintaining a secure and reliable environment.</p>
<p>The rapid growth of the Uwerx platform, with over 5,500 sign-ups and a substantial presence on Twitter and Telegram, reflects its appeal to freelancers and clients seeking cutting-edge solutions.</p>
<p class="s7">Uwerx (WERX) Presale Success: Breaking Records and Reaching New Heights</p>
<p>Uwerx achieved outstanding success during its presale by swiftly completing stages 1 to 4. In the Stage 5 presale, Uwerx tokens are available at an attractive price of $0.047725 per token, accompanied by a tempting 15% bonus on each purchase. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>This week, there will be a release of a clickable prototype for the presale, which will include pages for freelancer registration and client registration. Furthermore, the Uwerx Vault feature will be unveiled next week, and a poll will be conducted to determine the date of the test airdrop.</p>
<p>This presents a remarkable opportunity to acquire tokens at a favorable value. Market analysts anticipate a promising trajectory for Uwerx, projecting a price of $1.33 by Q4 2023.</p>
<p>Remaining responsive to community demands, the Uwerx team demonstrates flexibility by adjusting token allocations in light of the rapid speed of the presale.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t Miss Out on the 15% Bonus; Buy WERX tokens today: </p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, crypto experts and analysts have raised questions on whether Polygon (MATIC) price could plummet to zero amidst the SEC's tightening regulations on the crypto industry. </p>
<p>Amidst the uncertainty, seize the opportunity to participate in Uwerx presale bonuses, offering enticing rewards for early investors. </p>
<p>This article provides a comprehensive overview to help you navigate the evolving crypto community and make informed investment decisions.</p>
Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction
<p>Polygon (MATIC) is a &nbsp;crypto and blockchain platform built on top of the Ethereum (ETH) network. Polygon (MATIC) aims to address the limitations of the Ethereum blockchain by providing faster transaction processing and lower fees. </p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) achieves this through a combination of technologies, including sidechains, plasma chains, and a decentralized network of validators.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) holds a value of $0.6339, boasting a market capitalization of $6B and a 24-hour trading volume of $552M. Market experts project a promising trajectory for Polygon (MATIC), anticipating a rise to $2.05 by the first quarter of 2025.</p>
Disrupting the Industry: Uwerx's (WERX) Low Transaction Fee Sets it Apart from Traditional Platforms.
<p>Uwerx is revolutionizing the freelancer marketplace with its array of innovative features. One notable highlight is its customized matching system, which optimizes connections between freelancers and clients based on their specific requirements, skills, and budget.</p>
<p>Upon its launch on centralized exchanges, Uwerx plans to renounce contracts, cementing its disruptive approach. A significant aspect of this disruption is the platform's transaction fee, set at a mere 1%. This starkly contrasts the excessive charges imposed by traditional platforms like Upwork and Fiverr, making Uwerx a highly appealing choice for freelancers and clients.</p>
<p>Its latest feature&mdash;the Uwerx Vault&mdash;adds another layer of innovation for token holders. Users can earn rewards based on platform variables by staking their WERX tokens in the vault, enhancing their engagement and potential benefits.</p>
<p>Uwerx prioritizes security and reliability, evident in the rigorous audits conducted by reputable firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide users with a sense of confidence and trust in the platform's integrity.</p>
<p>Uwerx's achievements have garnered recognition, leading to its listing on CoinSniper. Moreover, it is set to be listed on Uniswap, a major decentralized exchange, on August 1st. These listings further enhance Uwerx's accessibility, liquidity, and overall standing in the crypto market.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Test Airdrop and Long-Term Stability Measures: Exciting Opportunities and Trust for Token Holders
<p>Uwerx recently launched the initial version of its Alpha platform, providing users with a glimpse into its functionality and user experience. The platform is now preparing to transition from Alpha to the eagerly awaited Beta phase, bringing further improvements and enhanced features for a smoother user journey.</p>
<p>Uwerx has made a comprehensive update available as a PDF document to demonstrate its commitment to transparency and user support. This update covers essential aspects such as sign-up, login, password recovery, freelancer and client roles, job creation, talent discovery, and key pages like activity tracking and the hiring dashboard.</p>
<p>Uwerx's progress in shaping the future of freelancing is undeniable, driven by innovation, lower fees, and user-centric features. The platform highly values user feedback, encouraging individuals to share their insights at feedback@uwerx.network to actively contribute to its evolution.</p>
<p>Exciting times lie ahead as Uwerx prepares for a Test Airdrop scheduled at the end of the presale on July 31st. This presents an excellent opportunity for participants to experience the platform's capabilities personally.</p>
<p>To ensure stability and trust for token holders, Uwerx has implemented a nine-month lock on team tokens and plans to extend the token liquidity lock for 25 years after the presale. These long-term commitments showcase Uwerx's dedication to maintaining a secure and reliable environment.</p>
<p>The rapid growth of the Uwerx platform, with over 5,500 sign-ups and a substantial presence on Twitter and Telegram, reflects its appeal to freelancers and clients seeking cutting-edge solutions.</p>
<p class="s7">Uwerx (WERX) Presale Success: Breaking Records and Reaching New Heights</p>
<p>Uwerx achieved outstanding success during its presale by swiftly completing stages 1 to 4. In the Stage 5 presale, Uwerx tokens are available at an attractive price of $0.047725 per token, accompanied by a tempting 15% bonus on each purchase. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>This week, there will be a release of a clickable prototype for the presale, which will include pages for freelancer registration and client registration. Furthermore, the Uwerx Vault feature will be unveiled next week, and a poll will be conducted to determine the date of the test airdrop.</p>
<p>This presents a remarkable opportunity to acquire tokens at a favorable value. Market analysts anticipate a promising trajectory for Uwerx, projecting a price of $1.33 by Q4 2023.</p>
<p>Remaining responsive to community demands, the Uwerx team demonstrates flexibility by adjusting token allocations in light of the rapid speed of the presale.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t Miss Out on the 15% Bonus; Buy WERX tokens today: </p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Orbiting 30281 Tightly - 10 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-30281-tightly-10-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-9-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-30281-tightly-10-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 30281 Tightly:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical guidance early in the Asian session as the pair tightly orbited the 30281.33 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29715.87 to 30456.&nbsp; &nbsp;Selling activity recently reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30465.99 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30403.73.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 30281 Tightly:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 10 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical guidance early in the Asian session as the pair tightly orbited the 30281.33 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29715.87 to 30456.&nbsp; &nbsp;Selling activity recently reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30465.99 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30403.73.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: Gemini Sues DCG And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-gemini-sues-dcg-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 12:35:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-gemini-sues-dcg-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Looks like Cameron Winklevoss made good on his promise of pursuing legal action against DCG CEO Barry Silbert after the latter failed to meet his final offer payment of $1.47 million. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Google Cloud's recently announced a partnership with infrastructure provider Voltage, unveiling a new trajectory for the tech giant's Bitcoin and Lightning ambitions.</p>
<p>Lightning Labs, the primary Bitcoin Lightning Network development firm, has rolled out a revolutionary set of tools designed for AI applications.</p>
<p>A recent report by JP Morgan looks to play down the effect that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF might bring to the crypto sector.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners have raked in an impressive revenue of $184 million in the second quarter of 2023, breaking previous records.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Perhaps because of incredibly bullish statements by Blackrock CEO Larry Fink, Bitcoin has set a new yearly high with expectations of going much higher.</p>
Ethereum
<p>Ethereum Name Service Labs has announced plans to introduce Layer 2 interoperability for its ENS domains during a community call on June 28.</p>
DeFi
<p>In the wake of a series of high-profile security breaches plaguing the DeFi space, a group of Ethereum community members has put forth a new standard, ERC 7265, aiming to enhance the security of DeFi protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The latest statement from the Uniswap Foundation has claimed that the launch of version 4 of the protocol depends on Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade.&nbsp;</p>
Altcoins
<p>The Multichain MPC bridge platform has seen abnormally large outflows, fueling concerns that the platform could be a target for a multi-million dollar exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance no longer supports deposits and withdrawals for several cross-chain bridge tokens linked with the Multichain project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin has expressed his sympathy and concerns for Solana and other cryptocurrencies in the context of the SEC&rsquo;s crackdown on the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>The Open Network (TON) has announced the release of an on-chain encrypted messaging feature, allowing private messages between TON users.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>After Cameron Winklevoss penned an open letter threatening litigation against Barry Silbert over the latter&rsquo;s role in the Gemini Earn Program, cryptocurrency exchange Gemini is suing DCG, the parent company of bankrupt crypto broker Genesis.</p>
<p>A new currency pegged to commodities, particularly gold, will be announced at the BRICS summit on August 22.</p>
<p>Crypto Exchange Bitfinex has announced that it has recovered some of the stolen assets from the 2016 Bitcoin hack but stated that a considerable number of assets are still yet to be recovered.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Indian government has partnered with Polygon and Airchains in order to develop a blockchain-based land ownership system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery, the law firm representing Voyager&rsquo;s committee of unsecured creditors, has sent the group a staggering bill of over $5 million for the work it has done between March and May.</p>
<p>Co-founders of bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital plan to donate their future earnings from their new venture to creditors who lost money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange LBank has announced the launch of the first unlimited crypto credit card.</p>
Regulation
<p>Israel is considering a bill that would exempt foreign residents from capital gains tax on the sale of digital assets and reduce tax on crypto options from 50% to about 25%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investigators from the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have concluded that Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky broke several US laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The UK parliament has passed a bill that could help the authorities seize and freeze cryptocurrencies used for crime.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to a recent report by the FATF, more than half of all UN member countries still need to implement the Travel Rule.</p>
<p>South Africa&rsquo;s financial regulator has ordered crypto exchanges in the country to apply for licenses before the end of the year to continue operating.</p>
<p>In an attempt to combat fraud, Belarus is looking to put an end to peer-to-peer crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
NFT
<p>Blur founder, Pacman, defends his NFT marketplace against accusations that the platform&rsquo;s strategies crashed the NFT market as the floor price of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has dropped to the lowest in the last 20 months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Members of the Azuki decentralized autonomous organization have initiated a Snapshot proposal to hold the project&rsquo;s founder accountable over allegations of misconduct.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>The Poly Network has fallen victim to another exploit after hackers manipulated a smart contract function on the cross-chain bridge protocol. According to security analysts, hackers allegedly leveraged a vulnerability in the smart contract system to mint an unlimited amount of tokens.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looks like Cameron Winklevoss made good on his promise of pursuing legal action against DCG CEO Barry Silbert after the latter failed to meet his final offer payment of $1.47 million. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Google Cloud's recently announced a partnership with infrastructure provider Voltage, unveiling a new trajectory for the tech giant's Bitcoin and Lightning ambitions.</p>
<p>Lightning Labs, the primary Bitcoin Lightning Network development firm, has rolled out a revolutionary set of tools designed for AI applications.</p>
<p>A recent report by JP Morgan looks to play down the effect that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF might bring to the crypto sector.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners have raked in an impressive revenue of $184 million in the second quarter of 2023, breaking previous records.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Perhaps because of incredibly bullish statements by Blackrock CEO Larry Fink, Bitcoin has set a new yearly high with expectations of going much higher.</p>
Ethereum
<p>Ethereum Name Service Labs has announced plans to introduce Layer 2 interoperability for its ENS domains during a community call on June 28.</p>
DeFi
<p>In the wake of a series of high-profile security breaches plaguing the DeFi space, a group of Ethereum community members has put forth a new standard, ERC 7265, aiming to enhance the security of DeFi protocols.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The latest statement from the Uniswap Foundation has claimed that the launch of version 4 of the protocol depends on Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade.&nbsp;</p>
Altcoins
<p>The Multichain MPC bridge platform has seen abnormally large outflows, fueling concerns that the platform could be a target for a multi-million dollar exploit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance no longer supports deposits and withdrawals for several cross-chain bridge tokens linked with the Multichain project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin has expressed his sympathy and concerns for Solana and other cryptocurrencies in the context of the SEC&rsquo;s crackdown on the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>The Open Network (TON) has announced the release of an on-chain encrypted messaging feature, allowing private messages between TON users.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>After Cameron Winklevoss penned an open letter threatening litigation against Barry Silbert over the latter&rsquo;s role in the Gemini Earn Program, cryptocurrency exchange Gemini is suing DCG, the parent company of bankrupt crypto broker Genesis.</p>
<p>A new currency pegged to commodities, particularly gold, will be announced at the BRICS summit on August 22.</p>
<p>Crypto Exchange Bitfinex has announced that it has recovered some of the stolen assets from the 2016 Bitcoin hack but stated that a considerable number of assets are still yet to be recovered.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Indian government has partnered with Polygon and Airchains in order to develop a blockchain-based land ownership system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>McDermott Will &amp; Emery, the law firm representing Voyager&rsquo;s committee of unsecured creditors, has sent the group a staggering bill of over $5 million for the work it has done between March and May.</p>
<p>Co-founders of bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital plan to donate their future earnings from their new venture to creditors who lost money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange LBank has announced the launch of the first unlimited crypto credit card.</p>
Regulation
<p>Israel is considering a bill that would exempt foreign residents from capital gains tax on the sale of digital assets and reduce tax on crypto options from 50% to about 25%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investigators from the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) have concluded that Celsius and its former CEO, Alex Mashinsky broke several US laws.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The UK parliament has passed a bill that could help the authorities seize and freeze cryptocurrencies used for crime.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to a recent report by the FATF, more than half of all UN member countries still need to implement the Travel Rule.</p>
<p>South Africa&rsquo;s financial regulator has ordered crypto exchanges in the country to apply for licenses before the end of the year to continue operating.</p>
<p>In an attempt to combat fraud, Belarus is looking to put an end to peer-to-peer crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
NFT
<p>Blur founder, Pacman, defends his NFT marketplace against accusations that the platform&rsquo;s strategies crashed the NFT market as the floor price of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection has dropped to the lowest in the last 20 months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Members of the Azuki decentralized autonomous organization have initiated a Snapshot proposal to hold the project&rsquo;s founder accountable over allegations of misconduct.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>The Poly Network has fallen victim to another exploit after hackers manipulated a smart contract function on the cross-chain bridge protocol. According to security analysts, hackers allegedly leveraged a vulnerability in the smart contract system to mint an unlimited amount of tokens.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[USDT Stablecoin Is Flowing To Exchanges, Experts Say It Is More Profitable To Hold Tradecurve]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/usdt-stablecoin-is-flowing-to-exchanges-experts-say-it-is-more-profitable-to-hold-tradecurve</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-91.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-91.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-91.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/usdt-stablecoin-is-flowing-to-exchanges-experts-say-it-is-more-profitable-to-hold-tradecurve</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past month, thousands of investors have moved their Tether (USDT) stablecoin to exchanges, in an effort to hedge against price fluctuations. At its peak in June, USDT was experiencing a daily trading volume of $33 billion, making USDT the number one most traded cryptocurrency in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, with the U.S. economy struggling and several banks collapsing, some investors believe that stablecoins may not be as safe as first perceived. As a result, many investors are now choosing to diversify their portfolios with new altcoins like Tradecurve, which is on track to hit a 125% ROI in July.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;&nbsp;</p>
USDT Experiences A Surge In Tokens On Exchanges
<p>Throughout June, a total of 13.4 billion USDT was sent to cryptocurrency exchanges. This mass movement has been triggered by a recent SEC lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase, as well as 55 new cryptocurrencies being added to the SEC&rsquo;s list of securities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An increase in USDT being sent to exchanges could suggest that many investors are looking to buy altcoins and other cryptocurrencies, which is good news for the market. This would imply that the market is turning bearish, which will likely drive up the value of projects.</p>
<p>However, an increase in USDT transactions could also suggest that investors want to minimize losses. This could explain the current increase in USDT transactions, as many projects have decreased in value by over 30%&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve&rsquo;s Stage 4 Presale Starts With A Big Win
<p>Although USDT is pegged to the USD, which in theory makes it more stable, Tradecurve is providing investors with significantly higher returns. Tradecurve started its presale at $0.01 and has already increased to $0.018, an 80% ROI for bullish investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now the project is on track to increase to $0.0215, taking its token returns to 125%. While these returns sound high, experts predict that Tradecurve could surge by 50x during its presale, meaning there are still plenty of opportunities for investors to profit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve has been able to thrive during the recent market conditions due to its unique new hybrid exchange. The Tradecurve exchange will combine the best of decentralized exchanges, including anonymous trading, with the best of centralized exchanges, such as the opportunity to trade traditional assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This all-in-one exchange is the perfect solution to current market trends and will open up thousands of opportunities for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Another benefit of Tradecurve is its unique educational features. As part of Tradecurves ecosystem, investors will be able to profit from AI trading bots with a proven track record, as well as copy trading subscriptions. Copy trading will allow experienced investors to generate an income, while providing new investors with the opportunity to learn from the market's most experienced veterans.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, Tradecurve has also developed a lucrative metaverse trading academy designed for traders of all levels. Just four stages into its presale Tradecurve has raised $2.8 million and is being compared to the Binance ICO.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stage four tokens are currently selling out fast, with crypto whales buying at record rates to maximize their returns in one of the market's highest potential projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about $TCRV presale tokens:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past month, thousands of investors have moved their Tether (USDT) stablecoin to exchanges, in an effort to hedge against price fluctuations. At its peak in June, USDT was experiencing a daily trading volume of $33 billion, making USDT the number one most traded cryptocurrency in the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, with the U.S. economy struggling and several banks collapsing, some investors believe that stablecoins may not be as safe as first perceived. As a result, many investors are now choosing to diversify their portfolios with new altcoins like Tradecurve, which is on track to hit a 125% ROI in July.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;&nbsp;</p>
USDT Experiences A Surge In Tokens On Exchanges
<p>Throughout June, a total of 13.4 billion USDT was sent to cryptocurrency exchanges. This mass movement has been triggered by a recent SEC lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase, as well as 55 new cryptocurrencies being added to the SEC&rsquo;s list of securities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An increase in USDT being sent to exchanges could suggest that many investors are looking to buy altcoins and other cryptocurrencies, which is good news for the market. This would imply that the market is turning bearish, which will likely drive up the value of projects.</p>
<p>However, an increase in USDT transactions could also suggest that investors want to minimize losses. This could explain the current increase in USDT transactions, as many projects have decreased in value by over 30%&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve&rsquo;s Stage 4 Presale Starts With A Big Win
<p>Although USDT is pegged to the USD, which in theory makes it more stable, Tradecurve is providing investors with significantly higher returns. Tradecurve started its presale at $0.01 and has already increased to $0.018, an 80% ROI for bullish investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now the project is on track to increase to $0.0215, taking its token returns to 125%. While these returns sound high, experts predict that Tradecurve could surge by 50x during its presale, meaning there are still plenty of opportunities for investors to profit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve has been able to thrive during the recent market conditions due to its unique new hybrid exchange. The Tradecurve exchange will combine the best of decentralized exchanges, including anonymous trading, with the best of centralized exchanges, such as the opportunity to trade traditional assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This all-in-one exchange is the perfect solution to current market trends and will open up thousands of opportunities for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Another benefit of Tradecurve is its unique educational features. As part of Tradecurves ecosystem, investors will be able to profit from AI trading bots with a proven track record, as well as copy trading subscriptions. Copy trading will allow experienced investors to generate an income, while providing new investors with the opportunity to learn from the market's most experienced veterans.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, Tradecurve has also developed a lucrative metaverse trading academy designed for traders of all levels. Just four stages into its presale Tradecurve has raised $2.8 million and is being compared to the Binance ICO.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stage four tokens are currently selling out fast, with crypto whales buying at record rates to maximize their returns in one of the market's highest potential projects.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about $TCRV presale tokens:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price Prediction: ADA’s Team Responds to SEC's Claims of Unregistered Security]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/cardano-ada-price-prediction-adas-team-responds-to-secs-claims-of-unregistered-security</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-195829.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-195829.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-195829.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/cardano-ada-price-prediction-adas-team-responds-to-secs-claims-of-unregistered-security</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) and Uwerx are making headlines with significant updates in the ever-evolving realm of cryptocurrencies. Cardano (ADA)'s team responds to the SEC's allegations of being unregistered security, shedding light on their regulatory compliance efforts. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Uwerx's presale is nearing its sell-out, captivating investors with its innovative platform for freelancers. </p>
<p>This article delves into the latest developments and examines the potential price prediction for Cardano (ADA), offering insights into the dynamic and promising opportunities Uwerx presents. Stay informed and discover the exciting prospects that await in the crypto world.</p>
Cardano (ADA): Empowering the Future of Blockchain Technology
<p>Cardano (ADA) is a testament to successfully implementing a power-efficient Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, positioning itself among the most extensive networks to achieve this remarkable feat. </p>
<p>By leveraging intelligent contracts and the Cardano (ADA) token, the platform empowers users to actively engage in network operations, fostering a society prioritizing security, transparency, and fairness.</p>
<p>Priced at $0.3537, Cardano (ADA) presents an enticing opportunity for investors and enthusiasts alike. In-depth analysis and diligent market observation suggest a projected value of $0.90 by Q2 2024, highlighting the platform's potential for growth and its undeniable appeal in innovative blockchain technology. </p>
<p>As Cardano (ADA) continues to advance, it remains a compelling force driving transformation within the industry. Stay tuned to witness the ongoing evolution of Cardano (ADA) as it forges ahead, revolutionizing the blockchain landscape and redefining the possibilities of decentralized technology.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Redefining Freelancing with Cutting-Edge Solutions
<p>Uwerx is making waves in the freelance industry by introducing a revolutionary platform that leverages blockchain technology to empower freelancers and clients. With its focus on innovation, transparency, and user-centric features, Uwerx is poised to disrupt traditional freelance platforms and create a more efficient and rewarding ecosystem.</p>
<p>To ensure the long-term stability of the project, Uwerx has implemented a groundbreaking token lock mechanism. The team's tokens will remain locked for an impressive nine months, demonstrating their commitment to the project's success. Also, WERX tokens will be on a 25-year liquidity lock starting after the presale.</p>
<p>Uwerx has strongly emphasized security, subjecting its intelligent contracts to thorough audits by renowned firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide an extra layer of assurance to users.</p>
<p>With its listing on CoinSniper and upcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st, Uwerx is expanding its reach and enhancing liquidity for WERX tokens. These listings will offer increased trading opportunities, further bolstering the token's value and market accessibility.</p>
<p>A key differentiator for Uwerx is its transaction fee of just 1%. This fee reduction positions Uwerx as a cost-effective alternative to industry giants like Upwork and Fiverr, who charge 10-20%, enabling freelancers to retain more earnings and fostering greater participation on the platform.</p>
<p>The introduction of the Uwerx Vault adds an exciting dimension to the platform. Freelancers can securely store their WERX tokens in the vault, taking advantage of staking opportunities and earning rewards based on platform variables. </p>
Uwerx (WERX): Continuous Community Growth
<p>This week, a clickable prototype will be launched during the presale, featuring registration pages for both freelancers and clients. Furthermore, the upcoming week will witness the introduction of the Uwerx Vault feature, alongside a poll to determine the test airdrop's date.</p>
<p>The recent launch of the Alpha platform showcases Uwerx's commitment to delivering a robust user interface and a long last experience for users. This initial version includes signing up, logging in, job creation, talent sourcing, and activity monitoring. The team is actively working toward the Beta version, which will introduce additional enhancements and further streamline the platform's capabilities.</p>
<p>The success of Uwerx's presale has been astounding, with each stage surpassing expectations. In Stage 5, the presale allows investors to secure WERX tokens for $0.047725 per token, with an additional 15% bonus on every purchase. The overwhelming response underscores the market's confidence in Uwerx's vision and potential. </p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>After the presale concludes on July 31st, token holders can look forward to a 6-week vesting period. Tokens will be gradually distributed during this period according to a predetermined schedule, ensuring a balanced and controlled release.</p>
<p>Seize the chance to join this extraordinary adventure and contribute to shaping the future of freelance work. Uwerx values your invaluable feedback, so don't hesitate to share it at feedback@uwerx.network and let us know what you think.</p>
Stay ahead of the Uwerx presale by using the links below:
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) and Uwerx are making headlines with significant updates in the ever-evolving realm of cryptocurrencies. Cardano (ADA)'s team responds to the SEC's allegations of being unregistered security, shedding light on their regulatory compliance efforts. </p>
<p>Meanwhile, Uwerx's presale is nearing its sell-out, captivating investors with its innovative platform for freelancers. </p>
<p>This article delves into the latest developments and examines the potential price prediction for Cardano (ADA), offering insights into the dynamic and promising opportunities Uwerx presents. Stay informed and discover the exciting prospects that await in the crypto world.</p>
Cardano (ADA): Empowering the Future of Blockchain Technology
<p>Cardano (ADA) is a testament to successfully implementing a power-efficient Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, positioning itself among the most extensive networks to achieve this remarkable feat. </p>
<p>By leveraging intelligent contracts and the Cardano (ADA) token, the platform empowers users to actively engage in network operations, fostering a society prioritizing security, transparency, and fairness.</p>
<p>Priced at $0.3537, Cardano (ADA) presents an enticing opportunity for investors and enthusiasts alike. In-depth analysis and diligent market observation suggest a projected value of $0.90 by Q2 2024, highlighting the platform's potential for growth and its undeniable appeal in innovative blockchain technology. </p>
<p>As Cardano (ADA) continues to advance, it remains a compelling force driving transformation within the industry. Stay tuned to witness the ongoing evolution of Cardano (ADA) as it forges ahead, revolutionizing the blockchain landscape and redefining the possibilities of decentralized technology.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Redefining Freelancing with Cutting-Edge Solutions
<p>Uwerx is making waves in the freelance industry by introducing a revolutionary platform that leverages blockchain technology to empower freelancers and clients. With its focus on innovation, transparency, and user-centric features, Uwerx is poised to disrupt traditional freelance platforms and create a more efficient and rewarding ecosystem.</p>
<p>To ensure the long-term stability of the project, Uwerx has implemented a groundbreaking token lock mechanism. The team's tokens will remain locked for an impressive nine months, demonstrating their commitment to the project's success. Also, WERX tokens will be on a 25-year liquidity lock starting after the presale.</p>
<p>Uwerx has strongly emphasized security, subjecting its intelligent contracts to thorough audits by renowned firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network. These audits provide an extra layer of assurance to users.</p>
<p>With its listing on CoinSniper and upcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st, Uwerx is expanding its reach and enhancing liquidity for WERX tokens. These listings will offer increased trading opportunities, further bolstering the token's value and market accessibility.</p>
<p>A key differentiator for Uwerx is its transaction fee of just 1%. This fee reduction positions Uwerx as a cost-effective alternative to industry giants like Upwork and Fiverr, who charge 10-20%, enabling freelancers to retain more earnings and fostering greater participation on the platform.</p>
<p>The introduction of the Uwerx Vault adds an exciting dimension to the platform. Freelancers can securely store their WERX tokens in the vault, taking advantage of staking opportunities and earning rewards based on platform variables. </p>
Uwerx (WERX): Continuous Community Growth
<p>This week, a clickable prototype will be launched during the presale, featuring registration pages for both freelancers and clients. Furthermore, the upcoming week will witness the introduction of the Uwerx Vault feature, alongside a poll to determine the test airdrop's date.</p>
<p>The recent launch of the Alpha platform showcases Uwerx's commitment to delivering a robust user interface and a long last experience for users. This initial version includes signing up, logging in, job creation, talent sourcing, and activity monitoring. The team is actively working toward the Beta version, which will introduce additional enhancements and further streamline the platform's capabilities.</p>
<p>The success of Uwerx's presale has been astounding, with each stage surpassing expectations. In Stage 5, the presale allows investors to secure WERX tokens for $0.047725 per token, with an additional 15% bonus on every purchase. The overwhelming response underscores the market's confidence in Uwerx's vision and potential. </p>
<p>The price is set to rise to $0.05245 on Monday, July 10th at 18:00 UTC.</p>
<p>After the presale concludes on July 31st, token holders can look forward to a 6-week vesting period. Tokens will be gradually distributed during this period according to a predetermined schedule, ensuring a balanced and controlled release.</p>
<p>Seize the chance to join this extraordinary adventure and contribute to shaping the future of freelance work. Uwerx values your invaluable feedback, so don't hesitate to share it at feedback@uwerx.network and let us know what you think.</p>
Stay ahead of the Uwerx presale by using the links below:
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Slowed by 30142 Technicals - 9 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-slowed-by-30142-technicals-9-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-slowed-by-30142-technicals-9-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Slowed by 30142:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from bearish sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair failed to sustain a break of the 30407 level, representing the 38.2% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Selling activity reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the same depreciating range.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30422.49 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30234.43.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Slowed by 30142:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from bearish sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair failed to sustain a break of the 30407 level, representing the 38.2% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp; Selling activity reversed around the 30148.60 area, representing a test of the 23.6% retracement of the same depreciating range.&nbsp; Earlier selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this increases the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30422.49 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30234.43.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[XRP’s Regulatory Hurdles Will Not Stifle InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) as Growth Surges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/xrps-regulatory-hurdles-will-not-stifle-inqubeta-qube-and-cardano-ada-as-growth-surges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-200531.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-200531.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-08-at-200531.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/xrps-regulatory-hurdles-will-not-stifle-inqubeta-qube-and-cardano-ada-as-growth-surges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The crypto market has recently experienced a bearish trend that has concerned many investors. This downturn can largely be attributed to the SEC lawsuits against major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase, which have caused significant uncertainty.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, the classification of several tokens as securities has raised concerns about the future of established cryptocurrencies. However, despite these challenges, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have defied the odds and continued their upward growth trajectory. Let's take a closer look at these two tokens and explore their features and growth potential.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE): Dominating the AI Crypto Sector
<p class="s5">InQubeta (QUBE) has garnered significant attention for its advancements in the AI crypto sector. Here are some notable features that make QUBE a promising investment:</p>
<p class="s5">1. AI Integration: InQubeta harnesses the power of artificial intelligence within its blockchain ecosystem. This integration allows for enhanced automation, data analysis, and decision-making processes, positioning QUBE at the forefront of innovation in the AI space.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Diverse Utility: QUBE serves as a utility token within the InQubeta ecosystem, providing access to a wide range of AI-based services and products. These include AI-powered investment strategies, predictive analytics, and personalized recommendations, creating value for token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Strong Community Support: InQubeta has built a vibrant community of supporters and contributors who actively participate in the project's development. The community's collective knowledge and expertise contribute to the ecosystem's ongoing growth and success.</p>
Don't Miss the InQubeta Presale
<p class="s5">Investors should not overlook the ongoing InQubeta (QUBE) presale, as it presents an excellent opportunity to get involved in this promising project. Here are some essential details about the presale:</p>
<p class="s5">- Successful Presale: The InQubeta presale has already raised over $850,000 within a few weeks of its launch, highlighting the strong interest in the project.</p>
<p class="s5">- Multiple Payment Options: The presale accepts various payment systems, including popular cryptocurrencies like BTC, USDT, ETH, BNB, and more. This flexibility ensures accessibility and convenience for a wide range of investors.</p>
<p class="s5">- Inclusive Entry Fee: The presale welcomes participants with a minimum entry fee of $50, making it an inclusive opportunity and promoting decentralized token distribution.</p>
<p class="s5">- Growth Potential: Experts have predicted that InQubeta (QUBE) has the potential to increase its value by up to 50 times before the end of 2023, making it an enticing investment option for long-term gains.</p>
<p></p>
Cardano (ADA): A Must-Have in Every Investor's Portfolio
<p class="s5">Cardano (ADA) is a top cryptocurrency offering unique features and robust fundamentals. Here are some reasons why ADA should be considered a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio:</p>
<p class="s5">1. Proof-of-Stake (PoS) Protocol: Cardano operates on a PoS consensus mechanism, which ensures scalability, energy efficiency, and security. This approach sets Cardano apart from other cryptocurrencies and positions it for long-term success.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Smart Contract Capabilities: Cardano is actively developing its smart contract capabilities, which will enable the creation and execution of decentralized applications (dApps) on its blockchain. This positions ADA to compete with established smart contract platforms.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Robust Ecosystem: Cardano has fostered a vibrant ecosystem with numerous projects, partnerships, and community initiatives. This ecosystem offers a fertile ground for innovation and collaboration, increasing the potential for growth and adoption of ADA.</p>
Conclusion
<p class="s5">Despite the regulatory challenges faced by the crypto market, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have demonstrated resilience and continued their growth trajectory. InQubeta'sdominance in the AI crypto sector, its promising features, and its ongoing presale success position it as an attractive investment option. Cardano's solid fundamentals and active ecosystem make ADA a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio. As the crypto market evolves, these tokens showcase their potential for long-term gains and underline the importance of diversification in the ever-changing landscape of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="s10">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The crypto market has recently experienced a bearish trend that has concerned many investors. This downturn can largely be attributed to the SEC lawsuits against major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase, which have caused significant uncertainty.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, the classification of several tokens as securities has raised concerns about the future of established cryptocurrencies. However, despite these challenges, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have defied the odds and continued their upward growth trajectory. Let's take a closer look at these two tokens and explore their features and growth potential.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE): Dominating the AI Crypto Sector
<p class="s5">InQubeta (QUBE) has garnered significant attention for its advancements in the AI crypto sector. Here are some notable features that make QUBE a promising investment:</p>
<p class="s5">1. AI Integration: InQubeta harnesses the power of artificial intelligence within its blockchain ecosystem. This integration allows for enhanced automation, data analysis, and decision-making processes, positioning QUBE at the forefront of innovation in the AI space.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Diverse Utility: QUBE serves as a utility token within the InQubeta ecosystem, providing access to a wide range of AI-based services and products. These include AI-powered investment strategies, predictive analytics, and personalized recommendations, creating value for token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Strong Community Support: InQubeta has built a vibrant community of supporters and contributors who actively participate in the project's development. The community's collective knowledge and expertise contribute to the ecosystem's ongoing growth and success.</p>
Don't Miss the InQubeta Presale
<p class="s5">Investors should not overlook the ongoing InQubeta (QUBE) presale, as it presents an excellent opportunity to get involved in this promising project. Here are some essential details about the presale:</p>
<p class="s5">- Successful Presale: The InQubeta presale has already raised over $850,000 within a few weeks of its launch, highlighting the strong interest in the project.</p>
<p class="s5">- Multiple Payment Options: The presale accepts various payment systems, including popular cryptocurrencies like BTC, USDT, ETH, BNB, and more. This flexibility ensures accessibility and convenience for a wide range of investors.</p>
<p class="s5">- Inclusive Entry Fee: The presale welcomes participants with a minimum entry fee of $50, making it an inclusive opportunity and promoting decentralized token distribution.</p>
<p class="s5">- Growth Potential: Experts have predicted that InQubeta (QUBE) has the potential to increase its value by up to 50 times before the end of 2023, making it an enticing investment option for long-term gains.</p>
<p></p>
Cardano (ADA): A Must-Have in Every Investor's Portfolio
<p class="s5">Cardano (ADA) is a top cryptocurrency offering unique features and robust fundamentals. Here are some reasons why ADA should be considered a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio:</p>
<p class="s5">1. Proof-of-Stake (PoS) Protocol: Cardano operates on a PoS consensus mechanism, which ensures scalability, energy efficiency, and security. This approach sets Cardano apart from other cryptocurrencies and positions it for long-term success.</p>
<p class="s5">2. Smart Contract Capabilities: Cardano is actively developing its smart contract capabilities, which will enable the creation and execution of decentralized applications (dApps) on its blockchain. This positions ADA to compete with established smart contract platforms.</p>
<p class="s5">3. Robust Ecosystem: Cardano has fostered a vibrant ecosystem with numerous projects, partnerships, and community initiatives. This ecosystem offers a fertile ground for innovation and collaboration, increasing the potential for growth and adoption of ADA.</p>
Conclusion
<p class="s5">Despite the regulatory challenges faced by the crypto market, both InQubeta (QUBE) and Cardano (ADA) have demonstrated resilience and continued their growth trajectory. InQubeta'sdominance in the AI crypto sector, its promising features, and its ongoing presale success position it as an attractive investment option. Cardano's solid fundamentals and active ecosystem make ADA a valuable addition to any investor's portfolio. As the crypto market evolves, these tokens showcase their potential for long-term gains and underline the importance of diversification in the ever-changing landscape of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="s10">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Britanniacoin's Official Pre-release: introducing a unique vision for the future]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/britanniacoins-official-pre-release-introducing-a-unique-vision-for-the-future</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/main_2_1683669032Sm2XnMEnqv.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/main_2_1683669032Sm2XnMEnqv.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/main_2_1683669032Sm2XnMEnqv.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:05:10 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/britanniacoins-official-pre-release-introducing-a-unique-vision-for-the-future</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, July 8th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Aptius Ltd, a British financial enterprise, has developed a new cryptocurrency called BritanniaCoin which will be available for pre-sale from June 18th onwards, ahead of its launch later this year. BritanniaCoin is a British-built blockchain that introduces real-world applications while honouring British cultural heritage.</p><p>The pre-release contains 316,000 coins for sale, fixed at 6 USD per coin, in honour of the official unification of England and Scotland in 1707, 316 years ago. The pre-release presents an opportunity to purchase BritanniaCoin before its launch on exchanges at 8 USD per coin. BritanniaCoin is also launching a software wallet for the public, downloadable on the Apple App Store and Google Play. As part of BritanniaCoin's commitment to charitable causes, 10% of the proceeds from the pre-sale will be donated to charity, as listed on the BritanniaCoin website.</p><p>During its pre-sale this summer, BritanniaCoin intends to give away 125,000 coins. BritanniaCoin is 100% self-funded and developed with no silent partners, as detailed in the white paper. These initiatives aim to foster an ecosystem that represents British values, integrates historic cultural legacy with technological innovation, and supports charitable organizations such as Hearts of Gold to improve the lives of vulnerable people.</p><p>BritanniaCoin introduces a proprietary blockchain with zero fees and a 20% faster block confirmation time than Bitcoin.</p><p>After the 1st round pre-release for commercial customers started in September 2022, BritanniaCoin launched its own bespoke hardware infrastructure. This hardware wallet platform&nbsp;intends to facilitate customer&nbsp;security, anonymity, and technological innovation. This exclusive hardware wallet is currently available to private investors and commercial clients who get in touch via their website. Moreover, the prospect of providing customers of the planned NFT project with access to hardware wallets in the future is something that is currently being considered. Following the completion of its 2nd stage ICO, BritanniaCoin intends to center its blockchain ecosystem, brand identity, and community on this hardware technology basis.</p><p>BritanniaCoin pursues multiple long-term goals, including expanding its community and improving the user experience. In addition, BritanniaCoin has its own British-themed NFT&nbsp;project that provides holders unique advantages, offering access to airdrops, special discounts, voting rights, an active role in selecting which charity institutions to support and signature events, such as their recent pre-release party held at the East India Club.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p>In the aftermath of the ICO,&nbsp;BritanniaCoin intends to launch BritanniaPay, consisting of their software wallet compatible with iOS and Android and connected with the company's current hardware wallet network. BritanniaPay is an innovative new initiative that prioritizes British brands and businesses by integrating blockchain technology into its own payment system. Users can pay for their purchases at various UK and international retailers with BritanniaCoin alongside Bitcoin, Ethereum and other established cryptocurrencies.</p><p>BritanniaCoin unites a diverse team, as the Co-founder and CEO Daniel M. Ashworth brings over five years of experience in the cryptocurrency sector and co-founded Aptius in 2018, a Crypto and Forex trading company. Co-founder and CTO Jonathan Peters has 10 years of programming experience, including blockchain architecture, network infrastructures, and algorithmic trading software. COO Demetri Georgiev has over 10 years of experience in logistics operations and supports the project's day-to-day operations. Events Manager Mark Turley has acquired over 18 years of experience arranging entertainment events and manages the project's unique range of events in magnificent venues, such as the East India club. Charities Co-ordinator Mary Johnston has over 30 years of experience in sales and marketing and is actively involved in Hearts of Gold, the nominated charitable foundation supported by BritanninaCoin.</p><p>For more details about BritanniaCoin, access the project&rsquo;s website.</p><p>About BritanniaCoin</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BritanniaCoin is a cryptocurrency that deploys real-world utilities developed by Aptius Ltd, a British financial organization. Available for pre-sale from June 18th, BritanniaCoin intends to celebrate British cultural heritage.</p>ContactDaniel M. AshworthBritanniacoin Ltdinfo@britanniacoin.org]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, July 8th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Aptius Ltd, a British financial enterprise, has developed a new cryptocurrency called BritanniaCoin which will be available for pre-sale from June 18th onwards, ahead of its launch later this year. BritanniaCoin is a British-built blockchain that introduces real-world applications while honouring British cultural heritage.</p><p>The pre-release contains 316,000 coins for sale, fixed at 6 USD per coin, in honour of the official unification of England and Scotland in 1707, 316 years ago. The pre-release presents an opportunity to purchase BritanniaCoin before its launch on exchanges at 8 USD per coin. BritanniaCoin is also launching a software wallet for the public, downloadable on the Apple App Store and Google Play. As part of BritanniaCoin's commitment to charitable causes, 10% of the proceeds from the pre-sale will be donated to charity, as listed on the BritanniaCoin website.</p><p>During its pre-sale this summer, BritanniaCoin intends to give away 125,000 coins. BritanniaCoin is 100% self-funded and developed with no silent partners, as detailed in the white paper. These initiatives aim to foster an ecosystem that represents British values, integrates historic cultural legacy with technological innovation, and supports charitable organizations such as Hearts of Gold to improve the lives of vulnerable people.</p><p>BritanniaCoin introduces a proprietary blockchain with zero fees and a 20% faster block confirmation time than Bitcoin.</p><p>After the 1st round pre-release for commercial customers started in September 2022, BritanniaCoin launched its own bespoke hardware infrastructure. This hardware wallet platform&nbsp;intends to facilitate customer&nbsp;security, anonymity, and technological innovation. This exclusive hardware wallet is currently available to private investors and commercial clients who get in touch via their website. Moreover, the prospect of providing customers of the planned NFT project with access to hardware wallets in the future is something that is currently being considered. Following the completion of its 2nd stage ICO, BritanniaCoin intends to center its blockchain ecosystem, brand identity, and community on this hardware technology basis.</p><p>BritanniaCoin pursues multiple long-term goals, including expanding its community and improving the user experience. In addition, BritanniaCoin has its own British-themed NFT&nbsp;project that provides holders unique advantages, offering access to airdrops, special discounts, voting rights, an active role in selecting which charity institutions to support and signature events, such as their recent pre-release party held at the East India Club.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p>In the aftermath of the ICO,&nbsp;BritanniaCoin intends to launch BritanniaPay, consisting of their software wallet compatible with iOS and Android and connected with the company's current hardware wallet network. BritanniaPay is an innovative new initiative that prioritizes British brands and businesses by integrating blockchain technology into its own payment system. Users can pay for their purchases at various UK and international retailers with BritanniaCoin alongside Bitcoin, Ethereum and other established cryptocurrencies.</p><p>BritanniaCoin unites a diverse team, as the Co-founder and CEO Daniel M. Ashworth brings over five years of experience in the cryptocurrency sector and co-founded Aptius in 2018, a Crypto and Forex trading company. Co-founder and CTO Jonathan Peters has 10 years of programming experience, including blockchain architecture, network infrastructures, and algorithmic trading software. COO Demetri Georgiev has over 10 years of experience in logistics operations and supports the project's day-to-day operations. Events Manager Mark Turley has acquired over 18 years of experience arranging entertainment events and manages the project's unique range of events in magnificent venues, such as the East India club. Charities Co-ordinator Mary Johnston has over 30 years of experience in sales and marketing and is actively involved in Hearts of Gold, the nominated charitable foundation supported by BritanninaCoin.</p><p>For more details about BritanniaCoin, access the project&rsquo;s website.</p><p>About BritanniaCoin</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BritanniaCoin is a cryptocurrency that deploys real-world utilities developed by Aptius Ltd, a British financial organization. Available for pre-sale from June 18th, BritanniaCoin intends to celebrate British cultural heritage.</p>ContactDaniel M. AshworthBritanniacoin Ltdinfo@britanniacoin.org]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Gemini Sues DCG After Dispute Over Earn Program]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/gemini-sues-dcg-after-dispute-over-earn-program</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/gemini-sues-dcg-after-dispute-over-earn-program</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Gemini is suing DCG, the parent company of bankrupt crypto broker Genesis, after a dispute over the Gemini Earn Program.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exchange decided to sue Digital Currency Group (DCG) and its CEO after the company missed the deadline to agree to a restructuring deal put forward by the Winklevoss twins.</p>
The Restructuring Proposal&nbsp;
<p>Winklevoss twins-founded Gemini exchange had set Thursday afternoon as the deadline for Digital Currency Group and Genesis to agree to a restructuring deal. Gemini stated that if the deal was not agreed to within the specified deadline, it would pursue litigation. Crypto lending firm Genesis had filed for bankruptcy in January following the collapse of key counterparties of the firm, such as FTX, causing it to freeze all redemptions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Genesis&rsquo; lending unit had outlined a plan to exit bankruptcy, it has so far been unable to reach an agreement on a restructuring plan for creditors, to whom it owes over $3 billion. The largest creditor, Winklevoss twins-founded Gemini, is looking to recover around $1.1 billion. In a letter to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, Cameron Winklevoss shared what he called his &ldquo;best and final offer&rdquo; and stated that the deadline for DCG to agree to the proposal was 4 p.m. EDT (2000 GMT) on July 6, adding that he wanted a simple yes or no answer and no further delays or extensions.</p>
<p>The restructuring proposal put forward by Winklevoss included a forbearance payment of $275 million, a debt tranche of $355 million due in two years, and another debt tranche of $835 million due in five years. DCG would also be able to retain the proceeds from the sale of Genesis&rsquo; lending unit.&nbsp;</p>
DCG Misses Deadline, Gemini Sues&nbsp;
<p>However, DCG missed the deadline set by Gemini to agree to the restructuring deal, leading to the latter suing DCG. According to the lawsuit, DCG and its CEO, Barry Silbert, misrepresented the accounting treatment of liabilities that the company had assumed from Genesis. These liabilities stemmed from losses that Genesis suffered after the Singapore-based crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) collapsed. In a long thread on Twitter, Cameron Winklevoss stated that the exchange had filed a lawsuit against DCG and Silbert for personally masterminding a fraud scheme against creditors.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today, @Gemini filed a lawsuit against @DCGco and @BarrySilbert personally in New York court. Barry was not only the architect and mastermind of the DCG and Genesis fraud against creditors; he was directly and personally involved in perpetrating it.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Winklevoss alleged that after Gemini discontinued the Earn program, Silbert reached out to the firm, urging them to continue the program even after knowing that Genesis was &ldquo;massively insolvent.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;When Gemini notified Genesis it would be terminating the Earn program in October 2022, Barry reached out to set up a meeting to induce Gemini to continue Earn. He did this knowing Genesis was massively insolvent. Barry claimed that Genesis faced only a timing issue &ndash; a lie that hid the gaping hole on Genesis&rsquo;s balance sheet.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Winklevoss further alleged that even after the collapse of Three Arrows Capital, Silbert, and other Genesis executives claimed everything was fine because DCG was stepping in to absorb the losses.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;When Three Arrows Capital (3AC) collapsed in June 2022, it blew a $1.2 billion hole in Genesis&rsquo;s balance sheet. Instead of coming clean, Genesis claimed that everything was business as usual because DCG had stepped in to absorb the losses. It&rsquo;s now clear this was a carefully crafted lie.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Gemini co-founder went on to allege that DCG, Silbert, and other Genesis executives conspired to create false financial reports to mislead creditors.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Barry, DCG, and Genesis all conspired to create false financial reports to hide the truth from Gemini and creditors. One report pretended that this phony 10-YEAR promissory note was a &lsquo;Current Asset.&rsquo; A total lie and complete misrepresentation. A falsified balance sheet pretended that the note was a &lsquo;receivable&rsquo; with a value of $1.1 billion. Another lie.&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, in a statement, A DCG spokesperson reiterated that DCG expects to close the Genesis bankruptcy case soon enough.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Any suggestion of wrongdoing by DCG or any of its employees is baseless, defamatory, and completely false. From day one, DCG has remained committed to reaching an amicable solution for all parties to the Genesis bankruptcy.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Gemini is suing DCG, the parent company of bankrupt crypto broker Genesis, after a dispute over the Gemini Earn Program.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exchange decided to sue Digital Currency Group (DCG) and its CEO after the company missed the deadline to agree to a restructuring deal put forward by the Winklevoss twins.</p>
The Restructuring Proposal&nbsp;
<p>Winklevoss twins-founded Gemini exchange had set Thursday afternoon as the deadline for Digital Currency Group and Genesis to agree to a restructuring deal. Gemini stated that if the deal was not agreed to within the specified deadline, it would pursue litigation. Crypto lending firm Genesis had filed for bankruptcy in January following the collapse of key counterparties of the firm, such as FTX, causing it to freeze all redemptions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While Genesis&rsquo; lending unit had outlined a plan to exit bankruptcy, it has so far been unable to reach an agreement on a restructuring plan for creditors, to whom it owes over $3 billion. The largest creditor, Winklevoss twins-founded Gemini, is looking to recover around $1.1 billion. In a letter to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, Cameron Winklevoss shared what he called his &ldquo;best and final offer&rdquo; and stated that the deadline for DCG to agree to the proposal was 4 p.m. EDT (2000 GMT) on July 6, adding that he wanted a simple yes or no answer and no further delays or extensions.</p>
<p>The restructuring proposal put forward by Winklevoss included a forbearance payment of $275 million, a debt tranche of $355 million due in two years, and another debt tranche of $835 million due in five years. DCG would also be able to retain the proceeds from the sale of Genesis&rsquo; lending unit.&nbsp;</p>
DCG Misses Deadline, Gemini Sues&nbsp;
<p>However, DCG missed the deadline set by Gemini to agree to the restructuring deal, leading to the latter suing DCG. According to the lawsuit, DCG and its CEO, Barry Silbert, misrepresented the accounting treatment of liabilities that the company had assumed from Genesis. These liabilities stemmed from losses that Genesis suffered after the Singapore-based crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) collapsed. In a long thread on Twitter, Cameron Winklevoss stated that the exchange had filed a lawsuit against DCG and Silbert for personally masterminding a fraud scheme against creditors.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today, @Gemini filed a lawsuit against @DCGco and @BarrySilbert personally in New York court. Barry was not only the architect and mastermind of the DCG and Genesis fraud against creditors; he was directly and personally involved in perpetrating it.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Winklevoss alleged that after Gemini discontinued the Earn program, Silbert reached out to the firm, urging them to continue the program even after knowing that Genesis was &ldquo;massively insolvent.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;When Gemini notified Genesis it would be terminating the Earn program in October 2022, Barry reached out to set up a meeting to induce Gemini to continue Earn. He did this knowing Genesis was massively insolvent. Barry claimed that Genesis faced only a timing issue &ndash; a lie that hid the gaping hole on Genesis&rsquo;s balance sheet.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Winklevoss further alleged that even after the collapse of Three Arrows Capital, Silbert, and other Genesis executives claimed everything was fine because DCG was stepping in to absorb the losses.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;When Three Arrows Capital (3AC) collapsed in June 2022, it blew a $1.2 billion hole in Genesis&rsquo;s balance sheet. Instead of coming clean, Genesis claimed that everything was business as usual because DCG had stepped in to absorb the losses. It&rsquo;s now clear this was a carefully crafted lie.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Gemini co-founder went on to allege that DCG, Silbert, and other Genesis executives conspired to create false financial reports to mislead creditors.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Barry, DCG, and Genesis all conspired to create false financial reports to hide the truth from Gemini and creditors. One report pretended that this phony 10-YEAR promissory note was a &lsquo;Current Asset.&rsquo; A total lie and complete misrepresentation. A falsified balance sheet pretended that the note was a &lsquo;receivable&rsquo; with a value of $1.1 billion. Another lie.&rdquo;</p>

<p>However, in a statement, A DCG spokesperson reiterated that DCG expects to close the Genesis bankruptcy case soon enough.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Any suggestion of wrongdoing by DCG or any of its employees is baseless, defamatory, and completely false. From day one, DCG has remained committed to reaching an amicable solution for all parties to the Genesis bankruptcy.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Google Cloud Taps Into Voltage To Offer Bitcoin $BTC Services]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/google-cloud-taps-into-voltage-to-offer-bitcoin-btc-services</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/google-cloud-x-voltage-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/google-cloud-x-voltage-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/google-cloud-x-voltage-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/google-cloud-taps-into-voltage-to-offer-bitcoin-btc-services</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Google Cloud's recently announced a partnership with infrastructure provider Voltage, unveiling a new trajectory for the tech giant's Bitcoin and Lightning ambitions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The agreement will enable Google Cloud, a $225-billion data and cloud service, to extend Bitcoin-related services worldwide while assisting Voltage's global operations expansion.</p>
Google&rsquo;s Outsourced Bitcoin and Lightning Team
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The collaboration sees Voltage functioning as Google's outsourced Bitcoin and Lightning team. Voltage CEO, Graham Krizek, explained that the infrastructure provider will facilitate Bitcoin or Lightning integration for companies interested in these services via Google. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The deal has not only generated substantial social media interest but also signals Google&rsquo;s evolving recognition of Bitcoin and Lightning's potential. This increased attention isn't isolated within Google alone, but industry-wide. Christopher Calicott, managing director of venture capital firm Tramell Venture Partners, suggested that any corporation adjacent to payments "would ignore Lightning at their peril."</p>
Google Ventures Fueling Bitcoin Momentum
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Google's interests in blockchain, Bitcoin, and Web3 companies have been increasingly apparent since 2020, primarily via Google Ventures (GV), its investment arm. Voltage benefited from GV's interest, receiving participation in a $6-million seed round in 2021. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This significant financial backing is seen as an indication of the rising momentum for Bitcoin and related technologies. Calicott pointed out that when companies invest, it sends a potent signal of their focus, adding weight to the Bitcoin and Lightning narrative. Krizek concurred, stating that the partnership is indicative of an increased Bitcoin focus strategy within larger organizations, including Google. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite its competitor, Apple, showing an aversion to Lightning by recently delisting Damus, a Lightning-friendly decentralized social media protocol, the Lightning Network is gaining traction among billion-dollar businesses globally. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Both Binance and Coinbase, two leading crypto exchanges, have recently committed to Lightning integrations. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Google Cloud's partnership with Voltage marks a significant step towards further integrating Bitcoin and Lightning technologies within the wider tech industry. With the growing corporate interest and investment in these areas, the expectation for further services rollout, along with expanded efforts in Bitcoin education, continues to rise.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Google Cloud's recently announced a partnership with infrastructure provider Voltage, unveiling a new trajectory for the tech giant's Bitcoin and Lightning ambitions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The agreement will enable Google Cloud, a $225-billion data and cloud service, to extend Bitcoin-related services worldwide while assisting Voltage's global operations expansion.</p>
Google&rsquo;s Outsourced Bitcoin and Lightning Team
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The collaboration sees Voltage functioning as Google's outsourced Bitcoin and Lightning team. Voltage CEO, Graham Krizek, explained that the infrastructure provider will facilitate Bitcoin or Lightning integration for companies interested in these services via Google. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The deal has not only generated substantial social media interest but also signals Google&rsquo;s evolving recognition of Bitcoin and Lightning's potential. This increased attention isn't isolated within Google alone, but industry-wide. Christopher Calicott, managing director of venture capital firm Tramell Venture Partners, suggested that any corporation adjacent to payments "would ignore Lightning at their peril."</p>
Google Ventures Fueling Bitcoin Momentum
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Google's interests in blockchain, Bitcoin, and Web3 companies have been increasingly apparent since 2020, primarily via Google Ventures (GV), its investment arm. Voltage benefited from GV's interest, receiving participation in a $6-million seed round in 2021. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This significant financial backing is seen as an indication of the rising momentum for Bitcoin and related technologies. Calicott pointed out that when companies invest, it sends a potent signal of their focus, adding weight to the Bitcoin and Lightning narrative. Krizek concurred, stating that the partnership is indicative of an increased Bitcoin focus strategy within larger organizations, including Google. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite its competitor, Apple, showing an aversion to Lightning by recently delisting Damus, a Lightning-friendly decentralized social media protocol, the Lightning Network is gaining traction among billion-dollar businesses globally. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Both Binance and Coinbase, two leading crypto exchanges, have recently committed to Lightning integrations. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Google Cloud's partnership with Voltage marks a significant step towards further integrating Bitcoin and Lightning technologies within the wider tech industry. With the growing corporate interest and investment in these areas, the expectation for further services rollout, along with expanded efforts in Bitcoin education, continues to rise.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Lightning Labs Integrates AI For Bitcoin Transactions $BTC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lightning-labs-integrates-ai-for-bitcoin-transactions-btc</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lightning-labs-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lightning-labs-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lightning-labs-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lightning-labs-integrates-ai-for-bitcoin-transactions-btc</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Lightning Labs, the primary Bitcoin Lightning Network development firm, has rolled out a revolutionary set of tools designed for artificial intelligence (AI) applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These tools enable AI applications to directly interact with Bitcoin transactions on the network's layer-2 solution, including sending, receiving, and holding Bitcoin. </p>
Unveiling an AI-Compatible Toolkit 
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Introduced on July 6, this toolkit stands to significantly benefit Large Language Models (LLMs)&mdash;software applications trained on extensive datasets to generate human-like responses. By integrating these new tools, LLMs can bypass traditional payment processes, making transactions faster, cheaper, and enabling pay-per-use AI models on the lightning network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The toolkit is built on two key components&mdash;the "L402 protocol" and "Langchain". The L402 protocol is an authentication mechanism unique to the Lightning Network, designed to streamline payments within the network. Langchain, on the other hand, is a library that simplifies AI application operations. </p>
Enhancing Accessibility and Interactions
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This suite of tools aims to increase the accessibility of AI infrastructure for both humans and autonomous AI agents. A significant feature, LangChainBitcoin, allows Langchain agents to interact directly with Bitcoin and the Lightning Network. This interaction includes capabilities such as holding a Bitcoin balance and sending/receiving Bitcoin on Lightning, functionalities made possible through the recently released OpenAI GPT function calls. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This development is especially impactful for the fast-growing class of AI agents, which previously encountered difficulties accessing traditional fiat payment systems due to their lack of official registration with any nation. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These, whole developers and AI agents increasingly adopt and explore these new capabilities, open for the potential and transformative impact of such an innovation to be fully realized, marking an important moment in the advancement of the crypto industry in general.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In particular industry-wise, the rollout of these tools by Lightning Labs represents a major stride in the integration of AI and Bitcoin transactions. As the current capacity of the Lightning Network stands at 5,432 BTC, approximately $163.5 million, these tools provide significant opportunities for developers operating in these fields.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Lightning Labs, the primary Bitcoin Lightning Network development firm, has rolled out a revolutionary set of tools designed for artificial intelligence (AI) applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These tools enable AI applications to directly interact with Bitcoin transactions on the network's layer-2 solution, including sending, receiving, and holding Bitcoin. </p>
Unveiling an AI-Compatible Toolkit 
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Introduced on July 6, this toolkit stands to significantly benefit Large Language Models (LLMs)&mdash;software applications trained on extensive datasets to generate human-like responses. By integrating these new tools, LLMs can bypass traditional payment processes, making transactions faster, cheaper, and enabling pay-per-use AI models on the lightning network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The toolkit is built on two key components&mdash;the "L402 protocol" and "Langchain". The L402 protocol is an authentication mechanism unique to the Lightning Network, designed to streamline payments within the network. Langchain, on the other hand, is a library that simplifies AI application operations. </p>
Enhancing Accessibility and Interactions
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This suite of tools aims to increase the accessibility of AI infrastructure for both humans and autonomous AI agents. A significant feature, LangChainBitcoin, allows Langchain agents to interact directly with Bitcoin and the Lightning Network. This interaction includes capabilities such as holding a Bitcoin balance and sending/receiving Bitcoin on Lightning, functionalities made possible through the recently released OpenAI GPT function calls. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This development is especially impactful for the fast-growing class of AI agents, which previously encountered difficulties accessing traditional fiat payment systems due to their lack of official registration with any nation. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These, whole developers and AI agents increasingly adopt and explore these new capabilities, open for the potential and transformative impact of such an innovation to be fully realized, marking an important moment in the advancement of the crypto industry in general.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In particular industry-wise, the rollout of these tools by Lightning Labs represents a major stride in the integration of AI and Bitcoin transactions. As the current capacity of the Lightning Network stands at 5,432 BTC, approximately $163.5 million, these tools provide significant opportunities for developers operating in these fields.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Prepares For Next Rally, Tradecurve Leads the Altcoin Pump with 80%]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-btc-prepares-for-next-rally-tradecurve-leads-the-altcoin-pump-with-80</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-90.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-90.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-90.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-btc-prepares-for-next-rally-tradecurve-leads-the-altcoin-pump-with-80</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>It has been a bullish month for Bitcoin (BTC) so far, with the cryptocurrency peaking at $31,486 before settling in the $30k range. But while Bitcoin (BTC) prepares for the next rally, it appears that Tradecurve &mdash; a new cryptocurrency trading platform &mdash; is leading the altcoin pump with 80% gains during the ongoing presale. Let's look at why these two assets are so bullish.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve: More Gains Ahead?
<p>Tradecurve is shaping up to be a comprehensive trading platform that offers a wide array of investment options &mdash; think stocks, commodities, currencies, and indices &mdash; all under one roof. The aim is to offer a one-stop-shop for users to manage their diverse investment portfolios, irrespective of where they are in the world.</p>
<p>The beauty of Tradecurve lies in its simplicity. Joining the platform is as easy as providing an email and linking your DeFi wallet. There's no need to go through the usual hoops of identity verification or other cumbersome onboarding procedures, making it a breath of fresh air in the otherwise intrusive investment landscape.</p>
<p>Beyond just trading, Tradecurve also offers an arsenal of advanced tools designed to amplify your trading experience and potential returns. They offer a subscription to an AI-powered trading tool, for instance, that automates trading strategies and offers in-depth analytics on all markets.</p>
<p>The TCRV token, the lifeblood of the Tradecurve platform, also unlocks a host of benefits. Holders can stake tokens to earn passive income, avail of VIP account benefits, get discounts on subscription fees, and more as Tradecurve continues to establish itself in the DeFi world.</p>
<p>At present, the TCRV token is available at a bargain price of $0.018 during the presale. Considering that experts predict the value of the token could skyrocket to $1.00 after its listing on leading exchanges later this year, this presale might just be a golden opportunity to jump on board the Tradecurve bandwagon.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) To $40K?
<p>Tradecurve isn't the only digital asset in the spotlight &mdash; Bitcoin (BTC) is preparing for its next rally and could hit $40,000 in July. This prediction comes from noted crypto analysts who suggest that an influx of institutional investors could push Bitcoin (BTC) prices to fresh all-time highs.</p>
<p>This news was triggered by the news that Blackrock, the largest global asset manager in the world, recently filed an Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) for Bitcoin (BTC). This significant move signals Wall Streets' increasing confidence in Bitcoin (BTC), marking a pivotal moment in the cryptocurrency sphere.</p>
<p>While this news should have long-term impacts, Bitcoin (BTC)'s price has already pushed from $28.4k to a peak of just above $31k within a week. Analysts are watching closely, speculating this news could herald the onset of a new bull market for Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<p>You see, approval of the Bitcoin ETF could trigger a substantial flow of capital into the crypto market. ETFs present an opportunity for traditional and institutional investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin without the need to personally buy, store, and manage the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>However, they caution that for this upward trajectory to continue, Bitcoin (BTC) will first need to break through the $31-32k resistance level. The current price of $30,600 has the market bullish, with many anticipating a breakout and pump to the $36,000 - $40,000 range within days.</p>
<p>To find more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token, visit the links below:</p>
<p>Click Here For the Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been a bullish month for Bitcoin (BTC) so far, with the cryptocurrency peaking at $31,486 before settling in the $30k range. But while Bitcoin (BTC) prepares for the next rally, it appears that Tradecurve &mdash; a new cryptocurrency trading platform &mdash; is leading the altcoin pump with 80% gains during the ongoing presale. Let's look at why these two assets are so bullish.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve: More Gains Ahead?
<p>Tradecurve is shaping up to be a comprehensive trading platform that offers a wide array of investment options &mdash; think stocks, commodities, currencies, and indices &mdash; all under one roof. The aim is to offer a one-stop-shop for users to manage their diverse investment portfolios, irrespective of where they are in the world.</p>
<p>The beauty of Tradecurve lies in its simplicity. Joining the platform is as easy as providing an email and linking your DeFi wallet. There's no need to go through the usual hoops of identity verification or other cumbersome onboarding procedures, making it a breath of fresh air in the otherwise intrusive investment landscape.</p>
<p>Beyond just trading, Tradecurve also offers an arsenal of advanced tools designed to amplify your trading experience and potential returns. They offer a subscription to an AI-powered trading tool, for instance, that automates trading strategies and offers in-depth analytics on all markets.</p>
<p>The TCRV token, the lifeblood of the Tradecurve platform, also unlocks a host of benefits. Holders can stake tokens to earn passive income, avail of VIP account benefits, get discounts on subscription fees, and more as Tradecurve continues to establish itself in the DeFi world.</p>
<p>At present, the TCRV token is available at a bargain price of $0.018 during the presale. Considering that experts predict the value of the token could skyrocket to $1.00 after its listing on leading exchanges later this year, this presale might just be a golden opportunity to jump on board the Tradecurve bandwagon.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) To $40K?
<p>Tradecurve isn't the only digital asset in the spotlight &mdash; Bitcoin (BTC) is preparing for its next rally and could hit $40,000 in July. This prediction comes from noted crypto analysts who suggest that an influx of institutional investors could push Bitcoin (BTC) prices to fresh all-time highs.</p>
<p>This news was triggered by the news that Blackrock, the largest global asset manager in the world, recently filed an Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) for Bitcoin (BTC). This significant move signals Wall Streets' increasing confidence in Bitcoin (BTC), marking a pivotal moment in the cryptocurrency sphere.</p>
<p>While this news should have long-term impacts, Bitcoin (BTC)'s price has already pushed from $28.4k to a peak of just above $31k within a week. Analysts are watching closely, speculating this news could herald the onset of a new bull market for Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<p>You see, approval of the Bitcoin ETF could trigger a substantial flow of capital into the crypto market. ETFs present an opportunity for traditional and institutional investors to gain exposure to Bitcoin without the need to personally buy, store, and manage the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>However, they caution that for this upward trajectory to continue, Bitcoin (BTC) will first need to break through the $31-32k resistance level. The current price of $30,600 has the market bullish, with many anticipating a breakout and pump to the $36,000 - $40,000 range within days.</p>
<p>To find more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token, visit the links below:</p>
<p>Click Here For the Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Best Crypto To Buy Now Not Named Bitcoin]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/best-crypto-to-buy-now-not-named-bitcoin</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-648.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-648.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-648.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/best-crypto-to-buy-now-not-named-bitcoin</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the crypto market's meteoric rise, more people are keen to explore cryptocurrencies beyond the typical Bitcoin investment. This burgeoning interest is further piqued by the myriad of projects that have sprung up, each promising unique value propositions and significant ROI. While the sheer volume of altcoins can be daunting to newcomers, this article will explore the seven best crypto to buy now not named Bitcoin. From altcoins specializing in fractionalized NFT investing, play-to-earn gaming rewards, and enhancing DeFi connectivity to revolutionizing rendering processes, these coins offer a diversified investment portfolio for beginners and experienced investors.</p>
Best Crypto To Buy Now Not Named Bitcoin
<p>Beyond Bitcoin, the crypto market brims with promising altcoins, each representing unique value propositions. Seven standout tokens include InQubeta, pioneering fractionalized NFT investing in AI startups; DigiToads, intertwining play-to-earn gaming with NFTs; Manifold Finance, augmenting DeFi connectivity; Ocean Protocol, democratizing data access; Trust Wallet Token, driving a popular wallet ecosystem; Render, revolutionizing rendering processes; and Litecoin, an enduring alternative to Bitcoin. These diverse tokens offer profitable investment opportunities for every investor's portfolio.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE) -&nbsp; Best Altcoin For Fractionalized NFT Investing
<p>A game-changing project in the cryptocurrency space, InQubeta has set its sights on changing how we invest in AI startups. With the QUBE token at its core, InQubeta offers an innovative and sophisticated platform for fractionalized investment in AI enterprises. Its groundbreaking approach allows even the smallest investors to have a stake in some of the most promising AI projects in the industry.</p>
<p>InQubeta leverages the power of Web3 to bring to life the world's first fractionalized AI NFT crowdfunding platform. The platform turns investment opportunities into Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs), which can then be fractionalized and distributed to investors. This revolutionary approach to fundraising means that everyone can get a piece of the AI startup action, thereby democratizing investment and engaging a broader community of stakeholders.</p>
<p>The QUBE token is an integral part of the InQubeta ecosystem. It is a deflationary token, meaning its supply reduces over time due to a burning mechanism. Thus, 2% of QUBE token sales and 1% of purchases are burned, ensuring scarcity and helping to bolster the token's value over time. The token is vested over 12 weeks.</p>
<p>InQubeta has its own custom-built NFT marketplace, which allows AI startups to raise funds and offer reward and equity-based NFTs to their investors. By purchasing QUBE tokens, holders can directly invest in these promising projects, fostering a thriving ecosystem and generating potential returns, with experts anticipating the price of QUBE to rise more than 5x after the presale.</p>
<p></p>
DigiToads (TOADS) - Play-to-Earn (P2E) Gaming and Rewards
<p>DigiToads operates as a full utility meme coin with a unique play-to-earn (P2E) gaming aspect, setting it apart as one of the best cryptos for beginners looking to delve into the NFT space. The P2E model incorporates a fascinating web3 game where players can collect, nurture, and battle DigiToads, adding an interactive dimension to this cryptocurrency investment. These digital amphibians can be acquired through buying, trading, or winning, making TOADS tokens an integral part of the gaming ecosystem. These tokens purchase various items, including food, potions, and training equipment for the DigiToads, creating an engaging virtual environment for players.</p>
<p>This play-to-earn feature extends beyond mere gaming; it provides a pathway for players to earn TOADS tokens, one of the top crypto coins to buy today. The DigiToads game rewards the top 25% of players on the leaderboard with TOADS tokens, creating a competitive environment that incentivizes player performance. Furthermore, 50% of the funds obtained from in-game item sales are allocated to the prize fund for distribution among the top 25% of players. Therefore, the game design caters to a fun and competitive player experience and serves as an avenue for participants to earn cryptocurrency rewards.</p>
<p>Considering the high-growth potential of TOADS tokens, they are arguably one of the best cryptos to invest in now. The P2E model is up-and-coming for those wondering what crypto to invest in, as the DigiToads project offers a direct earning potential through gameplay. Moreover, the regular prize pool payouts to top performers in the game underscore the potential returns for skilled and dedicated players. As the popularity of P2E gaming continues to rise, DigiToads is positioned as a leading project in this innovative intersection of gaming and crypto investments. It is one of the most promising presales to buy now that can experience over 450% growth in the near future.</p>
<p></p>
&nbsp;Manifold Finance ($FOLD): Enhancing DeFi Connectivity
<p>The crypto world undeniably provides opportunities for beginners, especially those keen to dive into DeFi projects. Manifold Finance ($FOLD) is the best crypto for beginners. Born as a middleware product, $FOLD is designed to augment connectivity between DeFi protocols and safeguard users from MEV (Maximal Extractable Value) attacks&mdash;a high value feature for anyone venturing into crypto. The functionality to shield users from MEV attacks has been the first offering in the Manifold Finance product line. MEV refers to the profit potential by changing the order of transactions within a block. In this area, miners or validators enjoy the power to choose transactions for inclusion in blocks.</p>
<p>Selected as a promising cryptocurrency for beginners, $FOLD&mdash;through its product, OpenMEV&mdash;provides security against sandwich attacks, a common MEV attack. Sandwich attacks occur when a trader places transactions before and after a victim transaction, capturing the price difference. OpenMEV shields users from such exploitations, returning funds and fees to traders. Utilizing MEV opportunities, OpenMEV employs secure smart contract techniques to scale services like SushiSwap for end-users, an invaluable aspect for beginner cryptocurrency investors seeking the best crypto to invest in.</p>
Ocean Protocol (OCEAN) - Best Altcoin For Democratising Access to Data
<p>OCEAN, an ERC20 token, is undoubtedly a standout in the crypto space, aiming to democratize access to data. This initiative presents the potential to challenge tech giants such as Google and Facebook, making it one of the best cryptos to invest in now. Ocean Protocol enables data owners to sell their information through the Ocean Market app, providing consumers with previously inaccessible private data. This offers AI practitioners and data scientists advantages, granting access to more data, crypto-secured provenance, and income opportunities.</p>
<p>Fulfilling the top crypto to buy criteria, OCEAN's utilization in buying and selling data, governance, and staking makes it a hot contender. The Ocean Protocol was founded in 2017 by Bruce Pon and Trent McConaghy. It aims to democratize data, enhance AI capabilities, and spread the benefits of artificial intelligence. OCEAN has a capped max supply of 1.41 billion tokens. A portion was allocated for community projects and burning a fraction of network revenue&mdash;elements worth considering when deciding on the best cryptocurrency to buy today.</p>
Trust Wallet Token (TWT) - Top Cryptocurrency Wallet Ecosystem
<p>Trust Wallet Token (TWT) should be on the radar for those considering which crypto to buy. The TWT token is the official token of Trust Wallet, a mobile-based cryptocurrency wallet that boasts extensive support for over 250,000 distinct assets across 33 blockchains&mdash;an ideal choice for anyone looking to make the best crypto investments. The "Earn" feature in the Trust Wallet allows users to generate passive income simply by pressing a button. Accessibility is central to Trust Wallet's design, with no KYC verification or barriers to trading cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>TWT, a token based on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), is fast garnering attention, mainly due to the benefits it offers its holders. These include participating in governance activities, voting on crucial decisions for the Trust Wallet app, and receiving discounts for buying cryptocurrencies within the ecosystem&mdash;elements seriously worthy of consideration for those figuring out what crypto to invest in.</p>
Render (RNDR): Revolutionizing the Rendering Process
<p>Render, an innovative platform revolutionizing the rendering process, connects artists and GPU providers. This is achieved through the power of blockchain and cutting-edge technologies. The platform streamlines the creation of high-quality 3D graphics and animations. Artists can access powerful GPUs to render their works at affordable costs, using RNDR tokens to pay for the rendering services. This platform has applications across multiple sectors, including film, gaming, and architecture, making it an exciting prospect for those looking for the best coin to invest in.</p>
<p>The RNDR token, based on the Ethereum blockchain, is used as a medium of exchange on the Render network. For those asking, "What crypto should I buy?", RNDR offers an interesting proposition. This is due to its unique proposition, linking providers of GPU power with those who need it, combined with its potential to disrupt the rendering industry. By tokenizing GPU power, Render allows miners to monetize their idle resources, making RNDR one of the top 5 cryptocurrencies for individuals looking to invest in a transformative project.</p>
Litecoin (LTC): The Silver to Bitcoin's Gold
<p>Litecoin (LTC) has been prominent in cryptocurrency since its inception in 2011. The "silver to Bitcoin's gold" is what makes Litecoin one of the best digital currencies for boosting their portfolio. An open-source project based on the Bitcoin protocol, Litecoin features several significant improvements, such as a faster block generation time and a different hashing algorithm.</p>
<p>With its longevity in the crypto market and the backing of an active developer community, Litecoin continues to be an appealing option for investors. Buying LTC offers a robust entry point for those wondering how to get into cryptocurrency. It is widely available on most cryptocurrency exchanges, enjoys high liquidity, and can be used for various applications, including online shopping and forex trading. Given these features, Litecoin is undeniably one of the best cryptocurrencies to buy now.</p>
Best Crypto To Buy Now Not Named Bitcoin - Conclusion
<p>While Bitcoin remains a dominant force in the space, it's clear that the market is teeming with diverse and promising altcoins that offer unique value propositions. InQubeta, DigiToads, Manifold Finance, Ocean Protocol, Trust Wallet Token, Render, and Litecoin are just a few examples of cryptocurrencies that have carved a niche in this expansive universe. These tokens represent an array of innovative technologies and concepts ranging from play-to-earn gaming, democratizing data access, and enhancing DeFi connectivity to fractionalized NFT investing. Thus, by expanding investment horizons beyond Bitcoin, investors can tap into a range of potentially rewarding opportunities and help to drive forward the next wave of crypto-innovation. </p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;Join InQubeta Communities</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the crypto market's meteoric rise, more people are keen to explore cryptocurrencies beyond the typical Bitcoin investment. This burgeoning interest is further piqued by the myriad of projects that have sprung up, each promising unique value propositions and significant ROI. While the sheer volume of altcoins can be daunting to newcomers, this article will explore the seven best crypto to buy now not named Bitcoin. From altcoins specializing in fractionalized NFT investing, play-to-earn gaming rewards, and enhancing DeFi connectivity to revolutionizing rendering processes, these coins offer a diversified investment portfolio for beginners and experienced investors.</p>
Best Crypto To Buy Now Not Named Bitcoin
<p>Beyond Bitcoin, the crypto market brims with promising altcoins, each representing unique value propositions. Seven standout tokens include InQubeta, pioneering fractionalized NFT investing in AI startups; DigiToads, intertwining play-to-earn gaming with NFTs; Manifold Finance, augmenting DeFi connectivity; Ocean Protocol, democratizing data access; Trust Wallet Token, driving a popular wallet ecosystem; Render, revolutionizing rendering processes; and Litecoin, an enduring alternative to Bitcoin. These diverse tokens offer profitable investment opportunities for every investor's portfolio.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE) -&nbsp; Best Altcoin For Fractionalized NFT Investing
<p>A game-changing project in the cryptocurrency space, InQubeta has set its sights on changing how we invest in AI startups. With the QUBE token at its core, InQubeta offers an innovative and sophisticated platform for fractionalized investment in AI enterprises. Its groundbreaking approach allows even the smallest investors to have a stake in some of the most promising AI projects in the industry.</p>
<p>InQubeta leverages the power of Web3 to bring to life the world's first fractionalized AI NFT crowdfunding platform. The platform turns investment opportunities into Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs), which can then be fractionalized and distributed to investors. This revolutionary approach to fundraising means that everyone can get a piece of the AI startup action, thereby democratizing investment and engaging a broader community of stakeholders.</p>
<p>The QUBE token is an integral part of the InQubeta ecosystem. It is a deflationary token, meaning its supply reduces over time due to a burning mechanism. Thus, 2% of QUBE token sales and 1% of purchases are burned, ensuring scarcity and helping to bolster the token's value over time. The token is vested over 12 weeks.</p>
<p>InQubeta has its own custom-built NFT marketplace, which allows AI startups to raise funds and offer reward and equity-based NFTs to their investors. By purchasing QUBE tokens, holders can directly invest in these promising projects, fostering a thriving ecosystem and generating potential returns, with experts anticipating the price of QUBE to rise more than 5x after the presale.</p>
<p></p>
DigiToads (TOADS) - Play-to-Earn (P2E) Gaming and Rewards
<p>DigiToads operates as a full utility meme coin with a unique play-to-earn (P2E) gaming aspect, setting it apart as one of the best cryptos for beginners looking to delve into the NFT space. The P2E model incorporates a fascinating web3 game where players can collect, nurture, and battle DigiToads, adding an interactive dimension to this cryptocurrency investment. These digital amphibians can be acquired through buying, trading, or winning, making TOADS tokens an integral part of the gaming ecosystem. These tokens purchase various items, including food, potions, and training equipment for the DigiToads, creating an engaging virtual environment for players.</p>
<p>This play-to-earn feature extends beyond mere gaming; it provides a pathway for players to earn TOADS tokens, one of the top crypto coins to buy today. The DigiToads game rewards the top 25% of players on the leaderboard with TOADS tokens, creating a competitive environment that incentivizes player performance. Furthermore, 50% of the funds obtained from in-game item sales are allocated to the prize fund for distribution among the top 25% of players. Therefore, the game design caters to a fun and competitive player experience and serves as an avenue for participants to earn cryptocurrency rewards.</p>
<p>Considering the high-growth potential of TOADS tokens, they are arguably one of the best cryptos to invest in now. The P2E model is up-and-coming for those wondering what crypto to invest in, as the DigiToads project offers a direct earning potential through gameplay. Moreover, the regular prize pool payouts to top performers in the game underscore the potential returns for skilled and dedicated players. As the popularity of P2E gaming continues to rise, DigiToads is positioned as a leading project in this innovative intersection of gaming and crypto investments. It is one of the most promising presales to buy now that can experience over 450% growth in the near future.</p>
<p></p>
&nbsp;Manifold Finance ($FOLD): Enhancing DeFi Connectivity
<p>The crypto world undeniably provides opportunities for beginners, especially those keen to dive into DeFi projects. Manifold Finance ($FOLD) is the best crypto for beginners. Born as a middleware product, $FOLD is designed to augment connectivity between DeFi protocols and safeguard users from MEV (Maximal Extractable Value) attacks&mdash;a high value feature for anyone venturing into crypto. The functionality to shield users from MEV attacks has been the first offering in the Manifold Finance product line. MEV refers to the profit potential by changing the order of transactions within a block. In this area, miners or validators enjoy the power to choose transactions for inclusion in blocks.</p>
<p>Selected as a promising cryptocurrency for beginners, $FOLD&mdash;through its product, OpenMEV&mdash;provides security against sandwich attacks, a common MEV attack. Sandwich attacks occur when a trader places transactions before and after a victim transaction, capturing the price difference. OpenMEV shields users from such exploitations, returning funds and fees to traders. Utilizing MEV opportunities, OpenMEV employs secure smart contract techniques to scale services like SushiSwap for end-users, an invaluable aspect for beginner cryptocurrency investors seeking the best crypto to invest in.</p>
Ocean Protocol (OCEAN) - Best Altcoin For Democratising Access to Data
<p>OCEAN, an ERC20 token, is undoubtedly a standout in the crypto space, aiming to democratize access to data. This initiative presents the potential to challenge tech giants such as Google and Facebook, making it one of the best cryptos to invest in now. Ocean Protocol enables data owners to sell their information through the Ocean Market app, providing consumers with previously inaccessible private data. This offers AI practitioners and data scientists advantages, granting access to more data, crypto-secured provenance, and income opportunities.</p>
<p>Fulfilling the top crypto to buy criteria, OCEAN's utilization in buying and selling data, governance, and staking makes it a hot contender. The Ocean Protocol was founded in 2017 by Bruce Pon and Trent McConaghy. It aims to democratize data, enhance AI capabilities, and spread the benefits of artificial intelligence. OCEAN has a capped max supply of 1.41 billion tokens. A portion was allocated for community projects and burning a fraction of network revenue&mdash;elements worth considering when deciding on the best cryptocurrency to buy today.</p>
Trust Wallet Token (TWT) - Top Cryptocurrency Wallet Ecosystem
<p>Trust Wallet Token (TWT) should be on the radar for those considering which crypto to buy. The TWT token is the official token of Trust Wallet, a mobile-based cryptocurrency wallet that boasts extensive support for over 250,000 distinct assets across 33 blockchains&mdash;an ideal choice for anyone looking to make the best crypto investments. The "Earn" feature in the Trust Wallet allows users to generate passive income simply by pressing a button. Accessibility is central to Trust Wallet's design, with no KYC verification or barriers to trading cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>TWT, a token based on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), is fast garnering attention, mainly due to the benefits it offers its holders. These include participating in governance activities, voting on crucial decisions for the Trust Wallet app, and receiving discounts for buying cryptocurrencies within the ecosystem&mdash;elements seriously worthy of consideration for those figuring out what crypto to invest in.</p>
Render (RNDR): Revolutionizing the Rendering Process
<p>Render, an innovative platform revolutionizing the rendering process, connects artists and GPU providers. This is achieved through the power of blockchain and cutting-edge technologies. The platform streamlines the creation of high-quality 3D graphics and animations. Artists can access powerful GPUs to render their works at affordable costs, using RNDR tokens to pay for the rendering services. This platform has applications across multiple sectors, including film, gaming, and architecture, making it an exciting prospect for those looking for the best coin to invest in.</p>
<p>The RNDR token, based on the Ethereum blockchain, is used as a medium of exchange on the Render network. For those asking, "What crypto should I buy?", RNDR offers an interesting proposition. This is due to its unique proposition, linking providers of GPU power with those who need it, combined with its potential to disrupt the rendering industry. By tokenizing GPU power, Render allows miners to monetize their idle resources, making RNDR one of the top 5 cryptocurrencies for individuals looking to invest in a transformative project.</p>
Litecoin (LTC): The Silver to Bitcoin's Gold
<p>Litecoin (LTC) has been prominent in cryptocurrency since its inception in 2011. The "silver to Bitcoin's gold" is what makes Litecoin one of the best digital currencies for boosting their portfolio. An open-source project based on the Bitcoin protocol, Litecoin features several significant improvements, such as a faster block generation time and a different hashing algorithm.</p>
<p>With its longevity in the crypto market and the backing of an active developer community, Litecoin continues to be an appealing option for investors. Buying LTC offers a robust entry point for those wondering how to get into cryptocurrency. It is widely available on most cryptocurrency exchanges, enjoys high liquidity, and can be used for various applications, including online shopping and forex trading. Given these features, Litecoin is undeniably one of the best cryptocurrencies to buy now.</p>
Best Crypto To Buy Now Not Named Bitcoin - Conclusion
<p>While Bitcoin remains a dominant force in the space, it's clear that the market is teeming with diverse and promising altcoins that offer unique value propositions. InQubeta, DigiToads, Manifold Finance, Ocean Protocol, Trust Wallet Token, Render, and Litecoin are just a few examples of cryptocurrencies that have carved a niche in this expansive universe. These tokens represent an array of innovative technologies and concepts ranging from play-to-earn gaming, democratizing data access, and enhancing DeFi connectivity to fractionalized NFT investing. Thus, by expanding investment horizons beyond Bitcoin, investors can tap into a range of potentially rewarding opportunities and help to drive forward the next wave of crypto-innovation. </p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;Join InQubeta Communities</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bulls Seek to Hold 29427:  8 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-bulls-seek-to-hold-29427-8-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-july-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-july-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-july-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-bulls-seek-to-hold-29427-8-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bulls Seek to Hold 29427:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 8 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained impacted by bearish technical sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair came off to the 29715.97 area after trading as high as the 31525.10 area, a recent twelve-month high reached a few trading sessions ago.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders then lifted BTC/USD to the 30363.57 area, a move that represented a test of the 38.2% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.97.&nbsp; Decent selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this elevates the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30243.31 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30393.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bulls Seek to Hold 29427:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 8 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained impacted by bearish technical sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair came off to the 29715.97 area after trading as high as the 31525.10 area, a recent twelve-month high reached a few trading sessions ago.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders then lifted BTC/USD to the 30363.57 area, a move that represented a test of the 38.2% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.97.&nbsp; Decent selling pressure recently intensified around the 31142.38 area and this elevates the risk of another test of the 29427 area, representing the 38.2% retracement of the broader appreciating range from 26165.98 to 31443.67.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below that area, the 28604.83 level represents the 50% retracement of that appreciating range.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, areas of potential technical support and buying pressure include the 29427, 28886, 28804, 28182, 28096, and 27306 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Technicians are closely watching to see how much technical support develops around the 28095.44 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30243.31 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30393.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[JP Morgan report attempts to undermine Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/jp-morgan-report-attempts-to-undermine-spot-bitcoin-etf</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:04:44 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/jp-morgan-report-attempts-to-undermine-spot-bitcoin-etf</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>A recent report by JP Morgan looks to play down the effect that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF might bring to the crypto sector.</p>
The hype caused by Blackrock
<p>Once it was announced that the biggest asset manager in the world (Blackrock) had filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF, the whole crypto market was thrown into a frenzy of hope and optimism that this would be the spark that ignites the next crypto bull run.</p>
<p>There is no bigger player than Blackrock, and add to this the pro-crypto and bitcoin comments made by its CEO Larry Fink on national TV, and you have the perfect narrative to help the crypto market explode higher.</p>
Bitcoin spot ETF is anathema to banks
<p>Such a scenario is absolute anathema to the commercial banking system. Should institutions and the average retail investor get the message that bitcoin is worth investing in, and given the parlous state of the US dollar and all other fiat currencies, a trickle of crypto buying could become an avalanche.</p>
JP Morgan report attempts damage limitation
<p>The line taken by strategists in the JP Morgan report that was released on Thursday is that the Blackrock ETF &ldquo;is unlikely to be a game changer for crypto markets&rdquo;. One of the main arguments for this was that Spot Bitcoin ETFs already exist in Canada and Europe, yet have not gained a significant amount of investor interest.</p>
<p>Another avenue of reasoning that was explored by the report was that in the JP Morgan view, a Spot ETF had only &ldquo;marginal&rdquo; benefits over a Futures ETF. While some advantages of a Spot ETF were laid out, the only real &lsquo;disadvantage&rsquo; appeared to be that a Spot ETF could potentially take trading activity and liquidity away from the already existent Futures ETFs&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given that a Bitcoin Futures ETF is really more for institutional use than it is for retail investors, this surely can&rsquo;t be seen as an argument against the Spot ETF. In traditional finance both types of ETF exist and they are used as tools for different types of investor activity.</p>
Opinion
<p>Even as JP Morgan tries to influence markets against any activity that might promote interest or further buying into bitcoin products, they must surely be seeing the writing on the wall. CEO Jamie Dimon is still making his &ldquo;pet rock&rdquo; references to bitcoin, but as influential as he might be in financial circles, this kind of ridiculous name-calling is starting to become embarrassing for him.</p>
<p>JP Morgan is after all an institution that is there to make money, and staying out of such a potentially game-changing asset as bitcoin could be financial suicide.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Granted there is probably a lot of pressure to follow this line by the Biden Administration, perhaps with promises of more tasty regional banks to be thrown at JP Morgan when they fail, to be gobbled up with relish, but how long can it stay out of what can become an alternative asset that can potentially be worth trillions?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent report by JP Morgan looks to play down the effect that the approval of a Spot Bitcoin ETF might bring to the crypto sector.</p>
The hype caused by Blackrock
<p>Once it was announced that the biggest asset manager in the world (Blackrock) had filed for a Spot Bitcoin ETF, the whole crypto market was thrown into a frenzy of hope and optimism that this would be the spark that ignites the next crypto bull run.</p>
<p>There is no bigger player than Blackrock, and add to this the pro-crypto and bitcoin comments made by its CEO Larry Fink on national TV, and you have the perfect narrative to help the crypto market explode higher.</p>
Bitcoin spot ETF is anathema to banks
<p>Such a scenario is absolute anathema to the commercial banking system. Should institutions and the average retail investor get the message that bitcoin is worth investing in, and given the parlous state of the US dollar and all other fiat currencies, a trickle of crypto buying could become an avalanche.</p>
JP Morgan report attempts damage limitation
<p>The line taken by strategists in the JP Morgan report that was released on Thursday is that the Blackrock ETF &ldquo;is unlikely to be a game changer for crypto markets&rdquo;. One of the main arguments for this was that Spot Bitcoin ETFs already exist in Canada and Europe, yet have not gained a significant amount of investor interest.</p>
<p>Another avenue of reasoning that was explored by the report was that in the JP Morgan view, a Spot ETF had only &ldquo;marginal&rdquo; benefits over a Futures ETF. While some advantages of a Spot ETF were laid out, the only real &lsquo;disadvantage&rsquo; appeared to be that a Spot ETF could potentially take trading activity and liquidity away from the already existent Futures ETFs&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given that a Bitcoin Futures ETF is really more for institutional use than it is for retail investors, this surely can&rsquo;t be seen as an argument against the Spot ETF. In traditional finance both types of ETF exist and they are used as tools for different types of investor activity.</p>
Opinion
<p>Even as JP Morgan tries to influence markets against any activity that might promote interest or further buying into bitcoin products, they must surely be seeing the writing on the wall. CEO Jamie Dimon is still making his &ldquo;pet rock&rdquo; references to bitcoin, but as influential as he might be in financial circles, this kind of ridiculous name-calling is starting to become embarrassing for him.</p>
<p>JP Morgan is after all an institution that is there to make money, and staying out of such a potentially game-changing asset as bitcoin could be financial suicide.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Granted there is probably a lot of pressure to follow this line by the Biden Administration, perhaps with promises of more tasty regional banks to be thrown at JP Morgan when they fail, to be gobbled up with relish, but how long can it stay out of what can become an alternative asset that can potentially be worth trillions?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uniswap v4 Depends On Ethereum's Cancun Upgrade]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/uniswap-v4-depends-on-ethereum-s-cancun-upgrade</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 14:21:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/uniswap-v4-depends-on-ethereum-s-cancun-upgrade</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The latest statement from the Uniswap Foundation has claimed that the launch of version 4 of the protocol depends on Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade.&nbsp;</p>
Cancun, Audit, Then V4
<p>The Uniswap Foundation recently put forth an announcement elaborating its plans for the much-awaited Uniswap v4 protocol. Although the foundation&rsquo;s Governance Lead, Erin Koen, has disclosed that the launch is scheduled for later this year, the fact is that a lot depends on the successful deployment of Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade, which is scheduled to go live around the end of September.</p>
<p>Uniswap v4 will also require thorough auditing before it goes live, a process that can only start after Cancun and can take as long as one to four months.&nbsp;</p>
V4 To Reinvent Uniswap
<p>The v4 launch will bring forth a major reinvention for the Uniswap platform, which is already the largest decentralized exchange protocol. One of the most noteworthy changes that will be incorporated will be &ldquo;hooks&rdquo; or smart contracts that can enable additional customization of the protocol&rsquo;s liquidity pools to create a more modular exchange structure through features like dynamic fees, on-chain limit orders, and tailored on-chain oracles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another revolutionary feature that is to be incorporated with the v4 launch is a &ldquo;flash accounting&rdquo; system, which will reduce fees for liquidity providers and is being predicted to contribute significantly to gas savings. This mechanism leverages "transient storage," which will be activated by the proposed EIP-1153 change in Ethereum's protocol, set to be integrated during Cancun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, in contrast to the v3 model, which involved transferring assets into and out of pools after each swap, the new method will only transfer net balances.</p>
Roadmap For V4
<p>For now, the next &ldquo;protocol code frozen&rdquo; stage will focus on incorporating the EIP-1153 into the protocol code for the next version. Ideally, the EIP-1153 will be successfully integrated into Etheruem&rsquo;s Cancun upgrade, which will allow the Uniswap Foundation to roll out the v4 protocol.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Koen has claimed that the foundation will not be rushing the process and instead take the necessary time to do due diligence and ensure the integrity of the Uniswap ecosystem and user safety. Therefore v4 launch will only go ahead after the necessary parameters are satisfied.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Ethereum community is eagerly anticipating the upcoming Cancun upgrade, fueling even more excitement for the potential advancements in the next version of Uniswap. This pivotal moment holds great significance for the DeFi space, as these developments have the potential to reshape the industry and reinvent decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest statement from the Uniswap Foundation has claimed that the launch of version 4 of the protocol depends on Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade.&nbsp;</p>
Cancun, Audit, Then V4
<p>The Uniswap Foundation recently put forth an announcement elaborating its plans for the much-awaited Uniswap v4 protocol. Although the foundation&rsquo;s Governance Lead, Erin Koen, has disclosed that the launch is scheduled for later this year, the fact is that a lot depends on the successful deployment of Ethereum&rsquo;s upcoming Cancun upgrade, which is scheduled to go live around the end of September.</p>
<p>Uniswap v4 will also require thorough auditing before it goes live, a process that can only start after Cancun and can take as long as one to four months.&nbsp;</p>
V4 To Reinvent Uniswap
<p>The v4 launch will bring forth a major reinvention for the Uniswap platform, which is already the largest decentralized exchange protocol. One of the most noteworthy changes that will be incorporated will be &ldquo;hooks&rdquo; or smart contracts that can enable additional customization of the protocol&rsquo;s liquidity pools to create a more modular exchange structure through features like dynamic fees, on-chain limit orders, and tailored on-chain oracles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another revolutionary feature that is to be incorporated with the v4 launch is a &ldquo;flash accounting&rdquo; system, which will reduce fees for liquidity providers and is being predicted to contribute significantly to gas savings. This mechanism leverages "transient storage," which will be activated by the proposed EIP-1153 change in Ethereum's protocol, set to be integrated during Cancun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, in contrast to the v3 model, which involved transferring assets into and out of pools after each swap, the new method will only transfer net balances.</p>
Roadmap For V4
<p>For now, the next &ldquo;protocol code frozen&rdquo; stage will focus on incorporating the EIP-1153 into the protocol code for the next version. Ideally, the EIP-1153 will be successfully integrated into Etheruem&rsquo;s Cancun upgrade, which will allow the Uniswap Foundation to roll out the v4 protocol.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Koen has claimed that the foundation will not be rushing the process and instead take the necessary time to do due diligence and ensure the integrity of the Uniswap ecosystem and user safety. Therefore v4 launch will only go ahead after the necessary parameters are satisfied.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Ethereum community is eagerly anticipating the upcoming Cancun upgrade, fueling even more excitement for the potential advancements in the next version of Uniswap. This pivotal moment holds great significance for the DeFi space, as these developments have the potential to reshape the industry and reinvent decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC Miners Break Records With $184M]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/btc-miners-break-records-with-184-million-usd</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-mining-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-mining-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-mining-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 12:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/btc-miners-break-records-with-184-million-usd</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin miners have raked in an impressive revenue of $184 million in the second quarter of 2023, breaking previous records.&nbsp;</p>
BRC-20 And Ordinals Boon For Miners
<p>The second quarter of 2023 has been particularly profitable for Bitcoin miners everywhere. It has brought with it a significant surge in profits, earning them a staggering total revenue of $184 million. Crypto analysts have attributed the million-dollar windfall to the popularity and rising demand for BRC-20 tokens and Ordinals. Coinmetrics pointed out that previously the fee market for Bitcoin miners used to be rather uneventful. However, the market has turned itself around and has raked in significant transaction fees for Bitcoin miners from April to June, with the latest transaction fee total being more than that of the five previous quarters combined.&nbsp;</p>
What Is Ordinals Protocol?&nbsp;
<p>The Ordinals protocol was launched in early 2023, and despite some pushback from the crypto community has enabled people to create NFT-like assets on Bitcoin by inscribing data to an individual &lsquo;satoshi.&rsquo; (1 satoshi = 1/100,000,000 BTC; and is the smallest unit a BTC can be broken down to).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Its popularity got a boost when MicroStrategy co-founder and major Bitcoin proponent pointed out the protocol&rsquo;s role in raking in profits for BTC miners.&nbsp;</p>
Transaction Fee Surge Due To BRC-20
<p>The BRC-20 tokens were inspired by Etheruem&rsquo;s ERC-20 tokens and have blown up to reach over $240 million in market capitalization since its launch in March. To mint these tokens, users must submit a transaction accompanied by a fee. This transaction initiates the process of minting tokens on Bitcoin's network and ensures their inclusion in the subsequent block of transactions.</p>
<p>Soon after their launch, these tokens invoked a new surge of excitement in May, as more and more people chose to pay higher fees to expedite their transactions. This pushed up BTC&rsquo;s transaction fees in May, leading to speculation that the network was under attack.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nick Hansen, CEO and co-founder of Luxor Technologies, said,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;BRC-20s introduced this urgency because what you needed to do was get your transactions confirmed faster than other peoples&rsquo; transactions. Then you would basically win the coins from the mint.&rdquo;</p>

Miners Continue To Profit
<p>Notably, the revenue earned by Bitcoin miners from transaction fees surpassed the block subsidy for the first time since 2017, indicating the substantial impact of these fees on miners' earnings.</p>
<p>However, the enthusiasm surrounding BRC-20 tokens has subsided, leading to a decline in payout amounts associated with transaction fees. Despite the diminished fervor, miners continue to receive substantial funds from transaction fees, especially when compared to previous years.</p>
<p>Hansen pointed out,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have calmed down, but we're still seeing persistent demand for Bitcoin block space. Miners are still making 10 to 15 times more from their transaction fee volume than they would have last year.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin miners have raked in an impressive revenue of $184 million in the second quarter of 2023, breaking previous records.&nbsp;</p>
BRC-20 And Ordinals Boon For Miners
<p>The second quarter of 2023 has been particularly profitable for Bitcoin miners everywhere. It has brought with it a significant surge in profits, earning them a staggering total revenue of $184 million. Crypto analysts have attributed the million-dollar windfall to the popularity and rising demand for BRC-20 tokens and Ordinals. Coinmetrics pointed out that previously the fee market for Bitcoin miners used to be rather uneventful. However, the market has turned itself around and has raked in significant transaction fees for Bitcoin miners from April to June, with the latest transaction fee total being more than that of the five previous quarters combined.&nbsp;</p>
What Is Ordinals Protocol?&nbsp;
<p>The Ordinals protocol was launched in early 2023, and despite some pushback from the crypto community has enabled people to create NFT-like assets on Bitcoin by inscribing data to an individual &lsquo;satoshi.&rsquo; (1 satoshi = 1/100,000,000 BTC; and is the smallest unit a BTC can be broken down to).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Its popularity got a boost when MicroStrategy co-founder and major Bitcoin proponent pointed out the protocol&rsquo;s role in raking in profits for BTC miners.&nbsp;</p>
Transaction Fee Surge Due To BRC-20
<p>The BRC-20 tokens were inspired by Etheruem&rsquo;s ERC-20 tokens and have blown up to reach over $240 million in market capitalization since its launch in March. To mint these tokens, users must submit a transaction accompanied by a fee. This transaction initiates the process of minting tokens on Bitcoin's network and ensures their inclusion in the subsequent block of transactions.</p>
<p>Soon after their launch, these tokens invoked a new surge of excitement in May, as more and more people chose to pay higher fees to expedite their transactions. This pushed up BTC&rsquo;s transaction fees in May, leading to speculation that the network was under attack.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nick Hansen, CEO and co-founder of Luxor Technologies, said,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;BRC-20s introduced this urgency because what you needed to do was get your transactions confirmed faster than other peoples&rsquo; transactions. Then you would basically win the coins from the mint.&rdquo;</p>

Miners Continue To Profit
<p>Notably, the revenue earned by Bitcoin miners from transaction fees surpassed the block subsidy for the first time since 2017, indicating the substantial impact of these fees on miners' earnings.</p>
<p>However, the enthusiasm surrounding BRC-20 tokens has subsided, leading to a decline in payout amounts associated with transaction fees. Despite the diminished fervor, miners continue to receive substantial funds from transaction fees, especially when compared to previous years.</p>
<p>Hansen pointed out,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have calmed down, but we're still seeing persistent demand for Bitcoin block space. Miners are still making 10 to 15 times more from their transaction fee volume than they would have last year.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BRICS nations summit in August will turn monetary system upside down]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/brics-nations-summit-in-august-will-turn-monetary-system-upside-down</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 12:00:27 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/brics-nations-summit-in-august-will-turn-monetary-system-upside-down</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>At the BRICS summit on August 22, a new currency is to be announced which will be pegged to commodities, and gold in particular.</p>
<p>Central banks around the world bought almost 230 tons of gold in the first three months of this year, which is the most buying of gold in a single quarter that has ever been seen.</p>
Precious metals price suppression
<p>That the price of gold is still depressed perhaps bears testament to how the price of precious metals is being suppressed by the big commercial banks on the London Bullion Metals Exchange (LBMA) and the Commodities Exchange (COMEX).</p>
<p>However, as the alleged price suppression continues, large entities are able to buy gold and silver at rock-bottom prices in preparation for a world where tangible resources are much more likely to be valued than fiat currencies printed out of thin air.</p>
<p>The recent dumping of the gold and silver prices after huge shorting took place might be one of the western commercial banks&rsquo; last ditch attempts to keep both gold and silver from rocketing higher, which would have the potential to tear the heart out of the dollar.</p>
The BRICS nations
<p>The BRICS nations is the term for the original five countries that compose this trading block: China, Russia, India, Brazil, and South Africa. Saudi Arabia is among one of 25 other countries that are formally applying for membership of BRICS.</p>
<p>The BRICS nations hold and produce a significant share of the world&rsquo;s resources. China and Russia are the 6th and 7th biggest gold producers in the world, and Saudi Arabia and Russia are 2 of the 3 largest energy producers.</p>
<p>With China, India, Brazil, and Russia, BRICS has 4 of the 7 largest countries in the world measured by land mass, and also 4 of the 9 largest populations.</p>
<p>If 50% of the world&rsquo;s wheat production is also put into the mix it can be seen that the BRICS nations have a massive amount of power and should they put up a rival reserve currency to the dollar they will need to be taken extremely seriously.</p>
Creation of a new bond market
<p>Some analysts and detractors might say that a BRICS reserve currency cannot really get off the ground without a deep and liquid bond market to underpin it. Be that as it may, renowned economist Jim Rickards has posited that this could be done if BRICS+ created a bond market in around 20 countries at the same time.</p>
<p>With the massive population that the BRICS have, retail investors could be encouraged to buy the bonds, much like what happened with the Liberty Bonds, which were used in the US for the financing of the war in 1917.</p>
<p>If all this should come to pass then the financial upheaval and turmoil in the West, where currency is based on nothing, has the potential to completely change the world order. There is not much time left for retail investors to protect themselves with gold, silver, and bitcoin.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the BRICS summit on August 22, a new currency is to be announced which will be pegged to commodities, and gold in particular.</p>
<p>Central banks around the world bought almost 230 tons of gold in the first three months of this year, which is the most buying of gold in a single quarter that has ever been seen.</p>
Precious metals price suppression
<p>That the price of gold is still depressed perhaps bears testament to how the price of precious metals is being suppressed by the big commercial banks on the London Bullion Metals Exchange (LBMA) and the Commodities Exchange (COMEX).</p>
<p>However, as the alleged price suppression continues, large entities are able to buy gold and silver at rock-bottom prices in preparation for a world where tangible resources are much more likely to be valued than fiat currencies printed out of thin air.</p>
<p>The recent dumping of the gold and silver prices after huge shorting took place might be one of the western commercial banks&rsquo; last ditch attempts to keep both gold and silver from rocketing higher, which would have the potential to tear the heart out of the dollar.</p>
The BRICS nations
<p>The BRICS nations is the term for the original five countries that compose this trading block: China, Russia, India, Brazil, and South Africa. Saudi Arabia is among one of 25 other countries that are formally applying for membership of BRICS.</p>
<p>The BRICS nations hold and produce a significant share of the world&rsquo;s resources. China and Russia are the 6th and 7th biggest gold producers in the world, and Saudi Arabia and Russia are 2 of the 3 largest energy producers.</p>
<p>With China, India, Brazil, and Russia, BRICS has 4 of the 7 largest countries in the world measured by land mass, and also 4 of the 9 largest populations.</p>
<p>If 50% of the world&rsquo;s wheat production is also put into the mix it can be seen that the BRICS nations have a massive amount of power and should they put up a rival reserve currency to the dollar they will need to be taken extremely seriously.</p>
Creation of a new bond market
<p>Some analysts and detractors might say that a BRICS reserve currency cannot really get off the ground without a deep and liquid bond market to underpin it. Be that as it may, renowned economist Jim Rickards has posited that this could be done if BRICS+ created a bond market in around 20 countries at the same time.</p>
<p>With the massive population that the BRICS have, retail investors could be encouraged to buy the bonds, much like what happened with the Liberty Bonds, which were used in the US for the financing of the war in 1917.</p>
<p>If all this should come to pass then the financial upheaval and turmoil in the West, where currency is based on nothing, has the potential to completely change the world order. There is not much time left for retail investors to protect themselves with gold, silver, and bitcoin.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitfinex Recovers Assets Stolen During Infamous 2016 Bitcoin Hack]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitfinex-recovers-assets-stolen-during-infamous-2016-bitcoin-hack</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitfinex-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitfinex-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitfinex-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitfinex-recovers-assets-stolen-during-infamous-2016-bitcoin-hack</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Exchange Bitfinex has announced that it has recovered some of the stolen assets from the 2016 Bitcoin hack but stated that a considerable number of assets are still yet to be recovered.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exchange stated in a press release that it had received the assets in question from the United States Department of Homeland Security.&nbsp;</p>
Tip Of The Iceberg&nbsp;
<p>According to the announcement, the exchange revealed that it had managed to recover $312,219 in cash and 6.9 in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) worth around $1951 at today&rsquo;s prices. The assets, stolen during the 2016 hack, were returned by the United States Department of Homeland Security. US authorities seized control of the funds in 2022 after arresting two individuals in connection with the Bitfinex hack. The exchange has been working with authorities to recover the assets stolen during the hack and return them to customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitfinex stated in its blog post that the United States government was continuing to make progress in prosecuting the individuals involved with the breach. The United States Customs and Border Protection agency conducted the seizure of the recovered assets. This agency is the law enforcement agency of the US Department of Homeland Security. Paolo Ardoino, the Chief Technology Officer at Bitfinex, thanked the authorities, stating,&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are extremely pleased to be able to reach another successful milestone in the recovery of assets stolen from Bitfinex in 2016. This specific seizure demonstrates the commitment of law enforcement officials to diligently track all the proceeds of the crime committed against Bitfinex almost seven years ago. We look forward to recovering as much of the stolen bitcoin as we possibly can and redistributing that to holders of the tokens that were issued in response to the hack in 2016.&rdquo;</p>
The Bitfinex Hack&nbsp;
<p>The Bitfinex hack was one of the biggest hacks to hit crypto at the time, with the hackers managing to steal around 119,756 Bitcoin (BTC) from the exchange thanks to a security breach. At the time, the stolen assets were worth around $71.8 million. However, at current prices, their valuation stands at a staggering $3.6 billion. On several occasions, the hackers had moved the stolen crypto around to launder the funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, US authorities were tracking the assets and managed to arrest the hackers in 2022. The culprits, Ilya Lichtenstein and Heather Morgan were a married couple from New York. Both were subsequently charged with conspiracy to commit money laundering. The arrest also led to the seizure of most of the stolen funds, totaling around $3.6 billion worth of Bitcoin. Deputy Attorney General Lisa O. Monaco stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today&rsquo;s arrests, and the department&rsquo;s largest financial seizure ever, show that cryptocurrency is not a safe haven for criminals. In a futile effort to maintain digital anonymity, the defendants laundered stolen funds through a labyrinth of cryptocurrency transactions; thanks to the meticulous work of law enforcement, the department once again showed how it can and will follow the money, no matter what form it takes.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Bitfinex had issued a statement as well, expressing gratitude for the recovery, adding,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re pleased that the DOJ has recovered a significant portion of the bitcoin stolen during the 2016 hack. We have been cooperating extensively with DOJ since its investigation of this incident began.&rdquo;</p>

Redemption Of Stolen Assets&nbsp;
<p>Ardoino had stated that Bitfinex was looking forward to recovering as much of the stolen assets as possible and redistributing them to holders of the Recovery Right Tokens (RRt), which were issued after the hack. The tokens were intended to act as an IOU, and holders could exchange them for cash or iFinex capital stock at a later date. Currently, around 30 million RRT tokens are in circulation, which means that the amount recovered is insufficient to redeem all RRT tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Under Bitfinex&rsquo;s contractual obligations, RRT token holders were to be redeemed at $1, after which up to 80% of any recovered assets were to be paid to SED, UNUS, and LEO token holders. According to Bitfinex, RRT token holders will have their tokens redeemed pro rata today, based on the size of their RRT holdings, on the 6th of July, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Exchange Bitfinex has announced that it has recovered some of the stolen assets from the 2016 Bitcoin hack but stated that a considerable number of assets are still yet to be recovered.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exchange stated in a press release that it had received the assets in question from the United States Department of Homeland Security.&nbsp;</p>
Tip Of The Iceberg&nbsp;
<p>According to the announcement, the exchange revealed that it had managed to recover $312,219 in cash and 6.9 in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) worth around $1951 at today&rsquo;s prices. The assets, stolen during the 2016 hack, were returned by the United States Department of Homeland Security. US authorities seized control of the funds in 2022 after arresting two individuals in connection with the Bitfinex hack. The exchange has been working with authorities to recover the assets stolen during the hack and return them to customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitfinex stated in its blog post that the United States government was continuing to make progress in prosecuting the individuals involved with the breach. The United States Customs and Border Protection agency conducted the seizure of the recovered assets. This agency is the law enforcement agency of the US Department of Homeland Security. Paolo Ardoino, the Chief Technology Officer at Bitfinex, thanked the authorities, stating,&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are extremely pleased to be able to reach another successful milestone in the recovery of assets stolen from Bitfinex in 2016. This specific seizure demonstrates the commitment of law enforcement officials to diligently track all the proceeds of the crime committed against Bitfinex almost seven years ago. We look forward to recovering as much of the stolen bitcoin as we possibly can and redistributing that to holders of the tokens that were issued in response to the hack in 2016.&rdquo;</p>
The Bitfinex Hack&nbsp;
<p>The Bitfinex hack was one of the biggest hacks to hit crypto at the time, with the hackers managing to steal around 119,756 Bitcoin (BTC) from the exchange thanks to a security breach. At the time, the stolen assets were worth around $71.8 million. However, at current prices, their valuation stands at a staggering $3.6 billion. On several occasions, the hackers had moved the stolen crypto around to launder the funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, US authorities were tracking the assets and managed to arrest the hackers in 2022. The culprits, Ilya Lichtenstein and Heather Morgan were a married couple from New York. Both were subsequently charged with conspiracy to commit money laundering. The arrest also led to the seizure of most of the stolen funds, totaling around $3.6 billion worth of Bitcoin. Deputy Attorney General Lisa O. Monaco stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today&rsquo;s arrests, and the department&rsquo;s largest financial seizure ever, show that cryptocurrency is not a safe haven for criminals. In a futile effort to maintain digital anonymity, the defendants laundered stolen funds through a labyrinth of cryptocurrency transactions; thanks to the meticulous work of law enforcement, the department once again showed how it can and will follow the money, no matter what form it takes.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Bitfinex had issued a statement as well, expressing gratitude for the recovery, adding,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;re pleased that the DOJ has recovered a significant portion of the bitcoin stolen during the 2016 hack. We have been cooperating extensively with DOJ since its investigation of this incident began.&rdquo;</p>

Redemption Of Stolen Assets&nbsp;
<p>Ardoino had stated that Bitfinex was looking forward to recovering as much of the stolen assets as possible and redistributing them to holders of the Recovery Right Tokens (RRt), which were issued after the hack. The tokens were intended to act as an IOU, and holders could exchange them for cash or iFinex capital stock at a later date. Currently, around 30 million RRT tokens are in circulation, which means that the amount recovered is insufficient to redeem all RRT tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Under Bitfinex&rsquo;s contractual obligations, RRT token holders were to be redeemed at $1, after which up to 80% of any recovered assets were to be paid to SED, UNUS, and LEO token holders. According to Bitfinex, RRT token holders will have their tokens redeemed pro rata today, based on the size of their RRT holdings, on the 6th of July, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
