<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:36:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Paxos Gives USDP Stablecoin Access to Mexico With Mercado Libre Partnership</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paxos-gives-usdp-stablecoin-access-to-mexico-with-mercado-libre-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 04:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paxos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257675</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/paxos_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/paxos_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Paxos's Pax Dollar (USDP) is a regulated stablecoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain fintech company Paxos has announced partnering with online marketplace Mercado Libre to bring the Pax Dollar (USDP) stablecoin to users in Mexico. Transactions will be facilitated by MercadoPago, which happens to be a digital wallet app by Mercado Libre.</p>
<p>The latest move is part of Paxos&#8217; vision to position itself as an &#8220;established leader&#8221; in digital assets throughout the region. Data cited by the company stated that over 60% of its active wallets currently support customers in Latin America.</p>
<h2>Paxos&#8217;s Presence in Latin America</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://paxos.com/2023/06/28/paxos-partners-with-mercado-pago-to-open-access-to-pax-dollar-usdp-for-mexican-customers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, Paxos said that the adoption of USDP by Mercado Pago in Mexico further builds on the established partnership between the fintech firms, as Mexican users will now be able to access the regulated stablecoin via Mercado Pago.</p>
<p>In a statement, Arnoldo Reyes, Head of Latin America of Paxos, highlighted the increasing demand for &#8220;transformational technology&#8221; by digital asset consumers in the region. He added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Mexico is one of the most active marketplaces for digital assets with millions of users tapping into the ecosystem to gain access to key financial services. The launch of USDP within Mercado Pago represents another way that Mercado Libre continues to democratize access to commerce and financial services through innovative digital asset solutions throughout Latin America.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Paxos-issued stablecoin, USDP, is subject to strict regulatory oversight by the New York State Department of Financial Services. USDP reserves are held in cash and cash equivalents, while its attestation reports are issued by WithumSmith+Brown, PC, which happens to be an independent third-party accounting firm.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the company website states that Withum’s examination is carried out in accordance with attestation standards set up by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA).</p>
<h2>Push For Stablecoin Regulations</h2>
<p>The stablecoin market has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stablecoin-market-cap-marks-the-biggest-increase-in-3-months/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">grown</a> significantly over the past decade. Despite much new proliferation, the ecosystem has not managed to steer away from backlash and FUD. In fact, Paxos&#8217;s development comes amidst growing calls for stablecoin-related regulations across the world, especially after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/global-watchdogs-to-regulate-stablecoins-following-terrausd-ust-fiasco/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">TerraUSD&#8217;s</a> (UST) collapse and the subsequent FTX implosion.</p>
<p>Italy’s top banking authority, for one, <a href="https://twitter.com/bancaditalia/status/1673310957743886336" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">released</a> a new report titled &#8220;Markets, Infrastructures and Payment Systems,&#8221; calling on regulators to implement the same financial conduct standards for stablecoin issuers in the industry. It said that regulating stablecoins is crucial because of its close ties with the DeFi market.</p>
<p>Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) <a href="https://www.thestandard.com.hk/section-news/section/2/253257/HKMA-seeks-views-on-stablecoins" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">aims</a> to roll out a regulatory framework for stablecoins by the end of 2024 and is currently in the process of seeking public views regarding the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paxos-gives-usdp-stablecoin-access-to-mexico-with-mercado-libre-partnership/" rel="nofollow">Paxos Gives USDP Stablecoin Access to Mexico With Mercado Libre Partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Jumps Into Institutional Trading Tech Market With Tradelink&#8217;s Launch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-jumps-into-institutional-trading-tech-market-with-tradelinks-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257604</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ledger_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ledger_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tradelink purpotedly reduces transaction charges by 80%. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent crypto wallet service provider Ledger has announced the launch of a new trading and settlement network technology dubbed Tradelink.</p>
<p>The new product offering is designed for asset managers, custodians, and exchanges/OTC with off-exchange trading capabilities and aims to eliminate unnecessary complexities while simultaneously boosting operational speed.</p>
<ul>
<li>As per the company&#8217;s <a href="https://enterprise.ledger.com/tradelink/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">website</a>, Tradelink enables trade on multiple exchanges without on-chain liquidity re-balancing, as well as retaining custodial ownership of assets with off-exchange trading.</li>
<li>Other benefits include allowing mitigation of trading collateral risks across multiple third-party platforms, easy integration with preferred counter-parties, streamlined operations, and zero-transaction fees, among others.</li>
<li>At launch, partners will include asset managers such as Laser Digital and Hodl Group, digital asset trading and orchestration platforms such as Wyden, OTC brokers/providers, and platform partners such as Crypto.com, Bitstamp, Huobi, Wintermute, Coinsquare, NDAX, etc., will be in early stage access to all Ledger Enterprise clients at no additional cost.</li>
<li>Following the development, Sebastien Badault, VP of Enterprise Revenue at Ledger,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By unlocking better trading options for enterprises, we are empowering asset managers, custodians, and exchanges to navigate the changing landscape with confidence while making the whole ecosystem a safer and more transparent place.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Ledger recently came under fire from its online user after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-under-fire-for-allegedly-exposing-user-seed-phrases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">releasing</a> a controversial update that sparked concerns of major security flaws exposure by the manufacturer, which later issued a statement clarifying its decision to delay the launch.</li>
<li>The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-taps-1-4-billion-valuation-after-securing-109-million-funding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">secured</a> a $109 Million Series C extension fundraising round, tapping $1.4 billion in valuation this year with two more to go.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-jumps-into-institutional-trading-tech-market-with-tradelinks-launch/" rel="nofollow">Ledger Jumps Into Institutional Trading Tech Market With Tradelink&#8217;s Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canadian Lawmakers Publish Report Defending And Supporting Crypto, Coinbase Approves</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-lawmakers-publish-report-defending-and-supporting-crypto-coinbase-approves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257861</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/canada_flag-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/canada_flag-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Canadian House members want the government to protect citizens’ right to self custody, and recognize stablecoins as distinct from other cryptos.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Canadian House committee published a report on Wednesday providing 16 recommendations for how the nation’s government should regulate the blockchain industry – and they’re remarkably bullish.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase praised the report, saying it was “encouraged by the forward-thinking approach of the parliamentary committee.”</p>
<h2>Opening Canada to Crypto</h2>
<p>In its first <a href="https://www.ourcommons.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/INDU/report-15/page-18" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recommendation</a>, The Parliamentary Standing Committee on Industry and Technology (INDU) asked that the Canadian government recognize blockchain as a growing industry with the potential to create jobs and foster economic growth.</p>
<p>The committee’s position mimics that of British Prime Minister <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-uk-prime-minister-rishi-sunak-crypto-believer-or-cbdc-backer/" data-wpel-link="internal">Rishi Sunak</a>, who spearheaded a newly passed bill to recognize crypto transactions as legitimate, regulated financial activity.</p>
<p>Canada’s Prime Minister <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-bitcoin-seizures-and-freezing-bank-accounts-canada-finally-ends-emergencies-act/" data-wpel-link="internal">Justin Trudeau</a> has generally been dismissive of crypto, but his conservative political rival <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadas-new-conservative-party-leader-is-a-crypto-proponent/" data-wpel-link="internal">Pierre Poilievre</a> is proudly pro-Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The composition of the House committee is slightly left-leaning, but in some ways better resembles Poilievre’s position. Regarding the Bitcoin mining industry, the report suggests maintaining a “neutral and equitable position” to “foster a competitive digital asset mining environment” and “attract investments.”</p>
<p>It suggested investigating “equity between provinces” in its application of the Excise Tax Act to the mining industry to “ensure fair taxation.” In the United States, the Biden Administration recommended a debilitating 30% excise tax specifically targeted at miners in May (which has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-scraps-plans-for-bitcoin-mining-excise-tax-congressman-confirms/" data-wpel-link="internal">cast aside</a> for the time being).</p>
<p>Canadian lawmakers also advocated for protecting individuals’ “right to self custody”, and for providing ease of access to “safe and reliable on and off ramps.”</p>
<h2>Coinbase Responds</h2>
<p>Canada’s report was a breath of fresh air for Coinbase, which has frequently criticized the lack of regulatory clarity and hostility from the United States, where it is headquartered.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/canadian-lawmakers-back-blockchain-with-landmark-recommendations" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">response letter</a>, the company showed a particular fondness for the committee’s stablecoin recommendation, advocating a “unique regulatory approach” to such assets.</p>
<p>“Stablecoins, a type of cryptocurrency pegged to a stable asset like fiat currency, present novel regulatory considerations,” wrote Coinbase. “This tailored approach will enable effective oversight while promoting innovation.”</p>
<p>Canada’s <a href="https://www.osc.ca/sites/default/files/2023-02/csa_20230222_21-332_crypto-trading-platforms-pre-reg-undertakings.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">current position</a> on stablecoins is that they are securities – a position not shared by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) appears to also think they’re securities, given its recent lawsuit against Binance alleging that its stablecoin BUSD fits the bill.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-lawmakers-publish-report-defending-and-supporting-crypto-coinbase-approves/" rel="nofollow">Canadian Lawmakers Publish Report Defending And Supporting Crypto, Coinbase Approves</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DYDX Announces New Date for Its Cosmos-Based Public Testnet</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-announces-new-date-for-its-cosmos-based-public-testnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257769</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/dydx.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/dydx.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DYDX will release its public testnet on July 5, which is weeks earlier than previously announced. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DYDX Foundation, the non-profit organization behind the popular decentralized exchange (DEX) DYDX, has announced a new launch date for the public testnet of its Cosmos-based blockchain as it prepares to exit the Ethereum ecosystem later this year.</p>
<p>According to the foundation, the testnet is set to go live next week on July 5, which is earlier than the previous schedule. The team estimated in March that the public testnet would launch by the end of July after the third milestone (private testnet).</p>
<h2>DYDX Announces Public Testnet</h2>
<p>The upcoming release is the fourth phase of DYDX&#8217;s five-stage milestones to test its Cosmos-based blockchain before the full release of the mainnet.</p>
<p>During the private testnet, the team made several improvements to the network, including enabling documentation for market makers and validators, limit orders, dynamic funding rates, and ABCI 2.0 and other features of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cosmos-chains-can-evolve-into-polkadot-parachains-thanks-to-new-sdk/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cosmos-SDK</a>.</p>
<p>The public testnet will allow users to test and explore more features, including accessing order books, account balances, order history, and market data. It will also include many validators running the network&#8217;s software.</p>
<p>Although the upcoming testnet will initially support only Bitcoin and Ethereum markets, the project plans to expand the network to include at least 30 markets in the future.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are happy to announce that we completed Milestone 4 ahead of schedule! Our public testnet is set to go live on July 5 at 17:00 UTC. This public testnet will launch with Bitcoin and Ethereum markets but we anticipate that the open-source software will include approximately 30+ markets as the network gets upgraded,&#8221; DYDX <a href="https://dydx.exchange/blog/public-testnet" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are thrilled to announce that the dYdX Chain public testnet is set to launch on 7/05/2023 at 17:00 UTC! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f973.png" alt="🥳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/TD5caN6VSQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/TD5caN6VSQ</a></p>
<p>— dYdX (@dYdX) <a href="https://twitter.com/dYdX/status/1674124130462109699?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p></blockquote>
<h2>Exiting Ethereum</h2>
<p>On successful completion of the testnet, the DEX will move on to the last milestone (v5) before the eventual launch of the mainnet, which will see it migrate from Ethereum to Cosmos around September.</p>
<p>DYDX said <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchains-and-the-scalability-problem/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum&#8217;s scalability issue</a> was the primary reason it intends to move away from the network. The project noted that Ethereum could no longer process transactions fast enough, even after exploring several <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-layer-2-scaling-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">layer2 solutions</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-announces-new-date-for-its-cosmos-based-public-testnet/" rel="nofollow">DYDX Announces New Date for Its Cosmos-Based Public Testnet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fidelity Refiles Bitcoin Spot ETF Application After BlackRock</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fidelity]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257845</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Fidelity.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Fidelity.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Like ARK, Fidelity has modified its ETF proposal to match BlackRock.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fidelity Digital Assets – the $4.5 trillion asset manager’s crypto-arm – has resubmitted its filing to launch a Bitcoin Spot ETF in the United States.</p>
<p>Parts of the filing are virtually identical to BlackRock and ARK Invest’s respective submissions earlier this month.</p>
<h2>Fidelity Tries Again</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-044.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">19-b4 filing</a> with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Thursday, the proposal would allow the Cboe BZX Exchange to list and trade shares of Fidelity’s Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust.</p>
<p>Much like <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-amends-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-to-copy-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">ARK</a> on Wednesday, Fidelity began by rebutting the Commission’s justification for denying previous spot ETF applications, such as its own. The SEC’s main argument is that the applicants thus far have failed to form a surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) with a regulated market of significant size – and that CME Bitcoin Futures don’t count.</p>
<p>“In every prior approval order for Commodity-BasedTrust Shares, there has been a derivatives market that represents the regulated market of significant size, generally a Commodity Futures Trading Commission (the “CFTC”) regulated futures market,” read the filing.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the filing is taking cues from both BlackRock and ARK before it, with Cboe proposing to enter an SSA with “an operator of a United States-based spot trading platform for Bitcoin,” that represents a “substantial portion of US-based Bitcoin trading.”</p>
<p>James Seyffart – an ETF Research Analyst with Bloomberg Intelligence – published an unofficial estimate of the SEC’s next deadline to approve this ETF, predicting September 2 as the date. ARK, meanwhile, he slates for August 13 – ahead of BlackRock on August 19.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Updated. Was moving too fast before. <a href="https://t.co/WWFIK87xgK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/WWFIK87xgK</a></p>
<p>&mdash; James Seyffart (@JSeyff) <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1674472754647539746?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>The Risk of No ETF</h2>
<p>In its filing, Fidelity added that failing to approve a spot Bitcoin ETF is exposing investors to more investment risk – not less.</p>
<p>“The lack of a Spot Bitcoin ETP exposes U.S. investor assets to significant risk because investors that would otherwise seek crypto-asset exposure through a Spot Bitcoin ETP are forced to find alternative exposure through generally riskier means,” argued Fidelity.</p>
<p>The firm cited FTX, Celsius, BlockFi, and Voyager as examples of such “alternative means” of exposure – all crypto firms that went bankrupt and froze client assets last year from a combination of market turmoil and active mismanagement/fraud.</p>
<p>Fidelity plans to act as the custodian for the fund’s Bitcoin, unlike BlackRock, which plans to outsource that task to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-shares-have-jumped-nearly-40-since-the-sec-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" rel="nofollow">Fidelity Refiles Bitcoin Spot ETF Application After BlackRock</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Says Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a Mega Force in Today&#8217;s Market</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-says-artificial-intelligence-ai-is-a-mega-force-in-todays-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257738</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BlackRock has placed big bets AI saying that nascent tech can be a big driver of returns even when the macro environment is not your friend. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Asset management giant &#8211; BlackRock &#8211; believes that structural shifts like the rise of artificial intelligence (AI) have the potential to drive returns now and in the future. Its new report described the space as a &#8220;mega force&#8221; whose applications could disrupt entire industries.</p>
<p>BlackRock found that S&amp;P 500 gains have become increasingly concentrated in a handful of tech stocks, exceeding levels seen during the 2000s tech boom. The company believes that this &#8220;unusual&#8221; equity market demonstrates that AI can be a big catalyst of returns even during tough macro environment conditions.</p>
<ul>
<li>In its mid-year outlook <a href="https://www.blackrock.com/corporate/literature/whitepaper/bii-midyear-outlook-2023.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, the asset manager&#8217;s investment team wrote that the importance of data for AI and potential winners is &#8220;underappreciated.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Companies with vast sets of proprietary data have the ability to more quickly and easily leverage a large amount of data to create innovative models. New AI tools could analyze and unlock the value of the data gold mine some companies may be sitting on.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>BlackRock Investment Institute also revealed that it has an overweight allocation for AI-related shares in developed markets.</li>
<li>It also suggested that investors should get granular in portfolios in the &#8220;new regime&#8221; of economic volatility and high-interest rates, explaining that such a strategy is likely to be more crucial than relying on broad asset class returns.</li>
<li>The report highlighted that AI-driven productivity gains could boost profit margins and could benefit companies with high staffing costs or a large share of tasks that could be automated while simultaneously admitting that white-collar jobs are at an &#8220;increased risk&#8221; in the process.</li>
<li>Besides BlackRock, several companies have placed big bets on AI.</li>
<li>In April, Bitget <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-betting-big-on-ai-with-10m-investment-in-fetch-ai-ecosystem/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">pledged</a> $10 million for the development of the Fetch.ai ecosystem, which offers a service automation infrastructure that is powered by an AI agent network.</li>
<li>Wall Street banking giant JPMorgan was reportedly <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-26/jpmorgan-s-ai-puts-25-years-of-federal-reserve-talk-into-a-hawk-dove-score?sref=323RPL5z" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">developing</a> AI solutions.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-says-artificial-intelligence-ai-is-a-mega-force-in-todays-market/" rel="nofollow">BlackRock Says Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a Mega Force in Today&#8217;s Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cirus Launches Wallet as a Service Initiative (WaaS)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cirus-launches-wallet-as-a-service-initiative-waas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257827</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Untitled_design_4_1687974754wraq0tobdy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Untitled_design_4_1687974754wraq0tobdy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Rarotonga, Cook Islands, June 29th, 2023] A solution enabling Web3 wallet integration within existing enterprise platforms. Blockchain-based, Web3 initiative Cirus Foundation has developed a Wallet as a Service (WaaS) innovation unit. The initiative entails deploying Web3 wallets for existing businesses and platforms to create a secured value-share layer between their users. After [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Rarotonga, Cook Islands, June 29th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">A solution enabling Web3 wallet integration within existing enterprise platforms.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Blockchain-based, Web3 initiative<a href="https://cirusfoundation.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> Cirus Foundation</a> has developed a Wallet as a Service (WaaS) innovation unit. The initiative entails deploying Web3 wallets for existing businesses and platforms to create a secured value-share layer between their users.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">After the initial release of the Cirus Web3 Wallet, the core functionality of combining user data and digital currencies provides a basis for Cirus to connect with existing platforms and web applications seamlessly.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The initiative marks the first business-to-business approach in developing wallet adoption for the Cirus ecosystem. The team commented:</p>
<blockquote><p>“We believe we need a fast-track to adoption, although our approach will always entail what the end-user desires, the world needs a sovereign solution targeting businesses and platforms alike. In simpler terms, we need to prevent misappropriation by banks and the FTX’s of the world. This application places the user in ‘permissioned control of their asset’ while endorsed by the business. Think of the business as saying &#8211; ‘we don’t hold your assets &#8211; you do’. said Co-Founder, Michael Luckhoo</p></blockquote>
<figure style="width: 800px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image_1687974805LN1IeuFlCx.jpg" alt="The Cirus Wallet Linking with existing crypto exchange" width="800" height="429" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">The Cirus Wallet Linking with existing crypto exchange</figcaption></figure>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Without mass-scale adoption, Web3 will continue to suffer, and its true use cases will fail to make a lasting impact. The WaaS category creates an easier entry point for companies to integrate Web3 technology and better serve their client base.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>What defines WaaS? </strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Wallet-as-a-service refers to a platform that has the ability to enable Web3 functionality either inside an existing application or interfacing with a platform. Simply put, the users have ownership and control over their assets, enabling them to decide how their data and currencies are utilized by the business they engage with.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The team has confirmed that they have signed their first enterprise client to service the WaaS program, and although the Cirus wallet recently launched, this has sped up development efforts in this category.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Companies are not going to just roll over and hand back assets to their user base, but by educating the benefits to the business as a first-mover in the space, we can create a domino effect &#8211; first movers, willing followers and the unwilling followers. Eventually companies will be accredited for better business by enabling user-controlled management &#8211; almost like a better business bureau approval.” said David Brown, Head of Tokenomics</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Some examples where WaaS may apply include NFTs or tokens distributed by the business based on engagement, SDK kits for in-app wallet deployment, or wallets that connect the user account (data and currencies) to be exchanged with another party in a more secure format.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The team suggested the first use case will enable a more secure way to trade assets with existing centralized exchanges, therefore preventing user assets from being manipulated or withheld by the platform.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The most obvious choice was to solve how centralized exchanges operate as this was the central point of failure for our industry. We don’t need to experience a repeat of Mt.Gox, Quadriga or FTX! The world needs a renewed trust in the benefits of Web3, a new standard.” said Director, Mike Miclea</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The team commented that the WaaS initiative is part of a greater plan to establish an open and easily accessible economy that encourages the widespread adoption of Web3 technologies. Through this process, they are actively engaged in developing an end-user WaaS program where true customization of Web3 wallets can be achieved by anyone.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>About Cirus Foundation</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Cirus Foundation is the development team behind the Cirus Ecosystem, an accessible onramp designed to accelerate the adoption of Web 3.0 and the Ownership Economy. This consists of the Cirus suite of tools, which work together to give users true ownership over their assets, and the data streams they generate.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Website:</strong> <a href="https://www.cirusfoundation.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">www.cirusfoundation.com</a></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Media inquiries:</strong> Media@cirusfoundation.com</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>The Sovereign Self:</strong> <a href="http://bit.ly/440Av6l" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">bit.ly/440Av6l</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cirus-launches-wallet-as-a-service-initiative-waas/" rel="nofollow">Cirus Launches Wallet as a Service Initiative (WaaS)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Holders Lawyer John Deaton Comments on Jay Clayton&#8217;s Stance on Current Regulatory Regimen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-holders-lawyer-john-deaton-comments-on-jay-claytons-stance-on-current-regulatory-regimen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257816</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[John Deaton has some comments on a recent interview of Jay Clayton regarding the current regulatory approach of some US agencies. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The lawsuit between Ripple and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission has taken center stage once again as the agency continues with its predatory approach.</p>
<p>Earlier this month, the Commission filed a lawsuit against Coinbase for dealing with unregistered securities, calling out a number of coins for being securities. Interestingly enough, this list didn&#8217;t include XRP. Nonetheless, the financial watchdog has demonstrated a clear stance against crypto, and it&#8217;s one of war.</p>
<ul>
<li>That said, Jay Clayton, the former Chairman of the US SEC, had something to say about the current regimen at regulatory agencies.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>What we&#8217;re hearing from leaders of the regulatory organisations is &#8220;if we&#8217;re not losing cases, if we&#8217;re not being pushed back by the courts, we&#8217;re not doing enough.&#8221; That is a fundamental shift in how we as Americans view the role of the government. &#8211; Said Clayton.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>He added: &#8220;I don&#8217;t want to be in a situation where I know the government is bringing cases they think they&#8217;re going to lose. [&#8230;] This is an ethos now &#8211; unless we&#8217;re losing, we&#8217;re not bringing enough cases.&#8221;</li>
<li>Commenting on the matter was John Deaton &#8211; a lawyer representing thousands of XRP holders.</li>
<li>According to him, the Judge in the case between Ripple and the SEC &#8220;was alluding&#8221; to the exact point.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>You&#8217;re supposed to have a good faith basis to being a case, meaning you believe you can win by applying the law. You don&#8217;t wait until a judge tells you otherwise.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">This is exactly what the Judge in the <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Ripple</a> case was alluding to when she said SEC lawyers were not maintaining a faithful allegiance to the law. You’re supposed to have a good faith basis to being a case, meaning you believe you can win by applying the law. You don’t wait… <a href="https://t.co/l8IeBkL3Iu" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/l8IeBkL3Iu</a></p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1674143192713756672?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-holders-lawyer-john-deaton-comments-on-jay-claytons-stance-on-current-regulatory-regimen/" rel="nofollow">XRP Holders Lawyer John Deaton Comments on Jay Clayton&#8217;s Stance on Current Regulatory Regimen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s When SUI Network&#8217;s Tokens Will Be Unlocked</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-sui-networks-tokens-will-be-unlocked/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257780</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Network.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Network.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The circulating supply of SUI is expected to hit 1 billion by the end of 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sui network has laid out the SUI token release schedule just a day after the team behind the layer 1 blockchain and smart contract platform dismissed allegations that they unlocked staking rewards and &#8220;dumped&#8221; them on Binance.</p>
<p>The decision to share the details of the schedule is in the interest of transparency and open communication about the tokenomics, Sui said in a statement.</p>
<h2>SUI Token Distribution</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://sui.io/token-schedule" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> shared by the protocol, SUI token distribution is set to occur over the next seven years. So far, only a portion of the allocations for Stake Subsidies, Community Access Programs, and Community Reserve has been unlocked.</p>
<p>Allocations for early contributors and investors, on the other hand, will be rolled out starting in April 2024. SUI tokens in the treasury for Sui network creator Mysten Labs will be unlocked in 2025.</p>
<p>However, certain adjustments in the current schedule could be made in the future to ensure a stable tokenomics model that supports the Sui network&#8217;s health.</p>
<p>SUI was originally developed at Meta to drive its now-abandoned Diem project. Its native token <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-tanks-14-in-7-days-can-it-get-worse-meanwhile-wall-street-memes-presale-pumps-past-7m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">witnessed</a> a massive rally of 2,000% when listing in May following its presale.</p>
<p>But the subsequent dumping rumors slashed 50% of its value from its previous high. The claims were first made by a pseudonymous crypto commentator, &#8216;DeFiSquared&#8217;, who <a href="https://twitter.com/DefiSquared/status/1673572339789844480" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">took</a> to Twitter on June 27, accusing the Sui Foundation of dumping rewards from locked and non-circulating staked SUI on Binance.</p>
<p>The foundation quickly <a href="https://twitter.com/SuiFoundation/status/1673722229421670401" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">refuted</a> the claims and said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Sui Foundation has not sold staking rewards or any other tokens from locked and non-circulating staked SUI on Binance or otherwise. All insider token allocations remain subject to and compliant with their lock-ups and other restrictions on transfer,&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Cross-Border Payments Network on Sui</h2>
<p>Fintech firm Six Clovers, which was launched by PayPal veterans in 2021, <a href="https://www.sixclovers.com/versal-payments" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> the rollout of Versal Network on the Sui blockchain to allow faster, more cost-effective, and secure cross-border payments. It is also designed to help companies transact in stablecoins and central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) in real-time.</p>
<p>The focus will be to close the gap between Web2 and Web3, according to Six Clovers co-founder and CEO Jim Nguyen.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-sui-networks-tokens-will-be-unlocked/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s When SUI Network&#8217;s Tokens Will Be Unlocked</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How High Can Shiba Inu Price Go? Are These New Low Market Cap Meme Coins a Better Alternative?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-high-can-shiba-inu-price-go-are-these-new-low-market-cap-meme-coins-a-better-alternative/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257799</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shib_tl_wsm_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/shib_tl_wsm_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With the crypto market continuing to rebound, attention-grabbing meme coins are captivating the investment community. Shiba Inu, often called the &#8220;Dogecoin killer,&#8221; has been making headlines – with investors now debating whether the token can reach the fabled $1 level. However, newer low-cap meme coins are emerging, raising questions about whether they present a more [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the crypto market continuing to rebound, attention-grabbing meme coins are captivating the investment community.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu, often called the &#8220;Dogecoin killer,&#8221; has been making headlines – with investors now debating whether the token can reach the fabled $1 level.</p>
<p>However, newer low-cap meme coins are emerging, raising questions about whether they present a more promising investment opportunity than $SHIB.</p>
<h2>Challenges &amp; Competition Plague $SHIB Performance</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, $SHIB is priced at $0.00000735, exhibiting a bearish trend over the past week.</p>
<p>The market sentiment around this meme-based token is notably pessimistic, with investors growing weary of the recent price volatility.</p>
<p>As such, Shiba Inu is a textbook example of how up-and-down the cryptocurrency market can be – yet in recent times, the token has faced significant challenges.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-22.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257810" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-22.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="269" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-22.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-22-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-22-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Fierce competition from other meme coins, for example Pepe ($PEPE), and growing frustration over delays to the Shibarium layer-2 network have put further downward pressure on price.</p>
<p>Additionally, $SHIB has just rejected the 20-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) on the daily price chart, setting the stage for another sharp drop.</p>
<p>All of this has combined to create a pessimistic outlook on $SHIB at a time when new meme coins are vying for investor interest.</p>
<h2>Can $SHIB Ever Reach $1 – Or Is The Token Destined for Mediocrity?</h2>
<p>The future trajectory of $SHIB will depend on various factors, including ecosystem enhancements, community engagement, and broader market trends.</p>
<p>Per <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/memes/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap</a>, the daily $SHIB trading volume is now half of $PEPEs, highlighting the seismic shift in investor interest.</p>
<p>Furthermore, among the three major players in the meme coin market, Shiba Inu ($SHIB) has seen the most significant price drop over the past week.</p>
<p>In contrast, Dogecoin ($DOGE) and Pepe ($PEPE) have experienced less severe declines, highlighting $SHIB&#8217;s current underperformance in the niche.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-30.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257809" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-30.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="201" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-30.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-30-300x100.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-30-50x17.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>As such, the question of whether $SHIB can ever reach the $1 milestone has become increasingly complex.</p>
<p>Given the token&#8217;s current price and total supply, most investors believe Shiba Inu is unlikely to reach this level.</p>
<p>While the world of meme coins is renowned for its exponential returns, such an enormous price increase would require a confluence of factors that currently seem beyond reach.</p>
<p>These factors would include substantial reductions in the total $SHIB supply, massive demand increases, and the long-awaited release of the Shibarium network.</p>
<p>Due to this, $SHIB reaching $1 is an inherently uncertain prospect – meaning many investors are considering alternatives in the meme coin space.</p>
<h2>Could Low-Cap Meme Coins Outpace Shiba Inu?</h2>
<p>As investors question $SHIB’s potential to reach new heights, other opportunities are emerging in the meme coin landscape.</p>
<p>Two contenders, Thug Life, and Wall Street Memes, have recently captured the market’s attention due to their low market capitalizations and unique value propositions.</p>
<h2>Thug Life On a Mission to Shake Up the Crypto Market After Raising $100,000</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life ($THUG)</a> is a brand-new meme coin that has already made a splash in the market.</p>
<p>Offering a unique blend of comedy and 80’s nostalgia, Thug Life sets itself apart from other projects by drawing inspiration from the iconic Thug Life movement.</p>
<p>With values centered around fairness and the struggle of &#8220;hustling&#8221; in the crypto market, $THUG is gaining popularity as a token with enormous potential.</p>
<p>The Thug Life team has earmarked 70% of the total token supply for presale investors, with the remaining tokens distributed for marketing efforts and community rewards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-28.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257808" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-28.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="359" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-28.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-28-300x179.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-28-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This approach ensures that early backers receive a substantial stake in Thug Life&#8217;s success – which has led to a massive influx of new members to the project&#8217;s <a href="https://t.me/thuglifetoken" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p>In addition, Thug Life’s team has pledged to lock the liquidity pool for three months once $THUG makes its DEX debut, thereby removing the risk of a rug pull occurring.</p>
<p>Thug Life is even receiving attention from crypto influencers, such as Jacob Bury, who uploaded a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mVtbCRWEmgA&amp;ab_channel=JacobCryptoBury" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> stating that the token&#8217;s value could increase by 10x after launching.</p>
<p>Early investors can buy $THUG tokens through the ongoing presale phase for just $0.0007, with no minimum or maximum investment threshold.</p>
<p>This, coupled with the eagerly-anticipated airdrop campaign to be launched post-presale, makes $THUG a low-cap meme coin with the potential to outshine Shiba Inu.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Thug Life Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Reddit-Inspired Sensation Wall Street Memes Raises Over $11m Through Presale</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a> is another meme coin contender that pays homage to the highly influential Reddit subculture that has made waves in the financial world.</p>
<p>The project encapsulates the playful nature of this subculture, resonating with a massive community of crypto enthusiasts and Reddit users.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes&#8217; ongoing presale has gained attention due to the vast community of &#8220;degens&#8221; surrounding the brand.</p>
<p>Notably, Elon Musk, known for his penchant for meme coins, has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1636924379086077954" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">interacted</a> with the project&#8217;s Twitter account, stoking interest in the $WSM token.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-23.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257807" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-23.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="287" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-23.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-23-300x143.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-23-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Moreover, Wall Street Memes’ sizable community has been built following the success of the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls NFT collection</a>, which sold out in 32 minutes back in 2021.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, the Wall Street Memes presale has raised over $11.2 million in funding, with investors able to buy $WSM tokens for $0.0304.</p>
<p>With the token primed to debut on Tier-1 exchanges in the coming weeks, $WSM looks set to provide stiff competition to Shiba Inu and other leading meme coins.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-high-can-shiba-inu-price-go-are-these-new-low-market-cap-meme-coins-a-better-alternative/" rel="nofollow">How High Can Shiba Inu Price Go? Are These New Low Market Cap Meme Coins a Better Alternative?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
