<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:21:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrencies Can&#8217;t Be Allowed to Undermine Public Trust in Capital Market, Gensler Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrencies-cant-be-allowed-to-undermine-public-trust-in-capital-market-gensler-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 23:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254530</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC Chair has been in the eye of a storm since his recent lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman Gary Gensler has made his intentions clear about the digital assets class. These are securities, nothing less, he asserted in a recent interaction.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">They should be registered with the agency before being offered to investors or meet the requirements to seek exemptions, a CNBC <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/08/sec-chair-gensler-says-crypto-frenzy-is-rife-with-hucksters-fraudsters-scam-artists-.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> quoted him. He added that exchanges listing cryptocurrencies must also register themselves with the regulatory agency. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Tokens are Investment Contracts</span></h2>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Congress included a long list of 30-plus items in the definition of a security, including the term &#8216;investment contract&#8217;…. the vast majority of crypto tokens meet the investment contract test. … Thus, crypto security issuers need to register the offer and sale of their investment contracts with the SEC or meet the requirements for an exemption,&#8221; Gensler said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He was speaking remotely at Piper Sandler Global Exchange and FinTech Conference in New York City on June 8. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Hucksters. Fraudsters. Scam artists. Ponzi schemes. The public left in line at the bankruptcy court.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is how the SEC Chair described the current cryptocurrency scene, calling it reminiscent of the time before the federal securities laws came into being in 1933. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stressing the role of regulators in cryptocurrency trading, Gensler asserted that the people&#8217;s trust in the capital market should not be undermined by allowing unregulated crypto securities markets. </span></p>
<blockquote><p>“The crypto securities markets should not be allowed to undermine the well-earned trust the public has in the capital markets. The crypto markets should not be allowed to harm investors,” he added.</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC chair also rejected the idea that there has been a lack of clarity about whether crypto assets are securities. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;When crypto asset market participants go on Twitter or TV and say they lacked &#8216;fair notice&#8217; that their conduct could be illegal, don&#8217;t believe it. … They may have made a calculated economic decision to take the risk of enforcement as the cost of doing business.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lawsuits Against Binance and Coinbase</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Citing irregularities, the SEC filed lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase early this week. The charges against Binance include selling unregistered securities &#8211; BNB and BUSD &#8211; and operating as an unregistered securities exchange and broker-dealer in the US. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawsuit seeks disgorgement of &#8220;ill-gotten funds&#8221; and permanently banning the firm from operating as a crypto and securities business in the US. Acting on the SEC&#8217;s legal move, the US District Court for the District of Columbia has issued a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-summoned-by-u-s-district-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">summons</a> against Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ). However, CZ has been exempted from in-person appearance. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In particular, it charged the two exchanges with the commingling of funds, broker-dealer, and clearing house functions. Binance was also accused of commingling funds. Reacting to the news, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1666129111025324035" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>, &#8220;Regarding the SEC complaint against us today, we&#8217;re proud to represent the industry in court to finally get some clarity around crypto rules.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrencies-cant-be-allowed-to-undermine-public-trust-in-capital-market-gensler-says/" rel="nofollow">Cryptocurrencies Can&#8217;t Be Allowed to Undermine Public Trust in Capital Market, Gensler Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOJ Identifies and Charges Mt. Gox Hackers For Stealing 647,000 Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/doj-identifies-and-charges-mt-gox-hackers-for-stealing-647000-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mt. Gox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254649</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinMtGox.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The hackers that stole customers’ Bitcoin from Mt. Gox had compromised the exchange’s private keys as early as 2011. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After over a decade, the Department of Justice (DOJ) has tracked down and charged the hackers who stole hundreds of thousands of Bitcoin from the defunct crypto exchange giant Mt. Gox. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The primary criminals identified are Russian nationals Alexey Bilyuchenko (43) and Aleksandr Verner (29).</span></p>
<h2>Mt Gox Hackers Found</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As stated by the DOJ in a </span><a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/russian-nationals-charged-hacking-one-cryptocurrency-exchange-and-illicitly-operating-another" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">press release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Friday, both Bilyuchenko and Verner are charged with “conspiring to launder approximately 647,000 bitcoins from their hack of Mt. Gox.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Though </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mt-gox-creditor-refutes-bitcoin-dumping-rumours/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Mt. Gox</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> officially suspended trading in February 2014, the hack reportedly dates back to roughly September 2011, when co-conspirators “gained unauthorized access,” to the Japanese computer system holding the private keys controlling customers’ Bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The hackers then stole coins through to May 2014, after which the exchange had already forfeited plans to rebuild. The bulk of stolen assets was funneled through Bitcoin addresses connected to accounts controlled by Bilyuchenko, Verner, and their co-conspirators at other crypto exchanges. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“IRS Criminal Investigation (IRS-CI) is specially equipped to follow the complex financial trail left by criminals, and we are dedicated to holding those accountable for crimes committed,” said IRS-CI Chief Jim Lee in a statement. </span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400">Prior to its failure, Mt. Gox was one of the most dominant Bitcoin exchanges of all time, having controlled 70% of Bitcoin trading volume by 2014. Its hack still stands as the largest exchange hack of all time in BTC-denominated terms, with its lost 744,408 coins today representing over $19 billion in value. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Mt.Gox bankruptcy process is only wrapping up this year, with the exchange’s largest creditor having </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-mt-goxs-largest-creditors-want-to-get-paid-in-bitcoin-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">opted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to receive 90% of its owed assets in BTC in February. </span></p>
<h2>Beyond Mt. Gox</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After his massive Mt. Gox steal, Bilyuchenko also conspired with Alexander Vinnik to operate BTC-e from 2011 to 2017 – a cryptocurrency exchange funded using “ill-gotten gains from Mt. Gox.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the DOJ, BTC-e processed billions of dollars worth of transactions, much of which came from “hacking incidents, ransomware events, identity theft schemes, corrupt public officials, and narcotics distribution rings.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bilyuchenko has been charged with money laundering conspiracy for his crimes at Mt. Gox, and with both money laundering conspiracy and operating an unlicensed money services business at BTC-e.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/doj-identifies-and-charges-mt-gox-hackers-for-stealing-647000-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">DOJ Identifies and Charges Mt. Gox Hackers For Stealing 647,000 Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Completes 20th Quarterly Burn: Here’s How Much OKB Was Destroyed</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-completes-20th-quarterly-burn-heres-how-much-okb-was-destroyed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKEx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254527</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/OKX_Burn.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/OKX_Burn.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The latest round is the third-largest in OKB’s burn history.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seychelles-based cryptocurrency exchange OKX has implemented the 20th round of its Buy-Back and Burn program, burning nearly 5.5 million OKB tokens this time.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.okx.com/help-center/okb-buy-back-and-burn-report-2023-03-01-2023-5-31" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a>, the total number of OKB tokens bought back from the secondary market and burned was 5,497,312.77, worth $258 million at a 90-day average.</p>
<h2>OKX Burns 5.5M OKB Tokens</h2>
<p>The crypto exchange launched the Buy-Back and Burn program in May 2019. It started repurchasing OKB from the original supply of 300 million tokens every three months. While the buyback has no specific rules, the repurchase amount depends on the seasonal market and operating performance.</p>
<p>The 20th round of the program was between March 1 and May 31, 2023. As of today, OKX has burned a total of 64,042,314.70 OKB by sending them to an address that nobody can access, leaving roughly 35,957,685 OKB currently in circulation.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The OKB team will continue to cultivate a strong connection with its global supporters while listening to their feedback for future improvements. It is committed to offering better services to users,” the crypto exchange said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Notably, the number of tokens burned recently is the third-largest in OKX’s burn history. The largest value was 6.1 million OKB burned in the 5th round between June and August 2019. The second-largest value was over 5.9 million in the 6th round between September and November 2019.</p>
<p>OKB was trading at $44.94 at writing time, signaling a minor increase in the past 24 hours, according to data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<h2>OKX Pushes for Transparency</h2>
<p>Besides burning OKB tokens to add value to the crypto asset and make it more appealing to holders, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-applies-for-regulatory-approval-in-france/" data-wpel-link="internal">OKX</a> has been a significant force driving crypto adoption. The exchange has made efforts to push the new industry standard of transparency and trust within the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>Last month, OKX <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-publishes-7th-por-report-with-10b-in-crypto-assets-continues-expansion/" data-wpel-link="internal">published</a> its seventh proof-of-reserves (PoR) report, showing reserves of $10 billion in bitcoin (BTC), ether (ETH), and Tether (USDT). While the PoR covered other widely-used crypto assets, it showed that BTC, ETH, and USDT each had reserve ratios of 103%. The exchange also enabled users to independently verify its solvency through the zk-STARK technology.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-completes-20th-quarterly-burn-heres-how-much-okb-was-destroyed/" rel="nofollow">OKX Completes 20th Quarterly Burn: Here’s How Much OKB Was Destroyed</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Transitions Ethereum Needs To Make: Vitalik Buterin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3-transitions-ethereum-needs-to-make-vitalik-buterin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254644</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/VitalikButerin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/VitalikButerin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are the three things Ethereum must have to not “fail,” according to Vitalik. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin believes Ethereum still requires “three major technical transitions” to fully mature as a tech stack – and anything less will be insufficient. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a Friday blog post, the developer highlighted what’s needed to implement each of his ideal improvements, which could include “deep changes from applications and wallets.”</span></p>
<h2>Scaling, Security, and Privacy</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Buterin, Ethereum’s three transitions include layer-2 scaling (rollups), enhanced wallet security (smart contract wallets), and improved privacy – for both standard funds transfer and other Ethereum applications. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“You can only pick 3 out of 3,” wrote the developer. Failure of just one of these transitions would mean a failure of the entire protocol, as users are incentivized to adopt cheaper “centralized workarounds” that are more reliable and “somewhat hide your data.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Yet the transitions will be difficult: for instance, the adoption of layer 2 protocols, and stealth addresses, will encourage users to use far more blockchain addresses, dismantling the “one user ~= one address mental model,” the ecosystem has grown familiar with. For Buterin, this raises the following questions:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“If you want to pay someone, how will you get the information on how to pay them?&#8230; If users have many assets stored in different places across different chains, how do they do key changes and social recovery?”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Each transition will also require updated secondary infrastructure. “Using ENS is expensive,” wrote Buterin, referencing the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-ens-ethereum-name-service/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ethereum Name Service</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – a system for applying human-readable names to blockchain addresses. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">During a bull market, Buterin estimated that fees to register a domain name could surge back above $100. Thankfully, ENS has been developing tools to make its system work on L2, which will enable the “nearly-free” domain registration needed for “people to actually use ENS.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Radical reforms of the kind that we need are actually possible,” wrote Buterin, “But there&#8217;s a lot more application-layer reform that will need to be done.</span></p>
<h2>Ethereum’s Core Use Cases</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In December 2022, Vitalik </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ten-years-later-heres-what-vitalik-thinks-blockchain-is-good-for-and-what-its-not/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">reflected</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Ethereum’s feasible use cases, stating that “money” is still the most important application ever discovered for blockchain. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Others like decentralized finance (DeFi) remain relevant, however, so long as it sticks to simple over-collateralized loan products, and doesn’t inflate into an “overcapitalized monster” reliant on unsustainable forms of yield farming.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Some ideas, however, are not realistic:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Industrial supply-chain applications have not gone anywhere,” he wrote at the time. “Decentralized Amazon on the blockchain has not happened.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-transitions-ethereum-needs-to-make-vitalik-buterin/" rel="nofollow">3 Transitions Ethereum Needs To Make: Vitalik Buterin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russia&#8217;s Biggest Bank to Allow Crypto Trading This Summer (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/russias-biggest-bank-to-allow-crypto-trading-this-summer-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254518</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sberbank.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Sberbank.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Deputy Chairman Popov said the offering could be introduced to clients by the end of June. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The largest banking institution in Russia by assets value &#8211; Sberbank &#8211; will reportedly enable private investors to buy and sell digital currencies in the following weeks.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity jumped on the bandwagon a few years ago, attempting to launch several cryptocurrency projects. For one, it sought approval to issue its own digital currency and introduced the first blockchain-focused ETF in Russia. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sberbank Pushes Forward</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www-rbc-ru.translate.goog/crypto/news/6481e3789a79474b4d1771bc?_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;_x_tr_hl=es" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by a local media outlet, the bank will let customers make transactions with digital financial assets (DFA) on the Sberbank platform as early as June. The news was confirmed by Anatoly Popov &#8211; Deputy Chairman of the board &#8211; who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://tass-ru.translate.goog/ekonomika/17964407?ysclid=lin82vbcym737314931&amp;_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;_x_tr_hl=es" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">told</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> TASS:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If we talk about individuals, then in the second quarter, we believe, in June, this function will open for individuals. Individuals will have the opportunity to buy digital financial assets and sell them. Accordingly, exchange them for cash.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sberbank initially planned to introduce the offering at the end of Q1 this year, claiming it would &#8220;bring liquidity to the bank&#8217;s platform.&#8221; Alexander Vedyakhin &#8211; First Deputy Chairman of the organization &#8211; said last year: </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We need to give individuals the opportunity to access these platforms. Sber will give this opportunity at the end of the first quarter of 2023, maybe at the beginning of the second quarter. That is March-April. I think that the first individuals will enter our CFA platform and, accordingly, come there with liquidity.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that the bank prepared a special scoring (assessment system) for its customers before releasing the option. The move ensures that users consciously make an investment decision, understanding the existing risks.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Previous Crypto Forays</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlike the hostile stance shown by the Central Bank of the Russian Federation toward the cryptocurrency sector, Sberbank </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russias-sberbank-seeks-approval-to-launch-its-own-cryptocurrency/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sought</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> approval to launch its own digital asset and to register a blockchain platform in 2021. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sberbank reached a significant milestone a few months later, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sberbank-launches-the-first-blockchain-focused-etf-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">creating</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a blockchain exchange-traded fund (ETF) that tracks leading cryptocurrency companies, including Galaxy Digital, Coinbase, and Diginex. This was the first such product in Russia that enabled domestic investors to deal with the industry without having to buy, sell, or hold tokens. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, the bank </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russias-largest-lender-sberbank-secures-license-to-issue-exchange-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">obtained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a license in 2022 that allows it to issue and exchange cryptocurrencies. Sergey Popov &#8211; Director of the Transaction Business Division, Sberbank &#8211; shed further details:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Companies will be able to make their first transaction on our blockchain platform one month from now. We are just starting our work with digital assets, realizing that further development requires adaptation of the current regulatory framework. To do that, we are ready to work closely with the regulator and executive bodies.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/russias-biggest-bank-to-allow-crypto-trading-this-summer-report/" rel="nofollow">Russia&#8217;s Biggest Bank to Allow Crypto Trading This Summer (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Green Cryptos the Next Trend after Memes in 2023 as Ecoterra Nears $5M in Presale?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/are-green-cryptos-the-next-trend-after-memes-in-2023-as-ecoterra-nears-5m-in-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254626</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ecoterra_sponsored_cover.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ecoterra_sponsored_cover.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While the current FUD surrounding crypto is regarding the SEC suing crypto exchanges for selling securities, history often repeats itself, and the last bull market saw crypto prices plummet as Tesla dropped BTC payments due to environmental concerns. Therefore, cryptos that take sustainable climate action could perform well next time the sustainability narrative arises. We [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the current FUD surrounding crypto is regarding the SEC suing crypto exchanges for selling securities, history often repeats itself, and the last bull market saw crypto prices plummet as Tesla dropped BTC payments due to environmental concerns.</p>
<p>Therefore, cryptos that take sustainable climate action could perform well next time the sustainability narrative arises. We have already seen the top altcoin, Ethereum, make efforts to become more environmentally friendly.</p>
<p>After years of planning and development, Ethereum became the first blockchain to switch its consensus mechanism. Essentially, this means the rules that valid Ethereum transactions must abide by changed.</p>
<p>The network upgrade was known as “The Merge”, as it merged two blockchains into one. Following the upgrade, Ethereum’s consensus mechanism shifted from Proof-of-Work to Proof-of-Stake.</p>
<p>The difference between the two consensus mechanisms is that Proof-of-Work relies on computational energy to secure a blockchain network, whereas monetary value secures Proof-of-Stake networks.</p>
<p>Needless to say, this makes the Ethereum chain significantly more environmentally friendly, aligning it with the Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) targets of institutional buyers.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, this could significantly improve the ETH price. However, there are plenty more ways blockchain can help climate action.</p>
<h2><strong>Ecoterra</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra</a> is perhaps the most talking about green cryptocurrency right now. This is a trending presale crypto closing in on the $5 million total, showing huge faith from investors in the project.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254634" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-8.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="624" height="295" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-8.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-8-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-8-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>The project has four main pillars, the main one being “Recycle2Earn”. The others are a used goods marketplace, a carbon offset marketplace, and an impact tracker profile for companies.</p>
<p>Recycle2Earn is a new concept that Ecoterra has developed. It will involve placing “Reverse Vending Machines” (RVMs) in stores and supermarkets globally. Users can then recycle their goods in the RVMs. to earn $ECOTERRA.</p>
<p>Ecoterra has already attained partnerships with household brands like Dr. Pepper, San Pellegrino, and Heineken. The partnerships will mean Ecoterra users can recycle these brands&#8217; products in their RVMs.</p>
<p>The other three pillars of Ecoterra all relate to serving companies involved in the circular economy. Ecoterra leverages the benefits of blockchain, such as transparency and immutability, so that the public can track companies&#8217; climate actions, ensuring they are doing what they say they are.</p>
<p>Investors are currently able to buy Ecoterra tokens for $0.00925 &#8211; a discount on the listing price of $0.01.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2><strong>Chimpzee</strong></h2>
<p>Another upcoming green crypto at the moment is Chimpzee. While Ecoterra focuses on bringing new use cases to crypto, Chimpzee is revolutionizing existing blockchain use cases by making them more eco-friendly.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-10.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254633" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-10.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="624" height="292" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-10.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-10-300x140.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-10-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>Several traders have hyped Chimpzee as one of the best green cryptos to buy. YouTuber <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l9gR5LC-SzE" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Jacob Bury</a> is bullish on the Chimpzee, highlighting in a recent video that the project presents huge potential for attracting new investors.</p>
<p>One of the reasons Chimpzee is proving so popular is that it integrates trending use cases while protecting the environment. The project will feature a Shop2Earn, Trade2Earn, and Play2Earn mechanism, as well as customized AI chimpanzee avatar NFTs.</p>
<p>Chimpzee has already taken initiatives to combat climate action. For example, just surpassed the $500K presale total raise mark, the project has pledged to plant 20,000 trees with the One Tree Planted charity. Additionally, 10% of the token’s total supply has been allocated to charity wallets.</p>
<p>Currently, in its stage 1 presale, CHMPZ is available to buy at $0.000625. However, the presale round is set to end in eight days, following which the price will rise to $0.00064. The IEO price is set at $0.00185, representing a 196% gain for investors who buy now.</p>
<h2><strong>Mooky</strong></h2>
<p>Mooky is quickly gaining notoriety as the best eco-friendly meme coin. With Pepe and other smaller meme coins exploding recently, traders have high hopes that the Mooky token could be next to perform well<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254632" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-7.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="624" height="286" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-7.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-7-300x138.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-7-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is currently in its presale, having raised over $750K and already being noticed by multiple high-profile analysts. YouTuber <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sLEJ6a2Z76g" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Borch Crypto</a>, who has 78K subscribers, highlighted the coin recently, touting it could be the next 100X presale gem.</p>
<p>According to the Mooky “Greenpaper”, Mooky is a DeFi token that aims to protect the environment. The token will let users vote on how the project helps save the environment. Therefore Mooky could become an attractive investment for conservationists and environmentalists in crypto.</p>
<p>The project will feature 1,000 “value-backed” NFTs that will grant holders access to the project’s “Ventures Club” and governance. Similarly to Chimpzee, Mooky will have a charity wallet, although Mooky’s allocation is 5%.</p>
<p>So far, the project has proven massively popular among its community, having already amassed over 12K <a href="https://twitter.com/MOOKYcoin?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a> followers and 3K <a href="https://t.me/MOOKYTOKEN" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram</a> members.</p>
<p>Currently, the presale is in stage 8 of 12, priced at $0.00000735, with the price increasing to $0.00003125 by the final round. The stage 12 price represents a 325% increase from its current valuation.</p>
<h2><strong>Ethereum</strong></h2>
<p>As mentioned, Ethereum has already taken considerable action in aligning with ESG targets. With Bitcoin showing no signs of transitioning to Proof-of-Stake, this could make Ethereum a more attractive investment for environmentally conscious institutional investors.</p>
<p>According to figures from <a href="https://pre-sustainability.com/articles/blockchain-and-our-planet-change-is-possible/#:~:text=As%20soon%20as%20the%20Ethereum,one%20day%20to%20the%20next." data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Pre-sustainability</a>, the transition from Proof-of-Work to Proof-of-Stake caused Ethereum’s energy usage to drop by 99.98%.</p>
<p>Also, a study from the CCRI (Crypto Carbon Ratings Institute) was highlighted by the <a href="https://ethereum.org/en/energy-consumption/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ethereum Foundation</a> and shows the difference in energy usage between Ethereum and Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The study found that Bitcoin uses 131 TWh/yr in energy, whereas Ethereum PoS uses 0.0026 TWh/yr. This also means Ethereum uses energy less than Netflix, AirBnB, and PayPal, which are all regarded as ESG-friendly companies.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254631" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-6.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="624" height="515" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-6.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-6-300x248.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-6-50x41.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>Both Ethereum and Bitcoin have market caps in the multi-billions, so institutional investors have a far more significant impact on price than retail.</p>
<p>Moreover, since Ethereum is the leading smart contract blockchain, with the <a href="https://defillama.com/chains" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">highest TVL</a> and most dApps, buying Ethereum enables investors to capture gains from a range of sustainable crypto protocols. This is known as the “Pick-and-Shovel” method, which many investors use for risk management and diversification.</p>
<p>We can also see from the chart below that Ethereum has followed a consistent uptrend against Bitcoin since 2019. Considering its environmental advantages against Bitcoin, the trend will likely continue looking ahead, with Ethereum potentially overtaking Bitcoin by market cap one day.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254630" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-3.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="624" height="315" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-3.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-3-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-3-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<h2><strong>Algorand</strong></h2>
<p>Algorand is another cryptocurrency blockchain targeted toward sustainability. According to the Algorand website, the blockchain is carbon-negative, which is not something that can be said for Ethereum.</p>
<p>The website also says an Algorand transaction “uses roughly 0.0000004 kg of CO2, in contrast, a Bitcoin transaction emits 338 tons of CO2”.</p>
<p>Algorand also focuses on the social and governance ethics from the ESG framework, aiming to bank the 1.7 billion unbanked individuals worldwide and improve social equality.</p>
<p>Another thing to note about Algorand is that its blockchain architecture leverages relay and participation nodes to remain highly scalable, decentralized, and secure without sacrificing sustainability.</p>
<p>The ALGO price is amid a long-term downtrend. However, it has recently approached a macro key level. If it begins to bounce from here, it will form a double bottom pattern and potentially see a strong movement upwards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254629" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="624" height="312" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/are-green-cryptos-the-next-trend-after-memes-in-2023-as-ecoterra-nears-5m-in-presale/" rel="nofollow">Are Green Cryptos the Next Trend after Memes in 2023 as Ecoterra Nears $5M in Presale?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Kwon Supposedly Transferred $29M in Crypto to a Mysterious Wallet After his Arrest</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-supposedly-transferred-29m-in-crypto-to-a-mysterious-wallet-after-his-arrest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254500</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Do_Kwon1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Do_Kwon1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kwon or "someone under his direction" purportedly moved almost $30 million in crypto after the arrest in Montenegro and cashed out the funds. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dan Sunghan &#8211; Director of the Financial Crime Investigation Bureau at the Seoul Southern District Prosecution Service &#8211; claimed that the former crypto mogul Do Kwon had moved nearly $30 million in digital currencies to an unknown wallet shortly after his arrest in Montenegro.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 31-year-old South Korean has faced huge criticism and was blamed for having a hand in the massive LUNA/USD collapse last year that triggered multi-billion investor losses. He allegedly spent several months on the run before being detained by the authorities of Montenegro in March this year. Chances are high that he will be extradited to the USA or South Korea and face justice there.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kwon&#8217;s Suspicious Crypto Dealings</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to Sunghan, Terraform Labs&#8217; Co-Founder &#8211; Do Kwon, or someone from his inner cycle </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/korean-prosecutors-seek-crypto-millions-tied-to-do-kwon-and-terrausd-1.1930362" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">transferred</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the crypto stash from a wallet belonging to the Luna Foundation Guard (LFG) after the arrest and later cashed it out. The prosecutor said the magistrates are trying to detect where the moved funds ended up:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We&#8217;re assuming that Do Kwon, or someone under his direction, took out the amount and moved it to another wallet, not to Sygnum, and cashed it out somewhere else.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is not the first time Kwon&#8217;s name has been connected with perplexing transfers. The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-cashed-10k-btc-using-a-swiss-bank-claims-the-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suggested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this year that he cashed out 10,000 bitcoin shortly after the Terra crash. The regulator claimed he used an unnamed Swiss bank to conduct the transaction. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another recent report </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-transferred-7-million-to-a-law-firm-shortly-before-the-terra-crash-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">indicated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the developer sent 9 billion won (nearly $7 million) to the law firm Kim &amp; Chang before<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-what-happened-to-luna-and-why-the-price-can-continue-crashing/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the LUNA/USD fallout</a>. Nonetheless, attorneys from the company refused to shed additional details on the matter, saying:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are unable to provide specifics on individual cases. We have conducted our legal advisory services as usual and have legitimately received the fee for the services.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kwon&#8217;s Unknown Future</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Blamed by numerous agencies, watchdogs, and fallen investors as the main culprit behind the Terra collapse, Kwon didn&#8217;t help his case as he failed to cooperate with the relative authorities on solving the issue. Instead, he escaped his homeland and supposedly swapped multiple destinations in the past year, including<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/reports-of-do-kwon-escaping-via-dubai-not-false-says-south-korean-prosecutor/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the UAE</a>, Mauritius, Seychelles, Russia, and more.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Several sources <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-do-kwon-is-currently-hiding-in-serbia-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">at the end of 2022 that he popped up in Europe, specifically Serbia. The hunt was so intense that it even grabbed the attention of Interpol, which issued a red notice for him. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite his successful maneuvers from law enforcement agencies, Kwon was finally </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-do-kwon-reportedly-arrested-in-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">detained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in the Balkan country of Montenegro in March. His arrest happened at the airport in the capital Podgorica while he was carrying a falsified passport, hinting that he was about to move to another nation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The South Korean spent some time in a local correctional facility before applying to be released on a $440K bail. The request was initially denied by a high court in Montenegro but later </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/montenegrin-basic-court-reapproves-do-kwons-430k-bail-request/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">approved</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by the Basic Court of Podgorica.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Still, his problems seem far from over. The United States and South Korea have both insisted on Kwon&#8217;s extradition. Should he be found guilty in America, he could spend over 100 years in jail, while the maximum sentence in his homeland could be 40 years. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-supposedly-transferred-29m-in-crypto-to-a-mysterious-wallet-after-his-arrest/" rel="nofollow">Do Kwon Supposedly Transferred $29M in Crypto to a Mysterious Wallet After his Arrest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple (XRP) Only Major Alt in Green as SEC Takes Binance and Coinbase to Court: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-only-major-alt-in-green-as-sec-takes-binance-and-coinbase-to-court-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254555</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance and Coinbase are under heavy fire. The United States Securities and Exchange Commission is out for blood.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What a week&#8230;</p>
<p>There&#8217;s absolutely no need to beat around the bush, so let&#8217;s kick it off directly &#8230; the United States Securities and Exchange Commission sued Binance. That&#8217;s right, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange is under siege. Binance, Binance US, and Changpeng Zhao are all named in the lawsuit, as the SEC is out for blood.</p>
<p>The Commission has asked the court to freeze the assets of Binance US and has also issued a summons for CZ. Since he&#8217;s not a US citizen, though, reports have it that he doesn&#8217;t have to be physically present but can attend remotely.</p>
<p>The markets tumbled, needless to say. Bitcoin plummeted toward $25K, while Binance Coin suffered even more. The entire cryptocurrency community was taken by surprise by this sudden move.</p>
<p>And if that was all, perhaps things might have looked somewhat okay. But that was far from everything. The SEC is truly out for blood. The very next day, it filed against Coinbase.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s right, the two largest cryptocurrency exchanges, one of which is a publicly-traded company in the United States, are currently being sued by the Securities and Exchange Commission for violating securities laws. The market took a beating but was able to recover to a point where Bitcoin currently trades at $26,600, down 1.6% in the past seven days.</p>
<p>In the lawsuit against Coinbase, the SEC alleged that multiple cryptocurrencies are securities, naming ADA, SOL, MATIC, and others directly. As a result, ADA is down 15%, MATIC &#8211; 14%, and SOL &#8211; 10%. Expectedly, BNB is down about 15% as well.</p>
<p>If you don&#8217;t want to go through the full documentation, we&#8217;ve summarized them both in two pieces found below:</p>
<ul>
<li><em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">The 3 Takeaways From the Lawsuit Between the SEC and Coinbase</a></em></li>
<li><em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">3 Most Serious Claims in the SEC Lawsuit v. Binance</a></em></li>
</ul>
<p>Amid all this, the only major cryptocurrency that&#8217;s holding well and is trading in the green for the past seven days is Ripple&#8217;s XRP. Perhaps one thing to do with it is the fact that the SEC&#8217;s claim against Coinbase didn&#8217;t name XRP a security.</p>
<p>All in all, the week was amongst the most intense ones in a while, and it&#8217;s very interesting to see how the industry will deal with the situation. Both Binance and Coinbase will be fighting the SEC claims.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Market Data</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254603" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover.jpg" alt="sec_coinbase_binance_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sec_coinbase_binance_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,154B | 24H Vol: $29B | BTC Dominance: 44.8%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $26,600 (-1.6%) | ETH: $1,848 (-2.1%) | BNB: $262 (-14.6%)</p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Better Not Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Plummets After SEC Sues Binance for Securities Violations. </strong>The world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Binance &#8211; has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission for allegedly violating securities laws, among other things.</p>
<p><strong>SEC Sues Coinbase, Day After Filing a Lawsuit Against Binance. </strong>If the above wasn&#8217;t enough&#8230; well, the SEC also sued Coinbase for violating securities laws. This <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">happened</a> exactly one day after the Commission filed against Binance in what seems to be a massive move against the crypto industry.</p>
<p><strong>Binance CEO Summoned By U.S. District Court. </strong>Binance&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Changpeng Zhao &#8211; is also under fire by the SEC. He has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-summoned-by-u-s-district-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">issued</a> a summons by the US District Court for the District of Columbia following the lawsuit against himself and his exchange.</p>
<p><strong>Binance US Delists 101 Trading Pairs Following SEC Freezing Order. </strong>Almost immediately after the SEC sued Binance, CZ, and Binance US, the latter <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-delists-101-trading-pairs-following-sec-freezing-order/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> it has no plans of resuming trading for 101 trading pairs on its platform. Some of the targeted pairs include EOS/USDT, AAVE/USDT, COMP/USDT, and so forth.</p>
<p><strong>The 3 Takeaways From the Lawsuit Between the SEC and Coinbase. </strong>The complaint of the SEC against Coinbase is 101 pages long. We&#8217;ve <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">summarized</a> the three main takeaways from the lawsuit, which will most likely have an impact on the industry.</p>
<p><strong>3 Most Serious Claims in the SEC Lawsuit V. Binance. </strong>Binance, CZ, and Binance US are the defendants in the latest lawsuit against the US Securities and Exchange Commission. Here are some of the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">most serious claims</a> the agency made against the firm and its CEO.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ripple, Binance Coin, Cardano, Solana, and Polygon – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-jun-9-xrp-ada-bnb-sol-and-matic/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-only-major-alt-in-green-as-sec-takes-binance-and-coinbase-to-court-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">Ripple (XRP) Only Major Alt in Green as SEC Takes Binance and Coinbase to Court: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ERD DeFi Lending Platform and USDE Stablecoin Unveiled at EDCON 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/erd-defi-lending-platform-and-usde-stablecoin-unveiled-at-edcon-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254563</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imageedit_9_7486743647_1686286060Pl2NumqKxj.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/imageedit_9_7486743647_1686286060Pl2NumqKxj.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Podgorica, Montenegro, June 9th, 2023] At EDCON 2023 in Montenegro, the Ethereum Reserve Dollar (“ERD”) team introduced their innovative decentralized lending platform and USDE stablecoin to the industry. ERD is a lending platform that allows users to borrow USDE, a USD-pegged stablecoin native to the platform, using liquid staking derivatives (LSDs) and [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Podgorica, Montenegro, June 9th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>At EDCON 2023 in Montenegro, the Ethereum Reserve Dollar (“ERD”) team introduced their innovative decentralized lending platform and USDE stablecoin to the industry. ERD is a lending platform that allows users to borrow USDE, a USD-pegged stablecoin native to the platform, using liquid staking derivatives (LSDs) and blue-chip DeFi tokens as collateral. The protocol maintains a minimum collateralization ratio of 110%, striking a balance between decentralization, capital efficiency, and price stability.</p>
<p>In the fast-paced world of blockchain and cryptocurrencies, the demand for fully decentralized stablecoins is growing. The challenge has been to simultaneously achieve capital efficiency, price stability, and decentralization, a combination that has proven difficult to achieve.</p>
<p>Numerous attempts have been made to create stablecoins that are both decentralized and capital efficient. However, these efforts often led to significant price fluctuations, causing depegging and collapse. The industry has thus been left with a choice between capital efficiency and decentralization, with price stability being a crucial requirement for any stablecoin&#8217;s survival and expansion.</p>
<p>Ethereum Reserve Dollar is designed to address these challenges. ERD is fully decentralized, providing a safer solution to the dominant centralized and semi-centralized stablecoins in the market. It employs a fully decentralized lending protocol and a robust liquidation mechanism, enabling users to borrow USDE using LSDs and blue-chip DeFi tokens as collateral. The platform secures loans with a Stability Pool containing USDE, which allows for immediate liquidation and bypasses the need for liquidators to prepare USDE or engage in a complex auction process. Furthermore, the protocol&#8217;s design allows users to borrow at only a 110% collateralization ratio, achieving an ideal combination of decentralization, capital efficiency, and price stability.</p>
<p>Notably, ERD also aims to provide greater value as a governance token and introduce widely distributed decentralized assets on the ETH network, addressing limitations observed in similar protocols, such as those of the Liquity Protocol.</p>
<p><span style="color: #767676; font-size: 19px; font-style: italic;">“Looking back at the collapses of so many failed stablecoins, and the depegging of USDT in 2022 and USDC in 2023, the industry is still searching for a truly decentralized, capital-efficient, and robust solution,&#8221; said Steve Hopkins, ERD’s CMO. “ERD is this and so much more; it&#8217;s a solution designed to become a truly decentralized reserve asset on the Ethereum network. We believe ERD offers a significant step forward in blockchain and DeFi technology. We’re thrilled to share it with the world.”</span></p>
<p>The ERD team will launch their testnet event on June 12, 2023. This event will offer the opportunity to experience the platform&#8217;s unique features and benefits firsthand while also entitling early adopters to share in the upside of the project’s growth.</p>
<p>The ERD Protocol is set to redefine the stablecoin landscape. With its unique features and benefits, it offers a promising solution for efficient and decentralized lending. The team encourages everyone to participate in the upcoming testnet event and experience the future of DeFi.</p>
<p>For more information about the ERD Protocol and its upcoming testnet event, please visit the official website at <a href="https://www.erd.xyz/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://erd.xyz/</a> and follow the project on Twitter at <a href="https://twitter.com/Ethereum_ERD" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">@Ethereum_ERD</a>.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Testnet_Announcement_20230531_1686258246CPbd7UfSfo.jpg" /></p>
<h2>About ERD</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.erd.xyz/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ERD</a> is a decentralized lending protocol that enables users to borrow in USDE, a stablecoin pegged to the US dollar, using LSDs and blue-chip DeFi tokens as collateral. It aims to address the dominance of centralized stablecoins and offer a truly decentralized, capital-efficient alternative. The protocol offers a minimum collateralization ratio of 110% and secures loans with a stable pool containing USDE and other Ethereum-based assets. The benefits of ERD include low-interest rates, high capital efficiency, direct redemptions, and decentralization. Its goal is to become a truly decentralized reserve asset on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>Long live Ethereum Reserve Dollar. On Ethereum, By Ethereum, For Ethereum.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/erd-defi-lending-platform-and-usde-stablecoin-unveiled-at-edcon-2023/" rel="nofollow">ERD DeFi Lending Platform and USDE Stablecoin Unveiled at EDCON 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis Jun-9: XRP, ADA, BNB, SOL, and MATIC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-jun-9-xrp-ada-bnb-sol-and-matic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254546</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptopost_friday_0206231-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptopost_friday_0206231-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, Solana, and Polygon. Ripple (XRP) Ripple continues to surprise the market with its strength, considering that in the past week, most altcoins ended up in red. More so, XRP has managed to close in green with a 2.6% increase in price, making it [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, Solana, and Polygon.</p>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>Ripple continues to surprise the market with its strength, considering that in the past week, most altcoins ended up in red. More so, XRP has managed to close in green with a 2.6% increase in price, making it the best performer on our list today.</p>
<p>This resilience has taken the price just under the key resistance at 53 cents. Volatility also increased this week, and buyers already attempted to break higher but were pushed back by bears.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, XRP seems well-positioned to break the key resistance since the momentum is firmly on the buyer&#8217;s side. The indicators on the daily timeframe are also bullish, and another push higher could turn the 53 cents level into support.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254552" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254552" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254552" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41" width="2852" height="1458" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41-1024x523.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41-768x393.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41-1536x785.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41-2048x1047.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT_2023-06-09_14-40-41-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254552" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>Cardano is the exact opposite of XRP. The price has made a lower low and closed the week with a 16% loss. This major crash could also be explained by the fact that the US SEC declared ADA security in the lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>Sentiment about Cardano is quite bearish at this time, and the price reflects this. For this reason, the cryptocurrency seems more likely to continue to fall toward the key support at 30 cents.</p>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking ahead</span></span>, buyers have to do their best to stop the assault from bears and reverse the downtrend at the key support. Any weakness is likely to translate into further losses for Cardano holders in the future.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254551" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254551" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254551" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04" width="2852" height="1458" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04-1024x523.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04-768x393.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04-1536x785.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04-2048x1047.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-04-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254551" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Binance Coin (BNB)</span></p>
<p>With Binance sued by the US SEC, the price of its token, BNB, took a nosedive and closed the week with a 15% loss. This also pushed it to the key support at $250.</p>
<p>The current PA is bearish and has remained so for all week. However, the selling pressure appears to be fading as we approach the weekend. So long the key support at $250 holds, then buyers could try to turn around this situation.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Binance Coin buyers should try their best to hold at the current support, because any weakness here could see it quickly fall to $200 next.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254550" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254550" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254550" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40.png" alt="BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40" width="2852" height="1458" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40-1024x523.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40-768x393.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40-1536x785.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40-2048x1047.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BNBUSDT_2023-06-09_14-41-40-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254550" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Solana (SOL) </span></p>
<p>Solana&#8217;s volatility increased considering the events of this past week, and the buyers failed to defend themselves from the incoming sell pressure. For this reason, SOL closed the week with a 9% loss.</p>
<p>The price also made a lower low, and sellers appear to have the upper hand right now. If the pressure continues, then SOL could fall to the key support at $17.5.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Solana continues to find itself in a large range, and despite this most recent loss in valuation, the support might hold, just like it did in March. If so, this cryptocurrency will likely continue to move sideways.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254549" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254549" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254549" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56" width="2852" height="1458" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56-1024x523.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56-768x393.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56-1536x785.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56-2048x1047.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-09_14-42-56-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254549" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Polygon (MATIC)</h2>
<p>Polygon shares a lot in terms of price action with Cardano. Since MATIC was also listed as a security alongside ADA in the SEC lawsuits against Coinbase, the price was quick to react and fell by 13% this week.</p>
<p>With MATIC in a clear downtrend with lower lows and lower highs, it needs a miracle to change this price action. Buyers have vanished since February, and they could not stop this bearish trend.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, MATIC has good support at 75 cents, and bulls could attempt to make a stand here. However, in the past, every support level was eventually broken by sellers, and it is unclear if MATIC has the strength to hold here.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254548" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254548" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254548" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52.png" alt="MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52" width="2852" height="1458" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52-1024x523.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52-768x393.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52-1536x785.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52-2048x1047.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-09_14-44-52-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254548" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-jun-9-xrp-ada-bnb-sol-and-matic/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis Jun-9: XRP, ADA, BNB, SOL, and MATIC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
