<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Green Crypto Chimpzee Raises More than $700,000 While Helping to Fight Climate Change – Next Big Thing?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-chimpzee-raises-more-than-700000-while-helping-fight-climate-change-next-big-thing.htm</link><description>The eco-friendly crypto project, Chimpzee, has achieved a significant milestone with its $CHMPZ token presale, surpassing $729,000.  &lt;br /&gt;
This remarkable achievement can be attributed to the real value utility the project offers in promoting environmental sustainability. &lt;br /&gt;
Chimpzee is a decentralized project that empowers individuals to make a positive impact on the environment and conserve wildlife while earning crypto rewards. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-chimpzee-raises-more-than-700000-while-helping-fight-climate-change-next-big-thing.htm"&gt;Read More: Green Crypto Chimpzee Raises More than $700,000 While Helping to Fight Climate Change – Next Big Thing?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-chimpzee-raises-more-than-700000-while-helping-fight-climate-change-next-big-thing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118901/316562/chimpzee.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="801980"/></item><item><title>USDC-Issuer Circle Looking to Launch Stablecoin in Japan</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/usdc-issuer-circle-looking-issue-stablecoin-japan.htm</link><description>The firm behind USDC stablecoin, Circle, is looking to launch a stablecoin in Japan under new regulations that came into effect last month.  &lt;br /&gt;
In an interview with Coindesk Japan, Circle CEO Jeremy Alliare said that Japan would become an extremely large market for them if stablecoin adoption in cross border trade and global commerce picks up in the coming time.  &lt;br /&gt;
Allaire further expressed interest in pursuing different partnerships in the Asian country. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/usdc-issuer-circle-looking-issue-stablecoin-japan.htm"&gt;Read More: USDC-Issuer Circle Looking to Launch Stablecoin in Japan&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>USDC</category><category>Circle</category><category>Jeremy Allaire</category><category>Japan</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/usdc-issuer-circle-looking-issue-stablecoin-japan.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118897/316559/jeremy-allaire.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="100956"/></item><item><title>BlackRock CEO Praises Bitcoin for 'Digitizing Gold', Says BTC Could 'Revolutionize Finance'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-ceo-praises-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold-says-btc-could-revolutionize-finance.htm</link><description>BlackRock CEO Larry Fink has expessed support for Bitcoin (BTC), referring to it as an "international asset" that could revolutionize finance.   &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent interview on Fox Business, Fink stated that his company is keen on reducing the cost and complexity associated with investing in Bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
He said that he believes this move would democratize the cryptocurrency market and make it more accessible for retail investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-ceo-praises-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold-says-btc-could-revolutionize-finance.htm"&gt;Read More: BlackRock CEO Praises Bitcoin for 'Digitizing Gold', Says BTC Could 'Revolutionize Finance'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Bitcoin ETF</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-ceo-praises-bitcoin-for-digitizing-gold-says-btc-could-revolutionize-finance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118864/316523/adobestock-389547752-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="221477"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu is Going to Zero as SHIB Price Falls 10% and This Lesser Known Meme Coin Might Be the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-going-zero-as-shib-price-falls-10-lesser-known-meme-coin-might-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>The price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) has dropped by 1.5% in the past hour, cutting away at gains the meme token had made as part of a market-wide rally this morning. &lt;br /&gt;
At $0.00000750, SHIB is up by a very modest 0.4% in 24 hours, with the altcoin down by 4.5% in a fortnight and by 6.6% in the last 30 days. &lt;br /&gt;
Even more worryingly, SHIB has also fallen by 7% since the beginning of the year, whereas many major tokens have actually recovered substantially, with Bitcoin (BTC) increasing by 85%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-going-zero-as-shib-price-falls-10-lesser-known-meme-coin-might-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu is Going to Zero as SHIB Price Falls 10% and This Lesser Known Meme Coin Might Be the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-going-zero-as-shib-price-falls-10-lesser-known-meme-coin-might-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118872/316543/shiba-inu-is-going-to-zer.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1058862"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Mining Activity Sees Huge Surge in UAE – Here’s the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-activity-sees-huge-surge-uae-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Bitcoin mining companies have been looking for a suitable region to call home ever since they were forced to leave China.  &lt;br /&gt;
Many of them are now eyeing the United Arab Emirates as a potential location to set up shop in, as the country started emerging as the crypto mining hub in the Middle East. &lt;br /&gt;
Some major mining companies have already signed agreements and entered partnerships with the digital asset arm of a sovereign wealth fund from Abu Dhabi. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-activity-sees-huge-surge-uae-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Mining Activity Sees Huge Surge in UAE – Here’s the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-activity-sees-huge-surge-uae-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118871/316537/bitcoin-mining-activity-s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="512534"/></item><item><title>Bankrupt Lending Firm Celsius Moves $70 Million in Altcoins to Swap for Bitcoin and Ether</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-lending-firm-celsius-moves-70-million-altcoins-swap-for-bitcoin-ether.htm</link><description>Celsius Network, the bankrupt crypto lending firm, has made its first swap converting its altcoin holdings into Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH), a week after receiving a court order to liquidate its altcoin assets. &lt;br /&gt;
A New York court passed an order on June 30, allowing Celsius debtors to trade their altcoin for BTC and ETH starting July 1....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-lending-firm-celsius-moves-70-million-altcoins-swap-for-bitcoin-ether.htm"&gt;Read More: Bankrupt Lending Firm Celsius Moves $70 Million in Altcoins to Swap for Bitcoin and Ether&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-lending-firm-celsius-moves-70-million-altcoins-swap-for-bitcoin-ether.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118861/316520/bankrupt-2922154-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="494218"/></item><item><title>Pepe Coin Price Prediction as PEPE Rises 4% in 24 Hours – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-rises-4-24-hours-time-buy.htm</link><description>The Pepe Coin price has risen by 4% in the past 24 hours, jumping to $0.00000173 amid a market-wide rally today. &lt;br /&gt;
PEPE is now up by 14% in a week and by 70% in the last 30 days, although it remains 60% down from its all-time high of $0.00000431, set back in early May. &lt;br /&gt;
PEPE's ascent could mean that it's due to correct in the next day or two, but with the market seemingly regaining a significant amount of optimism, the meme token could just as easily rise for a little while longer....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-rises-4-24-hours-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin Price Prediction as PEPE Rises 4% in 24 Hours – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-rises-4-24-hours-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118865/316531/pepe-coin-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1331130"/></item><item><title>Binance CEO: Exchange Gearing Up for Increased Crypto Trading Volumes – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-exchange-gearing-up-for-increased-crypto-trading-volumes-heres-why.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange, is doing “a lot of preparation” to be ready for increased trading volumes over the coming months, CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) has said. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking in an AMA (“ask me anything”) session on Twitter Spaces on Wednesday, CZ said that if history is a guide, trading volumes will rise going forward....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-exchange-gearing-up-for-increased-crypto-trading-volumes-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance CEO: Exchange Gearing Up for Increased Crypto Trading Volumes – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-exchange-gearing-up-for-increased-crypto-trading-volumes-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118866/316529/changpeng-zhao.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="34077"/></item><item><title>Nasdaq Refiles Valkyrie's Bitcoin ETF Application with Coinbase Surveillance-Sharing Agreement</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nasdaq-refiles-valkyries-bitcoin-etf-application-with-coinbase-surveillance-sharing-agreement.htm</link><description>Stock exchange giant Nasdaq has refiled Valkyrie’s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) with Coinbase as its “surveillance-sharing” partner.  &lt;br /&gt;
As per a July 3 filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the stock exchange submitted a proposed rule change allowing the listing of a spot Bitcoin ETF for the Valkyrie Bitcoin Fund. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nasdaq-refiles-valkyries-bitcoin-etf-application-with-coinbase-surveillance-sharing-agreement.htm"&gt;Read More: Nasdaq Refiles Valkyrie's Bitcoin ETF Application with Coinbase Surveillance-Sharing Agreement&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin ETF</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>US SEC</category><category>Nasdaq</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nasdaq-refiles-valkyries-bitcoin-etf-application-with-coinbase-surveillance-sharing-agreement.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118845/316526/bitcoin-etf-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="144638"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Insights from BlackRock CEO and Calls for DE Dollarization</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-insights-from-blackrock-ceo-calls-for-de-dollarization.htm</link><description>Bitcoin price is currently trading at $30,543, experiencing around 1% decrease on Thursday. Notably, Larry Fink, the esteemed leader of BlackRock, has expressed his support for Bitcoin, recognizing its potential to revolutionize the financial landscape.  &lt;br /&gt;
Despite the recent decline, Bitcoin is still up 1% for the week, highlighting its resilience and ongoing market interest. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-insights-from-blackrock-ceo-calls-for-de-dollarization.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Insights from BlackRock CEO and Calls for DE Dollarization&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-insights-from-blackrock-ceo-calls-for-de-dollarization.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118829/316453/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1495601"/></item><item><title>Binance Labs Leads $4M Funding for AI Blockchain Data Firm Web3Go</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-leads-4m-funding-for-ai-blockchain-data-firm-web3go.htm</link><description>Singapore-based blockchain start-up Web3Go has raised $4 million in a seed round led by Binance Labs, the venture capital and incubator arm of crypto exchange giant Binance. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the press release, other participants in the seed round financing included Hashkey Capital, NGC, Shima Capital, IVC, LIF, Big Brain Holdings, and Archerman Capital. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-leads-4m-funding-for-ai-blockchain-data-firm-web3go.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Labs Leads $4M Funding for AI Blockchain Data Firm Web3Go&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Web3</category><category>Binance</category><category>Investment</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>HashKey Group</category><category>AI</category><category>BNB Chain</category><category>Polkadot</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-leads-4m-funding-for-ai-blockchain-data-firm-web3go.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118840/316511/f0rzdzyauaasqod-t.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="226508"/></item><item><title>CFTC Finds Celsius Network and Its Ex-CEO Guilty of Breaking Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cftc-finds-celsius-network-and-its-ex-ceo-guilty-of-breaking-rules.htm</link><description>Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) investigators have ruled that crypto lender Celsius Network and its former CEO Alex Mashinsky violated US rules before the company collapsed.  &lt;br /&gt;
The findings suggest that Celsius misled investors and failed to register with the CFTC, Bloomberg reported Wednesday, citing people familiar with the matter. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cftc-finds-celsius-network-and-its-ex-ceo-guilty-of-breaking-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: CFTC Finds Celsius Network and Its Ex-CEO Guilty of Breaking Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Alex Mashinsky</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cftc-finds-celsius-network-and-its-ex-ceo-guilty-of-breaking-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118853/316510/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="203716"/></item><item><title>Financial Regulator: South African Crypto Exchanges Must Be Licensed by Year-End</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/financial-regulator-south-african-crypto-exchanges-must-be-licensed-by-year-end.htm</link><description>South Africa’s Financial Sector Conduct Authority (FSCA) has mandated that all crypto exchanges register and obtain operational licenses by the end of 2023.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to the regulator, firms that fail to comply with this guideline and continue operating without a license will face the possibility of closing down or paying fines. &lt;br /&gt;
The FSCA received about 20 applications following two weeks of opening license registrations....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/financial-regulator-south-african-crypto-exchanges-must-be-licensed-by-year-end.htm"&gt;Read More: Financial Regulator: South African Crypto Exchanges Must Be Licensed by Year-End&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/financial-regulator-south-african-crypto-exchanges-must-be-licensed-by-year-end.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118811/316430/south-africa-g5d12a3c35-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="366420"/></item><item><title>Chinese Banks Join Beijing’s Efforts to Integrate CBDC With Social Security Cards</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-banks-join-beijings-efforts-integrate-cbdc-social-security-cards.htm</link><description>Chinese state-owned banks are set to join efforts to integrate the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC), the digital yuan, with government-issued social security cards. &lt;br /&gt;
Late last month, the Chinese Ministry of Human Resources and Social Security said it wanted to “explore and promote” ways to “add digital yuan payment functions” to the cards. &lt;br /&gt;
The plastic cards are used as a form of identification in banks and government offices....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-banks-join-beijings-efforts-integrate-cbdc-social-security-cards.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Banks Join Beijing’s Efforts to Integrate CBDC With Social Security Cards&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-banks-join-beijings-efforts-integrate-cbdc-social-security-cards.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118808/316411/china-0507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="504388"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Gains 5% in 7 Days – Is a New Bull Market Starting?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-gains-5-7-days-new-bull-market-starting.htm</link><description>In the past seven days, Shiba Inu (SHIB) has experienced a gain of 5%, bringing its price to 0.00000781.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, the cryptocurrency quickly reversed its upward movement and began testing the double bottom support at $0.00000740.  &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, this support level coincides with an upward trendline, further reinforcing its significance. &lt;br /&gt;
The current price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) stands at $0.000007, accompanied by a 24-hour trading volume of $128,372,878. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-gains-5-7-days-new-bull-market-starting.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Gains 5% in 7 Days – Is a New Bull Market Starting?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-gains-5-7-days-new-bull-market-starting.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118827/316449/shiba.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="305943"/></item><item><title>Brazil’s Central Bank Uploads CBDC Files to GitHub – Digital BRL Rollout Imminent?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazils-central-bank-uploads-cbdc-files-github-digital-brl-rollout-imminent.htm</link><description>The Brazilian Central Bank has uploaded a large collection of central bank digital currency (CBDC)-related documents to GitHub – as the nation edges closer to a digital real rollout. &lt;br /&gt;
The collection of documents was uploaded to the bank’s GitHub page on June 3, but a number of files were also updated on June 4. &lt;br /&gt;
The Brazilian media outlet Portal do Bitcoin pointed out that the documents contain key details about four aspects of the coin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazils-central-bank-uploads-cbdc-files-github-digital-brl-rollout-imminent.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazil’s Central Bank Uploads CBDC Files to GitHub – Digital BRL Rollout Imminent?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazils-central-bank-uploads-cbdc-files-github-digital-brl-rollout-imminent.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118727/316274/brazil-0507.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="575121"/></item><item><title>Bitget Crypto Exchange Ventures into Crypto Loans Market Despite 2022 Sector Challenges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitget-crypto-exchange-ventures-into-crypto-loans-market-despite-2022-sector-challenges.htm</link><description>The crypto derivatives exchange Bitget has launched a new crypto lending program that will let users stake their own coins in exchange for loans in another. &lt;br /&gt;
The platform aims to cater to borrowers who are dissatisfied with traditional lenders, a press release from the firm said. &lt;br /&gt;
It explained that the new program, dubbed the Crypto Loans program, will enable borrowers to use their coins as collateral to secure loans of an equivalent amount denominated in another cryptocurrency....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitget-crypto-exchange-ventures-into-crypto-loans-market-despite-2022-sector-challenges.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitget Crypto Exchange Ventures into Crypto Loans Market Despite 2022 Sector Challenges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitget</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitget-crypto-exchange-ventures-into-crypto-loans-market-despite-2022-sector-challenges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118790/316372/crypto-loan.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="148105"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Starts Forming Bearish Chart Pattern – Time to Sell?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-starts-forming-bullish-chart-pattern-time-buy.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) price is currently trading at $30,450, unable to break above the psychological level of $31,000.  &lt;br /&gt;
The formation of a bearish chart pattern suggests a potential downward trend in the near term.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this Bitcoin price prediction, we will analyze the market conditions and explore whether this bearish pattern presents a buying opportunity for investors. &lt;br /&gt;
The current price of Bitcoin is $30,417, with a 24-hour trading volume of $12.6 billion....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-starts-forming-bullish-chart-pattern-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Starts Forming Bearish Chart Pattern – Time to Sell?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-starts-forming-bullish-chart-pattern-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118826/316444/5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480456"/></item><item><title>Crypto Comeback Boosts ProShares' Bitcoin Futures ETF Above $1 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-comeback-boosts-proshares-bitcoin-futures-etf-above-1-billion.htm</link><description>The recent resurgence in the crypto market, triggered by BlackRock's unexpected filing for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), has led to a significant increase in inflows into ProShares' Bitcoin futures-based ETF. &lt;br /&gt;
ProShares' fund, which trades under the ticker code BITO, experienced inflows of $14.9 million on June 29 and $11.9 million on July 3, bringing its total assets under management (AuM) to $1.04 billion, according to ETF.com....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-comeback-boosts-proshares-bitcoin-futures-etf-above-1-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Comeback Boosts ProShares' Bitcoin Futures ETF Above $1 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>ProShares</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-comeback-boosts-proshares-bitcoin-futures-etf-above-1-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118784/316353/etf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="65232"/></item><item><title>'Get Ready to Comply' - UK Regulator's Message to Crypto Companies</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/get-ready-to-comply-uk-regulators-message-to-crypto-companies.htm</link><description>The United Kingdom's Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) has issued a warning to all crypto asset firms operating in the country, reminding them to ensure marketing compliance by the October deadline. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a letter dated July 4, the FCA has stated that starting from October 8, crypto companies marketing to users in the UK must be in compliance with the financial promotions regime or face the consequences....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/get-ready-to-comply-uk-regulators-message-to-crypto-companies.htm"&gt;Read More: 'Get Ready to Comply' - UK Regulator's Message to Crypto Companies&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>UK FCA</category><category>Regulation</category><category>British Investors</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/get-ready-to-comply-uk-regulators-message-to-crypto-companies.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118801/316398/adobestock-ascannio-1-med.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="53501"/></item></channel></rss>
