<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:03:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Accuses Binance.US of Inflating Trading Volumes]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-accuses-binanceus-of-inflating-trading-volumes</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-us-cz-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-us-cz-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-us-cz-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:34:49 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-accuses-binanceus-of-inflating-trading-volumes</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In its newest scare tactic, the SEC alleged Binance.US inflated its trading volumes through a practice known as &ldquo;wash trading.&rdquo; </p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has repeatedly increased the regulatory pressure against Binance.US. Binance has become the subject of the US&rsquo;s efforts to eliminate crypto exchanges it deems to have acted improperly.</p>
SEC: Binance.US Engaged in &ldquo;Wash Trading&rdquo;
<p>US regulatory action this time comes as the SEC accused Binance&rsquo;s US arm, Binance.US, of inflating its trading volumes &ndash; a practice known as &ldquo;wash trading.&rdquo; The Wall Street Journal (WSJ) first reported the news and said some of the exchange&rsquo;s crypto trading was a &ldquo;mirage&rdquo;, according to SEC.</p>
<p>Most accusations levelled against the exchange and its CEO, Changpeng &lsquo;CZ&rsquo; Zhao, came after the SEC sued Binance, Binance.US, and CZ. In its claims against the exchange, the SEC alleged that trading volumes on Binance.US were inflated by a firm owned by Zhao.</p>
<p>The WSJ report says the securities agency alleges that Binance.US inflated trading volumes &ldquo;by using dozens of user accounts held by Sigma Chain, a Swiss trading company controlled by Zhao.&rdquo; The WSJ also cites an academic report and boldly claims that over 70% of trading volume on crypto exchanges is derived from wash trading.</p>
<p>Binance.US filed a lawsuit against the SEC for its claims of improper handling of customer funds and said the SEC were &ldquo;misleading: the public in its ongoing cases. The SEC accused Binance and CZ of commingling customer assets in a press release.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Given that Changpeng Zhao and Binance have control of the platforms&rsquo; customers&rsquo; assets and have been able to commingle customer assets or divert customer assets as they please, as we have alleged, these prohibitions are essential to protecting investor assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&nbsp;A spokesperson addressed the SEC&rsquo;s allegations of wash trading, saying they are &ldquo;entirely unfounded.&rdquo; The WSJ further reports the spokesperson said the claims are &ldquo;based on a fundamental misunderstanding of the facts and a misapplication of the relevant law.&rdquo;</p>
Binance.US Feels the Pressure
<p>The exchange naturally has felt the effects of the SEC&rsquo;s endless lawsuits and allegations. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Recent reports indicated Binance&rsquo;s US affiliate laid off some of its staff following the agency&rsquo;s actions.</p>
Binance Seeks Dismissal of CFTC Complaint
<p>In a July 24 report, news agency Reuters said that Binance and its CEO are &ldquo;planning to seek dismissal of a Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) complaint accusing the crypto exchange of violating the Commodity Exchange Act and certain related federal regulations.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Binance has until July 27 to submit its response to the CFTC&rsquo;s complaint and will reportedly seek a dismissal. In March, the CFTC revealed it was suing Binance and its CEO, accusing the exchange of trading on its own platform and CZ of indulging in insider trading.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In its newest scare tactic, the SEC alleged Binance.US inflated its trading volumes through a practice known as &ldquo;wash trading.&rdquo; </p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has repeatedly increased the regulatory pressure against Binance.US. Binance has become the subject of the US&rsquo;s efforts to eliminate crypto exchanges it deems to have acted improperly.</p>
SEC: Binance.US Engaged in &ldquo;Wash Trading&rdquo;
<p>US regulatory action this time comes as the SEC accused Binance&rsquo;s US arm, Binance.US, of inflating its trading volumes &ndash; a practice known as &ldquo;wash trading.&rdquo; The Wall Street Journal (WSJ) first reported the news and said some of the exchange&rsquo;s crypto trading was a &ldquo;mirage&rdquo;, according to SEC.</p>
<p>Most accusations levelled against the exchange and its CEO, Changpeng &lsquo;CZ&rsquo; Zhao, came after the SEC sued Binance, Binance.US, and CZ. In its claims against the exchange, the SEC alleged that trading volumes on Binance.US were inflated by a firm owned by Zhao.</p>
<p>The WSJ report says the securities agency alleges that Binance.US inflated trading volumes &ldquo;by using dozens of user accounts held by Sigma Chain, a Swiss trading company controlled by Zhao.&rdquo; The WSJ also cites an academic report and boldly claims that over 70% of trading volume on crypto exchanges is derived from wash trading.</p>
<p>Binance.US filed a lawsuit against the SEC for its claims of improper handling of customer funds and said the SEC were &ldquo;misleading: the public in its ongoing cases. The SEC accused Binance and CZ of commingling customer assets in a press release.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Given that Changpeng Zhao and Binance have control of the platforms&rsquo; customers&rsquo; assets and have been able to commingle customer assets or divert customer assets as they please, as we have alleged, these prohibitions are essential to protecting investor assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&nbsp;A spokesperson addressed the SEC&rsquo;s allegations of wash trading, saying they are &ldquo;entirely unfounded.&rdquo; The WSJ further reports the spokesperson said the claims are &ldquo;based on a fundamental misunderstanding of the facts and a misapplication of the relevant law.&rdquo;</p>
Binance.US Feels the Pressure
<p>The exchange naturally has felt the effects of the SEC&rsquo;s endless lawsuits and allegations. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Recent reports indicated Binance&rsquo;s US affiliate laid off some of its staff following the agency&rsquo;s actions.</p>
Binance Seeks Dismissal of CFTC Complaint
<p>In a July 24 report, news agency Reuters said that Binance and its CEO are &ldquo;planning to seek dismissal of a Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) complaint accusing the crypto exchange of violating the Commodity Exchange Act and certain related federal regulations.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Binance has until July 27 to submit its response to the CFTC&rsquo;s complaint and will reportedly seek a dismissal. In March, the CFTC revealed it was suing Binance and its CEO, accusing the exchange of trading on its own platform and CZ of indulging in insider trading.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Opens Payment Platform Amid Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/federal-reserve-opens-payment-platform-amid-crypto-crackdown</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fednow-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fednow-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fednow-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/federal-reserve-opens-payment-platform-amid-crypto-crackdown</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The United States Federal Reserve has officially launched its new instant payment system dubbed FedNow.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch comes as the Federal Reserve looks to modernize and streamline the United States&rsquo; payment system. Research on financial systems has been ongoing since 2021 FedNow enables instant payment between users and banks and boasts of its 24/7/365 operations. Users will have full access to their funds and also do not have to pay anything to join the service. The Federal Reserve expects the service to speed up the flow of money throughout the country.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the FedNow&rsquo;s own website, the initial launch will simply focus on &ldquo;core clearing and settlement capabilities&rdquo; and additional features will be launched in phases, depending on industry demands and changes in technology. As more banks and credit unions adopt the service, users and businesses can expect more benefits. As of writing, early adopters of the service include big banks like JPMorgan Chase, Wells Fargo, and BNY Mellon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While this development is of course a net positive for everyday users, the launch of FedNow raises a glaring question, especially regarding the United States&rsquo; own financial system. There are already existing systems like Venmo, Paypal or even The Clearing House&rsquo;s Real-Time Payments (RTP) Network that enable instant payments. So the question becomes what is FedNow really for? And what comes next after FedNow? </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although the Federal Reserve has said that FedNow will not be used as a springboard to the launch of the United States&rsquo; own central bank digital currency (CBDC), this has not stopped the cryptocurrency community from speculating and worrying. If the Federal Reserve, and by extension the United States government, is serious about digital currencies, then it should also relax the current hostile environment to cryptocurrency enablked by none other than the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC, at the helm of Gary Gensler, has been on a warpath against cryptocurrency platforms with its unflinching stance that all crypto assets (save for Bitcoin) are securities.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, there is the recent issue of the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) bloc developing its own CBDC patently as a rival to the U.S. dollar. The United States is currently at a crossroads and the next big move after FedNow will be crucial not just to the everyday user but the entire world&rsquo;s monetary system.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The United States Federal Reserve has officially launched its new instant payment system dubbed FedNow.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch comes as the Federal Reserve looks to modernize and streamline the United States&rsquo; payment system. Research on financial systems has been ongoing since 2021 FedNow enables instant payment between users and banks and boasts of its 24/7/365 operations. Users will have full access to their funds and also do not have to pay anything to join the service. The Federal Reserve expects the service to speed up the flow of money throughout the country.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the FedNow&rsquo;s own website, the initial launch will simply focus on &ldquo;core clearing and settlement capabilities&rdquo; and additional features will be launched in phases, depending on industry demands and changes in technology. As more banks and credit unions adopt the service, users and businesses can expect more benefits. As of writing, early adopters of the service include big banks like JPMorgan Chase, Wells Fargo, and BNY Mellon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While this development is of course a net positive for everyday users, the launch of FedNow raises a glaring question, especially regarding the United States&rsquo; own financial system. There are already existing systems like Venmo, Paypal or even The Clearing House&rsquo;s Real-Time Payments (RTP) Network that enable instant payments. So the question becomes what is FedNow really for? And what comes next after FedNow? </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although the Federal Reserve has said that FedNow will not be used as a springboard to the launch of the United States&rsquo; own central bank digital currency (CBDC), this has not stopped the cryptocurrency community from speculating and worrying. If the Federal Reserve, and by extension the United States government, is serious about digital currencies, then it should also relax the current hostile environment to cryptocurrency enablked by none other than the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC, at the helm of Gary Gensler, has been on a warpath against cryptocurrency platforms with its unflinching stance that all crypto assets (save for Bitcoin) are securities.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, there is the recent issue of the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) bloc developing its own CBDC patently as a rival to the U.S. dollar. The United States is currently at a crossroads and the next big move after FedNow will be crucial not just to the everyday user but the entire world&rsquo;s monetary system.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Claims Ripple Ruling Was Wrong, Sets Out to Appeal]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-claims-ripple-ruling-was-wrong-sets-out-to-appeal</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-v-ripple-h-fixed.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-v-ripple-h-fixed.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-v-ripple-h-fixed.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-claims-ripple-ruling-was-wrong-sets-out-to-appeal</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent statement, the SEC claimed that the recent Ripple ruling was incorrect, while disclosing that it has already decided and is currently moving in to post an appeal.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">There has been some intertwining contexts with latest legal fracas with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which involves Terraform Labs and its co-founder, Do Kwon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, the SEC's recent motion against Terraform Labs has revived discussions around the landmark Ripple Labs case, signaling a possible appeal on the horizon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Institutional vs. Retail: Divergent Perspectives</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In the Ripple Labs case, the court determined that Ripple's XRP token sales to institutional investors breached SEC rules. However, the judge ruled that Ripple's offerings to retail investors on exchanges didn't infringe on these same regulations. This bifurcation of institutional and retail sales was broadly seen as a victory for the crypto industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a stark departure from this view, the SEC, in its most recent filing against Terraform Labs and Kwon, voiced its disapproval. The agency stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"The decision creates an artificial distinction between the expectations of sophisticated institutional and retail investors."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the SEC's view, the ruling reformulates the decades-old Howey Test, a metric used to identify when assets are securities, transforming it into a more subjective standard. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Accordingly, the SEC requested that the court reject this part of the Ripple decision and hinted at a possible appeal in the Ripple case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple Ruling's Impact on Terraform Labs Lawsuit</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple ruling has become a crucial reference in the ongoing lawsuit against Terraform Labs and Kwon. Their legal representatives cited the Ripple decision in their dismissal motion, arguing that it "confirms the legal insufficiency of the SEC&rsquo;s argument."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">They were referring to the SEC's assertion that certain tokens, including the ill-fated TerraUSD stablecoin, were securities due to their method of sale.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, the SEC has doubled down on its accusations that Terraform Labs and Kwon offered and sold unregistered securities as part of a fraudulent scheme, causing a loss of at least $40 billion in market value. The SEC also underscored that the institutional investor aspect of the Ripple ruling supports its case against Terraform Labs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC notes that institutional buyers in such a case (such as trading firms that purchased crypto assets from Terraform Labs with no restrictions on resale) purchased ostensibly on the reason that the assets were an investment on top of Terraform Lab's initiatives.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The legal entanglements involving the SEC, Ripple Labs, and now Terraform Labs, highlightts the evolving dynamics between the emerging crypto industry and established securities regulations. The nuanced interpretation of these regulations in relation to cryptocurrencies like XRP and TerraUSD has far-reaching implications for the industry. How these cases play out in the courts will set precedents that could shape the crypto landscape for years to come.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">SEC's Prospective Appeal</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC's recent motion reveals its plan to challenge the federal court ruling in favor of Ripple Labs. U.S. District Judge Analisa Torres upheld that nearly half of Ripple's XRP sales did not contravene investor-protection laws. This verdict sparked hope among other defendants embroiled in disputes with the SEC regarding their cryptocurrency sales, which, according to the SEC, often constitute illegally sold securities. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This court ruling has become a beacon of hope for defendants like Do Kwon, co-founder of Terraform Labs. Kwon, currently serving time in prison, faces an SEC lawsuit alleging fraudulent activities and various legal infringements. The lawsuit was filed in February in Manhattan federal court. In light of the recent Ripple Labs ruling, Kwon's defense is employing it as a basis to refute the SEC's accusations. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Precedent in Flux</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the SEC signalling its intent to appeal the Ripple Labs ruling, a cloud of uncertainty hangs over the crypto industry. The final decision on the Ripple case could profoundly influence ongoing and future lawsuits, including Terraform Labs.Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent statement, the SEC claimed that the recent Ripple ruling was incorrect, while disclosing that it has already decided and is currently moving in to post an appeal.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">There has been some intertwining contexts with latest legal fracas with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which involves Terraform Labs and its co-founder, Do Kwon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, the SEC's recent motion against Terraform Labs has revived discussions around the landmark Ripple Labs case, signaling a possible appeal on the horizon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Institutional vs. Retail: Divergent Perspectives</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In the Ripple Labs case, the court determined that Ripple's XRP token sales to institutional investors breached SEC rules. However, the judge ruled that Ripple's offerings to retail investors on exchanges didn't infringe on these same regulations. This bifurcation of institutional and retail sales was broadly seen as a victory for the crypto industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a stark departure from this view, the SEC, in its most recent filing against Terraform Labs and Kwon, voiced its disapproval. The agency stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"The decision creates an artificial distinction between the expectations of sophisticated institutional and retail investors."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the SEC's view, the ruling reformulates the decades-old Howey Test, a metric used to identify when assets are securities, transforming it into a more subjective standard. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Accordingly, the SEC requested that the court reject this part of the Ripple decision and hinted at a possible appeal in the Ripple case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple Ruling's Impact on Terraform Labs Lawsuit</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple ruling has become a crucial reference in the ongoing lawsuit against Terraform Labs and Kwon. Their legal representatives cited the Ripple decision in their dismissal motion, arguing that it "confirms the legal insufficiency of the SEC&rsquo;s argument."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">They were referring to the SEC's assertion that certain tokens, including the ill-fated TerraUSD stablecoin, were securities due to their method of sale.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, the SEC has doubled down on its accusations that Terraform Labs and Kwon offered and sold unregistered securities as part of a fraudulent scheme, causing a loss of at least $40 billion in market value. The SEC also underscored that the institutional investor aspect of the Ripple ruling supports its case against Terraform Labs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC notes that institutional buyers in such a case (such as trading firms that purchased crypto assets from Terraform Labs with no restrictions on resale) purchased ostensibly on the reason that the assets were an investment on top of Terraform Lab's initiatives.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The legal entanglements involving the SEC, Ripple Labs, and now Terraform Labs, highlightts the evolving dynamics between the emerging crypto industry and established securities regulations. The nuanced interpretation of these regulations in relation to cryptocurrencies like XRP and TerraUSD has far-reaching implications for the industry. How these cases play out in the courts will set precedents that could shape the crypto landscape for years to come.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">SEC's Prospective Appeal</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC's recent motion reveals its plan to challenge the federal court ruling in favor of Ripple Labs. U.S. District Judge Analisa Torres upheld that nearly half of Ripple's XRP sales did not contravene investor-protection laws. This verdict sparked hope among other defendants embroiled in disputes with the SEC regarding their cryptocurrency sales, which, according to the SEC, often constitute illegally sold securities. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This court ruling has become a beacon of hope for defendants like Do Kwon, co-founder of Terraform Labs. Kwon, currently serving time in prison, faces an SEC lawsuit alleging fraudulent activities and various legal infringements. The lawsuit was filed in February in Manhattan federal court. In light of the recent Ripple Labs ruling, Kwon's defense is employing it as a basis to refute the SEC's accusations. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Precedent in Flux</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the SEC signalling its intent to appeal the Ripple Labs ruling, a cloud of uncertainty hangs over the crypto industry. The final decision on the Ripple case could profoundly influence ongoing and future lawsuits, including Terraform Labs.Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ripple CEO: SEC Created “Mess,” Consumers Left Paying the Price]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ripple-ceo-sec-created-mess-consumers-left-paying-the-price</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-1920-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-1920-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-1920-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:58:17 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ripple-ceo-sec-created-mess-consumers-left-paying-the-price</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&rsquo;s CEO Brad Garlinghouse blasted the SEC, accusing it of creating a &ldquo;mess&rdquo; by declaring itself the &ldquo;cop on the crypto beat when it had no legal jurisdiction.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse took to Twitter today to defend Judge Torres&rsquo; recent decision, which declared that Ripple&rsquo;s sale of its XRP token did not constitute a sale of securities.</p>
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s chief further blamed the SEC for creating the &ldquo;mess&rdquo; surrounding crypto regulation when it had no right to do so.</p>
Garlinghouse Speaks Out Against SEC
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s partial victory against the SEC has been celebrated by most of the industry but has seen some backlash from the naysayers. Judge Analisa Torres ruled on July 13 the XRP token, concerning retail sales on digital asset exchanges, is not necessarily a security. Torres, however, did rule that XRP qualifies as a security under the Howey Test when sold to institutional investors.</p>
<p>At the time of the ruling, Garlinghouse commented that institutional sale represents &ldquo;the smallest piece&rdquo; of the suit and believes if the SEC decides to appeal the decision regarding retail sales, it would only &ldquo;solidify&rdquo; Torres&rsquo; decision. Garlinghouse further labelled the SEC a &ldquo;bully&rdquo; for targeting &ldquo;weak players&rdquo; in the industry without the necessary resources to build a strong defence.</p>
<p>The Ripple CEO continued his criticism of the agency in defence to retail consumers. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;An important topic has come up about protecting retail. The SEC created this mess by proclaiming it was the cop on the crypto beat when it had no legal jurisdiction Where&rsquo;s that gotten us? Consumers left holding the bag in bankruptcy court while the SEC holds press conferences.&rdquo;</p>

<p>In the same thread, Garlinghouse defended Judge Torres&rsquo; application of the law, emphasizing &ldquo;legislation &ndash; not more regulation by enforcement &ndash; is the only way to provide clear rules and protect retail.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It&rsquo;s absurd to blame a Judge for faithfully applying the law. We all know legislation &ndash; not more regulation by enforcement &ndash; is the only way forward to provide clear rules and protect retail. Glad to see more members of Congress like @RepRitchie, @PatrickMcHenry champion this.</p>
&mdash; Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) July 22, 2023
<p>

</p>
SEC May Appeal Decision But Will Take Years
<p>While it has not clearly stated it would appeal Torres&rsquo; ruling, the SEC did hint at the possibility.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Journal (WSJ) reported that disgraced Terraform Labs co-founder, Do Kwon is trying to use the landmark ruling as precedence in his own battle against the securities agency. In a motion involving Kwon, the SEC urged the presiding judge not to seek guidance from the Ripple ruling. The SEC said Judge Torres&rsquo; decision &ldquo;adds baseless requirements&rdquo; to the Howey Test and stated there would be a &ldquo;further review&rdquo; of the ruling.</p>
<p>Prominent crypto and pro-Ripple lawyer John Deaton clarified the implications of a possible appeal by the SEC.</p>
<p>Deaton said on Twitter that he does not view a potential appeal as a setback to the industry.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">An appeal is not even close to be a setback. First, it will be two years from now before a decision is issued by the 2nd Circuit, if it&rsquo;s appealed. The Torres Decision is the law until then - at least in the 2nd Circuit. Second, even if the 2nd Circuit said Torres was wrong&hellip; https://t.co/GzW31D9edQ</p>
&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) July 22, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Mr Deaton explained that a possible SEC appeal would take at least two years to come to fruition and said that until such a decision is revealed, Judge Torres&rsquo; ruling remains the law.</p>
<p>He assured nervous XRP holders,</p>

<p>&ldquo;Don&rsquo;t let anyone underestimate how significant this win is.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&rsquo;s CEO Brad Garlinghouse blasted the SEC, accusing it of creating a &ldquo;mess&rdquo; by declaring itself the &ldquo;cop on the crypto beat when it had no legal jurisdiction.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse took to Twitter today to defend Judge Torres&rsquo; recent decision, which declared that Ripple&rsquo;s sale of its XRP token did not constitute a sale of securities.</p>
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s chief further blamed the SEC for creating the &ldquo;mess&rdquo; surrounding crypto regulation when it had no right to do so.</p>
Garlinghouse Speaks Out Against SEC
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s partial victory against the SEC has been celebrated by most of the industry but has seen some backlash from the naysayers. Judge Analisa Torres ruled on July 13 the XRP token, concerning retail sales on digital asset exchanges, is not necessarily a security. Torres, however, did rule that XRP qualifies as a security under the Howey Test when sold to institutional investors.</p>
<p>At the time of the ruling, Garlinghouse commented that institutional sale represents &ldquo;the smallest piece&rdquo; of the suit and believes if the SEC decides to appeal the decision regarding retail sales, it would only &ldquo;solidify&rdquo; Torres&rsquo; decision. Garlinghouse further labelled the SEC a &ldquo;bully&rdquo; for targeting &ldquo;weak players&rdquo; in the industry without the necessary resources to build a strong defence.</p>
<p>The Ripple CEO continued his criticism of the agency in defence to retail consumers. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;An important topic has come up about protecting retail. The SEC created this mess by proclaiming it was the cop on the crypto beat when it had no legal jurisdiction Where&rsquo;s that gotten us? Consumers left holding the bag in bankruptcy court while the SEC holds press conferences.&rdquo;</p>

<p>In the same thread, Garlinghouse defended Judge Torres&rsquo; application of the law, emphasizing &ldquo;legislation &ndash; not more regulation by enforcement &ndash; is the only way to provide clear rules and protect retail.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It&rsquo;s absurd to blame a Judge for faithfully applying the law. We all know legislation &ndash; not more regulation by enforcement &ndash; is the only way forward to provide clear rules and protect retail. Glad to see more members of Congress like @RepRitchie, @PatrickMcHenry champion this.</p>
&mdash; Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) July 22, 2023
<p>

</p>
SEC May Appeal Decision But Will Take Years
<p>While it has not clearly stated it would appeal Torres&rsquo; ruling, the SEC did hint at the possibility.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Journal (WSJ) reported that disgraced Terraform Labs co-founder, Do Kwon is trying to use the landmark ruling as precedence in his own battle against the securities agency. In a motion involving Kwon, the SEC urged the presiding judge not to seek guidance from the Ripple ruling. The SEC said Judge Torres&rsquo; decision &ldquo;adds baseless requirements&rdquo; to the Howey Test and stated there would be a &ldquo;further review&rdquo; of the ruling.</p>
<p>Prominent crypto and pro-Ripple lawyer John Deaton clarified the implications of a possible appeal by the SEC.</p>
<p>Deaton said on Twitter that he does not view a potential appeal as a setback to the industry.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">An appeal is not even close to be a setback. First, it will be two years from now before a decision is issued by the 2nd Circuit, if it&rsquo;s appealed. The Torres Decision is the law until then - at least in the 2nd Circuit. Second, even if the 2nd Circuit said Torres was wrong&hellip; https://t.co/GzW31D9edQ</p>
&mdash; John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) July 22, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Mr Deaton explained that a possible SEC appeal would take at least two years to come to fruition and said that until such a decision is revealed, Judge Torres&rsquo; ruling remains the law.</p>
<p>He assured nervous XRP holders,</p>

<p>&ldquo;Don&rsquo;t let anyone underestimate how significant this win is.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Worldcoin Is Officially Launched, Vitalik Buterin Reacts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/worldcoin-is-officially-launched-vitalik-buterin-reacts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-orb-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-orb-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-orb-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/worldcoin-is-officially-launched-vitalik-buterin-reacts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to the rollout of the Worldcoin crypto services, Vitalik Buterin published a detailed essay about biometric proof of personhood.</p>
Worldcoin&rsquo;s Mission to Help Distinguish Humans from AI Bots Online
<p>The CEO of OpenAI Sam Altman together with Alex Blania founded Worldcoin over three years ago. The main idea behind the project is to present a solution which can effectively verify human identity online without violating users&rsquo; privacy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With AI technology developing extremely rapidly in the latest months, many believe that soon it&rsquo;s going to take over lots of human jobs leaving thousands unemployed. It might also get to the point where it will become very difficult to tell the difference between humans and AI bots online.</p>
<p>Worldcoin offers a digital proof of personhood called World ID. In order to get a World ID, one needs to use an Orb, a sophisticated biometric verification device which scans users&rsquo; irises to verify that they&rsquo;re human.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Worldcoin also confirmed that it plans to create an AI-funded Universal Basic Income (UBI) service, thus helping to combat income inequality. Users in the countries &ldquo;where laws allow&rdquo; should be able to receive the Worldcoin digital currency (WLD) for simply being human.&nbsp;</p>
Worldcoin Starts the Rollout of Its Services&nbsp;
<p>On July 24, Worldcoin published a letter from cofounders on its website announcing the official launch of the product. One can access the Worldcoin services via World App, the company&rsquo;s owned crypto wallet which is already available on iOS and Android. However, to get verified for World ID, it&rsquo;s also required to visit an Orb, the eyeball-scanning device which is not globally distributed yet.</p>
<p>Over 2 million people already signed up for World ID during the project&rsquo;s Beta phase. Numerous crypto exchange platforms such as Binance, OKX, and Huobi have already confirmed the listing of the Worldcoin&rsquo;s token.</p>
Vitalik Buterin Describes Potential Risks of the Worldcoin&rsquo;s Identity Verification System
<p>On the same day of Worldcoin&rsquo;s launch, the Ethereum network cofounder Vitalik Buterin published an extensive blog post about biometric proof of personhood in general and World ID in particular.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Buterin, proof of personhood solutions are crucial as they help solve &ldquo;a lot of anti-spam and anti-concentration-of-power problems&rdquo; as well as increase privacy and reduce dependence on centralized authorities. Many apps today use government-backed identity systems such as state IDs or credit cards, which inevitably intrude on users&rsquo; privacy.</p>
<p>However, digital identity verification solutions have their issues as well. Buterin identifies at least four major risks with Worldcoin&rsquo;s construction: privacy, accessibility, centralization, and security.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Vitalik Buterin then compares World ID to other types of identity verification and concludes that there is no ideal form of proof of personhood:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I definitely do not envy the people attempting the task, and it will likely take years to find a formula that works. The concept of proof-of-personhood in principle seems very valuable, and while the various implementations have their risks, not having any proof-of-personhood at all has its risks too&hellip;&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p></p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In response to the rollout of the Worldcoin crypto services, Vitalik Buterin published a detailed essay about biometric proof of personhood.</p>
Worldcoin&rsquo;s Mission to Help Distinguish Humans from AI Bots Online
<p>The CEO of OpenAI Sam Altman together with Alex Blania founded Worldcoin over three years ago. The main idea behind the project is to present a solution which can effectively verify human identity online without violating users&rsquo; privacy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With AI technology developing extremely rapidly in the latest months, many believe that soon it&rsquo;s going to take over lots of human jobs leaving thousands unemployed. It might also get to the point where it will become very difficult to tell the difference between humans and AI bots online.</p>
<p>Worldcoin offers a digital proof of personhood called World ID. In order to get a World ID, one needs to use an Orb, a sophisticated biometric verification device which scans users&rsquo; irises to verify that they&rsquo;re human.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Worldcoin also confirmed that it plans to create an AI-funded Universal Basic Income (UBI) service, thus helping to combat income inequality. Users in the countries &ldquo;where laws allow&rdquo; should be able to receive the Worldcoin digital currency (WLD) for simply being human.&nbsp;</p>
Worldcoin Starts the Rollout of Its Services&nbsp;
<p>On July 24, Worldcoin published a letter from cofounders on its website announcing the official launch of the product. One can access the Worldcoin services via World App, the company&rsquo;s owned crypto wallet which is already available on iOS and Android. However, to get verified for World ID, it&rsquo;s also required to visit an Orb, the eyeball-scanning device which is not globally distributed yet.</p>
<p>Over 2 million people already signed up for World ID during the project&rsquo;s Beta phase. Numerous crypto exchange platforms such as Binance, OKX, and Huobi have already confirmed the listing of the Worldcoin&rsquo;s token.</p>
Vitalik Buterin Describes Potential Risks of the Worldcoin&rsquo;s Identity Verification System
<p>On the same day of Worldcoin&rsquo;s launch, the Ethereum network cofounder Vitalik Buterin published an extensive blog post about biometric proof of personhood in general and World ID in particular.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Buterin, proof of personhood solutions are crucial as they help solve &ldquo;a lot of anti-spam and anti-concentration-of-power problems&rdquo; as well as increase privacy and reduce dependence on centralized authorities. Many apps today use government-backed identity systems such as state IDs or credit cards, which inevitably intrude on users&rsquo; privacy.</p>
<p>However, digital identity verification solutions have their issues as well. Buterin identifies at least four major risks with Worldcoin&rsquo;s construction: privacy, accessibility, centralization, and security.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Vitalik Buterin then compares World ID to other types of identity verification and concludes that there is no ideal form of proof of personhood:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I definitely do not envy the people attempting the task, and it will likely take years to find a formula that works. The concept of proof-of-personhood in principle seems very valuable, and while the various implementations have their risks, not having any proof-of-personhood at all has its risks too&hellip;&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Explores Emerging Narratives in Cryptocurrency and Regulatory Environment for 2023 - Vol. 9]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lbank-explores-emerging-narratives-in-cryptocurrency-and-regulatory-environment-for-2023-vol-9</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2__1690208985e6sXrM4cKr.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2__1690208985e6sXrM4cKr.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2__1690208985e6sXrM4cKr.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:33:38 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/lbank-explores-emerging-narratives-in-cryptocurrency-and-regulatory-environment-for-2023-vol-9</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>In a recent engaging conversation hosted by LBank, the persisting implications of the XRP court case on the cryptocurrency market were examined. Despite a tentative win for XRP, experts on the panel agreed that the legal challenges are far from concluded. The discussion also delved into the importance of robust infrastructure in the cryptocurrency domain and how it continues to be a magnet for venture capitalist investments. The burgeoning sector of blockchain gaming and the future of on-chain gaming platforms were other key talking points.</p><p>Founder of Network Spotlight, Mikhail, shared his insights on the potential impact of the XRP case on funding within the Web 3.0 ecosystem. He emphasized the necessity for project builders to outpace investors in understanding their domain given their specialist status. He further advised founders to stress their domain expertise, deep understanding of the solutions they offer, and ability to adapt in an ever-evolving industry.</p><p>Michael Rippe, CCO of zkHoldem, a company specializing in blockchain-based Texas Hold'em, expressed a hopeful outlook for XRP and the broader crypto market despite the pending resolution of the XRP case.</p><p>Michael Lee, Director of Corporate Development at the South Korean gaming firm, Come to us, outlined their new initiative, Explore and Play (X PLA), and their transformation into a transmedia entity. He emphasized their dedication to the evolving landscape of Web 3.0.</p><p>Manuel Vazquez, CEO of OscarSwap, succinctly clarified the relationship between Ripple and XRP, noting that XRP existed prior to Ripple's inception and was adopted by Ripple as a store of value. He pointed out that while Ripple's method of offering XRP to institutional investors is under investigation, XRP's decentralized nature disqualifies it from being classified as a security.</p><p>Echoing Vazquez's explanation of the Ripple-XRP relationship and the ongoing SEC legal issues, Sam, AMA Host at Future Lounge, conveyed his optimism for the crypto sphere, suggesting that victories in these cases will bolster confidence in the continued expansion of the crypto sector.</p><p>Alexandre Raffin, CEO of GAINS, concluded the discussion by underscoring the importance of generating authentic value in the gaming and crypto sectors. He also highlighted the power of memes in building communities and shaping belief systems, along with the potential of AI to enhance user experience.</p><p>About LBank Labs</p><p>LBank Labs, a prominent player in the web3 space, manages a versatile $100 Million fund that extends beyond specific protocols and exchanges. With a team of experienced web3 veterans from prestigious entities, they have built an extensive network of expertise and connections. Their investment strategy includes fund-of-fund investments, direct investments in early-stage projects, and liquid projects, enabling them to explore diverse opportunities. LBank Labs actively promotes their investment thesis, &ldquo;The Other Angle,&rdquo; through engaging discussions and focuses on the PSE principles to foster sustainable growth and innovation in the web3 landscape. With a Fund of Fund network comprising 12 funds and over $1 billion in AUM, and offices in seven global regions, LBank Labs is well-positioned to expand their network and drive innovation in the web3 ecosystem, together with their partners and collaborators.</p>ContactLBank Exchangepress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>In a recent engaging conversation hosted by LBank, the persisting implications of the XRP court case on the cryptocurrency market were examined. Despite a tentative win for XRP, experts on the panel agreed that the legal challenges are far from concluded. The discussion also delved into the importance of robust infrastructure in the cryptocurrency domain and how it continues to be a magnet for venture capitalist investments. The burgeoning sector of blockchain gaming and the future of on-chain gaming platforms were other key talking points.</p><p>Founder of Network Spotlight, Mikhail, shared his insights on the potential impact of the XRP case on funding within the Web 3.0 ecosystem. He emphasized the necessity for project builders to outpace investors in understanding their domain given their specialist status. He further advised founders to stress their domain expertise, deep understanding of the solutions they offer, and ability to adapt in an ever-evolving industry.</p><p>Michael Rippe, CCO of zkHoldem, a company specializing in blockchain-based Texas Hold'em, expressed a hopeful outlook for XRP and the broader crypto market despite the pending resolution of the XRP case.</p><p>Michael Lee, Director of Corporate Development at the South Korean gaming firm, Come to us, outlined their new initiative, Explore and Play (X PLA), and their transformation into a transmedia entity. He emphasized their dedication to the evolving landscape of Web 3.0.</p><p>Manuel Vazquez, CEO of OscarSwap, succinctly clarified the relationship between Ripple and XRP, noting that XRP existed prior to Ripple's inception and was adopted by Ripple as a store of value. He pointed out that while Ripple's method of offering XRP to institutional investors is under investigation, XRP's decentralized nature disqualifies it from being classified as a security.</p><p>Echoing Vazquez's explanation of the Ripple-XRP relationship and the ongoing SEC legal issues, Sam, AMA Host at Future Lounge, conveyed his optimism for the crypto sphere, suggesting that victories in these cases will bolster confidence in the continued expansion of the crypto sector.</p><p>Alexandre Raffin, CEO of GAINS, concluded the discussion by underscoring the importance of generating authentic value in the gaming and crypto sectors. He also highlighted the power of memes in building communities and shaping belief systems, along with the potential of AI to enhance user experience.</p><p>About LBank Labs</p><p>LBank Labs, a prominent player in the web3 space, manages a versatile $100 Million fund that extends beyond specific protocols and exchanges. With a team of experienced web3 veterans from prestigious entities, they have built an extensive network of expertise and connections. Their investment strategy includes fund-of-fund investments, direct investments in early-stage projects, and liquid projects, enabling them to explore diverse opportunities. LBank Labs actively promotes their investment thesis, &ldquo;The Other Angle,&rdquo; through engaging discussions and focuses on the PSE principles to foster sustainable growth and innovation in the web3 landscape. With a Fund of Fund network comprising 12 funds and over $1 billion in AUM, and offices in seven global regions, LBank Labs is well-positioned to expand their network and drive innovation in the web3 ecosystem, together with their partners and collaborators.</p>ContactLBank Exchangepress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price Prediction - Tradecurve Outruns Polygon (MATIC) In User Base]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/solana-sol-price-prediction-tradecurve-outruns-polygon-matic-in-user-base</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-24-at-172645.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-24-at-172645.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-24-at-172645.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/solana-sol-price-prediction-tradecurve-outruns-polygon-matic-in-user-base</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">As uncertainties prevail in the market, crypto investors have altered their investment strategies. Thus, they are looking for real-world utility tokens that can offer a stable profit. Subsequently, the presale of Tradecurve (TCRV) is selling out quickly.Meanwhile, Solana (SOL) and Polygon (MATIC) seem to be losing their Midas touch.</p>
<p class="s5">Whales are accumulating TCRV tokens in large numbers, as their value can grow by 100x in the next six months.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Solana (SOL) Joins Hands With Coca-Cola
<p class="s5">Expanding its ecosystem, Solana (SOL) has partnered with Coca-Cola in Serbia. Under this partnership, Solana&rsquo;s platform SolSea and Coca-Cola will jointly work on an NFT offering at a music event.</p>
<p class="s5">As per the official statement, Solana and the soda company will provide 100 limited-edition hoodies and NFTs to participants. Earlier, a report had suggested that Solana has witnessed a significant rise in the NFT space this year.</p>
<p class="s5">The price trajectory of Solana has also responded positively to the partnership. The exchange rate of Solana has increased by 21% in the past week. At the time of writing, Solana is trading at $22.29.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Revolut Announces Delisting Polygon (MATIC)
<p class="s5">Polygon has faced several challenges and weathering of its user base since the SEC labeled MATIC as a security. Many exchanges have announced delisting Polygon (MATIC), with the Revolut being the latest one.</p>
<p class="s5">While making the announcement, Revolut stated that it will delist Polygon by September 18. Earlier, two leading exchanges, Robinhood and Bakkt, had already announced the delisting of Polygon. According to analysts, this move can cause a severe fall in Polygon&rsquo;s user base and price.</p>
<p class="s5">The market value of Polygon has seen a drop of 7% in the last 30 days. Consequently, Polygon is now trading at $6.34.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Tradecurve Becomes The Face Of Next-gen Cryptos
<p class="s5">After the collapse of the FTX exchange, which caused a loss of around $2 billion in the crypto market, investors have become apprehensive about centralized exchanges. The market trust in centralized exchanges has suffered a blow. Therefore, the demand for decentralized exchanges has increased, and Tradecurve (TCRV) is considered the best option by experts.</p>
<p class="s5">It is a unique blockchain platform, which enables users to trade a wide range of assets without relying on fiat payments. It keeps users&rsquo; identities anonymous, and allows them to trade privately.</p>
<p class="s5">On this platform, users are not required to undergo any KYC checks. This is contrary to existing trading platforms like ByBit and Robinhood, where users must share their personal details.</p>
<p class="s5">Its native crypto is TCRV, which will fuel the platform&rsquo;s ecosystem. The token&rsquo;s smart contract has been verified by Cyber Scope, and the team verification was performed by Assure DeFi. The token&rsquo;s presale is live, and currently progressing through the fourth stage, where a token is available for purchase at $0.018.</p>
<p class="s5">So far, the price of a token has increased by 80%, and is likely to rise to $0.025 in stage 5. Moreover, the platform&rsquo;s value may rise 50 times before the end of the presale round. Interestingly, only 40% of the total 1.8 billion tokens will be available during the presale.</p>
<p class="s5">For more information about the Tradecurve presale:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">As uncertainties prevail in the market, crypto investors have altered their investment strategies. Thus, they are looking for real-world utility tokens that can offer a stable profit. Subsequently, the presale of Tradecurve (TCRV) is selling out quickly.Meanwhile, Solana (SOL) and Polygon (MATIC) seem to be losing their Midas touch.</p>
<p class="s5">Whales are accumulating TCRV tokens in large numbers, as their value can grow by 100x in the next six months.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Solana (SOL) Joins Hands With Coca-Cola
<p class="s5">Expanding its ecosystem, Solana (SOL) has partnered with Coca-Cola in Serbia. Under this partnership, Solana&rsquo;s platform SolSea and Coca-Cola will jointly work on an NFT offering at a music event.</p>
<p class="s5">As per the official statement, Solana and the soda company will provide 100 limited-edition hoodies and NFTs to participants. Earlier, a report had suggested that Solana has witnessed a significant rise in the NFT space this year.</p>
<p class="s5">The price trajectory of Solana has also responded positively to the partnership. The exchange rate of Solana has increased by 21% in the past week. At the time of writing, Solana is trading at $22.29.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Revolut Announces Delisting Polygon (MATIC)
<p class="s5">Polygon has faced several challenges and weathering of its user base since the SEC labeled MATIC as a security. Many exchanges have announced delisting Polygon (MATIC), with the Revolut being the latest one.</p>
<p class="s5">While making the announcement, Revolut stated that it will delist Polygon by September 18. Earlier, two leading exchanges, Robinhood and Bakkt, had already announced the delisting of Polygon. According to analysts, this move can cause a severe fall in Polygon&rsquo;s user base and price.</p>
<p class="s5">The market value of Polygon has seen a drop of 7% in the last 30 days. Consequently, Polygon is now trading at $6.34.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Tradecurve Becomes The Face Of Next-gen Cryptos
<p class="s5">After the collapse of the FTX exchange, which caused a loss of around $2 billion in the crypto market, investors have become apprehensive about centralized exchanges. The market trust in centralized exchanges has suffered a blow. Therefore, the demand for decentralized exchanges has increased, and Tradecurve (TCRV) is considered the best option by experts.</p>
<p class="s5">It is a unique blockchain platform, which enables users to trade a wide range of assets without relying on fiat payments. It keeps users&rsquo; identities anonymous, and allows them to trade privately.</p>
<p class="s5">On this platform, users are not required to undergo any KYC checks. This is contrary to existing trading platforms like ByBit and Robinhood, where users must share their personal details.</p>
<p class="s5">Its native crypto is TCRV, which will fuel the platform&rsquo;s ecosystem. The token&rsquo;s smart contract has been verified by Cyber Scope, and the team verification was performed by Assure DeFi. The token&rsquo;s presale is live, and currently progressing through the fourth stage, where a token is available for purchase at $0.018.</p>
<p class="s5">So far, the price of a token has increased by 80%, and is likely to rise to $0.025 in stage 5. Moreover, the platform&rsquo;s value may rise 50 times before the end of the presale round. Interestingly, only 40% of the total 1.8 billion tokens will be available during the presale.</p>
<p class="s5">For more information about the Tradecurve presale:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Take Out 29089 - 25 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-take-out-29089-25-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-24-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-24-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-24-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 16:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-take-out-29089-25-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Take Out 29089:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 25 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained quite weak early in the Asian session as the pair plummeted to the 28973.24 area after trading as high as the 30350.70 area, a brief move that represented a test of a recent price objective associated with buying pressure around the 29525 and 29757.44 areas.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 29403 and 29089 levels during the acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 30421.29 and 29851.28 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 28775, 29386, and 27757 levels.&nbsp; The rapid depreciation also represented a test of the 28937 and 28845 levels, upside price objectives related to buying pressure from June around the 24750 and 26165 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives include the 29386, 28213, 28137, 27757, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29980.73 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29853.07.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Take Out 29089:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 25 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained quite weak early in the Asian session as the pair plummeted to the 28973.24 area after trading as high as the 30350.70 area, a brief move that represented a test of a recent price objective associated with buying pressure around the 29525 and 29757.44 areas.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 29403 and 29089 levels during the acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 30421.29 and 29851.28 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 28775, 29386, and 27757 levels.&nbsp; The rapid depreciation also represented a test of the 28937 and 28845 levels, upside price objectives related to buying pressure from June around the 24750 and 26165 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives include the 29386, 28213, 28137, 27757, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29980.73 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29853.07.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Conflux (CFX) Price Prediction: Is Uwerx (WERX) A Better Crypto Investment Than The Them?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/conflux-cfx-price-prediction-is-uwerx-werx-a-better-crypto-investment-than-the-them</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-24-at-164722.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-24-at-164722.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-24-at-164722.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 16:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/conflux-cfx-price-prediction-is-uwerx-werx-a-better-crypto-investment-than-the-them</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Crypto enthusiasts usually go for cryptocurrencies that have been around for a while because of these coins' proven success in the market. But the story is different with the new project Uwerx, which has traders buying in bulk even though it has yet to launch. </p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx is having a successful presale, to the amazement of its developers and the benefit of early investors. Having smashed through its first four stages in less than two months, analysts believe Uwerx will make a better investment than Open Campus (EDU) and Conflux (CFX). </p>
Open Campus (EDU) Sees An Downward Trend
<p class="s5">Open Campus (EDU) has reached a wider audience since it partnered with Animoca Brands to launch the Web3 Global Educators Fund. This has translated to an increase in the number of members joining the Open Campus (EDU) community. </p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, the project's Publisher NFTs have become a favorite among educators and content creators as it gives them the means to earn revenue for their work. </p>
<p class="s5">Despite the increase in Open Campus (EDU) adoption, the project has not risen in price in the last seven days. Open Campus trades at $1.00, representing a -13.84% decrease in the last seven days. Analysts predict it to trade at $2.07 by the first quarter of 2024</p>
Conflux (CFX) Rises In The Last 24hrs
<p class="s5">The past 24hrs have been good to Conflux (CFX). The project trades at $0.24, representing a 9.37% increase within 24 hours. Although this current price represents a -23.55% decrease in the last seven days, Conflux (CFX) holders believe this could be the start of the project's bull run. </p>
<p class="s5">Conflux (CFX) announced on June 2 via Twitter that it has partnered with Code4arena. This collaboration will provide enhanced security for both ecosystems.</p>
<p class="s5">Following the partnership, the Conflux (CFX) team announced on June 6 that they were aware of the recent cross-chain irregularity in their ecosystem. They assured users they had taken preventive action by removing Multichain's co-mint rights. This will ensure the security of user assets. The project also stated that they had not detected any loss, and the ecosystem was functioning as usual.</p>
<p class="s5">With more partnerships and improvements, analysts believe the CFX token could increase to $0.31 by the end of this year.</p>
Join The Future Of Decentralized Freelancing With Uwerx (WERX)
<p class="s5">According to a 2022 statistic from Velocity Global, at least 36% of the American workforce freelances. This suggests a need to bring new ideas and innovations to the freelance industry. Uwerx is entering the cryptocurrency market as a much-needed innovation that will revolutionalize the gig economy. It will offer unique benefits to freelancers, such as a minimal 1% transaction fee, fast payments, intellectual property rights protection, and more. </p>
<p class="s5">Still on presale, Uwerx is already making significant strides and attracting investors' attention. Uwerx is currently valued at $0.05245 in its ongoing fifth presale stage. However, analysts see the project growing exponentially in the coming months. They predict the WERX token to rise above $2.6 by Q4 2024.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx takes the security of investors' funds seriously. The project has received audits from InterFi Network and SolidProof, ensuring top-tier protection. It also implemented a 25-year lock on developers' liquidity tokens on June 7, 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, Uwerx released the Alpha version of its platform on May 19, 2023. This version features a Landing page, Sign-up page, Login page, Forgot Password, Hiring Dashboard, Freelancer/Client Initiation, The Initial Step of Job Creation and Initial Step of Finding Talent, My Activity, and Job Creation process pages. </p>
<p class="s5">All these features will lead to the rollout of the platform's Beta version, enabling users to test and experience the platform. User feedback is expected and can be sent to the email: feedback@uwerx.network.</p>
<p class="s5">The Uwerx Vault is another fantastic feature of Uwerx. Launched in April 2023, this feature allows users to store their WERX tokens for various lengths of time. Users will also earn rewards for using the Vault.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx's presale will end on July 31, 2023, so investors are advised to take advantage of the current low price to join the community before Uwerx launches into the coin market. </p>
<p class="s5">The Uwerx team pays attention to the community's needs and makes adjustments to solve those needs. The developers recently asked the community to vote on a test airdrop. 98.2% of respondents voted in favor of the test airdrop, which the team believes will enable users to verify their receiving wallet addresses. They will also relinquish smart contract ownership of the project, which will take effect once it lists on centralized exchanges. </p>
<p class="s5">These moves have increased investors' confidence in the project and have made them believe that Uwerx could be a prominent project in the coin market by the end of this year. </p>
<p class="s5">So what are you waiting for? Join this exciting presale and enjoy a 15% purchase bonus through the links below:</p>
<p class="s5">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network </p>
<p class="s5">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Crypto enthusiasts usually go for cryptocurrencies that have been around for a while because of these coins' proven success in the market. But the story is different with the new project Uwerx, which has traders buying in bulk even though it has yet to launch. </p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx is having a successful presale, to the amazement of its developers and the benefit of early investors. Having smashed through its first four stages in less than two months, analysts believe Uwerx will make a better investment than Open Campus (EDU) and Conflux (CFX). </p>
Open Campus (EDU) Sees An Downward Trend
<p class="s5">Open Campus (EDU) has reached a wider audience since it partnered with Animoca Brands to launch the Web3 Global Educators Fund. This has translated to an increase in the number of members joining the Open Campus (EDU) community. </p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, the project's Publisher NFTs have become a favorite among educators and content creators as it gives them the means to earn revenue for their work. </p>
<p class="s5">Despite the increase in Open Campus (EDU) adoption, the project has not risen in price in the last seven days. Open Campus trades at $1.00, representing a -13.84% decrease in the last seven days. Analysts predict it to trade at $2.07 by the first quarter of 2024</p>
Conflux (CFX) Rises In The Last 24hrs
<p class="s5">The past 24hrs have been good to Conflux (CFX). The project trades at $0.24, representing a 9.37% increase within 24 hours. Although this current price represents a -23.55% decrease in the last seven days, Conflux (CFX) holders believe this could be the start of the project's bull run. </p>
<p class="s5">Conflux (CFX) announced on June 2 via Twitter that it has partnered with Code4arena. This collaboration will provide enhanced security for both ecosystems.</p>
<p class="s5">Following the partnership, the Conflux (CFX) team announced on June 6 that they were aware of the recent cross-chain irregularity in their ecosystem. They assured users they had taken preventive action by removing Multichain's co-mint rights. This will ensure the security of user assets. The project also stated that they had not detected any loss, and the ecosystem was functioning as usual.</p>
<p class="s5">With more partnerships and improvements, analysts believe the CFX token could increase to $0.31 by the end of this year.</p>
Join The Future Of Decentralized Freelancing With Uwerx (WERX)
<p class="s5">According to a 2022 statistic from Velocity Global, at least 36% of the American workforce freelances. This suggests a need to bring new ideas and innovations to the freelance industry. Uwerx is entering the cryptocurrency market as a much-needed innovation that will revolutionalize the gig economy. It will offer unique benefits to freelancers, such as a minimal 1% transaction fee, fast payments, intellectual property rights protection, and more. </p>
<p class="s5">Still on presale, Uwerx is already making significant strides and attracting investors' attention. Uwerx is currently valued at $0.05245 in its ongoing fifth presale stage. However, analysts see the project growing exponentially in the coming months. They predict the WERX token to rise above $2.6 by Q4 2024.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx takes the security of investors' funds seriously. The project has received audits from InterFi Network and SolidProof, ensuring top-tier protection. It also implemented a 25-year lock on developers' liquidity tokens on June 7, 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, Uwerx released the Alpha version of its platform on May 19, 2023. This version features a Landing page, Sign-up page, Login page, Forgot Password, Hiring Dashboard, Freelancer/Client Initiation, The Initial Step of Job Creation and Initial Step of Finding Talent, My Activity, and Job Creation process pages. </p>
<p class="s5">All these features will lead to the rollout of the platform's Beta version, enabling users to test and experience the platform. User feedback is expected and can be sent to the email: feedback@uwerx.network.</p>
<p class="s5">The Uwerx Vault is another fantastic feature of Uwerx. Launched in April 2023, this feature allows users to store their WERX tokens for various lengths of time. Users will also earn rewards for using the Vault.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx's presale will end on July 31, 2023, so investors are advised to take advantage of the current low price to join the community before Uwerx launches into the coin market. </p>
<p class="s5">The Uwerx team pays attention to the community's needs and makes adjustments to solve those needs. The developers recently asked the community to vote on a test airdrop. 98.2% of respondents voted in favor of the test airdrop, which the team believes will enable users to verify their receiving wallet addresses. They will also relinquish smart contract ownership of the project, which will take effect once it lists on centralized exchanges. </p>
<p class="s5">These moves have increased investors' confidence in the project and have made them believe that Uwerx could be a prominent project in the coin market by the end of this year. </p>
<p class="s5">So what are you waiting for? Join this exciting presale and enjoy a 15% purchase bonus through the links below:</p>
<p class="s5">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network </p>
<p class="s5">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Creds by cheqd: Web3 Reputation Made Private & Secure]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/creds-by-cheqd-web3-reputation-made-private-and-secure</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/qqqqq.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/qqqqq.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/qqqqq.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/creds-by-cheqd-web3-reputation-made-private-and-secure</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized identity startup cheqd has announced the launch of a new platform called Creds for Web3 users to issue, hold and share digital credentials and build portable reputations.</p>
<p>The new tool was announced at the Nebular Summit in Paris, where attendees at the event were issued with the first Creds as part of a technology showcase. Creds give users a secure and private way to prove their identity in Web3 environments. What&rsquo;s more, they&rsquo;re fully portable and reusable, allowing users to slowly build up a strong reputation without ever revealing their true identity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd explains that there are many challenges around the issue of Web3 security, with crypto scams wiping out millions of dollars in user&rsquo;s funds, creating massive distrust in online communities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to cheqd, the best way to combat Web3 scams is to increase the trust and reputation of users, which is exactly what it&rsquo;s aiming to do with Creds. It provides a way for individuals to confirm their personhood and ownership of assets such as wallets and user handles across multiple platforms. So a moderator on a Discord server could prove their status and role, without revealing their identity. A scammer would not be able to prove this. In this way, not only will Creds help to prevent scams, but they can also prevent impersonation-based attacks and the spread of fake news by malicious individuals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd&rsquo;s idea with Creds is that users can build a verifiable reputation across multiple platforms and communities, with full control over which credentials they decide to share with which groups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Of course, a decentralized identity does more than simply improve security and prevent fraud. One of the most promising aspects of Creds is its ability to enable new kinds of gamified engagement for communities. By creating a reputation layer, projects can explore new gamification mechanics such as incentivized quests or &ldquo;learn-to-earn&rdquo; courses, where users are rewarded for learning and participating in forums and community activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd&rsquo;s Head of Marketing &amp; Community Eduardo Hotta said Web3 organizations are very interested in becoming more community-focused. &ldquo;As an example, it's preferable to have a smaller number of real active community members, or superfans, than to have a group with thousands of bots,&rdquo; he said. With Creds, projects can prove they have viable, active and engaged communities and encourage people to build reputations within them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd notes that similar decentralized identity projects in the past have made use of NFTs and SoulBound Tokens with varying levels of success. Creds differ from previous initiatives because these tokens are completely private, revocable and portable, able to be used with multiple platforms and ecosystems. With Creds, all personally identifiable information is stored off-chain, privately and securely. This data is verified by decentralized identifiers on-chain and cryptographically signed to ensure trust.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Creds are set to become a key aspect of cheqd&rsquo;s mission to build a trusted data economy based on lending markets, preference data markets and others that put users at the center. Cheqd supports these markets with a cutting-edge payment network that prioritizes individual&rsquo;s privacy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Creds offers a privacy-preserving alternative to the surveillance enabling tech of SBTs and NFTs where you have little control over your privacy, as activities and other information are written on the ledger making it public and immutable,&rdquo; said cheqd co-founder and Chief Executive Fraser Edwards. &ldquo;Creds are collectable, portable, secure and verifiable; it has all the best things that the NFT and SBT have with the addition of everything else they are missing."</p>

<p>At Nebular Summit, all attendees were issued with Creds, enabling them to verifiably prove their attendance at the event without revealing their identities or any other information about themselves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized identity startup cheqd has announced the launch of a new platform called Creds for Web3 users to issue, hold and share digital credentials and build portable reputations.</p>
<p>The new tool was announced at the Nebular Summit in Paris, where attendees at the event were issued with the first Creds as part of a technology showcase. Creds give users a secure and private way to prove their identity in Web3 environments. What&rsquo;s more, they&rsquo;re fully portable and reusable, allowing users to slowly build up a strong reputation without ever revealing their true identity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd explains that there are many challenges around the issue of Web3 security, with crypto scams wiping out millions of dollars in user&rsquo;s funds, creating massive distrust in online communities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to cheqd, the best way to combat Web3 scams is to increase the trust and reputation of users, which is exactly what it&rsquo;s aiming to do with Creds. It provides a way for individuals to confirm their personhood and ownership of assets such as wallets and user handles across multiple platforms. So a moderator on a Discord server could prove their status and role, without revealing their identity. A scammer would not be able to prove this. In this way, not only will Creds help to prevent scams, but they can also prevent impersonation-based attacks and the spread of fake news by malicious individuals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd&rsquo;s idea with Creds is that users can build a verifiable reputation across multiple platforms and communities, with full control over which credentials they decide to share with which groups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Of course, a decentralized identity does more than simply improve security and prevent fraud. One of the most promising aspects of Creds is its ability to enable new kinds of gamified engagement for communities. By creating a reputation layer, projects can explore new gamification mechanics such as incentivized quests or &ldquo;learn-to-earn&rdquo; courses, where users are rewarded for learning and participating in forums and community activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd&rsquo;s Head of Marketing &amp; Community Eduardo Hotta said Web3 organizations are very interested in becoming more community-focused. &ldquo;As an example, it's preferable to have a smaller number of real active community members, or superfans, than to have a group with thousands of bots,&rdquo; he said. With Creds, projects can prove they have viable, active and engaged communities and encourage people to build reputations within them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cheqd notes that similar decentralized identity projects in the past have made use of NFTs and SoulBound Tokens with varying levels of success. Creds differ from previous initiatives because these tokens are completely private, revocable and portable, able to be used with multiple platforms and ecosystems. With Creds, all personally identifiable information is stored off-chain, privately and securely. This data is verified by decentralized identifiers on-chain and cryptographically signed to ensure trust.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Creds are set to become a key aspect of cheqd&rsquo;s mission to build a trusted data economy based on lending markets, preference data markets and others that put users at the center. Cheqd supports these markets with a cutting-edge payment network that prioritizes individual&rsquo;s privacy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"Creds offers a privacy-preserving alternative to the surveillance enabling tech of SBTs and NFTs where you have little control over your privacy, as activities and other information are written on the ledger making it public and immutable,&rdquo; said cheqd co-founder and Chief Executive Fraser Edwards. &ldquo;Creds are collectable, portable, secure and verifiable; it has all the best things that the NFT and SBT have with the addition of everything else they are missing."</p>

<p>At Nebular Summit, all attendees were issued with Creds, enabling them to verifiably prove their attendance at the event without revealing their identities or any other information about themselves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Grizzly.Fi Launched the Grizzly Trade Decentralized Perpetual Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/grizzlyfi-launched-the-grizzly-trade-decentralized-perpetual-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/grizzlyfi-1920x1080.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/grizzlyfi-1920x1080.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/grizzlyfi-1920x1080.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/grizzlyfi-launched-the-grizzly-trade-decentralized-perpetual-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Grizzly.Fi, the trailblazing DeFi platform committed to democratizing innovative financial solutions, has shared a momentous announcement that transcends its vibrant community.</p>
<p>On July 21, 2023, Grizzly Trade, their decentralized perpetual platform built on opBNB in collaboration with Metavault Trade, officially launched on BNB Mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This highly anticipated release marks the platform's advancement into a new realm alongside its existing range of earning products, further benefiting the Grizzly ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
The First Decentralized Perpetuals on opBNB
<p>Grizzly, one of the most promising projects in the DeFi span, has launched its decentralized perpetual exchange, Grizzly Trade.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This strategic expansion marks a significant milestone for the Grizzly Ecosystem, as it taps into a new market and propels the platform towards its vision of becoming a decentralized hub for DeFi's finest utilities.</p>
<p>In collaboration with Metavault Trade, Grizzly.Fi has extended its product line to include a futures trading platform, providing additional benefits to the Grizzly ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The opBNB (BNB Layer 2) deployment process commenced on June 30, 2023, and made Grizzly Trade available for testing. Following the initial deployment on the opBNB Testnet, the platform was also launched on the BNB mainnet on July 21.</p>
<p>Grizzly Trade allows users to trade blue-chip cryptocurrencies such as BTC, ETH, and BNB with leverage of up to 50x while ensuring a fully non-custodial experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform boasts an intuitive and user-friendly interface, providing a glimpse of the upcoming V2 update, which aims to transform the growing ecosystem into a beginner-friendly crypto hub.</p>
<p>Beyond its appeal as a new product catering to a broader audience, Grizzly Trade plays a vital role within the Grizzly ecosystem, serving as a lucrative real yield source for yield farmers. By providing liquidity, users can earn 50% of all platform fees while simultaneously being exposed to BTC, ETH, BNB, and stablecoins.</p>
<p>One of the most notable features of Grizzly Trade is the built-in Buyback &amp; Burn functionality for Grizzly's native token, "GHNY." This unique feature utilizes 25% of all generated platform fees to purchase GHNY from the open market and burn it. This mechanism effectively curbs inflation, transforming GHNY into an ultrasound (deflationary) token.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Grizzly Trade not only expands the potential market size by introducing a utility already utilized by thousands of individuals regularly but also stabilizes inflation and drives the protocol's traction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It signifies an important step towards achieving the overarching goal of the Grizzly ecosystem: to lead and onboard the next million users into DeFi.</p>
Win Big with GrizzlyFi's "Trade to Earn" and "Trade to Win" Challenges!
<p>In parallel with this launch and to celebrate it, GrizzlyFi establishes new trading challenges to reward and encourage new users to explore the platform: 'Trade to Earn' and 'Trade to Win.' With these two challenges, users can win impressive prizes from a reward pool of $20,000 in the 'Trade to Earn' challenge with a $1,000 transaction volume. Also, they can compete for some of the $50,000 and $30,000 prize pools in the 'Trade to Win Beginner' and 'Trade to Win Pro' challenges, respectively.&nbsp;</p>
Discover Grizzly.Fi
<p>Grizzly.Fi is a tech company founded in 2021, and it incorporates a DeFi platform dedicated to democratizing decentralized finance for all.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Today, Grizzly.Fi is also one of the most intuitive Liquidity Mining platforms. Renowned for its solutions and unwavering dedication to inclusivity, the company sets the benchmark in the industry.</p>
<p>Apart from its exceptional accessibility, Grizzly.Fi upholds an unwavering focus on security and transparency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Employing cutting-edge security protocols, the platform ensures the utmost protection of users' funds and personal information while fostering a culture of complete operational transparency.</p>
Stay Updated
<p>For more information, discover the honeycomb of Grizzly.Fi and explore its exceptional range of products by visiting its official website. Also, engage with the company through social media on LinkedIn, Twitter, Discord, Telegram, Reddit, Instagram, and YouTube, to stay connected with the latest news and updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grizzly.Fi, the trailblazing DeFi platform committed to democratizing innovative financial solutions, has shared a momentous announcement that transcends its vibrant community.</p>
<p>On July 21, 2023, Grizzly Trade, their decentralized perpetual platform built on opBNB in collaboration with Metavault Trade, officially launched on BNB Mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This highly anticipated release marks the platform's advancement into a new realm alongside its existing range of earning products, further benefiting the Grizzly ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
The First Decentralized Perpetuals on opBNB
<p>Grizzly, one of the most promising projects in the DeFi span, has launched its decentralized perpetual exchange, Grizzly Trade.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This strategic expansion marks a significant milestone for the Grizzly Ecosystem, as it taps into a new market and propels the platform towards its vision of becoming a decentralized hub for DeFi's finest utilities.</p>
<p>In collaboration with Metavault Trade, Grizzly.Fi has extended its product line to include a futures trading platform, providing additional benefits to the Grizzly ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The opBNB (BNB Layer 2) deployment process commenced on June 30, 2023, and made Grizzly Trade available for testing. Following the initial deployment on the opBNB Testnet, the platform was also launched on the BNB mainnet on July 21.</p>
<p>Grizzly Trade allows users to trade blue-chip cryptocurrencies such as BTC, ETH, and BNB with leverage of up to 50x while ensuring a fully non-custodial experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform boasts an intuitive and user-friendly interface, providing a glimpse of the upcoming V2 update, which aims to transform the growing ecosystem into a beginner-friendly crypto hub.</p>
<p>Beyond its appeal as a new product catering to a broader audience, Grizzly Trade plays a vital role within the Grizzly ecosystem, serving as a lucrative real yield source for yield farmers. By providing liquidity, users can earn 50% of all platform fees while simultaneously being exposed to BTC, ETH, BNB, and stablecoins.</p>
<p>One of the most notable features of Grizzly Trade is the built-in Buyback &amp; Burn functionality for Grizzly's native token, "GHNY." This unique feature utilizes 25% of all generated platform fees to purchase GHNY from the open market and burn it. This mechanism effectively curbs inflation, transforming GHNY into an ultrasound (deflationary) token.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Grizzly Trade not only expands the potential market size by introducing a utility already utilized by thousands of individuals regularly but also stabilizes inflation and drives the protocol's traction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It signifies an important step towards achieving the overarching goal of the Grizzly ecosystem: to lead and onboard the next million users into DeFi.</p>
Win Big with GrizzlyFi's "Trade to Earn" and "Trade to Win" Challenges!
<p>In parallel with this launch and to celebrate it, GrizzlyFi establishes new trading challenges to reward and encourage new users to explore the platform: 'Trade to Earn' and 'Trade to Win.' With these two challenges, users can win impressive prizes from a reward pool of $20,000 in the 'Trade to Earn' challenge with a $1,000 transaction volume. Also, they can compete for some of the $50,000 and $30,000 prize pools in the 'Trade to Win Beginner' and 'Trade to Win Pro' challenges, respectively.&nbsp;</p>
Discover Grizzly.Fi
<p>Grizzly.Fi is a tech company founded in 2021, and it incorporates a DeFi platform dedicated to democratizing decentralized finance for all.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Today, Grizzly.Fi is also one of the most intuitive Liquidity Mining platforms. Renowned for its solutions and unwavering dedication to inclusivity, the company sets the benchmark in the industry.</p>
<p>Apart from its exceptional accessibility, Grizzly.Fi upholds an unwavering focus on security and transparency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Employing cutting-edge security protocols, the platform ensures the utmost protection of users' funds and personal information while fostering a culture of complete operational transparency.</p>
Stay Updated
<p>For more information, discover the honeycomb of Grizzly.Fi and explore its exceptional range of products by visiting its official website. Also, engage with the company through social media on LinkedIn, Twitter, Discord, Telegram, Reddit, Instagram, and YouTube, to stay connected with the latest news and updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Delio the next crypto lender to fall?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/delio-the-next-crypto-lender-to-fall</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/delio-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/delio-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/delio-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 10:57:44 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/delio-the-next-crypto-lender-to-fall</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The South Korean Financial Services Commission's (FSC) decision to seize Delio&rsquo;s assets cast doubts over its future operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>South Korea's crypto lending powerhouse, Delio, established in 2018, is currently navigating stormy waters. Its woes began when the FSC, a local financial watchdog, took control of both the company's and its customers' assets. This included not just the tangible assets but also their cold wallets and ledgers. The seizure, a result of an ongoing legal tussle with its depositors, has put Delio in a tight spot, making it challenging for them to offer their regular suite of services.&nbsp;</p>
A suspension of interest payments
<p>The firm has emphasised the need to safeguard its assets, especially considering the interests of its depositors. In light of these events, Delio made the tough call to suspend interest payments to its deposit and vault users starting July 24. This move was not isolated; other services that demanded additional expenditures, like operational costs, were also put on hold.&nbsp;</p>
Deposits and withdrawals stopped
<p>This decision has understandably heightened concerns among their clientele. Delio's recent actions can be traced back to June 14 when they abruptly stopped deposits and withdrawals on their platform. This move was a protective measure against market volatility, which was exacerbated by similar actions from their sister lending company, Haru Invest. Haru Invest's decision to halt withdrawals was influenced by the discovery of misleading information from its consignment operator, B&amp;S Holdings.</p>
FSC gets involved&nbsp;
<p>The FSC's involvement deepened when they initiated an investigation into Delio's sudden transaction suspension. This probe culminated in a lawsuit against Delio, accusing them of fraud, embezzlement, and breach of trust. The fallout from this legal action saw travel restrictions placed on Delio's CEO, Jeong Sang-ho, among others.&nbsp;</p>
One of the largest crypto lending platforms
<p>Despite the shadows currently cast on Delio, it's vital to recognize their significant standing in the crypto realm. They are one of South Korea's premier crypto lending platforms, boasting a vast array of services from custody to staking. Their impressive portfolio includes about $1 billion in Bitcoin, $200 million in Ether, and a staggering $8.1 billion in various other altcoins.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The South Korean Financial Services Commission's (FSC) decision to seize Delio&rsquo;s assets cast doubts over its future operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>South Korea's crypto lending powerhouse, Delio, established in 2018, is currently navigating stormy waters. Its woes began when the FSC, a local financial watchdog, took control of both the company's and its customers' assets. This included not just the tangible assets but also their cold wallets and ledgers. The seizure, a result of an ongoing legal tussle with its depositors, has put Delio in a tight spot, making it challenging for them to offer their regular suite of services.&nbsp;</p>
A suspension of interest payments
<p>The firm has emphasised the need to safeguard its assets, especially considering the interests of its depositors. In light of these events, Delio made the tough call to suspend interest payments to its deposit and vault users starting July 24. This move was not isolated; other services that demanded additional expenditures, like operational costs, were also put on hold.&nbsp;</p>
Deposits and withdrawals stopped
<p>This decision has understandably heightened concerns among their clientele. Delio's recent actions can be traced back to June 14 when they abruptly stopped deposits and withdrawals on their platform. This move was a protective measure against market volatility, which was exacerbated by similar actions from their sister lending company, Haru Invest. Haru Invest's decision to halt withdrawals was influenced by the discovery of misleading information from its consignment operator, B&amp;S Holdings.</p>
FSC gets involved&nbsp;
<p>The FSC's involvement deepened when they initiated an investigation into Delio's sudden transaction suspension. This probe culminated in a lawsuit against Delio, accusing them of fraud, embezzlement, and breach of trust. The fallout from this legal action saw travel restrictions placed on Delio's CEO, Jeong Sang-ho, among others.&nbsp;</p>
One of the largest crypto lending platforms
<p>Despite the shadows currently cast on Delio, it's vital to recognize their significant standing in the crypto realm. They are one of South Korea's premier crypto lending platforms, boasting a vast array of services from custody to staking. Their impressive portfolio includes about $1 billion in Bitcoin, $200 million in Ether, and a staggering $8.1 billion in various other altcoins.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[TFS Token Launches a New Liquidity Staking Feature]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/tfs-token-launches-a-new-liquidity-staking-feature</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/tfs_token_1200720_1_1689165352EhX7NAetsh.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/tfs_token_1200720_1_1689165352EhX7NAetsh.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/tfs_token_1200720_1_1689165352EhX7NAetsh.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 10:03:39 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/tfs-token-launches-a-new-liquidity-staking-feature</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Willemstad, Curacao, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Last year, the Fairspin platform launched two associated loyalty programs: Play To Earn and Hold To Earn. Within the first one, it is possible to receive TFS tokens as a rakeback; using the second one, it is possible to increase them thanks to the holding without any risks.&nbsp;</p><p>Both programs have already shown outstanding results. Since its launch, $726,234 and $1,759 091,86 were paid to players in frames of the Play To Earn and Hold To Earn respectively.&nbsp;</p><p>TFS Token team is pleased to announce another beneficial way to get additional income for TFS holders - the liquidity staking program.</p>What is liquidity staking?<p>Tokens and money, staked in such a program, will be used to increase liquidity on the PancakeSwap in the TFS-USDT pool. This will help improve the liquidity of the TFS token, thus strengthening its position on the market.&nbsp;</p><p>The Liquidity Staking option is available on the Staking Programs page on the Fairspin website.&nbsp;</p><p>Unlike the already existing staking programs, liquidity staking is permanent, which means if a user chooses this option, staking will continue until the option is not stopped by the user.&nbsp;</p><p>At the same time, the reward from the liquidity staking can be withdrawn at any time upon the user's request. There is no obligatory minimum staking time to withdraw the reward as well as there are no limits on the number of withdrawing requests.&nbsp;</p>How the reward is calculated<p>The amount of reward depends on the GGR of Fairspin casino and the number of tokens in the staking pool and the user's multiplier.</p><p>The user's multiplier depends on the length of your stake in days.</p><p>Calculation formula:</p><ul><li>from 0 to 1 day multiplier *0.3</li><li>from 7 to 30 days multiplier *0.6</li><li>30 to &infin; days multiplier *1</li></ul><p>The reward, in the end, will be equal to % of the GGR of the Fairspin casino multiplied by the user's share in the pool and multiplied by the time multiplier. If a user stakes tokens for 1 month and more, he will have the maximum benefit - a share of 0.5% of GGR.</p><p>The request to stop liquidity staking can be made at any time. A user can request to withdraw the full sum or a part of it.&nbsp;The tokens will be sent to a user&rsquo;s account immediately.&nbsp;</p><p>In case a user makes a request to withdraw a part of tokens from the Liquidity Staking, the reward multiplier for the rest of the tokens in Liquidity Staking will go back to the initial level.</p>About TFS Token&nbsp;<p>The TFS token is the driving force behind Fairspin, one of the leading global blockchain casinos, that ushers in a new era of trust and transparency in online gambling.</p><p>Built upon ERC-20/BEP-20 technology, the TFS token ensures immutable betting data, empowering players with complete access to their gaming history and rewards. With a limited supply and a focus on user rewards, the token introduces groundbreaking Play to Earn and Hold to Earn features, rewarding players for their engagement.</p><p>As the gaming industry continues to evolve, the TFS token stands at the forefront, revolutionizing the way players interact with online casinos and shaping the future of fair gaming.&nbsp;</p>ContactTFS Token PR teampr@fairspin.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Willemstad, Curacao, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Last year, the Fairspin platform launched two associated loyalty programs: Play To Earn and Hold To Earn. Within the first one, it is possible to receive TFS tokens as a rakeback; using the second one, it is possible to increase them thanks to the holding without any risks.&nbsp;</p><p>Both programs have already shown outstanding results. Since its launch, $726,234 and $1,759 091,86 were paid to players in frames of the Play To Earn and Hold To Earn respectively.&nbsp;</p><p>TFS Token team is pleased to announce another beneficial way to get additional income for TFS holders - the liquidity staking program.</p>What is liquidity staking?<p>Tokens and money, staked in such a program, will be used to increase liquidity on the PancakeSwap in the TFS-USDT pool. This will help improve the liquidity of the TFS token, thus strengthening its position on the market.&nbsp;</p><p>The Liquidity Staking option is available on the Staking Programs page on the Fairspin website.&nbsp;</p><p>Unlike the already existing staking programs, liquidity staking is permanent, which means if a user chooses this option, staking will continue until the option is not stopped by the user.&nbsp;</p><p>At the same time, the reward from the liquidity staking can be withdrawn at any time upon the user's request. There is no obligatory minimum staking time to withdraw the reward as well as there are no limits on the number of withdrawing requests.&nbsp;</p>How the reward is calculated<p>The amount of reward depends on the GGR of Fairspin casino and the number of tokens in the staking pool and the user's multiplier.</p><p>The user's multiplier depends on the length of your stake in days.</p><p>Calculation formula:</p><ul><li>from 0 to 1 day multiplier *0.3</li><li>from 7 to 30 days multiplier *0.6</li><li>30 to &infin; days multiplier *1</li></ul><p>The reward, in the end, will be equal to % of the GGR of the Fairspin casino multiplied by the user's share in the pool and multiplied by the time multiplier. If a user stakes tokens for 1 month and more, he will have the maximum benefit - a share of 0.5% of GGR.</p><p>The request to stop liquidity staking can be made at any time. A user can request to withdraw the full sum or a part of it.&nbsp;The tokens will be sent to a user&rsquo;s account immediately.&nbsp;</p><p>In case a user makes a request to withdraw a part of tokens from the Liquidity Staking, the reward multiplier for the rest of the tokens in Liquidity Staking will go back to the initial level.</p>About TFS Token&nbsp;<p>The TFS token is the driving force behind Fairspin, one of the leading global blockchain casinos, that ushers in a new era of trust and transparency in online gambling.</p><p>Built upon ERC-20/BEP-20 technology, the TFS token ensures immutable betting data, empowering players with complete access to their gaming history and rewards. With a limited supply and a focus on user rewards, the token introduces groundbreaking Play to Earn and Hold to Earn features, rewarding players for their engagement.</p><p>As the gaming industry continues to evolve, the TFS token stands at the forefront, revolutionizing the way players interact with online casinos and shaping the future of fair gaming.&nbsp;</p>ContactTFS Token PR teampr@fairspin.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[It’s Over 1000! X-Token Surges Following Musk’s Twitter Rebrand]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/its-over-1000-x-token-surges-following-musks-twitter-rebrand</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/elon-musk-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/elon-musk-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/elon-musk-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/its-over-1000-x-token-surges-following-musks-twitter-rebrand</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>An obscure altcoin called the X token has surged by over 1000% following Elon Musk&rsquo;s announcement that Twitter is rebranding itself to X.com.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the token in question has absolutely no association with the rebranded Twitter or X.com, as it is now known.&nbsp;</p>
An Unprecedented Surge&nbsp;
<p>The X token is linked to an NFT marketplace that announced its closure back in May and registered a staggering increase following Elon Musk&rsquo;s announcement to rebrand Twitter to X.com. The token, which was trading at $0.00002, jumped to $0.00025. According to data from CoinGecko, the token&rsquo;s value has jumped by over 1000% over the past 12 hours. Most of the token&rsquo;s trading volume is on the SushiSwap decentralized exchange (DEX). However, despite the massive surge, the token&rsquo;s trading volume remains low, amounting to just $51,000.&nbsp;</p>
Is There An Association With Twitter?
<p>The surge occurred after Elon Musk announced an upcoming logo change for the social media platform. Following the announcement, users likely thought the token was related to the rebranded platform. However, the token was part of a project started by X, a decentralized NFT marketplace operating across several chains, and has no association with the rebranded Twitter. The X DAO is in charge of the platform&rsquo;s governance, and users who have staked their X tokens can exercise their voting rights after obtaining the veX governance tokens.&nbsp;</p>
Twitter&rsquo;s Rebranding&nbsp;
<p>Elon Musk had announced his plans to rebrand Twitter on Sunday, stating that he intended to retire the iconic blue bird logo that had been part of Twitter&rsquo;s global identity since its inception. In a tweet, he stated that if a good enough X logo is posted, it could go live within 24 hours. Following the tweet, X.com began redirecting to Twitter.com, with Musk tweeting about the company&rsquo;s rebrand to X.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Soon we shall bid adieu to the Twitter brand and, gradually, all the birds. If a good enough X logo is posted tonight, we&rsquo;ll make it go live worldwide tomorrow.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Musk had also sent an email to Twitter employees telling them about the change to X. He added that this would be the last time he would be using an email address associated with Twitter. While some users, specifically Musk fans, applauded the changes, long-time users of Twitter are miffed with the changes. Marques Brownlee, one of the most well-known names in tech, tweeted that he was still going to call the platform Twitter. Musk responded to the tweet, stating, &ldquo;Not for long.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s rebrand is the clearest indication yet that Twitter is no longer the same social media platform purchased by Musk. Recently appointed chief executive officer of X Corp, which owns Twitter, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Twitter made one massive impression and changed the way we communicate. Now, X will go further, transforming the global town square. X is the future state of unlimited interactivity &ndash; centered in audio, video, messaging, and payments/banking &ndash; creating a global marketplace for ideas, goods, services, and opportunities. Powered by AI, X will connect us all in ways we&rsquo;re just beginning to imagine.&rdquo;</p>

Markets In Recovery?&nbsp;
<p>Apart from the X token surge, crypto markets remained dormant, with no major movements. The total market capitalization still stands at $1.23 trillion and has remained at that level for the past few days. Bitcoin prices had jumped over the $30,000 mark but have since fallen back, with BTC currently trading at $29,787. Most cryptocurrencies are firmly rooted in the red, with only a few exceptions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An obscure altcoin called the X token has surged by over 1000% following Elon Musk&rsquo;s announcement that Twitter is rebranding itself to X.com.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the token in question has absolutely no association with the rebranded Twitter or X.com, as it is now known.&nbsp;</p>
An Unprecedented Surge&nbsp;
<p>The X token is linked to an NFT marketplace that announced its closure back in May and registered a staggering increase following Elon Musk&rsquo;s announcement to rebrand Twitter to X.com. The token, which was trading at $0.00002, jumped to $0.00025. According to data from CoinGecko, the token&rsquo;s value has jumped by over 1000% over the past 12 hours. Most of the token&rsquo;s trading volume is on the SushiSwap decentralized exchange (DEX). However, despite the massive surge, the token&rsquo;s trading volume remains low, amounting to just $51,000.&nbsp;</p>
Is There An Association With Twitter?
<p>The surge occurred after Elon Musk announced an upcoming logo change for the social media platform. Following the announcement, users likely thought the token was related to the rebranded platform. However, the token was part of a project started by X, a decentralized NFT marketplace operating across several chains, and has no association with the rebranded Twitter. The X DAO is in charge of the platform&rsquo;s governance, and users who have staked their X tokens can exercise their voting rights after obtaining the veX governance tokens.&nbsp;</p>
Twitter&rsquo;s Rebranding&nbsp;
<p>Elon Musk had announced his plans to rebrand Twitter on Sunday, stating that he intended to retire the iconic blue bird logo that had been part of Twitter&rsquo;s global identity since its inception. In a tweet, he stated that if a good enough X logo is posted, it could go live within 24 hours. Following the tweet, X.com began redirecting to Twitter.com, with Musk tweeting about the company&rsquo;s rebrand to X.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Soon we shall bid adieu to the Twitter brand and, gradually, all the birds. If a good enough X logo is posted tonight, we&rsquo;ll make it go live worldwide tomorrow.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Musk had also sent an email to Twitter employees telling them about the change to X. He added that this would be the last time he would be using an email address associated with Twitter. While some users, specifically Musk fans, applauded the changes, long-time users of Twitter are miffed with the changes. Marques Brownlee, one of the most well-known names in tech, tweeted that he was still going to call the platform Twitter. Musk responded to the tweet, stating, &ldquo;Not for long.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s rebrand is the clearest indication yet that Twitter is no longer the same social media platform purchased by Musk. Recently appointed chief executive officer of X Corp, which owns Twitter, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Twitter made one massive impression and changed the way we communicate. Now, X will go further, transforming the global town square. X is the future state of unlimited interactivity &ndash; centered in audio, video, messaging, and payments/banking &ndash; creating a global marketplace for ideas, goods, services, and opportunities. Powered by AI, X will connect us all in ways we&rsquo;re just beginning to imagine.&rdquo;</p>

Markets In Recovery?&nbsp;
<p>Apart from the X token surge, crypto markets remained dormant, with no major movements. The total market capitalization still stands at $1.23 trillion and has remained at that level for the past few days. Bitcoin prices had jumped over the $30,000 mark but have since fallen back, with BTC currently trading at $29,787. Most cryptocurrencies are firmly rooted in the red, with only a few exceptions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[DeFi expert Özcan Köme Shares Insight About the Future Potential of DEXs]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/defi-expert-ozcan-kome-shares-insight-about-the-future-potential-of-dexs</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/6_1690180565wK4B4HDDyO.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/6_1690180565wK4B4HDDyO.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/6_1690180565wK4B4HDDyO.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:35:27 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/defi-expert-ozcan-kome-shares-insight-about-the-future-potential-of-dexs</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Zug, Switzerland, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p>&Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me, a seasoned DeFi expert whose crypto roots date back to 2016, shares a balanced perspective on the potential of the Decentralized Finance Landscape.<p>In the face of CeFi's limitations, &Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me believes that DeFi stands as a revolutionary concept, reshaping how financial services are accessed and utilized. DEXs, a crucial component of the DeFi space, have emerged as a groundbreaking solution with the potential to transform the way people interact with financial markets.</p><p>DEXs empower users with complete control over their assets through self-custody, eliminating the need for intermediaries. Trust in external entities becomes unnecessary, allowing individuals to truly own and manage their funds. Operating on public blockchains, DEXs ensure complete transparency in every transaction, enhancing trust among users and significantly reducing the risk of intransparency. Furthermore, DEXs operate in a decentralized and automated manner, reducing the potential for human errors. Users can trade with greater confidence in a safer environment.</p><p>Even prominent figures within the crypto industry acknowledge the potential of DEXs. CZ, the CEO and founder of Binance, a leading centralized exchange, publicly stated that DEXs are the future of finance, emphasizing their transformative impact on the industry.</p><p>&Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me acknowledges that while DEXs hold immense potential, certain challenges must be addressed. Notably, enhancing the execution speed and minimizing slippage compared to centralized counterparts are areas that require ongoing development. Nevertheless, "with continuous advancements in blockchain technology, we can remains optimistic that these obstacles will be overcomed"</p><p>The vision is for a future where DeFi (Decentralized Finance) and DEXs (Decentralized Exchanges) transform financial systems, making them accessible, transparent, and efficient for people worldwide. Embracing blockchain technology is seen as a way to pave the path towards a decentralized and inclusive financial ecosystem.</p><p>About &Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me</p><p>As the Founder of Cookielabs GmbH, a web3 advisory firm based in switzerland offering a range of services including tokenomics advisory, project management, web3 development, UI/UX design, and brand identity, &Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me has gained valuable experience in understanding the current needs and dynamics of the market. With his background in sales (achieving 8 figures in turnover) in his early days, he learned precisely what customers appreciate and what effectively captures their attention when it comes to marketing.&nbsp;</p>ContactMarketingDaniel SchmidCookielabs GmbHdanielschmid@cookielabs.ch]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zug, Switzerland, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p>&Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me, a seasoned DeFi expert whose crypto roots date back to 2016, shares a balanced perspective on the potential of the Decentralized Finance Landscape.<p>In the face of CeFi's limitations, &Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me believes that DeFi stands as a revolutionary concept, reshaping how financial services are accessed and utilized. DEXs, a crucial component of the DeFi space, have emerged as a groundbreaking solution with the potential to transform the way people interact with financial markets.</p><p>DEXs empower users with complete control over their assets through self-custody, eliminating the need for intermediaries. Trust in external entities becomes unnecessary, allowing individuals to truly own and manage their funds. Operating on public blockchains, DEXs ensure complete transparency in every transaction, enhancing trust among users and significantly reducing the risk of intransparency. Furthermore, DEXs operate in a decentralized and automated manner, reducing the potential for human errors. Users can trade with greater confidence in a safer environment.</p><p>Even prominent figures within the crypto industry acknowledge the potential of DEXs. CZ, the CEO and founder of Binance, a leading centralized exchange, publicly stated that DEXs are the future of finance, emphasizing their transformative impact on the industry.</p><p>&Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me acknowledges that while DEXs hold immense potential, certain challenges must be addressed. Notably, enhancing the execution speed and minimizing slippage compared to centralized counterparts are areas that require ongoing development. Nevertheless, "with continuous advancements in blockchain technology, we can remains optimistic that these obstacles will be overcomed"</p><p>The vision is for a future where DeFi (Decentralized Finance) and DEXs (Decentralized Exchanges) transform financial systems, making them accessible, transparent, and efficient for people worldwide. Embracing blockchain technology is seen as a way to pave the path towards a decentralized and inclusive financial ecosystem.</p><p>About &Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me</p><p>As the Founder of Cookielabs GmbH, a web3 advisory firm based in switzerland offering a range of services including tokenomics advisory, project management, web3 development, UI/UX design, and brand identity, &Ouml;zcan K&ouml;me has gained valuable experience in understanding the current needs and dynamics of the market. With his background in sales (achieving 8 figures in turnover) in his early days, he learned precisely what customers appreciate and what effectively captures their attention when it comes to marketing.&nbsp;</p>ContactMarketingDaniel SchmidCookielabs GmbHdanielschmid@cookielabs.ch]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ATPBot Launches Unique AI-Powered Crypto Investment App]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/atpbot-launches-unique-ai-powered-crypto-investment-app</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/_J1FQD4WAMV_HHKY44_1690164174MCDOLaHbz6.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/_J1FQD4WAMV_HHKY44_1690164174MCDOLaHbz6.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/_J1FQD4WAMV_HHKY44_1690164174MCDOLaHbz6.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:03:03 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/atpbot-launches-unique-ai-powered-crypto-investment-app</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>ATPBot has launched its AI-powered investment platform offering an innovative approach to cryptocurrency trading. By combining cutting-edge technology with expert strategy modeling, ATPBot is set to transform the way traders operate, providing a distinct advantage over manual trading methods.</p><p>Manual trading has long been plagued by extensive learning curves and significant capital investments. Traders struggle to control their emotions, leading to impulsive decisions that can be costly. Without systematic trading logic, risk management becomes a challenge. Moreover, manual traders face the inability to monitor the markets 24/7, missing out on lucrative opportunities.</p><p></p><p>Source: ATPBot, 40-month backtest profit 879%, max drawdown 33%</p><p>ATPBot changes the landscape by offering a seamless and automated trading experience. Its AI-powered algorithms eliminate emotional biases, enabling traders to make data-driven decisions based on preset stop-loss and take-profit parameters. With ATPBot, 24/7 monitoring of market trends becomes a reality, empowering users to capitalize on every opportunity.</p><p>The trading bot also offers distinct advantages compared to private equity firms, which demand exorbitant investment costs and high capital thresholds, excluding many potential investors. The lack of real-time visibility into one's funds and inflexible investment time frames add to the complexities. Additionally, the opacity surrounding fund allocation creates uncertainties for investors.</p><p>ATPBot welcomes investors of all levels with its affordable pricing, starting from a basic plan of just $999 per year, and a low minimum investment threshold of $5,000. Users gain full transparency into their funds and enjoy the flexibility to control their investments, including pausing, terminating, or switching strategies as desired.</p><p></p><p>Source: ATPBot, no fear of market ups and downs, perfect curve</p><p>Traditional trading bots are often limited by simplistic strategy templates, leaving traders exposed to higher risks. They lack the sophistication of AI-powered systems and cannot handle vast datasets effectively. The number of strategies is small, all the funds are trading at the same time, and the risk is high.</p><p>ATPBot's AI integration ensures unparalleled data processing capabilities, with high-performance servers that enable extensive backtesting and optimization. Users benefit from dynamic market evaluations, learning from each trade, and consistently improving performance.</p><p>ATPBot revolutionizes the trading landscape by addressing the limitations of manual trading, private equity firms, and traditional trading bots. With its AI-powered platform, extensive data processing capabilities, and unique strategies for each user, ATPBot delivers a competitive edge that sets it apart as the ultimate trading powerhouse. Interested investors can enter the ATPBot website to learn more, register an account and start using the power of ATPBot to make trades.</p><p>In addition to its platform functionality, ATPBot boasts a professional Discord community consisting of numerous quantitative trading researchers and practitioners. Within this space, users can interact with quantitative trading enthusiasts from around the world, sharing experiences and ideas. The community offers professional guidance on market trends, market analysis, and trading techniques, helping users advance further on the path of quantitative trading.</p><p>About ATPBot</p><p>ATPBot is a digital currency intelligent AI-quantitative trading bot platform, founded in 2021. ATPBot&rsquo;s mission is to become a leader in the field of digital currency trading and provide efficient, intelligent, and reliable quantitative trading solutions. ATPBot&rsquo;s team consists of AI algorithm and strategy modeling experts who provide collective intelligence and advanced machine learning models to drive growth and success for businesses. ATPBot seeks significant capital appreciation through a combination of quantitative methods and artificial intelligence (AI) strategies, and has developed an advanced AI algorithm model that has repeatedly outperformed the market.</p><p>Socials: Twitter | Discord</p>ContactJoan Trinabusiness@atpbot.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, July 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>ATPBot has launched its AI-powered investment platform offering an innovative approach to cryptocurrency trading. By combining cutting-edge technology with expert strategy modeling, ATPBot is set to transform the way traders operate, providing a distinct advantage over manual trading methods.</p><p>Manual trading has long been plagued by extensive learning curves and significant capital investments. Traders struggle to control their emotions, leading to impulsive decisions that can be costly. Without systematic trading logic, risk management becomes a challenge. Moreover, manual traders face the inability to monitor the markets 24/7, missing out on lucrative opportunities.</p><p></p><p>Source: ATPBot, 40-month backtest profit 879%, max drawdown 33%</p><p>ATPBot changes the landscape by offering a seamless and automated trading experience. Its AI-powered algorithms eliminate emotional biases, enabling traders to make data-driven decisions based on preset stop-loss and take-profit parameters. With ATPBot, 24/7 monitoring of market trends becomes a reality, empowering users to capitalize on every opportunity.</p><p>The trading bot also offers distinct advantages compared to private equity firms, which demand exorbitant investment costs and high capital thresholds, excluding many potential investors. The lack of real-time visibility into one's funds and inflexible investment time frames add to the complexities. Additionally, the opacity surrounding fund allocation creates uncertainties for investors.</p><p>ATPBot welcomes investors of all levels with its affordable pricing, starting from a basic plan of just $999 per year, and a low minimum investment threshold of $5,000. Users gain full transparency into their funds and enjoy the flexibility to control their investments, including pausing, terminating, or switching strategies as desired.</p><p></p><p>Source: ATPBot, no fear of market ups and downs, perfect curve</p><p>Traditional trading bots are often limited by simplistic strategy templates, leaving traders exposed to higher risks. They lack the sophistication of AI-powered systems and cannot handle vast datasets effectively. The number of strategies is small, all the funds are trading at the same time, and the risk is high.</p><p>ATPBot's AI integration ensures unparalleled data processing capabilities, with high-performance servers that enable extensive backtesting and optimization. Users benefit from dynamic market evaluations, learning from each trade, and consistently improving performance.</p><p>ATPBot revolutionizes the trading landscape by addressing the limitations of manual trading, private equity firms, and traditional trading bots. With its AI-powered platform, extensive data processing capabilities, and unique strategies for each user, ATPBot delivers a competitive edge that sets it apart as the ultimate trading powerhouse. Interested investors can enter the ATPBot website to learn more, register an account and start using the power of ATPBot to make trades.</p><p>In addition to its platform functionality, ATPBot boasts a professional Discord community consisting of numerous quantitative trading researchers and practitioners. Within this space, users can interact with quantitative trading enthusiasts from around the world, sharing experiences and ideas. The community offers professional guidance on market trends, market analysis, and trading techniques, helping users advance further on the path of quantitative trading.</p><p>About ATPBot</p><p>ATPBot is a digital currency intelligent AI-quantitative trading bot platform, founded in 2021. ATPBot&rsquo;s mission is to become a leader in the field of digital currency trading and provide efficient, intelligent, and reliable quantitative trading solutions. ATPBot&rsquo;s team consists of AI algorithm and strategy modeling experts who provide collective intelligence and advanced machine learning models to drive growth and success for businesses. ATPBot seeks significant capital appreciation through a combination of quantitative methods and artificial intelligence (AI) strategies, and has developed an advanced AI algorithm model that has repeatedly outperformed the market.</p><p>Socials: Twitter | Discord</p>ContactJoan Trinabusiness@atpbot.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celsius Reaches Settlements To Exit Bankruptcy, Return User Funds]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/celsius-reaches-settlements-to-exit-bankruptcy-return-user-funds</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/celsius-reaches-settlements-to-exit-bankruptcy-return-user-funds</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network has reached two crucial settlements to end its bankruptcy proceedings and clear a path for the return of customer assets, revealed court filings.</p>
<p>Any responses or objections to the settlements must be submitted in court by the 3rd of August.&nbsp;</p>
A Resolution In Sight&nbsp;
<p>Celsius Network filed for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy in 2022, and customers have been waiting in anticipation of the outcome of its bankruptcy proceedings. While the settlements that will allow the bankrupt crypto lender to return customer assets have been reached, they still have to be analyzed by Judge Martin Glenn at a hearing scheduled for the 10th of August. If agreed, the settlements will allow Celsius to conclude bankruptcy proceedings and see the long-awaited return of customer assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, there is also a confirmation hearing on Celsius&rsquo; reorganization plan that has been scheduled for October. This means customers could begin to see the disbursements of their crypto and assets before the end of the year. Lawyers representing Celsius Network have argued that customers are owed no more than the initially deposited amount. However, users have filed several claims seeking additional damages for alleged misconduct by the firm&rsquo;s former management.&nbsp;</p>
Unpacking The Settlements&nbsp;
<p>The first settlement addresses several claims related to fraud and misrepresentation allegedly committed by the previous Celsius management. Under the agreement, Celsius has committed to increase customer recoveries by 5%. Those account holders who do not want to participate in the settlement can opt-out and pursue individual claims against Celsius. Those who wish to remain part of the settlement will be eligible to receive a claim amount equivalent to 105% of their scheduled claim. This would also override any Proof of Claims filed earlier.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Any eligible Account Holder who does not opt out of the settlement will receive a claim in the amount of 105% of their scheduled claim, which will supersede and extinguish any related Proofs of Claim filed by such Account Holder. &ldquo;</p>

<p>The second settlement addresses claims by customers that had funds locked in Celsius&rsquo; interest-bearing Earn program. Under this agreement, Celsius customers that borrowed crypto can receive a portion of their funds in the form of crypto assets. Furthermore, customers of the Earn program will also be compensated with shares of the new company that would be created once the bankruptcy proceedings have concluded. With these resolutions, it is hoped that impacted customers of the bankrupt crypto lender can have some restitution, along with a stake in the company&rsquo;s future operations. Court documents state,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;[...] creditors have agreed to support an amended Plan that will provide Holders of Retail Borrower Deposit Claims with (a) the option to repay their principal balance of their loan [...] in exchange for an equivalent amount of cryptocurrency (which could lead to tax benefits for such Holders as compared to the Setoff Treatment) and (b) priority in electing a preference to exchange the NewCo Equity for Liquid Cryptocurrency at a 30% discount [...].&rdquo;</p>

What Comes After The Settlements&nbsp;
<p>Celsius is hoping to return user assets by the end of the year. The reorganization plan involves a partial return of crypto assets deposited on the platform. As compensation for the assets not returned, customers will receive shares of the new entity, which will be managed by a group of investors led by the founder of TechCrunch, Michael Arrington. The new firm will oversee the bankrupt crypto lender&rsquo;s mining business and illiquid assets.&nbsp;</p>
SEC Action Against Celsius&nbsp;
<p>Despite the developments, Celsius is not out of the woods yet, with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filing a lawsuit against the company and its CEO, Alex Mahshinsky, earlier this month. The SEC accused Mahshinsky and other Celsius executives of raising billions of dollars through fraudulent and unregistered offers and selling crypto asset securities. Additionally, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has also announced action against Mashinsky, issuing a fine of over $4.5 billion for squandering user assets and duping users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Celsius had filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in July 2022 after halting all withdrawals following the collapse of the Terra ecosystem and the resulting market carnage. Mashinsky, the former CEO, was arrested under criminal and civil charges and under charges of intending to manipulate the markets. However, he has pleaded not guilty to all charges.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network has reached two crucial settlements to end its bankruptcy proceedings and clear a path for the return of customer assets, revealed court filings.</p>
<p>Any responses or objections to the settlements must be submitted in court by the 3rd of August.&nbsp;</p>
A Resolution In Sight&nbsp;
<p>Celsius Network filed for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy in 2022, and customers have been waiting in anticipation of the outcome of its bankruptcy proceedings. While the settlements that will allow the bankrupt crypto lender to return customer assets have been reached, they still have to be analyzed by Judge Martin Glenn at a hearing scheduled for the 10th of August. If agreed, the settlements will allow Celsius to conclude bankruptcy proceedings and see the long-awaited return of customer assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, there is also a confirmation hearing on Celsius&rsquo; reorganization plan that has been scheduled for October. This means customers could begin to see the disbursements of their crypto and assets before the end of the year. Lawyers representing Celsius Network have argued that customers are owed no more than the initially deposited amount. However, users have filed several claims seeking additional damages for alleged misconduct by the firm&rsquo;s former management.&nbsp;</p>
Unpacking The Settlements&nbsp;
<p>The first settlement addresses several claims related to fraud and misrepresentation allegedly committed by the previous Celsius management. Under the agreement, Celsius has committed to increase customer recoveries by 5%. Those account holders who do not want to participate in the settlement can opt-out and pursue individual claims against Celsius. Those who wish to remain part of the settlement will be eligible to receive a claim amount equivalent to 105% of their scheduled claim. This would also override any Proof of Claims filed earlier.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Any eligible Account Holder who does not opt out of the settlement will receive a claim in the amount of 105% of their scheduled claim, which will supersede and extinguish any related Proofs of Claim filed by such Account Holder. &ldquo;</p>

<p>The second settlement addresses claims by customers that had funds locked in Celsius&rsquo; interest-bearing Earn program. Under this agreement, Celsius customers that borrowed crypto can receive a portion of their funds in the form of crypto assets. Furthermore, customers of the Earn program will also be compensated with shares of the new company that would be created once the bankruptcy proceedings have concluded. With these resolutions, it is hoped that impacted customers of the bankrupt crypto lender can have some restitution, along with a stake in the company&rsquo;s future operations. Court documents state,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;[...] creditors have agreed to support an amended Plan that will provide Holders of Retail Borrower Deposit Claims with (a) the option to repay their principal balance of their loan [...] in exchange for an equivalent amount of cryptocurrency (which could lead to tax benefits for such Holders as compared to the Setoff Treatment) and (b) priority in electing a preference to exchange the NewCo Equity for Liquid Cryptocurrency at a 30% discount [...].&rdquo;</p>

What Comes After The Settlements&nbsp;
<p>Celsius is hoping to return user assets by the end of the year. The reorganization plan involves a partial return of crypto assets deposited on the platform. As compensation for the assets not returned, customers will receive shares of the new entity, which will be managed by a group of investors led by the founder of TechCrunch, Michael Arrington. The new firm will oversee the bankrupt crypto lender&rsquo;s mining business and illiquid assets.&nbsp;</p>
SEC Action Against Celsius&nbsp;
<p>Despite the developments, Celsius is not out of the woods yet, with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filing a lawsuit against the company and its CEO, Alex Mahshinsky, earlier this month. The SEC accused Mahshinsky and other Celsius executives of raising billions of dollars through fraudulent and unregistered offers and selling crypto asset securities. Additionally, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has also announced action against Mashinsky, issuing a fine of over $4.5 billion for squandering user assets and duping users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Celsius had filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in July 2022 after halting all withdrawals following the collapse of the Terra ecosystem and the resulting market carnage. Mashinsky, the former CEO, was arrested under criminal and civil charges and under charges of intending to manipulate the markets. However, he has pleaded not guilty to all charges.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Eyeing 29477 Pain - 24 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-eyeing-29477-pain-24-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-23-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-23-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-23-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-eyeing-29477-pain-24-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 29477 Increasingly at Risk:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 24 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to lack conviction early in the Asian session as the pair remained below the 30000 figure and orbited the 29922.87 area, a downside price objective associated with recent selling pressure around the 30421 and 30281 levels.&nbsp; The 29477.92 area remains highly at risk of being absorbed by selling pressure as BTC/USD has twice tested this previous upside price objective after trading as high as the 31862.21 level.&nbsp; Related previous price objectives that are technically significant include the 28937, 28845, 28213, 28137, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives include the 29403, 29089, 28775, 28386, and 27757 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30011.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29884.81.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 29477 Increasingly at Risk:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 24 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to lack conviction early in the Asian session as the pair remained below the 30000 figure and orbited the 29922.87 area, a downside price objective associated with recent selling pressure around the 30421 and 30281 levels.&nbsp; The 29477.92 area remains highly at risk of being absorbed by selling pressure as BTC/USD has twice tested this previous upside price objective after trading as high as the 31862.21 level.&nbsp; Related previous price objectives that are technically significant include the 28937, 28845, 28213, 28137, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives include the 29403, 29089, 28775, 28386, and 27757 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30011.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29884.81.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: UK Rejects Treasury’s Proposal And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-uk-rejects-treasury-proposal-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 14:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-uk-rejects-treasury-proposal-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The UK&rsquo;s HM Treasury has officially rejected the House of Commons Treasury Committee&rsquo;s recent recommendation to regulate crypto trading not as financial assets but as gambling instruments. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Elon Musk&rsquo;s Tesla has continued to hodl its BTC reserves for the fourth consecutive quarter after being forced to divest 75% of its reserves in 2022 Q2.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After hitting the range bottom, BTC looks to be heading higher once more, with the bulls looking to test the $31,000 to $32,000 major resistance again.&nbsp;</p>
Ethereum
<p>In the midst of a rebounding crypto market, Vitalik Buterin has hinted at a forthcoming upgrade to the Ethereum network, which could potentially reduce costs by a factor of 100.</p>
DeFi
<p>DeFi protocol Conic Finance revealed that it had suffered an exploit, with the attacker draining over 1700 ETH worth $3.6 million from one of its Omnipools.</p>
<p>Uniswap founder Hayden Adam&rsquo;s Twitter account suffered a breach, with hackers sending out several tweets leading users to scam websites and phishing links.</p>
<p>Leading DEX platform Spectrum Finance has revealed its strategic collaboration with Cardano, the innovative smart contract platform.</p>
<p>Axelar has launched the Interchain Token Service, a solution designed to enhance the interoperability of ERC-20 tokens across all EVM-compatible chains.</p>
Altcoins
<p>Solana Labs has announced the rollout of the Solang compiler that will help EVM developers transition to the Solana ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto world eagerly awaits upcoming Litecoin's third halving event, which is expected to happen on August 2, 2023, once the 2,520,000th block is mined.&nbsp;</p>
Technology&nbsp;
<p>Crypto experts have raised questions on central bank digital currencies like where are all the mainstream media articles or televised debates on the advantages or disadvantages of implementing CBDCs nationwide.</p>
<p>Worldcoin has completed its migration to the Optimism ecosystem, with critical components such as the World ID and World App technology stack already migrated to the OP mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Starknet has disclosed the initiation of "appchains," a framework designed to enable developers to construct several application-specific blockchains within the Starknet ecosystem.</p>
Business
<p>The recently uncovered personal diaries of Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison could be used as key evidence in the upcoming trial of FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Venture capital firms Coinfund and Polychain Capital have successfully raised a total of $350 million in their latest fundraising rounds, showcasing returning confidence in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>American investor Cathie Wood&rsquo;s ARK Invest sold another $50.5 million worth of Coinbase shares to cash in on the recent crypto market rally.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance has abruptly ended its five-year partnership with the Argentine Football Association (AFA) after only one year.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>A bipartisan group of United States Senators has introduced the CANSEE Act to regulate DeFi platforms in order to curb money laundering and other financial transgressions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The UK government rejected a recent House of Commons Treasury Committee proposal, which suggested that retail crypto trading be regulated like gambling instruments.</p>
<p>In the face of legal turbulence surrounding its co-founder, Do Kwon, blockchain firm Terraform Labs has appointed a new CEO.</p>
<p>Myanmar&rsquo;s National Unity Government (NUG), a shadow government opposing the current military rule, is set to launch a crypto neobank operating on the Polygon blockchain network.</p>
<p>Enforcement authorities in China&rsquo;s northern province of Shanxi have uncovered an alleged USDT money laundering scheme amounting to over $55 million.</p>
<p>Third largest French bank, Societe Generale, has become the first bank to procure a licence to provide trading and custody of cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) underscored its views that crypto requires &ldquo;comprehensive policies to safeguard economies and investors.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The founder and former CEO of the now-defunct Thodex crypto exchange, Faruk Fateh Ozer, has received a seven-month prison sentence after he failed to submit relevant documents requested during the trial.</p>
<p>Representative Ritchie Torres becomes the latest US lawmaker to level criticism against the SEC and its Chairman Gary Gensler&rsquo;s position on crypto.</p>
<p>The clock has started ticking for the SEC to approve or reject BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong, is set to hold a private meeting with House Democrats on Wednesday, according to Democratic aides familiar with the agenda.</p>
<p>US Judge Sarah Netburn has ordered the SEC and Ripple to agree to possible settlement dates should both parties believe them to be constructive at this stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On Monday, the Financial Stability Board published its recommendations for a global regulatory framework for crypto-assets to &ldquo;promote the comprehensiveness and international consistency of regulatory and supervisory approaches.&rdquo;</p>
NFT
<p>Proof Collective is trying to rekindle interest in its Moonbirds NFTs with a brand new 20,000-piece Mythics collection, released almost a year after its initial mention in August 2022.</p>
<p>Staking protocol EtherFi has called out the OpenSea marketplace for its decision to suspend the trading of the former&rsquo;s EtherFan NFT collection last week.&nbsp;</p>
Web3
<p>Andreessen Horowitz partner Sriram Krishnan expressed confidence that Web3 has the potential to remedy the issues plaguing current Web2-based social media platforms.</p>
<p>The developers behind Polygon Labs have proposed changes to their governance system that are integral to their forthcoming Polygon 2.0 roadmap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The potential of AR games has yet to be fully realized, but developers have already created lots of highly original apps to enhance our experiences in the physical world.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The UK&rsquo;s HM Treasury has officially rejected the House of Commons Treasury Committee&rsquo;s recent recommendation to regulate crypto trading not as financial assets but as gambling instruments. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Elon Musk&rsquo;s Tesla has continued to hodl its BTC reserves for the fourth consecutive quarter after being forced to divest 75% of its reserves in 2022 Q2.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After hitting the range bottom, BTC looks to be heading higher once more, with the bulls looking to test the $31,000 to $32,000 major resistance again.&nbsp;</p>
Ethereum
<p>In the midst of a rebounding crypto market, Vitalik Buterin has hinted at a forthcoming upgrade to the Ethereum network, which could potentially reduce costs by a factor of 100.</p>
DeFi
<p>DeFi protocol Conic Finance revealed that it had suffered an exploit, with the attacker draining over 1700 ETH worth $3.6 million from one of its Omnipools.</p>
<p>Uniswap founder Hayden Adam&rsquo;s Twitter account suffered a breach, with hackers sending out several tweets leading users to scam websites and phishing links.</p>
<p>Leading DEX platform Spectrum Finance has revealed its strategic collaboration with Cardano, the innovative smart contract platform.</p>
<p>Axelar has launched the Interchain Token Service, a solution designed to enhance the interoperability of ERC-20 tokens across all EVM-compatible chains.</p>
Altcoins
<p>Solana Labs has announced the rollout of the Solang compiler that will help EVM developers transition to the Solana ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto world eagerly awaits upcoming Litecoin's third halving event, which is expected to happen on August 2, 2023, once the 2,520,000th block is mined.&nbsp;</p>
Technology&nbsp;
<p>Crypto experts have raised questions on central bank digital currencies like where are all the mainstream media articles or televised debates on the advantages or disadvantages of implementing CBDCs nationwide.</p>
<p>Worldcoin has completed its migration to the Optimism ecosystem, with critical components such as the World ID and World App technology stack already migrated to the OP mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Starknet has disclosed the initiation of "appchains," a framework designed to enable developers to construct several application-specific blockchains within the Starknet ecosystem.</p>
Business
<p>The recently uncovered personal diaries of Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison could be used as key evidence in the upcoming trial of FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Venture capital firms Coinfund and Polychain Capital have successfully raised a total of $350 million in their latest fundraising rounds, showcasing returning confidence in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>American investor Cathie Wood&rsquo;s ARK Invest sold another $50.5 million worth of Coinbase shares to cash in on the recent crypto market rally.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance has abruptly ended its five-year partnership with the Argentine Football Association (AFA) after only one year.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>A bipartisan group of United States Senators has introduced the CANSEE Act to regulate DeFi platforms in order to curb money laundering and other financial transgressions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The UK government rejected a recent House of Commons Treasury Committee proposal, which suggested that retail crypto trading be regulated like gambling instruments.</p>
<p>In the face of legal turbulence surrounding its co-founder, Do Kwon, blockchain firm Terraform Labs has appointed a new CEO.</p>
<p>Myanmar&rsquo;s National Unity Government (NUG), a shadow government opposing the current military rule, is set to launch a crypto neobank operating on the Polygon blockchain network.</p>
<p>Enforcement authorities in China&rsquo;s northern province of Shanxi have uncovered an alleged USDT money laundering scheme amounting to over $55 million.</p>
<p>Third largest French bank, Societe Generale, has become the first bank to procure a licence to provide trading and custody of cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) underscored its views that crypto requires &ldquo;comprehensive policies to safeguard economies and investors.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The founder and former CEO of the now-defunct Thodex crypto exchange, Faruk Fateh Ozer, has received a seven-month prison sentence after he failed to submit relevant documents requested during the trial.</p>
<p>Representative Ritchie Torres becomes the latest US lawmaker to level criticism against the SEC and its Chairman Gary Gensler&rsquo;s position on crypto.</p>
<p>The clock has started ticking for the SEC to approve or reject BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong, is set to hold a private meeting with House Democrats on Wednesday, according to Democratic aides familiar with the agenda.</p>
<p>US Judge Sarah Netburn has ordered the SEC and Ripple to agree to possible settlement dates should both parties believe them to be constructive at this stage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On Monday, the Financial Stability Board published its recommendations for a global regulatory framework for crypto-assets to &ldquo;promote the comprehensiveness and international consistency of regulatory and supervisory approaches.&rdquo;</p>
NFT
<p>Proof Collective is trying to rekindle interest in its Moonbirds NFTs with a brand new 20,000-piece Mythics collection, released almost a year after its initial mention in August 2022.</p>
<p>Staking protocol EtherFi has called out the OpenSea marketplace for its decision to suspend the trading of the former&rsquo;s EtherFan NFT collection last week.&nbsp;</p>
Web3
<p>Andreessen Horowitz partner Sriram Krishnan expressed confidence that Web3 has the potential to remedy the issues plaguing current Web2-based social media platforms.</p>
<p>The developers behind Polygon Labs have proposed changes to their governance system that are integral to their forthcoming Polygon 2.0 roadmap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The potential of AR games has yet to be fully realized, but developers have already created lots of highly original apps to enhance our experiences in the physical world.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Reshaping Crypto Payments Future with LYOPAY]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/reshaping-crypto-payments-future-with-lyopay</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lyopay-1920x1080.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lyopay-1920x1080.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lyopay-1920x1080.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/reshaping-crypto-payments-future-with-lyopay</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The transformative power of cryptocurrency has taken the world by storm, evolving from a digital novelty into a trillion-dollar technology. As the number of crypto users exceeds 420 million worldwide, with a global ownership rate of 4.2%, the demand for user-friendly platforms has reached a tipping point. Enter LYO Ecosystem&mdash;a game-changing solution designed to make cryptocurrency accessible and intuitive for everyday use.</p>
<p>With LYOPAY at its core, a crypto payments application, LYO Ecosystem expands its offerings into a comprehensive suite of crypto services. The goal is simple yet ambitious: to provide users with easy access to crypto-friendly products that empower them to participate fully in the digital finance revolution.</p>
<p>The LYO Ecosystem takes a holistic approach to drive adoption and user acquisition through its payment solutions, while also offering revenue-generating trading and financial service solutions. LYOPAY, the licensed and regulated company behind the ecosystem, has already garnered impressive achievements, boasting over 201,000 active users and processing a monthly volume of USD 500 million as of December 2022.</p>
<p>Let's take a closer look at some of the notable products within the LYO Ecosystem:</p>
LYOPAY App - Empowering Cryptocurrency Payments
<p>The LYOPAY app serves as a bridge between fiat and cryptocurrencies, allowing users to store, exchange, buy, and sell digital assets effortlessly. With Euro (&euro;) accounts featuring IBAN for SEPA transfers, LYOPAY facilitates seamless integration between traditional currencies and the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
LYOTRADE - A Reliable Cryptocurrency Exchange
<p>LYOTRADE is a regulated cryptocurrency exchange that prioritizes compliance with Anti-Money Laundering (AML) and Know Your Customer (KYC) procedures. Offering both centralized and decentralized exchange services through a third-party provider, LYOTRADE empowers users with diverse trading strategies, crypto loans, staking options, and convenient purchase and selling of cryptocurrencies using card and wire transfer methods.</p>
LYOPAY Pro &ndash; Unleashing the Potential of Cryptocurrencies and Fiat Money
<p>LYOPAY Pro, a cutting-edge payment application, takes the integration of cryptocurrencies and fiat money to new heights. Designed with a global audience in mind, LYOPAY Pro offers integrated fiat currencies, card services, digital banking, a feature-rich crypto wallet, rewards, SEPA and SWIFT transfers, branded physical and virtual cards, bespoke travel and concierge services, and much more.</p>
LYOTECH LABS &ndash; Driving Innovation in the Crypto-Friendly Landscape
<p>LYOTECH LABS, a dynamic research and development company, plays a pivotal role in the LYO Ecosystem. Specializing in the creation of crypto-friendly software and hardware, LYOTECH LABS pushes the boundaries of fintech innovation, revolutionizing the industry with user-centric solutions that leave a lasting impact.</p>
<p>By offering a range of state-of-the-art products, LYO Ecosystem sets new standards in the cryptocurrency realm. With unparalleled ease and convenience, users can embrace the advantages of digital transactions and become active participants in the evolving world of finance.</p>
<p>To explore the full range of LYO Ecosystem products and stay connected with the latest updates, visit their official website and social media channels. Join the movement and be part of the crypto revolution that is reshaping the global financial landscape.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The transformative power of cryptocurrency has taken the world by storm, evolving from a digital novelty into a trillion-dollar technology. As the number of crypto users exceeds 420 million worldwide, with a global ownership rate of 4.2%, the demand for user-friendly platforms has reached a tipping point. Enter LYO Ecosystem&mdash;a game-changing solution designed to make cryptocurrency accessible and intuitive for everyday use.</p>
<p>With LYOPAY at its core, a crypto payments application, LYO Ecosystem expands its offerings into a comprehensive suite of crypto services. The goal is simple yet ambitious: to provide users with easy access to crypto-friendly products that empower them to participate fully in the digital finance revolution.</p>
<p>The LYO Ecosystem takes a holistic approach to drive adoption and user acquisition through its payment solutions, while also offering revenue-generating trading and financial service solutions. LYOPAY, the licensed and regulated company behind the ecosystem, has already garnered impressive achievements, boasting over 201,000 active users and processing a monthly volume of USD 500 million as of December 2022.</p>
<p>Let's take a closer look at some of the notable products within the LYO Ecosystem:</p>
LYOPAY App - Empowering Cryptocurrency Payments
<p>The LYOPAY app serves as a bridge between fiat and cryptocurrencies, allowing users to store, exchange, buy, and sell digital assets effortlessly. With Euro (&euro;) accounts featuring IBAN for SEPA transfers, LYOPAY facilitates seamless integration between traditional currencies and the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
LYOTRADE - A Reliable Cryptocurrency Exchange
<p>LYOTRADE is a regulated cryptocurrency exchange that prioritizes compliance with Anti-Money Laundering (AML) and Know Your Customer (KYC) procedures. Offering both centralized and decentralized exchange services through a third-party provider, LYOTRADE empowers users with diverse trading strategies, crypto loans, staking options, and convenient purchase and selling of cryptocurrencies using card and wire transfer methods.</p>
LYOPAY Pro &ndash; Unleashing the Potential of Cryptocurrencies and Fiat Money
<p>LYOPAY Pro, a cutting-edge payment application, takes the integration of cryptocurrencies and fiat money to new heights. Designed with a global audience in mind, LYOPAY Pro offers integrated fiat currencies, card services, digital banking, a feature-rich crypto wallet, rewards, SEPA and SWIFT transfers, branded physical and virtual cards, bespoke travel and concierge services, and much more.</p>
LYOTECH LABS &ndash; Driving Innovation in the Crypto-Friendly Landscape
<p>LYOTECH LABS, a dynamic research and development company, plays a pivotal role in the LYO Ecosystem. Specializing in the creation of crypto-friendly software and hardware, LYOTECH LABS pushes the boundaries of fintech innovation, revolutionizing the industry with user-centric solutions that leave a lasting impact.</p>
<p>By offering a range of state-of-the-art products, LYO Ecosystem sets new standards in the cryptocurrency realm. With unparalleled ease and convenience, users can embrace the advantages of digital transactions and become active participants in the evolving world of finance.</p>
<p>To explore the full range of LYO Ecosystem products and stay connected with the latest updates, visit their official website and social media channels. Join the movement and be part of the crypto revolution that is reshaping the global financial landscape.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
