<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Balaji Forfeits and Settles $1 Million Bitcoin Bet &#8211; But Stands By Hyperinflation Thesis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/balaji-forfeits-and-settles-1-million-bitcoin-bet-but-stands-by-hyperinflation-thesis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 02:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249010</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/photo_2023-04-28_14-02-21.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/photo_2023-04-28_14-02-21.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Balaji explained on Twitter that he decided to “burn a million to tell you they’re printing trillions."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Former Coinbase CTO Balaji Srinivasan has withdrawn from his notorious $1 million Bitcoin bet, in which he gambled $1 million in USDC on the price of Bitcoin reaching $1 million. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, the investor stands by his thesis that the US dollar is on the road to hyperinflation, stressing that the economy will not experience the “soft landing” promised by Federal Reserve chairman Jerome Powell. </span></p>
<h2>Burning a Million Dollars</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1653451860488130565" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, Balaji announced that he had mutually agreed to settle his uber-bullish Bitcoin price bet upfront. He provided on-chain evidence of three $500,000 payments, including one to Medlock (the counterparty of the bet), another to charity organization Give Directly, and another to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/another-bitcoin-core-maintainer-steps-down-after-7-years/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Core development</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">That’s 50% more than the former exec had to commit – and comes 46 days ahead of schedule. Speaking at Consensus 2023 last week, he had </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/50-days-remaining-balaji-reflects-on-the-likelihood-of-his-1-million-bitcoin-forecast-consensus-2023-live/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">assigned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a roughly 10% probability to his prediction of financial calamity actually coming true within that time. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The reason I did this was because I do believe in the public good, but unfortunately we can&#8217;t rely on the public sector anymore to tell us when something&#8217;s wrong,” wrote Balaji. “So I spent my own money to send a provably costly signal that there’s something wrong with the economy.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an attached video, the investor explained that financial turmoil can happen fast – and without warning from regulators or the government. For example, Ben Bernanke said the economy might be in for a “mild recession” in April 2008, only five months before the great financial crisis officially began. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Likewise, it only took the Federal Reserve two days to inject $300 billion into the economy following Silicon Valley Bank’s collapse, and two weeks for $500 billion to flow out of commercial bank deposits into money market funds. </span></p>
<h2>The Economy is Breaking</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Balaji, multiple areas of the economy are already bordering on breaking. The US Debt ceiling is fast approaching, most US banks are now near insolvency, and the assets held by failed banks are now comparable to 2008 in value. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Furthermore, bonds suffered their worst year ever in 2022, which have been largely bought by banks and insurance companies. Student loan debt and credit card debt are also at all-time highs, amounting to $180 billion and $960 billion respectively. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Balaji also believes that countries are “de-dollarizing” at a rapid pace, echoing views </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/global-de-dollarization-and-the-role-of-bitcoin-arthur-hayes/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">published</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes last month that the dollar could be on track to lose its status as the global reserve currency.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“If you believe there’s a high probability of these simultaneous economic crises causing a massive print in 90 days, 900 days, or even 90 months — then you expect some kind of default, and you expect fiat crisis,” wrote Balaji on his </span><a href="https://balajis.com/fiat/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">site</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. “And you’ll want to be prepared, whatever that means to you.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/balaji-forfeits-and-settles-1-million-bitcoin-bet-but-stands-by-hyperinflation-thesis/" rel="nofollow">Balaji Forfeits and Settles $1 Million Bitcoin Bet &#8211; But Stands By Hyperinflation Thesis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden Administration Pushes Congress to Pass 30% Tax on Bitcoin Mining</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249001</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bitcoinmining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bitcoinmining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The White House views the Bitcoin mining industry as environmentally harmful and limited in economic benefit. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The White House is attempting to persuade Congress to pass a 30% climate change tax on cryptocurrency miners as part of its next federal budget.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The change, titled the Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) excise tax, is designed to encourage mining firms to start taking better account of their so-called ‘societal harms’, including higher energy prices and greenhouse gas emissions. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">Taxing Bitcoin Miners</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As reported by </span><a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/biden-proposes-30-climate-change-tax-on-cryptocurrency-mining-120033242.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Yahoo News</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, the president’s Council of Economic Advisors plans to publish a blog post to the White House’s website on Tuesday justifying the excise tax as an “example of the Administration’s efforts to fight climate change and reduce energy prices.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Currently, cryptomining firms do not have to pay for the full cost they impose on others, in the form of local environmental pollution, higher energy prices, and the impacts of increased greenhouse gas emissions on the climate,” the CEA stated in its post. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The tax would be phased in over 3 years, starting at 10% in the first year before rising to 20% and eventually 30% in the following two years. Over 10 years, it would generate an estimated $3.5 billion in revenue. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A CEA economist who spoke with Yahoo added that the economic benefits of crypto mining remain “unclear,” while concerns still loom about the industry’s financial stability and environmental risks. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">Critics of the Tax</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin mining has become unpopular with many left-wing politicians spanning numerous developed countries due to its suspected contributions to climate change through its vast energy consumption. In April 2022, a group of Democrat politicians including progressives like Alexandria Ocasio Cortez signed a letter to the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) to investigate whether mining firms were violating environmental statutes. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoiners </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-community-sends-letter-to-epa-debunking-proof-of-work-fud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">responded</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with their own letter to the agency the following month, debunking numerous misconceptions about the harms of Bitcoin mining. The community has generally been strictly opposed to attempts to regulate the mining industry or to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/greenpeace-blasts-bitcoin-with-artwork-depicting-environmental-damage-bitcoiners-love-it/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">change Bitcoin’s code</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> so as to remove mining from its operations. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Critics of Biden’s proposed excise tax believe the fee arbitrarily targets specific forms of energy consumption. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This puts a clear line in the sand that they do not like the industry. They are looking for ways to hamstring it,” Tom Mapes, director of energy policy at the Chamber of Digital Commerce, told Yahoo News. “This is just a way to go after the industry which they do not support.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" rel="nofollow">Biden Administration Pushes Congress to Pass 30% Tax on Bitcoin Mining</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sotheby’s Auction House Launches Marketplace for Secondary NFT Sales</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sothebys-auction-house-launches-marketplace-for-secondary-nft-sales/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 23:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248838</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Sotheby.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Sotheby.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[World-renowned auction house Sotheby’s has taken another step in the digital art world with the launch of its secondary NFT marketplace.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On May 1, the company announced an addition to Sotheby’s Metaverse in the form of a “dynamic destination to collect, buy, and sell remarkable digital works.”</p>
<p>The blockchain-based NFT marketplace will be primarily for secondary sales of digital art. According to the announcement, the marketplace will feature a rotating, curated selection of leading artists hand-picked by Sotheby’s specialists.</p>
<p>They will provide “expert guidance and context for each work, from thematic presentations to artist spotlights, for an easy-to-navigate experience designed for discovery.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The next evolution of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SothebysMetaverse?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#SothebysMetaverse</a> is here! The most trusted and dynamic destination to collect, buy and sell remarkable digital works.</p>
<p>Explore: <a href="https://t.co/hZvYIkO3xx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/hZvYIkO3xx</a> <a href="https://t.co/dCkaCKlXVm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/dCkaCKlXVm</a></p>
<p>— Sotheby&#8217;s Metaverse (@Sothebysverse) <a href="https://twitter.com/Sothebysverse/status/1653049950786265094?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Sotheby’s Secondary Market</h2>
<p>Sotheby’s launched the Metaverse platform in 2021 for its art auctions but has now expanded it to handle resales. It supports NFTs minted on Ethereum and layer-2 scaling network Polygon.</p>
<p>Automated smart contracts will govern the secondary sales process allowing buyers and sellers to send and receive payments in ETH or MATIC, the Polygon native token. It stated that there is a 2.5% fee for sellers.</p>
<p>The Sotheby’s marketplace will be a little more exclusive than industry leader OpenSea as only its experts will select the artwork. The featured artists will be changed every few months, it noted, adding that the initial selection will include renowned digital artists such as Tyler Hobbs, Claire Silver, Hackatao, Sam Spratt, and Refik Anadol.</p>
<p>The platform is powered by NFT commerce suite Mojito developed by Web3 venture studio Serotonin. Sotheby’s joined the $20 million <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sothebys-dives-deeper-into-crypto-by-investing-20m-in-the-nft-studio-mojito/" data-wpel-link="internal">investment round</a> for Mojito in November 2021.</p>
<p>Sotheby’s Vice President and Head of NFTs and Digital Art, Michael Bouhanna, said the move was an important step forward for the auction house in its evolution within the Web3 space.</p>
<p>In January, the auction house said it would <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sothebys-to-accept-crypto-for-a-555-carat-black-diamond-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">accept crypto</a> in an auction for a rare black diamond.</p>
<h2>NFT Markets Remain Flat</h2>
<p>NFT markets have declined this year, with trading volumes and prices plummeting. As <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/capitulation-nft-trading-volumes-and-prices-plummet-in-the-last-30-days/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, just six of the top 20 NFT collections by market capitalization recorded increased trading volumes over the past month.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Nonfungible market <a href="https://nonfungible.com/market-tracker" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tracker</a> reports that the number of daily sales has plunged from around 40,000 in October to roughly 5,000 in mid-April. However, the platform has stopped recording NFT metrics since the middle of last month.</p>
<p>Additionally, Cryptoslam <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/nftglobal" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reported</a> that there have been more sellers than buyers over the past couple of weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sothebys-auction-house-launches-marketplace-for-secondary-nft-sales/" rel="nofollow">Sotheby’s Auction House Launches Marketplace for Secondary NFT Sales</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto&#8217;s Shark Tank? CoinMarketCap Unveils &#8216;Killer Whales&#8217; Show</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptos-shark-tank-coinmarketcap-unveils-killer-whales-show/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 21:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248804</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TV_Show.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TV_Show.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CoinMarketCap is all set to release the world's first globally broadcasted Web3 television show.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Move over &#8220;Shark Tank,&#8221; CoinMarketCap has teamed up with a Web3 entertainment company called Hello Labs &#8211; founded by multi-award-winning Hollywood director and producer Paul Caslin &#8211; to release a competition show designed to entertain and educate audiences across the world on the intricacies and evolving tech of the Web3 space.</p>
<p>The new reality show is expected to capture the elements of both Web3 as well as entertainment.</p>
<h2>Killer Whales</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/644cf3db4bebb711c962723e/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, the upcoming show aims to cater to the growing interest of billions of Web3 users by providing a global platform for projects, both big and small, within the cryptocurrency and NFT space.</p>
<p>Dubbed &#8220;Killer Whale,&#8221; the reality show is produced by HELLO Labs and other unannounced co-producers. It closely resembles the format of Shark Tank, wherein the contestants will pitch their crypto and NFT projects to a panel of industry experts and judges referred to as &#8220;Whales&#8221; in the hopes of receiving the mentorship needed to take them to the next level.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Official KILLER WHALES trailer. Coming 2023. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/HELLOLabs?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#HELLOLabs</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Entertainment?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Entertainment</a> <a href="https://t.co/B7X9g2rcS0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/B7X9g2rcS0</a></p>
<p>— HELLO Labs (@thehellolabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/thehellolabs/status/1593472789410783232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">November 18, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The pitches will either receive &#8220;Swim&#8221; or &#8220;Sink&#8221; votes. The goal is to amass as many votes as possible from the judges &#8220;to stand the chance of topping the series leaderboard and being crowned the series winner,&#8221; the announcement read.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We want to provide a voice through our platform for the entire Web3 community when producing the show, so we have introduced a way for communities to vote for their favorite projects and NFTs and show their support. With the help of our judges, contestants will have the opportunity to bring their vision to life and make a significant impact in the world of cryptocurrency.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Interested candidates can submit their applications starting from May 2nd to Hello.one and CoinMarketCap. The applications will be reviewed by professional representations of industry experts. The selected projects will go through several rounds of interviews in Los Angeles. Killer Whales will begin filming in June. It will subsequently be released across major streaming services.</p>
<h2>Web3 Shows</h2>
<p>Technologies in Web3 are making some of the most exciting and transformative developments in the world today. In mid-2021, the producers of &#8220;Entourage&#8221; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hodl-will-be-the-name-of-the-first-crypto-based-tv-show-directed-by-the-producer-of-entourage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">came up</a> with the first scripted TV show about digital assets called &#8220;Hold On for Dear Life.&#8221;</p>
<p>More recently, Web3 story studio Toonstar today <a href="https://www.animationmagazine.net/2023/04/toonstar-launches-animated-comedy-space-junk-from-jon-heder-tony-cavalero-dominic-russo/#:~:text=Web3%20story%20studio%20Toonstar%20today,at%20Consensus%202023%20on%20Thursday." target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> the release of its new adult-animated series, Space Junk, marking its third original Web3 series release. Besides, &#8220;Krapopolis,&#8221; the Web3 animated TV series from &#8220;Rick and Morty&#8221; co-creator Dan Harmon is also slated for a release this year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptos-shark-tank-coinmarketcap-unveils-killer-whales-show/" rel="nofollow">Crypto&#8217;s Shark Tank? CoinMarketCap Unveils &#8216;Killer Whales&#8217; Show</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>From &#8216;Very Good Bank&#8217; to &#8216;Got Nothing for Shareholders:&#8217; Jim Cramer&#8217;s Dubious Advice for First Republic</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/from-very-good-bank-to-got-nothing-for-shareholders-jim-cramers-dubious-advice-for-first-republic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248802</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Jim_Cramer5.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Jim_Cramer5.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[From the crypto market to the collapsed Silicon Valley Bank, Cramer has given another wrong prediction about First Republic Bank.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Cramer, the host of CNBC&#8217;s Mad Money, has once again missed the mark with another one of his predictions for the stock and equity markets.</p>
<p>Less than two months after calling the embattled First Republic Bank a &#8220;very good bank,&#8221; the TV personality has turned around to tell the company&#8217;s shareholders that there is nothing for them as US authorities have taken it into receivership.</p>
<h2>A &#8220;Very Good Bank&#8221; Turned Sour</h2>
<p>First Republic Bank was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jpmorgan-to-acquire-first-republic-bank-after-californian-financial-regulators-seizure/" data-wpel-link="internal">taken </a>over by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. (FDIC) and the California Department of Financial Protection and Innovation on Monday after a week full of financial issues.</p>
<p>The bank&#8217;s troubles started in March when Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) had significant outflows. On March 10, when US authorities shut down SVB. Cramer tweeted that First Republic was the new focus, commending the bank.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">FRC is new focus&#8230; very good bank</p>
<p>— Jim Cramer (@jimcramer) <a href="https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1634197816359747585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">March 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>On the contrary, the financial institution had severe liquidity issues, forcing it to reduce its borrowings and suspend dividend payments to stockholders.</p>
<p>Within the following week, 11 major US banks had to come together to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/big-banks-help-stabilize-first-republic-with-30-billion-cash-injection/" data-wpel-link="internal">infuse</a> $30 billion in cash into First Republic to curb the impending banking crisis. Unfortunately, the company&#8217;s woes <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/deepening-crisis-at-first-republic-prompts-urgent-rescue-talks-what-does-it-mean-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">worsened</a> as depositors withdrew more than $100 billion by the end of the last quarter.</p>
<p>US authorities stepped in over the weekend to protect depositors and worked out a purchase agreement with JPMorgan Chase Bank. First Republic&#8217;s stock has fallen from levels above $200 to $2.98. When writing, the stock was trading at $3.51, a 71% decline from its price a week ago.</p>
<h2>Inverse Cramer Strikes Again</h2>
<p>While First Republic&#8217;s shares tumbled last week, Cramer released statements that contradicted his previous stance on the bank&#8217;s future. On one occasion, he praised his colleague David Faber, a financial journalist, for saying that the bank would have a hard time surviving the weekend.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Kudos to my colleague <a href="https://twitter.com/davidfaber?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@davidfaber</a> for saying that First Republic would have a hard time surviving the weekend when there was massive buying in the stock in the first half hour of trading. What the heck? Other outlets were saying the opposite with no real evidence</p>
<p>— Jim Cramer (@jimcramer) <a href="https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1652118622259621889?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>A few hours after the FDIC announced the sale of First Republic, Cramer <a href="https://twitter.com/jimcramer/status/1652960254072705024?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">congratulated</a> JPMorgan for their purchase and told the former&#8217;s shareholders that they had nothing left.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that Cramer&#8217;s controversial stance on the future of stocks has become a norm such that investors now bet against his predictions in a movement tagged &#8220;Inverse Cramer.&#8221; The TV personality made <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jim-cramer-advised-people-to-buy-silicon-valley-bank-stock-a-month-before-its-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">similar moves</a> with SVB a month before its collapse. The crypto market has also had its fair share of the CNBC host&#8217;s controversy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/from-very-good-bank-to-got-nothing-for-shareholders-jim-cramers-dubious-advice-for-first-republic/" rel="nofollow">From &#8216;Very Good Bank&#8217; to &#8216;Got Nothing for Shareholders:&#8217; Jim Cramer&#8217;s Dubious Advice for First Republic</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Multiple Bank Stocks Slide While Bitcoin Pumps After First Republic Failure</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-slide-while-bitcoin-pumps-after-first-republic-failure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248973</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PacWest, Western Alliance,  and other banks are dropping at the fastest rate since Silicon Valley Bank’s closure. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Another wave of banking fear swept the markets on Tuesday as stocks for PacWest, Western Alliance, and other financial institutions slid over 20% on the day. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This comes shortly after California financial watchdogs took control of First Republic Bank on Monday, of which 84 branches will reopen under JP Morgan Chase.</span></p>
<h2>Another Bank Stock Selloff</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The California-based PacWest Bancorp (PACW) saw its shares tank from $8.90 at 9:30 am ET on Monday down to just $5.50 by 11:10 am. It has since slightly recovered to $6.15 at writing time, representing a 27% net daily drop. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, Western Alliance Bancorporation (WAL) headquartered in Arizona has dipped by a similar 20.53% on the day, from $36.18 to $28.96. Other banks including Zions (ZION), and Comerica (CMA) have suffered losses of roughly 10%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Each represents some of the largest daily losses posted by such banks since mid-March, following the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank and Signature Bank on March 10 and 12. Both Western Alliance and First Republic </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-stop-trading-amid-post-svb-volatility/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">collapsed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a whopping 76% at the time, while PacWest fell 47%, feeling little in the way of recovery since that time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Among the three, First Republic lost the largest share of its deposits in the first quarter at 41%. PacWest and Western Alliance lost 17% and 11% of deposits respectively, as customers sought the perceived safety of larger banks or higher yields within money market funds. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has previously given </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/treasury-secretary-prepared-to-take-additional-action-to-protect-bank-deposits/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">mixed signals</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> as to whether her department and the Federal Reserve would agree to backstop deposits at smaller banks, as it did with Silicon Valley Bank in March. She’s previously indicated that the government would only backstop banks deemed to present “systemic risk” to the banking system, prompting </span><a href="https://twitter.com/theemikehobart/status/1636494845144432643" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">criticism</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that this could invite depositors to flee smaller banks for the privileged and protected larger firms. </span></p>
<h2>Crypto Twitter Responds</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In response to their tanking stock prices, BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes </span><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoHayes/status/1653403052899192833" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">predicted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that PacWest will be the next bank to collapse and enter receivership under the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation. Hayes became extra bullish on Bitcoin when the Silicon Valley Bank collapsed in March, which prompted the asset to soar from $20,000 to $28,000 at the time. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">PacWest Bancorp <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PACW&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PACW</a> might be next on the chopping block for bank failures. Down big again today.</p>
<p>We are just waiting on Jim Cramer to tell us that it is strong bank in order to confirm the FDIC can move in. <a href="https://t.co/84aiOKKPB5" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/84aiOKKPB5</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Wall Street Silver (@WallStreetSilv) <a href="https://twitter.com/WallStreetSilv/status/1653433532071419912?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Likewise, Bitcoin experienced a modest pump on Tuesday from $28,000 to $28,566.</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-slide-while-bitcoin-pumps-after-first-republic-failure/" rel="nofollow">Multiple Bank Stocks Slide While Bitcoin Pumps After First Republic Failure</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Sees First Quarterly Profit in 2 Years Due to Bitcoin Bet</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-sees-first-quarterly-profit-in-2-years-due-to-bitcoin-bet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 17:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248877</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/MicroStrategy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/MicroStrategy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The profit is due to the appreciation of the value of Bitcoin over the past year, allowing MicroStrategy to claim tax benefits.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy, an Enterprise Business Intelligence (BI) platform that provides software, cloud computing, and other services to a wide array of clients, also happens to be one of the world’s largest Bitcoin holders, with approximately 140k Bitcoin in reserves.</p>
<h2>Out-competing by HODLing</h2>
<p>The decision to purchase Bitcoin in bulk was made by then-CEO Michael Saylor in 2020, citing concerns over inflation. According to him, simply HODLing BTC has given his firm an edge over rivals in the BI industry.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Ultimately, it’s not easy to see what better strategy there might be. We found by simply acquiring and holding Bitcoin we can outperform our peers in the enterprise software business. The regulatory environment for Bitcoin is improving. As capital flows out of the crypto industry, it flows into Bitcoin.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The above statement seems to be in contradiction with the recent developments in the crypto industry, with spokespeople for behemoths such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-slams-sec-says-gensler-led-agency-caused-untold-harm-to-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a>, Kraken, and private investors all lambasting the U.S. government and its agencies for attempting to enforce regulation through penalties instead of maintaining a discourse with the firms it seeks to regulate.</p>
<h2>In The Green After More Than 2 Years</h2>
<p>Despite the current uncertainty regarding the regulation of cryptocurrencies in the U.S. and elsewhere, Bitcoin has made a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategys-bitcoin-investment-in-the-green-as-btc-reclaims-30k/" data-wpel-link="internal">comeback</a> recently, spiking by over 70% over the past quarter.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-01/microstrategy-posts-profit-on-benefit-tied-to-bitcoin-holdings" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Bloomberg, this has allowed MicroStrategy to turn a profit this quarter. The company&#8217;s quarterly report indicated that it had a net income of $461 million in Q1, with firm shares trading at $31.79 at the time this article was written. Revenues were also up by 2.2% over the past quarter, reaching $121 million.</p>
<p>This development is partly due to tax benefits resulting from MicroStrategy’s Bitcoin stash. The company took advantage of an impairment charge – a <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/i/impairment.asp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">process</a> used by investors to write off depreciating assets – relating to its Bitcoin holdings that netted it a tax cut of $18.9 million over the past quarter.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy further consolidated its balance sheets by taking advantage of Bitcoin’s price appreciation to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-repaid-205m-loan-to-silvargate-and-bought-6500-more-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">repay</a> a loan from Silvergate at a 22% discount.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">MicroStrategy repaid its $205M Silvergate loan at a 22% discount. As of 3/23/23, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MSTR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$MSTR</a> acquired an additional ~6,455 bitcoins for ~$150M at an average of ~$23,238 per <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#bitcoin</a> &amp; held ~138,955 BTC acquired for ~$4.14B at an average of ~$29,817 per bitcoin. <a href="https://t.co/ALp9VLkTpt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/ALp9VLkTpt</a></p>
<p>— Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1640325496654143488?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">March 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<blockquote><p>“We strengthened our capital structure by reducing leverage by fully repaying our bitcoin-backed loan. We also continued to strategically manage our balance sheet through the addition of 7,500 bitcoin in the quarter.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Due in no small part to Saylor’s confidence in Bitcoin, his company is now reporting profits in a fiscal environment where most of his peers are faltering, as inflation and a possible looming recession dampen investors’ prospects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-sees-first-quarterly-profit-in-2-years-due-to-bitcoin-bet/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy Sees First Quarterly Profit in 2 Years Due to Bitcoin Bet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dubai Regulator Reprimands OPNX Founders for Conducting Unregulated Activity</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-regulator-reprimands-opnx-founders-for-conducting-unregulated-activity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248903</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Dubai.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Dubai.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The reprimand was also sent to OPNX founders Mark Lamb and Sudhu Arumugam as well as it Chief Executive Officer Leslie Lamb.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OPNX &#8211; the project created by the defunct hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) founders &#8211; has been controversial from the very start. The exchange has now been reprimanded for conducting unregulated activity.</p>
<p>Dubai&#8217;s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) has issued a written reprimand to five OPNX founders, including Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, for carrying out virtual asset exchange services on an unregulated basis in and from the Emirate of Dubai as well as engaging in marketing, promotion and/or advertisement of OPNX services and its native token (FLEX) without the necessary permits from the regulator.</p>
<h2>OPNX Under Dubai Regulator&#8217;s Scrutiny</h2>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://www.vara.ae/en/#0" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a>, VARA said it became aware of OPNX soliciting and collecting personal data from the public to participate in its new exchange. It further added that the platform had been engaged in marketing the exchange without setting up warranted restrictions for the residents of Dubai and the United Arab Emirates (UAE).</p>
<p>Upon investigation of OPNX, the authorities issued two cease-and-desist orders to the founders even before its launch. A week after the official rollout of OPNX, VARA alerted investors that the platform was unregulated.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;VARA notes that thereafter, certain restrictions regarding residents of Dubai/UAE were subsequently applied on the OPNX website. Such restrictions were, however, not applied comprehensively across all OPNX communication channels or promotional and marketing materials &#8211; that have consequently, remained accessible to UAE residents thereafter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The regulator is currently monitoring the situation and investigating OPNX&#8217;s activity to assess further corrective measures as a result of the &#8220;continued lack of satisfactory remedial action&#8221; by the operators of the crypto platform.</p>
<h2>Heated Argument With &#8220;Investors&#8221;</h2>
<p>Several community members have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arthur-hayes-zhu-su-ann-kyle-davies-led-opnx-received-funding-from-bahrain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">expressed</a> their frustration over the new project primarily because it was founded by the same people who started the now-failed crypto hedge fund 3AC. Last month, OPNX <a href="https://twitter.com/OPNX_Official/status/1649426185015685126" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">identified</a> its financial backers to be Susquehanna (SIG), Nascent, AppWorks, DRW, MIAX Group, Merchant Bank International, Token Bay Capital, and Tuwaiq Limited.</p>
<p>However, the supposed investors have denied participating in the platform&#8217;s funding round or having any association with it at all. Nascent was the first to clap back, denying any affiliation, followed by DRW Trading, Taiwan-based AppWorks, and Susquehanna.</p>
<p>The denials <a href="https://twitter.com/therealleslamb0/status/1649658325490094081" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">prompted</a> strongly worded statements from CEO Leslie Lamb, who accused the &#8220;investors&#8221; of engaging in ugly tactics.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-regulator-reprimands-opnx-founders-for-conducting-unregulated-activity/" rel="nofollow">Dubai Regulator Reprimands OPNX Founders for Conducting Unregulated Activity</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Officially Launches Platform for Non-US Institutional Investors in Bermuda: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248921</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase International Exchange is available to non-US institutional clients and allows the trading of BTC and ETH perpetual futures. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase announced the launch of a Bermuda-based marketplace that will serve non-US institutional users, according to a recent report. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company has been eyeing other countries to relocate recently due to the regulatory hurdles in America. CEO Brian Armstrong held discussions with the authorities of Britain in April, suggesting that the UK could also become an expansion target for Coinbase.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Disappointed in the US </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase &#8211; the only publicly listed crypto exchange &#8211; has recently been on a mission to roll out its operations outside the US because of the regulatory uncertainty that remains a concern in the country. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">obtained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> approval from the Bermuda Monetary Authority in April and displayed intentions to establish an offshore derivatives marketplace in the region in the following days.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to a recent press release <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/05/02/coinbase-sets-up-shop-in-bermuda-as-it-battles-sec-at-home/?sh=12b0af7c7c62" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">seen</a> by Forbes, Coinbase International Exchange is already on and is available to non-American institutional clients. They could trade bitcoin and ether perpetual futures while all transactions will be settled in USDC. The option allows users to speculate on the price movements of the biggest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization without actually owning them.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Coinbase assured it remains committed to the US, it </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-is-going-offshore-unless-the-us-changes-regulatory-stance-coinbase-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">outlined</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that other countries have recognized the potential of the industry and imposed pertinent rules on it. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We would like to see the US take a similar approach instead of regulation by enforcement which has led to a disappointing trend for crypto development in the US,&#8221; the firm added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CEO Armstrong considers the States a key market for the digital asset sector but believes the local regulatory chaos could push numerous crypto entities outside the region. Apart from Bermuda, Coinbase has set eyes on Europe and, more specifically, the United Kingdom.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Armstrong praised Britain for its approach and intention to create a welcoming crypto regulatory environment. He even </span><a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1648013189437595909" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">met</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1648013189437595909" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> </a>with Andrew Griffith – economic secretary to the UK Treasury and Member of Parliament &#8211; and said his organization is &#8220;excited&#8221; to keep investing in the area. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another crypto exchange that disclosed expansion plans outside the US is Gemini. The entity, run by the Winklevoss brothers, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">established</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a new engineering hub in Gurgaon, India. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase&#8217;s Issues in the US</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is the agency that causes many of the exchange&#8217;s problems in its homeland. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-stock-falls-21-following-sec-investigation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">launched</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an investigation in 2022, alleging that some of the digital currencies listed on the platform are unregistered securities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The watchdog doubled down in March this year, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-issues-wells-notice-against-coinbase-for-listing-unregistered-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">issuing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a Wells Notice against Coinbase. The enforcement action could be connected to the company&#8217;s Earn, Prime, and Wallet products. Armstrong seemed not worried about the charges, stating:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;While we understand that this is all part of the journey to reforming our financial system, we are right on the law, confident in the facts, and welcome the opportunity for Coinbase (and by extension the broader crypto community) to get before a court.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-compels-sec-to-respond-to-rulemaking-petition-in-new-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">took</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> legal action against the SEC last week, asking a federal judge to force the agency to answer a months-old petition about whether it would allow certain crypto regulations. Coinbase urged the regulator in 2022 to &#8220;propose and adopt rules to govern the regulation of securities that are offered and traded via digitally native methods, including potential rules to identify which digital assets are securities.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Officially Launches Platform for Non-US Institutional Investors in Bermuda: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tykhe Block Ventures Holds First Close of $30M Blockchain Growth Fund, Commits 25% into MENA Region</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tykhe-block-ventures-holds-first-close-of-30m-blockchain-growth-fund-commits-25-into-mena-region/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248929</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tykhe.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tykhe.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Tykhe Block Ventures, a USA-based Venture Capital firm, has announced the first close of its Blockchain Growth Fund. The first close was led by a clutch of UHNWIs and Family Offices operating in South-East Asia &#38; Middle East. The firm has also committed that approximately $10 Mn of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>Tykhe Block Ventures, a USA-based Venture Capital firm, has announced the first close of its Blockchain Growth Fund. The first close was led by a clutch of UHNWIs and Family Offices operating in South-East Asia &amp; Middle East. The firm has also committed that approximately $10 Mn of the fund will be allocated to invest in blockchain &amp; Web3 startups in the Middle East region. Tykhe is also in the process of setting up their Dubai office and aims to launch a $100 Mn fund later this year.</p>
<p>Tykhe Block Ventures was started in 2021 by Prashant Malik, one of the leading investors in SEA (early investor in multiple unicorns like Urbanclap, Shadowfax, OfBusiness, Coinswitch) and widely recognized as the creator of Apache Cassandra – the distributed database used by majority of technology enterprises globally. Prashant built Cassandra when he joined Facebook as one of the earliest employees – that was later open-sourced as Apache Cassandra.</p>
<blockquote><p>“My passion for the blockchain space started in 2016, as it drew a lot of parallels from Cassandra which is a peer-to-peer masterless database running on a voting mechanism similar to blockchain. In 2021, together with my partners, we launched a pilot blockchain fund which did considerably well. That gave us the belief to launch the $30 Mn Blockchain Growth Fund. Despite the softness in the market, we have seen great interest from investors who believe that blockchain is going to be the next big narrative in the technology space, like how social media was when I started building Facebook.” said Prashant.</p></blockquote>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;">As Sponsors, Prashant and other Investment Partners have committed $5 Mn into the fund. The fund managers bring together a combined 30+ years of core blockchain investing experience where they have invested in more than 80+ companies.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;">“Stellar teams building in blockchain space reach out to us to access not just venture capital, but also relationship capital. Given my experience building Cassandra, I am able to guide them on setting a scalable and secure architecture for DLT (distributed ledger technology).” quoted Prashant. Some of the recent investments done as part of the Blockchain Growth Fund comprise of Trust Machines, Fan Tiger, DWallet Labs (Odsy Network), NFTPerp, Convrse.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;">The blockchain space has been recently marred by implosions of companies like Celsius, FTX and in general a deep correction in cryptocurrency prices. However, Tykhe views these developments as a necessary and healthy correction. “All the players that went down were centralized entities and have no co-relation to the ethos of blockchain technology – which stands for decentralization. Thanks to our thesis of investment in pure decentralized networks, our portfolio companies have been doing reasonably well, despite the global downturn. Infact, we are probably one of the few funds in our space that has clocked high-double digit returns in the last year – when everyone else has seen a deep correction” spoke Ganesh, who leads the Investment Team.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;">The global Web3 market size reached $3.2 billion in 2021 and is expected to register a CAGR of 43.7% to reach $81.5 billion in 2030, according to Emergen Research published in June 2022. The Middle East, and specifically Dubai, is home to a number of blockchain and cryptocurrency startups and exchanges, making it a natural hub for the industry.</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;">About Company</span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b; font-size: 16px;">Tykhe Block Ventures is a leading investment firm based in the United States, specializing in early-stage ventures within the blockchain sector. The company focuses on investing in disruptive Web3 startups that utilize distributed ledger technology, digital assets, and their key enabling infrastructure. By partnering with startups operating in these areas, Tykheblock Ventures aims to capitalize on the billion-dollar opportunities that industry leaders such as Gartner, BCG, and Goldman Sachs predict will emerge in the coming years.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tykhe-block-ventures-holds-first-close-of-30m-blockchain-growth-fund-commits-25-into-mena-region/" rel="nofollow">Tykhe Block Ventures Holds First Close of $30M Blockchain Growth Fund, Commits 25% into MENA Region</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
