<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Kraken Co-founder Jesse Powell Voices Concerns About FTX 2.0</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/kraken-co-founder-jesse-powell-voices-concerns-about-ftx-20.htm</link><description>The revival plans of crypto exchange FTX have been met with skepticism from industry insiders, with Jesse Powell, co-founder of Kraken, raising concerns about the feasibility of FTX 2.0's aspirations. &lt;br /&gt;
In a series of tweets, Powell questioned the viability of reviving the defunct FTX exchange, highlighting various challenges that could impede its resurrection....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kraken-co-founder-jesse-powell-voices-concerns-about-ftx-20.htm"&gt;Read More: Kraken Co-founder Jesse Powell Voices Concerns About FTX 2.0&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/kraken-co-founder-jesse-powell-voices-concerns-about-ftx-20.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121396/321396/jesse-powell.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="110451"/></item><item><title>OG Cryptos to Buy Now That Pumped 5x or More in the 2017 Bull Run</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/og-cryptos-buy-now-that-pumped-5x-or-more-2017-bull-run-1.htm</link><description>Crypto was a completely different world back in 2017. &lt;br /&gt;
The market went parabolic, with bitcoin (BTC) gaining as much as 20x at its December 2017 highs versus its starting point for the year. &lt;br /&gt;
Other coins saw even grander gains. &lt;br /&gt;
While many coins and projects that were popular back then have fallen out of favor as of 2023, a few OG (“original gangster”) coins have stood the test of time and are still in the spotlight in 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/og-cryptos-buy-now-that-pumped-5x-or-more-2017-bull-run-1.htm"&gt;Read More: OG Cryptos to Buy Now That Pumped 5x or More in the 2017 Bull Run&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Ether</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>ETH</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>DOGE</category><category>XRP</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/og-cryptos-buy-now-that-pumped-5x-or-more-2017-bull-run-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121427/321510/coins-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6827508"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 2 August – XDC Network, Kaspa, Maker</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-august-xdc-network-kaspa-maker.htm</link><description>Major cryptocurrencies saw an increase in their prices in the final hours of trading yesterday, coinciding with the news of MicroStrategy Inc's financial recovery in Q2. &lt;br /&gt;
Considering this latest development of the business intelligence giant reporting a substantial improvement in its financial status, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-august-xdc-network-kaspa-maker.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 2 August – XDC Network, Kaspa, Maker&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>XDC Network</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Kaspa</category><category>Xrp20</category><category>Maker</category><category>Shibie</category><category>XDC</category><category>XDC price</category><category>Kas</category><category>KAS price</category><category>MKR</category><category>MKR price</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Memecoins</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>WSM</category><category>Crypto Whales</category><category>Crypto Whale</category><category>Ethereum blockchain</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-august-xdc-network-kaspa-maker.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121425/321498/bc2a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="339407"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Billionaire Michael Saylor Makes Another $14 Million BTC Purchase – Time to Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-billionaire-michael-saylor-makes-another-14-million-btc-purchase-time-buy-dip.htm</link><description>On August 1st, the value of the popular cryptocurrency, Bitcoin, exceeded $29,000 and briefly even surpassed $30,000. &lt;br /&gt;
This surge was fueled by an increase in trading volume, as traders who had lost confidence in BTC in recent weeks re-entered the market. &lt;br /&gt;
 As a result, trading activity soared to a six-week high. This renewed interest from investors could potentially impact Bitcoin's price and overall market sentiment....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-billionaire-michael-saylor-makes-another-14-million-btc-purchase-time-buy-dip.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Billionaire Michael Saylor Makes Another $14 Million BTC Purchase – Time to Buy the Dip?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-billionaire-michael-saylor-makes-another-14-million-btc-purchase-time-buy-dip.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121423/321493/2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="487724"/></item><item><title>Binance CEO CZ Explores Diversifying Stablecoin Strategy, Eyes Smaller Algorithmic Tokens</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-explores-diversifying-stablecoin-strategy-eyes-smaller-algorithmic-tokens.htm</link><description>During a Twitter "Ask Me Anything" (AMA) session on July 31, Binance CEO Changpeng "CZ" Zhao expressed his intention to introduce smaller algorithmic Stablecoins to the market for investors to have alternatives to the existing global Stablecoin giants. &lt;br /&gt;
In the session, CZ highlighted concerns associated with large Stablecoins like Tether and Binance USD. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-explores-diversifying-stablecoin-strategy-eyes-smaller-algorithmic-tokens.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance CEO CZ Explores Diversifying Stablecoin Strategy, Eyes Smaller Algorithmic Tokens&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>stablecoins</category><category>Tether</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-explores-diversifying-stablecoin-strategy-eyes-smaller-algorithmic-tokens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121422/321495/661c297e-01b8-4d23-b860-4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="105502"/></item><item><title>Crypto Billionaire Justin Sun and Partners Step in to Aid DeFi Giant Curve Amid Crisis – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-sun-partners-step-aid-defi-giant-curve-amid-crisis-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Tron founder and wealthy crypto investor Justin Sun has stepped up to save decentralized exchange (DEX) protocol Curve Finance from a potential bad debt crisis....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-sun-partners-step-aid-defi-giant-curve-amid-crisis-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Billionaire Justin Sun and Partners Step in to Aid DeFi Giant Curve Amid Crisis – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-sun-partners-step-aid-defi-giant-curve-amid-crisis-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121424/321492/justin-sun-media-library-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="71205"/></item><item><title>AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Secures $3.2 Million in Funding – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-secures-32-million-funding-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>Crypto signals are like road signs in the digital currency highway. They guide investors by suggesting when to buy or sell a cryptocurrency. Given the unpredictable nature of crypto markets, these signals are essential tools for traders. &lt;br /&gt;
However, while some platforms offer reliable crypto signals, others are involved in dubious activities, causing significant financial losses for unsuspecting investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-secures-32-million-funding-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Secures $3.2 Million in Funding – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Crypto Signals</category><category>Crypto Presales</category><category>Presales</category><category>Best Presales</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-secures-32-million-funding-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121417/321433/f1-teldxwaauld5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="668481"/></item><item><title>FTX Proposes Rebooting Exchange for Offshore Customers in Bankruptcy Plan, FTT Token Holders Left Empty-Handed</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-proposes-rebooting-exchange-for-offshore-customers-in-bankruptcy-plan-ftt-token-holders-left-empty-handed.htm</link><description>The bankrupt crypto exchange FTX’s new management has proposed to reboot the exchange for offshore customers only, but holders of the FTT token would not benefit from the plan. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent filing, FTX’s management proposed to group the various creditors into different classes as a way for them to receive the claims they are entitled to....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-proposes-rebooting-exchange-for-offshore-customers-in-bankruptcy-plan-ftt-token-holders-left-empty-handed.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Proposes Rebooting Exchange for Offshore Customers in Bankruptcy Plan, FTT Token Holders Left Empty-Handed&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>FTT</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-proposes-rebooting-exchange-for-offshore-customers-in-bankruptcy-plan-ftt-token-holders-left-empty-handed.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121403/321407/ftx.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="489557"/></item><item><title>Crypto Sleuths Discover Potential Connections Between Sam Bankman-Fried and BALD Rugpull</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-sleuths-discover-potential-connections-between-sam-bankman-fried-and-bald-rugpull.htm</link><description>Connections can be found between Sam Bankman-Fried’s trading firm Alameda Research and the deployer of an alleged crypto scam called BALD. &lt;br /&gt;
According to members of the crypto community who have analyzed on-chain data, the deployer of the meme coin, which was built on Coinbase’s new layer 2 blockchain Base, has in the past interacted with wallets controlled by Alameda Research....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-sleuths-discover-potential-connections-between-sam-bankman-fried-and-bald-rugpull.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Sleuths Discover Potential Connections Between Sam Bankman-Fried and BALD Rugpull&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Alameda Research</category><category>BALD</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-sleuths-discover-potential-connections-between-sam-bankman-fried-and-bald-rugpull.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121401/321398/sam-bankman-fried.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="361316"/></item><item><title>Breaking: US Department of Justice Considering Fraud Charges Against Binance Crypto Exchange</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/breaking-us-department-of-justice-considering-fraud-charges-against-binance-crypto-exchange.htm</link><description>The US Department of Justice (DoJ) is mulling whether to press fraud charges against Binance, as per a Semafor report. &lt;br /&gt;
However, as per the report, the DoJ is worried that if it indicts Binance, it could trigger a rush to withdraw balances on the exchange, similar to the rush that brought down FTX last November. &lt;br /&gt;
They worry this could result in customers losing money, as well as cause a fresh bought of panic in the broader crypto market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/breaking-us-department-of-justice-considering-fraud-charges-against-binance-crypto-exchange.htm"&gt;Read More: Breaking: US Department of Justice Considering Fraud Charges Against Binance Crypto Exchange&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>DOJ</category><category>SEC</category><category>Charges</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/breaking-us-department-of-justice-considering-fraud-charges-against-binance-crypto-exchange.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121415/321426/adobestock-286536398-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="7383733"/></item><item><title>Six Asset Managers File Fresh SEC Applications to Launch Ethereum Futures ETFs in the US</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/six-asset-managers-file-fresh-sec-applications-launch-ethereum-futures-etfs-us.htm</link><description>Six prominent asset managers have filed fresh applications to the US securities and exchange commission (SEC), for the approval of Ethereum (ETH) futures exchange-traded funds (ETFs). The filings come weeks after the regulator accepted spot Bitcoin (BTC) ETF applications in a span of one week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/six-asset-managers-file-fresh-sec-applications-launch-ethereum-futures-etfs-us.htm"&gt;Read More: Six Asset Managers File Fresh SEC Applications to Launch Ethereum Futures ETFs in the US&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/six-asset-managers-file-fresh-sec-applications-launch-ethereum-futures-etfs-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121412/321419/cryptocurrency-3409658-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="257273"/></item><item><title>Crypto Trader That Made &amp; Lost $1 Million In $BALD Scam Buys New Low Cap Meme Coin On Base</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-trader-that-made-lost-1-million-bald-scam-buys-new-low-cap-meme-coin-base.htm</link><description>A crypto trader that made and then lost more than $1 million on $BALD, a meme coin that exploded to a market cap of $100 million over the weekend before crashing in price due to an apparent rug pull scam is touting a new low cap meme coin on Base called Toshi ($TOSHI). &lt;br /&gt;
Base is Coinbase’s Ethereum layer-2 scaling blockchain that is still in its fairly early testing stages, with limited access for the general public....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-trader-that-made-lost-1-million-bald-scam-buys-new-low-cap-meme-coin-base.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Trader That Made &amp; Lost $1 Million In $BALD Scam Buys New Low Cap Meme Coin On Base&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>BALD</category><category>Base</category><category>Cheatcoiner.eth</category><category>Toshi</category><category>Shibie Coin</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Barbie</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-trader-that-made-lost-1-million-bald-scam-buys-new-low-cap-meme-coin-base.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121405/321413/toshi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="402642"/></item><item><title>GameStop Decides to Shut Down NFT Wallet Citing Regulatory Uncertainty</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/gamestop-decides-shut-down-nft-wallet-citing-regulatory-uncertainty.htm</link><description>Popular video game retailer GameStop has announced plans to shut down its NFT wallet due to regulatory uncertainty in the crypto space.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a pop-up message on its NFT marketplace, GameStop would cease support for the wallet starting November 1.  &lt;br /&gt;
"Due to the regulatory uncertainty of the crypto space, GameStop has decided to remove its iOS and Chrome Extension wallets from the market on November 1, 2023," the pop-up message reads. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gamestop-decides-shut-down-nft-wallet-citing-regulatory-uncertainty.htm"&gt;Read More: GameStop Decides to Shut Down NFT Wallet Citing Regulatory Uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>GameStop</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/gamestop-decides-shut-down-nft-wallet-citing-regulatory-uncertainty.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121404/321412/adobestock-jhvephoto-1-1-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="120468"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – XPEPE, TAI, cvxCRV</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-xpepe-tai-cvxcrv.htm</link><description>Blue chip cryptocurrency markets have seen rollercoaster price action in the last 24 hours, with bitcoin (BTC) dipping to fresh one-and-a-half-month lows in the mid-$28,000s on Tuesday, before then briefly recovering to the north of $30,000 in the early hours of the Wednesday trading session. &lt;br /&gt;
Traders are still digesting the news that Microstrategy, one of the world’s biggest bitcoin whales, is going to sell $750 million in stock that would, in part, fund more bitcoin purchases....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-xpepe-tai-cvxcrv.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – XPEPE, TAI, cvxCRV&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>MicroStrategy</category><category>Fitch</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Halving</category><category>Shit Coins</category><category>Meme Coins</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-xpepe-tai-cvxcrv.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121399/321395/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Binance Denies Reports of Its Activities in China, Coinbase is Looking Into Adding Bitcoin Lightning Network, OKX Launches Account Abstraction Feature, Hyundai &amp; Kia Partner With Hedera</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-denies-reports-of-its-activities-in-china-coinbase-is-looking-into-adding-bitcoin-lightning-network-okx-launches-account-abstraction-feature-hyundai-kia-partner-with-hedera.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-denies-reports-of-its-activities-in-china-coinbase-is-looking-into-adding-bitcoin-lightning-network-okx-launches-account-abstraction-feature-hyundai-kia-partner-with-hedera.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Binance Denies Reports of Its Activities in China, Coinbase is Looking Into Adding Bitcoin Lightning Network, OKX Launches Account Abstraction Feature, Hyundai &amp; Kia Partner With Hedera&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Lightning Network</category><category>Brian Armstrong</category><category>Jack Dorsey</category><category>Europe</category><category>France</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Kenya</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>OpenAI</category><category>China</category><category>Binance</category><category>OKX</category><category>OKEx</category><category>Wallet</category><category>USDC</category><category>USDT</category><category>DeFi</category><category>SushiSwap</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-binance-denies-reports-of-its-activities-in-china-coinbase-is-looking-into-adding-bitcoin-lightning-network-okx-launches-account-abstraction-feature-hyundai-kia-partner-with-hedera.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121367/321371/adobestock-ahmed.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1175612"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Uniswap? UNI Price Rises 15% and This New XRP Project Could 100x This Year – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-uniswap-uni-price-rises-15-new-xrp-project-could-100x-year-heres-why.htm</link><description>Top decentralised exchange (DEX) Uniswap has seen UNI (native governance token) surge up +15% in a magnificent pump sending ripples through markets. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes amid a storm of anxiety sweeping through DeFi markets this week, following a serious exploit incident which saw Curve pools lose more than $47m to crypto thieves. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-uniswap-uni-price-rises-15-new-xrp-project-could-100x-year-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Uniswap? UNI Price Rises 15% and This New XRP Project Could 100x This Year – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-uniswap-uni-price-rises-15-new-xrp-project-could-100x-year-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121381/321383/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="390827"/></item><item><title>India Pushes For A Clear G20 Crypto Strategy, Backs FSB Recommendations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/india-pushes-for-clear-g20-crypto-strategy-backs-fsb-recommendations.htm</link><description>India has backed calls for a properly structured legal regime on digital assets globally in its latest release to the G20.  &lt;br /&gt;
The country which currently presides over the G20, an association of the world’s 20 leading economies has in recent months deliberated on its local crypto laws while making efforts towards embracing cross-border payments for its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/india-pushes-for-clear-g20-crypto-strategy-backs-fsb-recommendations.htm"&gt;Read More: India Pushes For A Clear G20 Crypto Strategy, Backs FSB Recommendations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>India</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>G20</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/india-pushes-for-clear-g20-crypto-strategy-backs-fsb-recommendations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121377/321372/flags-media-library-origi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="53366"/></item><item><title>Binance Officially Enters Japanese Crypto Market with Binance Japan Exchange</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-officially-enters-japanese-crypto-market-with-binance-japan-exchange.htm</link><description>The major crypto exchange Binance has officially entered the Japanese market with the launch of Binance Japan K.K. &lt;br /&gt;
In an announcement from Tuesday, Binance said it already offers Japanese crypto traders access to more tradable tokens that any other crypto exchange, with 30 tokens available for spot trading....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-officially-enters-japanese-crypto-market-with-binance-japan-exchange.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Officially Enters Japanese Crypto Market with Binance Japan Exchange&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Japan</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-officially-enters-japanese-crypto-market-with-binance-japan-exchange.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121371/321347/binance.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="37959"/></item><item><title>Coinbase to Add Bitcoin's Lightning Network for Payments in Response to Jack Dorsey’s Tweet</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-add-bitcoins-lightning-network-for-payments-response-jack-dorseys-tweet.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Coinbase’s CEO Brian Armstrong and former head of Twitter – now X – Jack Dorsey, highlighted the potential and future of Bitcoin’s Layer 2 (L2) payment protocol, the Lightning Network. &lt;br /&gt;
In response to Dorsey’s Tweet, Armstong said Wednesday that Coinbase is looking into best ways to add Lightning to its platform....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-add-bitcoins-lightning-network-for-payments-response-jack-dorseys-tweet.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase to Add Bitcoin's Lightning Network for Payments in Response to Jack Dorsey’s Tweet&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-add-bitcoins-lightning-network-for-payments-response-jack-dorseys-tweet.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121362/321330/lightning.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="107553"/></item><item><title>While XPEPE Token Shoots Up 1,000% Overnight, Viral Coin Wall Street Memes Just Raised $20 Million – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/while-xpepe-token-shoots-up-1000-overnight-viral-coin-wall-street-memes-just-raised-20-million-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>As leading meme coin Dogecoin (DOGE) continues to make gains into August, straight-to-DEX meme coin launches aren't missing out on the action - and the latest market entrant, XPEPE token has pumped a magnificent +1,000% overnight. &lt;br /&gt;
The meme coin vertical has seen a strong month as top tokens appear to be pushing up, Dogecoin surged +16.73% this month, while fresh-faced sensations such as Pepecoin saw -15% to the downside....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/while-xpepe-token-shoots-up-1000-overnight-viral-coin-wall-street-memes-just-raised-20-million-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: While XPEPE Token Shoots Up 1,000% Overnight, Viral Coin Wall Street Memes Just Raised $20 Million – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/while-xpepe-token-shoots-up-1000-overnight-viral-coin-wall-street-memes-just-raised-20-million-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121359/321340/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1199714"/></item></channel></rss>
