<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 01:51:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Titan Global Capital Management Settles with the SEC, Agrees to $1 Million Fine for Misleading Crypto Fund Claims</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/titan-global-capital-management-settles-with-sec-agrees-1-million-fine-for-misleading-crypto-fund-claims.htm</link><description>The New York-based fintech investment adviser, Titan Global Capital Management, has agreed to comply with the US Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) cease-and-desist order and paid fines exceeding $1 million for misleading investors about its cryptocurrency offering....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/titan-global-capital-management-settles-with-sec-agrees-1-million-fine-for-misleading-crypto-fund-claims.htm"&gt;Read More: Titan Global Capital Management Settles with the SEC, Agrees to $1 Million Fine for Misleading Crypto Fund Claims&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Titan Global Capital Management</category><category>Marketing</category><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 01:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/titan-global-capital-management-settles-with-sec-agrees-1-million-fine-for-misleading-crypto-fund-claims.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123154/325788/adobestock-286664985-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="138117"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Police to Freeze Suspected Fraudsters’ Crypto Holdings</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-freeze-suspected-fraudsters-crypto-holdings.htm</link><description>Brazilian police have asked courts to freeze the crypto holdings of suspected electronics-trading fraudsters as part of a “mega operation.” &lt;br /&gt;
The Brazilian media outlet Livecoins reported that officers took part in an operation codenamed Spin-Off. &lt;br /&gt;
The operation involves the Federal Police and the Receita Federal (the Special Department of Federal Revenue). &lt;br /&gt;
Officers raided properties in the states of São Paulo, Mato Grosso, and Mato Grosso do Sul....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-freeze-suspected-fraudsters-crypto-holdings.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Police to Freeze Suspected Fraudsters’ Crypto Holdings&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Police</category><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-freeze-suspected-fraudsters-crypto-holdings.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123084/325742/brz-2208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="925911"/></item><item><title>Higher Bond Yields Contribute to Bitcoin's Extended Losses</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/higher-bond-yields-contribute-bitcoins-extended-losses.htm</link><description>Bitcoin losses continued today as bond yields continued to rise, causing concern for investors. This downturn has seen the leading digital currency dip below its two-month low of $26,000 for a loss of 0.74% over the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
The drop in Bitcoin's price comes after a challenging week for the cryptocurrency. Over the past seven days, Bitcoin's price dropped more than 11%. Alongside this, other digital currencies, such as Ether and XRP, have also experienced sizable price decreases....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/higher-bond-yields-contribute-bitcoins-extended-losses.htm"&gt;Read More: Higher Bond Yields Contribute to Bitcoin's Extended Losses&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin Price</category><category>Bitcoin Down</category><category>Bitcoin Losses</category><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/higher-bond-yields-contribute-bitcoins-extended-losses.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123145/325782/3488040353-ccc6e20497-c.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="304992"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now August 22 – Render, Monero, Algorand</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-22-render-monero-algorand.htm</link><description>One of today's biggest crypto news stories comes from Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume. &lt;br /&gt;
On August 22, Binance announced the gradual launch of a new copy trading feature on its futures platform which went live at 6:45 AM UTC. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this development, what are the best cryptos to buy now? &lt;br /&gt;
Copy trading allows novice crypto traders to automatically replicate the trades of more experienced users in real time....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-22-render-monero-algorand.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now August 22 – Render, Monero, Algorand&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Render</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Monero</category><category>Sonik Coin</category><category>Algorand</category><category>RNDR</category><category>Rndr Price</category><category>XMR</category><category>Xmr Price</category><category>ALGO</category><category>ALGO PRICE</category><category>YPRED</category><category>SONIK</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptos</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Memecoins</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Ai Crypto</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-22-render-monero-algorand.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123144/325775/bctbt-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="275411"/></item><item><title>Against All Odds: Solo Miner Claims $160,000 Bitcoin Block Reward – Here's What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/against-all-odds-solo-miner-claims-160000-bitcoin-block-reward-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>On August 18, an unexpected event in the Bitcoin mining space took everyone by surprise. A lone miner, not backed by massive computational power, claimed the full reward of 6.25 Bitcoin for solving block 803,821.  &lt;br /&gt;
In simple terms, the miner earned about $160,000, minus a 2% fee retained by the mining service. So, how did this happen, and why is it such big news?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/against-all-odds-solo-miner-claims-160000-bitcoin-block-reward-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Against All Odds: Solo Miner Claims $160,000 Bitcoin Block Reward – Here's What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin Mining</category><category>How To Mine Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto Mining Service</category><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/against-all-odds-solo-miner-claims-160000-bitcoin-block-reward-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123142/325773/brian-wangenheim-op92ppqg.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="512534"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Bounces From $26,000 Support – Here are Key Levels to Watch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-from-26000-support-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</link><description>As the cryptocurrency market remains dynamic, the focus shifts once again to Bitcoin's price movement.  &lt;br /&gt;
Following a recent dip that saw Bitcoin briefly touch the $26,000 support level, market observers and investors are keen to assess the potential direction of the world's leading cryptocurrency.  &lt;br /&gt;
With this backdrop, it becomes crucial to analyze the key levels that could play a pivotal role in shaping Bitcoin's trajectory in the coming days. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-from-26000-support-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Bounces From $26,000 Support – Here are Key Levels to Watch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-from-26000-support-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123153/325786/22.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="491070"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Developers Allege Craig Wright’s ‘Bogus’ Claims May Lead To An Admission In The Collapse Of Mt. Gox</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-developers-allege-craig-wrights-bogus-claims-may-lead-an-admission-collapse-of-mt-gox.htm</link><description>Defense attorneys for 12 Bitcoin (BTC) core developers in the lawsuit filed by Craig Wright say the false ownership claims to Bitcoin can expose him to liabilities relating to the 80,000 stolen Bitcoin from Mt. Gox.  &lt;br /&gt;
Craig Wright claims he is the mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto and filed a lawsuit against 12 core Bitcoin developers asserting ownership of 111,000 BTC allegedly stolen from the Mt. Gox exchange....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-developers-allege-craig-wrights-bogus-claims-may-lead-an-admission-collapse-of-mt-gox.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Developers Allege Craig Wright’s ‘Bogus’ Claims May Lead To An Admission In The Collapse Of Mt. Gox&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Mt Gox</category><category>Bitcoin. Satoshi Nakomoto</category><category>Craig Wright</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-developers-allege-craig-wrights-bogus-claims-may-lead-an-admission-collapse-of-mt-gox.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123114/325770/bitcoin-8154779-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="315753"/></item><item><title>Google Bard Has Made This Dogecoin Price Prediction, But This Could Be The Next Meme Coin to Pump</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/google-bard-made-dogecoin-price-prediction-said-meme-coin-next-pump.htm</link><description>AI is bullish on Dogecoin. &lt;br /&gt;
That’s according to a chat recently shared by crypto news website Finbold with Google’s generative AI chatbot Bard. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Bard, Dogecoin could recover to $0.10 by the end of 2023, marking an increase of as much as 60% from its current price levels around $0.06....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/google-bard-made-dogecoin-price-prediction-said-meme-coin-next-pump.htm"&gt;Read More: Google Bard Has Made This Dogecoin Price Prediction, But This Could Be The Next Meme Coin to Pump&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>DOGE</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>AI</category><category>Bard</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/google-bard-made-dogecoin-price-prediction-said-meme-coin-next-pump.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123112/325767/doge-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="197943"/></item><item><title>Three Compelling Reasons Why a Spot Bitcoin (BTC) ETF Approval Really Matters, According to Bitwise</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/three-compelling-reasons-why-spot-bitcoin-btc-etf-approval-really-matters-according-bitwise.htm</link><description>There are three compelling reasons why a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) approval really matters, crypto index fund manager Bitwise argued in a recently shared threat on Twitter. &lt;br /&gt;
“Approval would make it vastly easier for investment professionals to gain exposure to bitcoin,” Bitwise argued, noting that “ETFs are among the most popular and efficient vehicles to access key markets or investment themes”....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/three-compelling-reasons-why-spot-bitcoin-btc-etf-approval-really-matters-according-bitwise.htm"&gt;Read More: Three Compelling Reasons Why a Spot Bitcoin (BTC) ETF Approval Really Matters, According to Bitwise&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>spot bitcoin ETF</category><category>Bitwise</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/three-compelling-reasons-why-spot-bitcoin-btc-etf-approval-really-matters-according-bitwise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123111/325766/btc-10.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131590"/></item><item><title>Momentum Capital Gains $10M Investment to Hunt for Crypto's Next 'Apple'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/momentum-capital-gains-10m-investment-hunt-for-cryptos-next-apple.htm</link><description>San Francisco-based crypto-native fund Momentum Capital has secured an investment of $10 million from Canada's BM Fund.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Monday press release, the company revealed that it acquired the new funding in July this year. &lt;br /&gt;
The investment will be used to expand Momentum Capital's team and support early-stage Web3 projects, as the fund seeks to uncover the next groundbreaking company in the crypto industry, often referred to as the "Apple" of cryptocurrencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/momentum-capital-gains-10m-investment-hunt-for-cryptos-next-apple.htm"&gt;Read More: Momentum Capital Gains $10M Investment to Hunt for Crypto's Next 'Apple'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>San Francisco</category><category>Venture capital</category><category>Fund</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/momentum-capital-gains-10m-investment-hunt-for-cryptos-next-apple.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123104/325755/alexander-grey-8a5ej1-mmq.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="160713"/></item><item><title>Citadel's EDX Joins With Anchorage Digital to Shake-Up Crypto Custody – Coinbase Institutional Business Threatened?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/citadels-edx-joins-with-anchorage-digital-to-shake-up-crypto-custody-coinbase-and-galaxy-institutional-business-threatened.htm</link><description>EDX Markets, a prominent institutional crypto exchange company, announced on Tuesday a collaboration with Anchorage Digital, a regulated crypto platform renowned for its comprehensive financial services and infrastructure solutions. &lt;br /&gt;
Anchorage will assume the role of custody provider for EDX's clearinghouse venture, known as EDX Clearing, which is scheduled for launch later this year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/citadels-edx-joins-with-anchorage-digital-to-shake-up-crypto-custody-coinbase-and-galaxy-institutional-business-threatened.htm"&gt;Read More: Citadel's EDX Joins With Anchorage Digital to Shake-Up Crypto Custody – Coinbase Institutional Business Threatened?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/citadels-edx-joins-with-anchorage-digital-to-shake-up-crypto-custody-coinbase-and-galaxy-institutional-business-threatened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123107/325771/img-0809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2032723"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – GUISE, XLRT, BT2017</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-guise-xlrt-bt2017.htm</link><description>Blue chip cryptocurrencies are falling once again this Tuesday, with Bitcoin (BTC) down around 1% on the day in the $25,800s and Ether (ETH) down 2% and back below $1,650. &lt;br /&gt;
Traders continue to fret about macro headwinds in the form of rising US long-dated yields, which recently hit multi-decade highs amid bets that US interest rates will remain higher for longer thanks to the continued outperformance of the US economy....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-guise-xlrt-bt2017.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – GUISE, XLRT, BT2017&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>ETH</category><category>Ether</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>SEC</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>ETF</category><category>Shitcoin</category><category>Meme coin</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-guise-xlrt-bt2017.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123108/325763/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>yPredict is Revolutionizing Crypto Trading with AI Signals, Sentiment Analysis, and More – $3.5 Million Raised</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-revolutionizing-crypto-trading-with-ai-signals-sentiment-analysis-more-35-million-raised.htm</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is transforming many industries, including cryptocurrency trading. As more people get involved in crypto trading, there's a growing need for tools that can provide accurate insights and predictions. This is where AI can play a significant role by analyzing vast amounts of data and offering traders better crypto signals for making informed decisions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-revolutionizing-crypto-trading-with-ai-signals-sentiment-analysis-more-35-million-raised.htm"&gt;Read More: yPredict is Revolutionizing Crypto Trading with AI Signals, Sentiment Analysis, and More – $3.5 Million Raised&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><category>Crypto Signals</category><category>Best Crypto Presale</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Ai Crypto</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-revolutionizing-crypto-trading-with-ai-signals-sentiment-analysis-more-35-million-raised.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123081/325761/f3gjc5txkaaxnza.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="214729"/></item><item><title>Oman Flags Off New Crypto Mining Facility With Expansion Plans As The Country Bets On Blockchain</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/oman-flags-off-new-crypto-mining-facility-with-expansion-plans-as-country-bets-blockchain.htm</link><description>Oman has launched a new digital asset mining facility, the second flagged off within months as it seeks to diversify the economy away from oil exports.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Middle Eastern country has flagged off the faculty which cost about 135 million Omani rials approximately $150 million and would be operated by Exahertz, a local firm in collaboration with Woonwalk Systems, a Dubai headquartered entity....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/oman-flags-off-new-crypto-mining-facility-with-expansion-plans-as-country-bets-blockchain.htm"&gt;Read More: Oman Flags Off New Crypto Mining Facility With Expansion Plans As The Country Bets On Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Oman</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Miner</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/oman-flags-off-new-crypto-mining-facility-with-expansion-plans-as-country-bets-blockchain.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123101/325754/pexels-karolina-grabowska.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="226257"/></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency Scammers Exploit ChatGPT-Powered Botnet on Social Platform X</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocurrency-scammers-exploit-chatgpt-powered-botnet-on-social-platform-x.htm</link><description>A recent investigation by researchers at Indiana University Bloomington has unveiled the use of a botnet powered by ChatGPT, a sophisticated AI language model developed by OpenAI, to promote cryptocurrency scams on X (formerly known as Twitter)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocurrency-scammers-exploit-chatgpt-powered-botnet-on-social-platform-x.htm"&gt;Read More: Cryptocurrency Scammers Exploit ChatGPT-Powered Botnet on Social Platform X&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocurrency-scammers-exploit-chatgpt-powered-botnet-on-social-platform-x.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123102/325756/adobestock-307544853.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="181892"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Thailand May Banish Facebook Because of Crypto Scam Ads, Terra Freezes Website Due to Phishing Scams, Phantom Launches the 'Sign In With Solana' Feature</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-thailand-may-banish-facebook-because-of-crypto-scam-ads-terra-freezes-website-due-to-phishing-scams-phantom-launches-the-sign-in-with-solana-feature.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-thailand-may-banish-facebook-because-of-crypto-scam-ads-terra-freezes-website-due-to-phishing-scams-phantom-launches-the-sign-in-with-solana-feature.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Thailand May Banish Facebook Because of Crypto Scam Ads, Terra Freezes Website Due to Phishing Scams, Phantom Launches the 'Sign In With Solana' Feature&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Thailand</category><category>Facebook</category><category>Ad</category><category>Scam</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Nomura</category><category>Ledger</category><category>CoinShares</category><category>Dubai</category><category>Terra</category><category>Phantom</category><category>Solana</category><category>Wallet</category><category>China</category><category>Legal</category><category>Court</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><category>Investment</category><category>AI</category><category>Web3</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-thailand-may-banish-facebook-because-of-crypto-scam-ads-terra-freezes-website-due-to-phishing-scams-phantom-launches-the-sign-in-with-solana-feature.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123054/325630/adobestock-diy13-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="278533"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried Pleads Not Guilty to Latest Fraud and Conspiracy Charges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-latest-fraud-and-conspiracy-charges.htm</link><description>FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has entered a not guilty plea in Manhattan federal court in response to a new indictment that alleges charges of fraud and conspiracy.  &lt;br /&gt;
This marks Bankman-Fried's first appearance in court since he was sent to jail following his bail revocation by U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan on August 11. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-latest-fraud-and-conspiracy-charges.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried Pleads Not Guilty to Latest Fraud and Conspiracy Charges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>USA</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-to-latest-fraud-and-conspiracy-charges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123082/325743/sbf-plea.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="107670"/></item><item><title>Top Meme Coin Prices Falter But Sonik Coin Powers Past $300k in Presale, Less Than 14 Days Left to Go</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-meme-coin-prices-falter-but-sonik-coin-powers-past-300k-presale-less-than-14-days-left-go.htm</link><description>Tuesday, August 22, 2023 – While top meme coin prices are faltering, new kid on the block, Sonik Coin, has raised more than $300k  from investors in its goal of becoming the fastest crypto ever to reach a $100 million market cap....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-meme-coin-prices-falter-but-sonik-coin-powers-past-300k-presale-less-than-14-days-left-go.htm"&gt;Read More: Top Meme Coin Prices Falter But Sonik Coin Powers Past $300k in Presale, Less Than 14 Days Left to Go&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-meme-coin-prices-falter-but-sonik-coin-powers-past-300k-presale-less-than-14-days-left-go.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123078/325734/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="497627"/></item><item><title>Dirk Lueth, Co-Founder of Upland, on the State of the MetaVerse, SuperApps, and Web3 Games | Ep. 258</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/dirk-lueth-co-founder-of-upland-on-the-state-of-the-metaverse-superapps-and-web3-games-ep-258.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Dirk Lueth, Co-Founder &amp; Co-CEO of Upland, talks about how Upland became the leading Web3 Metaverse SuperApp, why the future of web3 gaming will be completely open, and their partnership with FIFA Women’s World Cup. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/dirk-lueth-co-founder-of-upland-on-the-state-of-the-metaverse-superapps-and-web3-games-ep-258.htm"&gt;Read More: Dirk Lueth, Co-Founder of Upland, on the State of the MetaVerse, SuperApps, and Web3 Games | Ep. 258&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/dirk-lueth-co-founder-of-upland-on-the-state-of-the-metaverse-superapps-and-web3-games-ep-258.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123061/325625/dirk-lueth-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="118457"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Optimism? OP Price Rallies Up 5% and Launchpad Can Find the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-optimism-op-price-rallies-up-5-launchpad-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>As leading Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Optimism (OP) enters 5th day of recovery rally, investors are asking is it too late to buy optimism - but significant resistance levels could mark end of upside moves - find out more in OP price analysis. &lt;br /&gt;
Optimism has rallied +5% since yesterday, as OP price action continues to grind to the upside in a hard-fought recovery rally fuelling bag-holders hopes....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-optimism-op-price-rallies-up-5-launchpad-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Optimism? OP Price Rallies Up 5% and Launchpad Can Find the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-optimism-op-price-rallies-up-5-launchpad-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/123062/325631/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="417384"/></item></channel></rss>
